<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8631</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stella Artois </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The underdog of all

Tastes so bitter so fine

Grilling or watching football

Always the favorite of mine

Don't ever change you're perfect

For my Korean throat you refresh

In the morning never a regret

Oh so bitter yet so fresh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 08:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for that.

I mean i definitely see your point of view.

I guess i read too far into the post. It just felt like it was more out of spite than out of the desire for NoSleep to grow. 

Just the fact that those stories were compared to Chicken Soup kind of triggered me.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, honestly, if you don't think a story is horror you should report it. 
Or just downvote it if you're too lazy to report anything.

It does far more than writing about how these stories annoy you because it feels like it's out of a Chicken Soup book...

I mean the fact that they write a post on the OOC complaining about a group of stories really does feel like an attack...

Everyone submits the wrong thing from time to time. We get stories removed and we understand it, but I really feel like the OOC should not be used to criticize a block of stories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also some people actually assume we get paid. 

Ignorance is abundant in humanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's about the most bummish way to wake up in the morning...

Thanks for attacking the writers that spend hours out of their time in hopes of entertaining people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 11:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll figure it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 11:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 11:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely the app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 09:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're telling me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Strange Experiences With an App Called "Life is Beta" [Part 2] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 09:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right when I woke up this morning I checked my phone to make sure there werent any new Experiences. When I saw the blank screen I felt a bit of relief. I got ready for work and decided to skip out on breakfast today. Got on the same subway I did everyday and checked my phone during the whole entire ride. When it reached my stop I got off and walked the 300 meters to my work. 

I didnt get a single notification until I was in the middle of my lunch.

I was in my favorite sandwich shop halfway through my roast beef sandwich when I felt my phone vibrate in my pocket. With a sigh mixed with anticipation and fear, I checked my phone and saw that I have a new Experience. I clicked on the notification and found my character floating around like he always does, but for some reason his face looked like it was melting off. I tried tapping on the character, but it just stayed on the same screen. My character started to grab at his face trying to keep it in place, but after a couple of seconds he gave up and let his face slide to the ground. 

After a couple of seconds the face disappears from the ground and the character looks back up at me as if nothing happened. I felt wary, but I tapped on my character again.


The whole screen became a deep red and after a couple of seconds it flashed to a family of three enjoying a meal by a campfire in front of a house. They kept pulling out bits of meat from the pot and seemed to be enjoying every single bite. The boy was dancing around the pot while he bit of meat from a larger sized bone. After about 5 minutes of watching them eat, a man pulled up into their driveway. He was wearing a white and red shirt with a small cookie logo on the top right of the shirt. He sat with them and ate a couple of pieces before going into the house first. The boy walked behind the man and picked up a bloody foot off of the ground. He kicked it as hard as he could and started to laugh. He grabbed a hand after that and walked around and acted like he was holding it while the man and woman started to laugh along with him.

The scene started to speed past the family going back in, and finally started going back to its normal speed as soon as the sun rose the next morning.  The door swung open and I saw the man in the cookie shirt step outside while lugging two large bags. The boy ran behind him and started to punch his back, but the man pushed him down to the ground. 

The screen went black for a second and then showed me the man parking in front of a cookie store. He got the 2 large bags out and took them inside. Around 2 minutes later he comes back out, locks the front doors, and starts driving away. 

My phone jumps back to the home screen after that and I put the phone back in my pocket while I tried to make sense of what I just watched. I know that the two bags contained the man and the woman. The young boy is now at his house alone, but I did not really feel bad for him after I watched him play with dismembered body parts. 

In the middle of my thoughts my phone started buzzing again. The notification from the app simply said 
Countdown. I opened up the app and saw the number 32 fill up the screen. 

I knew automatically that I had to leave, but I felt a light tap on my shoulder. I looked behind me and saw a familiar face and shirt; a red and white shirt with a cookie on the top right and a smile displaying bright yellow teeth. He leaned over to me and pressed his lips right on my ear as he whispered Do I know you from somewhere? I jerked my body back and tried to rush out, but he grabbed on to my arm and tried to pull me back. With desperation kicking in, I used my other hand to jab the man in his eye. He yelped in pain and his grip softened around my arm. Seizing the opportunity, I kicked him in the knee and managed to leave the store as the timer hit 3 seconds.

I walked to the side of the building and peeked around the corner. I already started hearing screams coming from the shop when the timer hit zero, and within seconds I saw people rushing out of the store. They all seemed fine except a couple of people who had deep gashed in various places. One man was running out with a deep wound on his chest. He got to the middle of the parking lot before falling to the ground. 

The door opened for the final time, and Yellow Tooth came out with a butcher knife in one hand and with the other he was dragging a man face down. Once he got up to his car he flipped the man over and started to stuff him in his back seat. I wish I could wipe the image of the mans face from my head, but I know I will never forget it. The skin on his face was gone and the flesh of his face had been ripped in various places after being dragged on the asphalt. 

I knew I was still at risk of being seen by the man so I ran back to my company. I didnt stop running until I got to my desk. I took the phone out from my pants pocket and placed it on the desk. 

I know that the app is helping me, but I just wanted the notifications to stop. 

Knowing I was in no condition to work so I sent in an e-mail to the assistant manager that I will have to take the rest of the day off. I knew it would take around 20 minutes for the assistant manager to reply back with his answer; so I grabbed my phone and went to the restroom. 

I was sending my wife a text while I sat on the toilet, but a notification popped up and I automatically clicked it. 

This time the app didnt go to the screen with my floating character. It went automatically to an actual video of my wife and kid sitting on the bathroom floor. It looked like it was taken from outside of the bathroom window. 

The window started to go white from the persons deep breath, but my wife and kid were oblivious to it all. There was a time at the bottom right of the screen. 

13:35 pm.

The camera shifted down and I saw khaki pants and gray shoes and the video cut out. The screen went white and came back to a countdown with Get Him Now on the screen.

I walked into the office and grabbed a letter opener from my desk. I knew exactly who it was. His name is Brad and he has been eye fucking my wife since the Christmas party last year. When I got up to him I saw a picture of my wifes Facebook profile picture on his screen, and that was what confirmed all of my suspicions. I jammed the letter opener in his neck 6 times. Before anyone else could react I ran out the door and continued to run the 300 meters to the subway station. 

I didnt go back home. I know the police are looking for me.

I have received over 20 calls and 45 texts from my wife, but I am not going to check them. 

The only thing I checked was the last notification I received today.

Gotcha

Time for me to [figure this shit out] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=settings). 
 
[Part One] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5pmu3w/my_strange_experiences_with_an_app_called_life_is/)


[Final] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5q263v/my_strange_experiences_with_an_app_called_life_is/)
 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 07:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cjVQ36NhbMk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Side note: I hope the person that had the book published somehow sees the post.

I would love to see how he/she feels about you insulting their work just to make yourself look good(terrible) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sooooo you want us to give you our stories for free. (Which is okay)

You also want to make money off of our stories while we slave away between writing and working a job. (Not really okay)

You have not really submitted anything in to NoSleep at all besides 2 removed stories for lack of words, and you insult another person's book who more than likely made a good offer to the authors. (Not Okay At All)

Above all !@#$ing else you ask us to fund your publication so you can start making more money. (Really Douchey)

So, good luck with that.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever tried Korean Gravy before?

Is Korean Gravy even a thing?  

Does it exist or am I going insane? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he's been acting normally..

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not fat and you're not rich either:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahahhahha sounds like someone doesn't know how to read.

I'm glad you can spell bitch though:D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 11:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 11:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be impressed that my two year old son would be able to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 08:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is definitely going to have more parts to it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 07:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I called the number thinking it was nothing.

I heard a lady crying for help with chanting coming from the background.

I received a text just now, and I don't want to check it.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 07:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Strange Experiences With an App Called "Life is Beta" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 07:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I woke up to the sight of my 2 year old son tapping away on my cell phone. I put out my hand and after a couple of whines and tears he handed the phone back to me. I checked my phone to make sure he didnt make any phone calls or texts. 

After checking everything on my phone I didnt find any new calls or texts, but I did see an app called Life is Beta on my home screen now. The icon was just a circle inside of a solid blue square.

I put my phone in my pocket, and got ready for work. After I ate my breakfast I kissed my wife and son goodbye and walked to the subway station. The ride to work usually takes around 40 minutes so I turned my phone on and clicked on the app. 

The first thing that threw me off was the fact that there wasnt a loading screen or anything.  It just automatically jumped to a character floating in the middle of the screen. 

The next weird thing was the character looked just like me in every single way. Even the face was exactly like mine down to the two pimples I found on my forehead this morning. Feeling a bit curious, I tapped on the screen and he started to walk towards the right. The screen turned black for a second, and when it bounced to the next screen I almost dropped my phone. He was sitting in a subway while playing on his cell phone. 

After a couple of seconds the subway in the phone stops, and a couple of people got off and on the subway. Right as a lady in a yellow coat starts to get on the subway my character starts to flash and the scene freezes. I tap on the character and he gets up and bolts out of the subway. I try to tap outside of the subway, but the screen keeps showing the subway. The lady that boarded the subway started to pace around the subway, but no one really gave her notice. 

After she walked around three times she started to shake and took out two guns from her purse. The subway is filled with blood and people running around as she empties out both magazines. Once she ran out of bullets she took a knife out of purse and stabbed herself in the chest. 

The screen on my phone went dark and I felt the subway come to a stop. I looked up and saw a woman in a yellow coat boarding the subway. Without a second thought I ran out of the subway and caught a cab. 

The whole cab ride there I kept searching the news to see if there were any recent shootings in my area, but after a while I started to relax and by the time I got to work I was laughing to myself about how dumb I was listening to a dumb game. Right as I sat down in my office chair I got a phone call from my wife. When I picked up the phone I heard my wife say Please, please, please, just answer the phone. I said Hello? and I could hear her breathe a sigh of relief. She told me that she was watching the news when she heard about a lady shooting up the subway I usually rode to work. Right as she told me everything that happened I couldnt really respond. I felt my hand start to shake and my throat felt like it was closing up. I told her I love her and that I would call her back later and hung up the phone. 

I turned the app again, and saw that my character was floating in the middle of the screen. I kept tapping at him, but the screen would not change. I clicked the home button to my phone and tried deleting the app, but my phone did not give an option to delete the app. Frustrated and scared shitless, I just shoved my phone back into my pocket and tried to forget about what happened this morning. 

I didnt check the app again until around 2pm. I felt my phone vibrating so I checked it and saw a notification from Life is Beta. It said New Experience next to the logo; I didnt want to but I clicked on the box in case it was trying to warn me again.  

When I opened up the app I saw an animated version of my manager typing on his laptop. The view shifted to where I was looking at my managers laptop. 

On his screen was a lady holding up a man by his hair. I could see what my manager was typing out. Use your fingers to dig his eyeballs out. 

The woman held up 3 fingers on her other hand and my manager went back to typing. 300 hundred for that? Youre fucking nuts. $200 and we have a deal.

She nodded her head and using her index finger and thumb started to dig out the mans left eyeball. 

I clicked on the home button before I saw anything else, but once I closed out of the app I got another notification. It simply said Call 911.

I ran to the restroom after I dialed 911 and explained to the dispatcher about what my manager was dong on his laptop. I requested that I stay anonymous and hung up the phone.

Fifteen minutes later my manager was taken out of his office by two police officers. He was pleading with them and telling them it was all a misunderstanding, but we could hear the sounds of a man yelling out in pain from our managers laptop. 

That was the last notification I received today, but I will let you know if I receive anymore. 

Stay safe everyone, and be careful with [who you trust] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).

[For Part 2] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5pv010/my_strange_experiences_with_an_app_called_life_is/)

[Final] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5q263v/my_strange_experiences_with_an_app_called_life_is/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hallmark Inn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will never go back to the Hallmark Inn; and I would like to give you a very good reason why you shouldnt either. The Hallmark Inn used to be a wonderful hotel. I know this, because I went there when I was really young with my mother and father. The workers there treated us like royalty. The rooms were immaculate, and the tv was equipped with all of my favorite channels. Yesterday afternoon we were told by our manager that we had a company meeting at 8 am the next morning. 

We only lived about 3 hours away, but if we decided to go today we would be heading out at 5 am. So I asked Clark if he wanted to just go up to Nashville tonight after work. He was reluctant at first, but when I told him all about how amazing and cheap the Hallmark Inn was he became excited about my idea. I found the number to the hotel and went ahead and reserved a room for the night. After work we swung by both of our houses and grabbed a set of formal wear for the meeting and changed into some casual clothes for the evening. After I grabbed my things we headed off to Nashville. Clark was in the passenger seat trying to find something to do in Nasvhille while I drove. When he couldnt find anything that interested both of us I suggested maybe asking the hotel employees if they knew of anything. 

We got to the hotel within 2 hours due to my excessive speeding. When I got close to the hotel I started to get excited about spending a night in the hotel I had such fond memories of. The excitement started wavering when I saw how bad the hotel looked from the outside. The bricks have started to deteriorate, and the sign that once proudly displayed Hallmark Inn now read ark nn. Clark shot me a look of concern, but I just told him it looked a lot better inside.  

I didnt have a problem parking since there were only 2 other cars in the parking lot. The lack of cars would normally bother me, but I didnt think much of it since it was Monday. After I parked we walked up to the front doors and tried opening them. Three tries later I saw an old lady walk past the door. I banged on the door trying to get her attention, but she just completely ignored us and walked behind the desk. Getting a little pissed off by point I tried calling the hotel again. 

Busy signal.

I tried calling five more times, but each time I got a busy signal. 

Clark tapped on my shoulder and pointed at a little button on the right side of the door. With a little laugh he pressed the button. It made a little buzzing sound and I saw the old lady getting out of her chair and walk up to the doors. She stared at us for about 10 seconds and opened the door. 

What do you want? was the question she greeted us with.

I started to tell her about how I reserved the room, but in the middle of my sentence she turned around and walked behind the desk. She pulled out a key and stuck her hand out. We each took out 30 dollars and put it in her hand. She put the money in her pocket and threw the key on the desk in front of us. Room 201 was all she said before sitting back on her chair and stared at the front door. 

We both got the hint and walked out of the door. When we got to room 201 I unlocked the door and we walked inside. As soon as I looked inside of the room I apologized to Clark for the horrible recommendation. The once white walls were now piss yellow, the tv looked like the same exact tv that was there when I came here 12 years ago. The sheets on both of the beds looked like they havent been washed in the past year, and from the room I could see that the toilet in the bathroom was black on the bottom. Clark just laughed and told me it was just for a night. 

It was 11 pm by then so we just gave up on the idea of going out. 

I grabbed a bag of chips from my bag and we turned the tv on. 

Good News: Free Porn

Bad News: We only have that one channel.

After awkwardly watching terrible porn for a couple minutes I turned the tv off and reviewed over the meeting notes for tomorrow with Clark. When I got to the middle of the notes we heard a knock on the door. I ignored the knocking since it was 11:30 at night and continued with the notes. The person kept knocking on the door so I started to talk louder than the knocking hoping the person would just give up, but the knocking only got louder. Clark was the first to lose his patience. He walked up to the door and shouted What the fuck do you want? 

A guys voice answered back I just need to use your phone please. Ive been stabbed. Clark drew back the curtain and looked out the window. He waved me over to the window. When I looked out the window I saw a man wearing sunglasses standing outside with a huge gash on his right shoulder. I shouted Do you want me to call 911? The man just nodded his head. I got out my phone and dialed 911, but my phone immediately shut off after I tried calling. I tried turning my phone back on, but it wouldnt no matter how many times I tried. 

I tried using the landline in the room, but when I dialed 911 I just kept hearing an advertisement about Hallmark Inn. Clark already tried calling them on his phone, but the look on his face automatically told me he didnt have any luck contacting them either. I shouted at the man that we would take him to the front desk to see if they can help us. I opened the door and tried to leave, but the man shoved me back inside and walked through the door. He closed the hotel door and walked up to my bed and sat down. I got up to my feet and ran to where Clark was standing. 

The man took his shirt off and smiled at us while he started to rub his gash with his left hand. I wanted to tell him to get out, but I was fixated by his shoulder wound. He then took off his sunglasses and saw that the skin around his eyes was sewn shut. With a low guttural sound he started to tear at his face. As blood started to drip down his face I saw he managed to rip the sewn up skin revealing two empty eye sockets. 

I started to walk up to the man, but immediately came to a stop when tiny black bugs started pouring out of his eyes. They landed on his stomach and legs and started crawling into his gash. Soon his gash was completely filled with the black bugs falling out of his face. He started to scream as the gash continued to grow. After a couple of seconds his screaming suddenly stopped and the man became completely quiet and still. The bugs then crawled off of his body and went to the door. 

We ran to the restroom and locked the door. Clark sat in the bathtub and I sat on the counter next to the sink. I dont know when I fell asleep, but I woke up this morning to the sound of gurgling from the bathtub. I looked over at Clark and threw up in the sink. The black bugs were eating through his eyes and midsection. Clark tried to say something to me, but instead coughed out blood and some of the black bugs. 

I ran out of the restroom and saw that the bugs were no longer in front of the door. 

I ran out of the hotel room and got into my car. I didnt even think to call 911 again. I just wanted to go home. 

When I got home I called the manager and told him that I would not make it to the meeting. I hung up on him while he was telling me about the consequences if Im not there in the next hour.  

I dont know what those bugs were; or if they even are bugs. I really dont know what they are, but I do know that theyre inside of Hallmark Inn now.

So please promise me. 

[Dont stay at Hallmark Inn] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 13:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, yes it really ruins the authenticity to the story.

I just wish people would actually report the comment instead of saying "DUDE THE SIDE BAR" "READ THE RULE DICKWAD"

Whenever i get those comments on my stories i'll honestly just tell them "yeah, it's real" and then report. 

Report. Report. Report. guys. 

It probably makes the mod's life much easier when we all follow the rules.

Including the NoSleep Batman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't think cannibalism is scary AT ALL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 13:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do. Not. Overuse. Cuss words to compensate for the lack of emotions you put into the statement.

People like the occasional cuss word at times, but i have over used foul language in my stories when trying to make people feel sadness, anger, fear, and have had it backfire in my face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 11:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only submit once you are happy with it.

Do not care about upvotes. (some of the best stories never even break a hundred upvotes) 

Write. Write. Write. Every single day. (practice really makes something damn near close to perfection) 

Don't let one criticism ruin you. There will always be a person that loves it. 

Don't become discouraged if a story flops. There is always tomorrow. Consistency will create fans naturally. 

Eat a goat that has been dead for less than 3 days. Raw preferably but can be settled with cooked rare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it is a much smaller island than jeju </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 12:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't want to use the korean currency as it could potentially confuse people.

5 dollars = 5000 won. 

1.50= 1500

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 12:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know for sure yet.


I'll figure it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Korea Has Brought Me Weird Experiences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 10 years old I went to South Korea with my mother for summer break. When I first heard we were going to Korea I was extremely excited, but my excitement faded away when my mother told me we were going to one of the smaller islands of Korea. Being on an island may sound like a lot of fun, but the island we were going to was basically like a very small town with almost nothing to do. 

When I asked her why we were going there she told me that my grandmother on my fathers side has gotten very ill. My dad was moving from Seoul to the Island, and we were going to be there for my whole summer break. Of course, I was completely bummed about the thought of being constantly bored, but the thought of being able to see my dad was well worth it. He found a job in Korea a couple of years ago, and he has been there since. 

I just wish I had stayed at my grandmothers house the whole entire time. 

During the first week I was in Korea I played around at my grandmothers house. She had about 15 chickens she took care of so I played with them for a good bit, and when that got boring I would talk to my dad and followed him around while he took care of grandma. 

About 9 days into being in Korea my dad asked me if I could go to the local store and pick up a couple snacks for us. I grabbed the 5 out of his hands and started my walk to the store. I had gone with my dad a couple of times so I had the way memorized. Plus, once I got outside it was a straight 2 minute walk without any sort of turns. I got to the store and started to pick out my favorite snacks when I noticed a boy around my age was staring at me from the next aisle. I asked him what he wanted in Korean and he just shrugged his shoulders. 

I took the snacks to the counter and gave the lady my 5. She handed me back 2 dollars. The kid then tapped on my shoulders and asked if I could pay for his snack. He held up a snack that was maybe 50 cents so I went ahead and bought it for him. I knew my dad would have wanted me to so I didnt feel bad about spending more of his money. 

Before I could grab the snack out of his hands to pay for it he bolted out of the store with the snack in his hands. 

I headed out of the store and started the walk back home. About five minutes into the walk I notice that it was taking a lot longer than it should be. I started to walk faster, but I still felt like I was getting nowhere. I broke into a dead sprint and towards my house, but even after what seemed like 15 minutes of running I looked behind me and noticed that the store was still right behind me. 

I didnt know what else to do so I ran back into the store and told the lady I was having difficulty getting home. I gave her my fathers number and waited at the store until he came and got me. I told him about how I didnt seem to be getting anywhere no matter how fast I ran, but he just rubbed my head and told me the streets were confusing. I tried to explain that I literally felt like I wasnt moving anywhere, but he just laughed and walked with me back home. 

When we got back we played a couple games of hangman and munched on our snacks. In the middle of the third game I remembered to give my dad back his change and told him about trying to buy a snack for a boy, but he just ended up stealing the snack from the store. My dad then looked at me and asked me to describe the boy to him. After I was done he looked at me strangely when I finished my description about the boy. 

He asked me if I had gotten his name but I told him he didnt really say anything. He just asked for the snacks and then ran out the door. After we finished the third game he told me that he had to take care of grandma so I just doodled on a piece of paper. 

I cant really draw, but I like to draw squiggly lines around the paper and see if anything recognizable somehow comes out of the squiggles. After five minutes I gave up on the picture as it resembled absolutely nothing. 

I grabbed a book and went outside. I took a bag of chips with me and spent the next hour reading and eating chips. When I was about 40 pages into my book my dad asked me to come back inside. When I walked in my father was holding the drawing I ditched. He flipped it over when I walked in and saw it was a drawing of the boy I saw in the convenience store. I told him that was what the boy looked like, but that I didnt draw the picture. 

He looked over the picture again and threw it into the trash and left me in the room without another word. When he walked into my grandmas room he slammed the door. 

I didnt know what made him so mad, but I didnt really think about that. I was more concerned about why the picture changed on me. I drew scribbles, but the picture on the paper was a fully drawn out face.

I dont know why, but I rushed out the door and ran back to the store. I saw the boy walking around the store and I walked up to him. He didnt really notice me so I said Hello! He looked at me and I asked him what his name was. After a couple of second he said Umpyo.  I remembered my dad never took back his change so I asked him if he wanted to share a snack with me. He nodded his head and I bought the same snack he asked me to buy.

When I walked out of the store I saw that he was gone.

I was a bit bummed out, but I just started walking back to my house. When I was around half way there a man ran out of his house and grabbed me by my shoulders. He reeked of alcohol, and he asked with a sob Umpyo? I looked at him and he let go of me quickly. After he looked at me for about 5 seconds he went back into his house without even saying sorry.

I ran back into my house and into the room I was staying in. I stayed in there and read books until I became tired. Around 10 oclock I fell asleep. 

In the middle of the night I heard a light tapping on the window. I looked out and saw that it was Umpyo. I opened the window and he jumped in. When he landed he made absolutely zero noise. He put a finger up to his lips and pointed at my bed. After I gave him a confused look he walked up to the bed and used his finger to signal for me to move it. The bed was light so I moved it over a couple of feet. He pointed at one of the wooden panels on the floor. I felt over the panel and realized that there was a little opening. I lifted the panel up and found myself staring at a dead Umpyo.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope I kinda answered it haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *cracks knuckles

Alright...

So with me i like to think of cannibalism as an entirely new beast.

Yes, you are getting eaten, but how about the torture involved when you come across a more sadistic cannibal? They don't kill you off the bat. 

Example. 

Kidnapped and tied up to whatever unique your mind can come up with. A man in a horse mask walks up to you with a small butterfly knife. He starts to do a couple of butterfly knife tricks in front of you while giggling. Then with his final trick he jams it right on top of your knee cap. 

He slowly slices off a steak sized piece of meat from the top of your right thigh. You feel the excruciating pain of each slice. After 8 minutes he's finally done and walks up to the stove that is placed next to you.

With a dash of olive oil(gotta stay somewhat healthy) and soon the sweet smell of your flesh cooking overpowers your nose.

After he's done cooking he pours some oil on your open wound and puts the still hot pan over your exposed muscle. 

You scream and wince in pain. 

Beg him to stop.

He finally does.

That sweet smell hits your nose once again.

You look down on your leg and see that it is now predominately gray cooked flesh.

Tomorrow and the days following is just another cut of meat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha i have yet to make money.

I think i'll just stick to writing a story every day.

It's been almost two months since i've started and i am content with the following i have now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuckkkkkk

i'm out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a cut and a snip. 

And some thread into flesh

We took a step back

With a twinkle in our eyes

Several piles of meat

Sit on the cold gray floor

As the fire starts to grow

A sweet smell fills the air

Body parts of past mods

Eaten by the hungry flames

With the last thread done

Valka has been made!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only he put that much effort into his stories, he would've had the amount of upvotes without all of the extra running around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he manipulated votes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just kidding. so it's a person who was banned before.

Makes another account and continues to post stories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a person who was banned, and evaded it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 04:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed by mods.

Author was a ban evader. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/filmcronin

Mostly for me it was because you said you needed backers and collaborators. Which drew me in because I like to help out with writing as much as I can.

Then i saw what collaborating meant to your project.

I mean more power to you and I hope your movie goes well.

Just please when you post it later in the future please make sure you just say you can determine the ending for a small contribution instead of you saying you need collaborators.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And more than deserving of reaching past 200% of his goal. Btw. Is it okay if I give your schoolbus a shoutout on my author's page and if it is should I tag your profile or follow your page and tag it? 

u/filmcronin It isn't every project that asks for money that reveives judgement. It's people asking for money to "decide the ending" especially when it is the first type of post  on your reddit history </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And korea lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just saying...

We want something to be involved in for free.

u/decomprosed had a very good reason with his indiegogo project because he has been very involved with NoSleep and NoSleepOOC for a very long time now and is a staple member of the community.

He also waited a week before submitting(and even more) a status report of how it was going. 

I hinestly think the execution is poor on this one.

If you needed writers to help you with the movie without having to pay 50 you would have had some type of support.

Sorry but for that I'm very uninterested and a bit insulted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't cough on anyone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im sorry..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are in korea and work for a conference organizing company.

We work on different parts of conferences individually and call them projects. 

Sorry that statement confused you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have cold chicken noodle soup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't know what to tell you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They left the basement. They knew they had it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Is Something Far Worse Than The Common Cold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 14:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three days ago four people in our office caught a pretty bad cold. I know that may seem absolutely trivial, but let me tell you that this is no normal cold. I dont really know what started it, but I do know that it is that it has quickly contaminated almost our whole office, and if you happen to see someone so much as sniffle around you please avoid them at all costs. 

The first four people to catch it were actually four of our more healthy employees. When they first started to show signs of a typical cold they took all took a couple of days off. When they came back the yesterday we all made sure to wear our face masks during work. I forgot to bring mine, but the guy who worked across from me handed me his spare. Halfway through the day one of the four men started to cough non-stop for the next 2 to 3 minutes. When he took his facemask off I noticed that the inside of it was covered in a thick coating of phlegm. 

I felt a little sick to my stomach as I never handled the sight of phlegm, but I just took a sip of coke and waited till my stomach settled down. Once it settled down I got back to working on my project. Right as I was sending in my project to my team leader I heard the same guy go into another coughing fit. I turned around to make sure he was okay, but the first thing I saw was blood coming out of his mouth with every single cough. The other three sick men started freaking out and rushed out of the door. 

At that moment I saw enough so I took out my cell phone and dialed in the emergency number, but right as I was about to hit the dial button the man stopped coughing. I looked up at him and he smiled at me. I asked him if he was okay and he nodded his head. I asked him if he wanted me to call him an ambulance and he quickly told me he didnt need one. For the next ten minutes I made sure he didnt need an ambulance, and after him reassuring me several times I just shrugged my shoulders and sent in my project. 

When the clock hit 6 pm I got up immediately and gave my team leader a nod. He asked me if I finished all of the projects for today and I told him I finished all of my projects for today and half of my projects for tomorrow. He gave me a smile and told me to hurry home. On my drive back I noticed that pretty much everyone was wearing a facemask and I began to wonder if it has been spreading in other places as well. 

When I got to my apartment I walked up the five flights of stairs up to my room. When I walked past the first flight of stairs I started to hear what seemed like a groan coming from somewhere on the stairs; I ran up 3 more flights of stairs before I found my next door neighbor laying on the ground with a line of blood coming out of his mouth. I knelt down and tried to help him up, but he swatted my hands away. 

I just called the 119(emergency number) and told them about finding my neighbor lying on the stairs with blood coming out of his mouth. I left him there and went into my room and turned on my tv on before I laid down on my bed.

I watched a couple of movies and fell asleep. 
 
This morning when I woke up I looked outside of my window. I noticed that there were several people lying on the streets with little pools of blood around them. 

I heard sirens coming from a distance, and I saw an ambulance pull up to the bodies lying on the streets. Two guys popped out of the back of the ambulance and grabbed the bodies and threw them in to the car without a gurney. They started driving away before they closed the back doors and I saw that there were around 30 to 40 bodies inside of that ambulance.

I called my team leader to see if we were still working, and he told me that we were just having a half day and then we would be off for however long this sickness spreads. I got dressed for work and headed out to my car. When I started to pull out of my parking lot a lady jumped onto my windshield. She was screaming Help me please while banging on the window. I waited until she got off of my car and I drove off while screaming sorry! As I was driving off I saw that she was on her knees grabbing at anyone that passed by her. 

When I got to work I noticed that there were only 7 cars in the parking lot. We usually have around 24 to 27 cars in the parking lot. I ignored the panic that has taken over me since this morning and walked into the office. When I walked in through the doors I noticed that no one was in the office. I called my team leader and he told me to come into the meeting room. When I walked in four of the other employees grabbed me by my arms and legs and the team leader checked me over. As soon as they confirmed that I wasnt sick they put me down and pulled up a seat for me. I took it and the team leader told me that he had a basement in his house that we could all camp out in.

He had enough food to last for over six months, and we were the last ones in the company that hadnt caught whatever was going on. Seven of us out of our 35 employees were the only ones that managed to avoid whatever was going on.

We took the team leaders van to his house and we have been looking out his small basement window for the next couple of hours.

Its 3 pm now and we have witnessed eight deaths just outside of his window. One person fell over in just five feet away from the window. He kept coughing out blood until he stayed still for a while. He started blowing his nose really loud until he let out a grayish clump of mucus. He looked to have gained 20 pounds in the span of 20 minutes after he discharged the mucus. After 10 minutes his skin started to break all over his body and his bones started to rip through his skin and started tearing his flesh open.

He was dead five minutes after that, but his bones kept growing until they started to crack open and gray liquid started to pour out. 

I am only spreading this warning to you, because you never know who is sick or who isnt. The airports were fully booked today by people trying to avoid the sickness, but I will let you know now that they may seem fine now, but in a couple of days you will notice that people around you are now going into full on coughing fits.

Three of our employees have started to cough heavily in just the last 2 hours. 

If you see someone cough or even sniffle. 

Please avoid them [at all costs] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 13:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least you will always have your best friends with you... well kinda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you very much haha,

I keep thinking IP address but you're definitely right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Always Had a Helping Hand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 06:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone my name is Jay and I owe my life to two dark and blurry hands. I dont know what it is, and I know I probably will never find out. The amount of times it has saved my life is a mystery to me, but there are a couple of times I have actually seen them. Let me tell you about a couple.

At the age of 4 I ran out in to the middle of the street. I should have known better but my brother threw my unopened ice cream cone out onto the street as a joke. I know I should always look both ways before crossing, but my eyes were fixed on my abandoned treat. When I picked up my ice cream I instantly noticed two things. The sound of a car horn and two dark blurs slamming into my side. I was tossed into the air and landed on my neighbors lawn across the street.

I stayed on the grass while the car sped down the road. My brother was screaming on the other side asking me if I was okay, but I couldnt open my mouth to tell him that I was fine. My brother checked both sides and raced across the street and helped me up. When we got in our room I finally managed to calm down and told him about the two dark blurs that pushed me out of the way.
He shook his head no at me and told me that right before the car came he saw me jump out of the way just in time. I know I was four at that time, but I knew there was no way I could jump from the middle of the street and into our neighbors lawn across the street.

Fast forward to when I was 13. After my third period class we had a 10 minute break to get water, use the restroom, and eat some snacks. I took out the peanut butter and jelly sandwich my mother made for my snack and started to bite down on it. Midway through my first bite I heard a kid yell in pain right behind me. I turned around to see my bully, Mark, with a pencil lodged into the middle of his hand. I jumped out of my seat and stared at him. He was trying to pull the pencil out, but every time he touched the pencil he would go back to screaming in pain.

The teacher ran up to me and pulled me outside of the class while she called 911. She came back out and told me to sit on the bench by the guidance counselors office until she figured everything out. I waited on the bench for over an hour. During that time I saw three cops and 2 paramedics rush into the room. The cops followed the teacher to the principals office where they could review the cameras. The teacher came back with a puzzled look on her face. She apologized for making me wait for so long and told me to get back to class. Five days later she quit in the middle of class and walked out. She left her notepad on her desk so I scooped it up and went to the restroom.

I opened it up to see a sketch of two dark blurry hands with a bloody pencil in the right hand. Feeling a little creeped out; I just threw the notepad in the trash and decided to try and forget about it.
This is the last occurrence I want to tell you about.

When I just graduated college three of my old high school buddies invited me over to their house to celebrate. I gratefully accepted the invitation and was told to be there the next day at 8pm.
The following day at 6pm I started to drive over there since it took around an hour and thirty minutes. I arrived at 7:45 and knocked on his door. When the door opened I was greeted to the face of my once best friend. He gave me a hug and told me to grab a beer from the fridge.

We were all having a good time. We drank beer, played a couple rounds of beer pong, and started up a movie.

It was all fun until the hands I have only noticed a couple of times started to float in a circle around my head. I tried getting up but the hands just slammed me back down. For the next ten minutes the hands forced me to stay quiet and completely still. When I tried to speak the right hand covered my mouth and suffocated me until the desire to speak went away. Whenever I tried to signal to my friends that something was wrong the hands grabbed me by the wrists and held them down.

This is when the panic started to take over me. With sweat dripping down my forehead I tried to think of a way to get away from the hands. When I couldnt think of a way to get out I started to plea to the hands through my thoughts, but they just wouldnt stop holding me down.

At that moment I felt like I was betrayed by the very thing that saved my life multiple times. I shut my eyes and tried to calm myself down. After a couple of minutes I opened my eyes again only to see that the hands were gone. I looked to my left and right and saw that my friends were still sipping on beer while intently watching the movie. Just as I am about to tell my friends I was going to sleep in the spare bedroom I heard two gunshots from just outside of the house.

My friends and I bolted out of the couch and I was the first to run out the door. I saw two bodies lying on the ground. When I walked up I saw that they each had a gun in their hand. I flipped the first guy over to see that it was a face I didnt really recognize. Hell, I wouldnt have known who it had I not seen the scar in the middle of his hand.

My buddies flipped over the other body and that was the moment I knew that I should never trust anyone. It was my brother. Part of me wanted to feel grief and I did for a second until I found a note in his front pocket.

Once I finished reading it I spit on his face and dialed 911.
It definitely was short and to the point.

Dear Jay,

I wish you hadnt avoided that car.

I wish mom aborted you like she said she would to dad when she 

found out she was pregnant again.

You were a mistake and a burden.

With this bullet I will finally make our family perfect again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 06:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is that supposed to mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 06:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahah you follow The Donald and you don't see yourself as a cuck?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 06:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're banned. You're banned. 

It doesn't matter how good a story is. 

You follow the rules here. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moved from us to korea haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait why? Haha 

Were you just in wreck it ralph?!?!??! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So help me god if you glitch... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay battle start.

Rules follow the very structure of "calvin ball" 

Any questions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K... I'll stay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But i have a pocket knife which allows me 2 handicap points </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I-I'll leave now.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sword fight!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like it would be quite amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>       8    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remote Desktop Control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I am going to be judged very harshly for this, but I really need to tell everyone what I found out yesterday.

Before I let you know what happened I want to give you a little background of my less than admirable hobby. I go around electronic stores and go up to every single clearance laptop. I look up the ip address of each laptop and jot it down in my notebook. 

Then I go home and try every single ip address. I dont check the new ones for a couple of days unless I am out of older ones to try, but mostly I already have some for a couple of weeks before I try them on the Remote Desktop application. I dont do it to steal their credit card information or to expose them. I just do it because I have always been a very curious person. I just want to know what people did on their computers privately. I chose laptops because I knew people never really shut off their laptops so I had a better chance of logging in as long as they didnt have a password.

After 3 years of just finding the slightly awkward web search history to finding my friend and now ex-girlfriend talking shit about me on Facebook messages I started to get slightly bored with it last week.

Yesterday I made my usual run around the three electronic stores around my area and jotted down 4 new ip addresses. When I got home I checked my notebook and realized I was running low on new addresses so I decided to check the four new ones I found after I ate a little dinner. Sometimes laptops have sold within hours after I get home. 

Besides, I really did not feel like working so I called the local convenience store I managed. The assistant manager answered the phone with his usual mock happy customer service voice, but quickly became monotone when he realized it was me on the phone. I told him that I would not be able to come in since I woke up to a horrible headache and sore throat. He grumbled something over the phone, but before he could object I hung up on him. I then called the pizza restaurant famous for *Better Ingredients. Better Pizza.* and ordered 2 pepperoni pizzas with extra cheese. 

I turned on the tv and started to watch people getting ripped off by a pawnshop and waited on my pizza. When the pizza arrived I paid the man and sat down on the couch and devoured the first two slices. While the bald man offered 30 dollars for a 2,000 year old coin my eyes drifted off to the computer. With a feeling of slight excitement I grabbed the two boxes of pizza and walked up to my computer desk.  

While I was eating my third slice of pizza I sat down on my worn down chair and booted up my computer. I double clicked on Remote Desktop Connection, cracked my knuckles while it was starting up, and punched in the 1st ip address while I grabbed my fourth slice. I was highly disappointed when all four ip addresses didnt work so I sat back down and finished off the first pizza. 

I looked through my notebook I wrote the addresses on and made sure all of them were checked off. After going through it once I found 8 I have not tried yet. I had six from over 3 months ago and 2 from my trip last month; so I went back to my computer with my next box of pizza and tried all eight of them. Two of them went through. I looked through the most recent one only to find a person very obsessed with cats. The wallpaper was a picture of a white Persian next to a wine glass, and the photo folder had over 7,000 photos of cats. 

I closed out of the connection and input the one from around 4 months ago. The wallpaper on this desktop was one of the generic ones it was blue and black with the Windows logo in the bottom right edge. I always check the photos first and I opened the folder only to see a blank page. I clicked on videos after and I found 4 video files. They were marked 1a, 2b, 3c, 4d. 

I tried 1A first and grabbed another slice. The first 45 seconds was just complete darkness, but when the camera shifted up I could see that it was a brightly lit room. There was a man who looked to be around his 40s completely naked and tied to a wooden chair. He was crying and snot was dripping down his nose. The whole room was completely white and he was by himself sitting in the middle of the room. About 2 minutes later a woman dressed in a red track suit came in. She was holding a kitchen knife in one hand, and a bottle of vodka in the other. The closer she got to him the more the man struggled to get out of his chair. I saw his wrists start to bleed where he had been tugging so hard. When she was in front of him she grabbed his right thigh and cut a chunk of flesh from the top of his thigh to the knee cap. 

He still stayed remarkably composed after losing a large portion of flesh, but his composure crumpled when she started to pour the bottle of vodka onto his legs. I didnt have the audio turned on, but I could feel his scream creeping into my very soul.

I could see the look of desperation on his face and the pain in his eyes. She took of a ring from her left hand and shoved the diamond straight into his chest. She then shoved the thigh flesh down the knife as if she were making a demented kebab; after admiring her twisted art she drove the knife in the mans heart and walked out leaving him dying on the chair.

I have been one to easily stomach in violence, but the video automatically made me start to panic a little bit inside. I passed B2 and clicked C3. 

The setting was in a small house in the middle of the woods. A van pulled up to the house and a small boy hopped out of the sliding van door. A man came out carrying a big red hunk of meat. A woman hopped out of the driver seat. As the boy walked up to the camera he smiled from ear to ear and waved at the camera. He then walked up to his father and helped him chop off the hands and feet of what seemed like the skinned body of a man and threw them in the fire the mother started. They tore out the intestines and threw it in the pot that was on top of the fire and then started to chop the mans body into smaller chunks. Once they were done they threw the contents in to the pot. Ten minutes later the boy walked up to the pot and dunked his spoon in to the human broth. Once he took a sip he smiled and nodded at his father. Before anything else happened I turned the video off and sat in silence as the need to throw up became apparent.

The video made me absolutely sick to my stomach. I threw the slice of pizza back in the box and retched in front of my trash can. I didnt move until I was absolutely sure I wouldnt throw up. When I went back on the screen I exited out of the video section immediately and was about to close down the program until I saw a word document titled My Contribution

I opened the document and saw My Contribution and then a list afterwards. The first part of the list stopped me in my tracks as my brother was coming on the 19th of January for his winter break, and the name was unmistakably mine.  

1) See Toweyinger Brown on January 19, 2017.

 2) Tie James Taylor to his bed while he is sleeping.

 3) Cut off his right leg and then left leg. 

 4) Stitch his legs next to my legs.

 5) Cut his arms off and stitch them on my hips. 

 6) If he is not dead yet slice his neck and give him a hug.

 7) Look at the camera and tell them you are now closer to your brother.

The memory of my mother buying my brother a new laptop 3 months ago after he broke his last one hit me at that moment. Of course she bought him a clearance laptop. She had always liked store bought items, but she always made sure she found the best deals.

My brother and I have always been close. I just havent talked to him much in the last couple of years due to the difference in our schedules. He would message me occasionally, but I would always forget to reply. I kept missing his calls and forget to call back. The last time he came here on his summer break he joked around that he would find a way to make us closer, but I guess he was actually being serious. 

Walter I know that you use reddit as well. If you happen to read this story please know that I really do love you. Im sorry I have gotten so distracted with life, but please give me one last chance to [make it up to you] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).  



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 09:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thank you so much!!! 

I'm really glad to hear y'all are enjoying them!

I hope I don't disappoint with my future stories! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 09:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IDon'tKnowSorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 08:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha about a month and a half now lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Didn't Even Want To Learn How To Play The Piano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 15:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 14 years old my mother fell in love with Classical music. It started with Tchaikovsky playing from her portable Walkman to her blasting Bach in the kitchen cd player. I never cared for the music, but I knew how much she loved it so I always made it seem like I was just as interested in classical music as she was. 

Every morning I woke up to sound of classical music and to the smell of bacon. When I walked into the kitchen I would see my mother dancing while she cooked my breakfast. Those were one of the few moments I would truly share the same love my mother had for classical music. There is something about soft music playing in the background while stuffing my mouth with my mothers extra greasy pancakes and butter toast I loved so much.

I never found a problem with my mothers passion until four men lugged a piano into our living room. My mother brought out three beginner piano books out of her purse I knew that I was screwed. She already knew how to play the piano pretty well, and the only person that would need these books was me. Once the men left she tapped on the piano bench so I reluctantly walked up and sat down.

From then on my mother started to teach me how to play the piano. 

I never wanted to play any type of instrument so I decided to act like I was completely un-teachable. Whenever she told me how to play a certain note I would always hit the next key over. When I sensed that she was getting upset I would plant my face into my hands and complain about how difficult it was for me. No matter what I did she would still make me sit on the piano bench with her for 2 hours a day.

We would continuously practice the same song over and over again until she lost her patience. This was now a part of my schedule and I was about to just start actually trying. Two months later I was coming back home after school. I had decided that today was the day that I would start trying to learn how to play the piano. 

When I got home I found a random red sedan in our driveway. When I walked into the door I saw a very uninterested woman sitting on our couch. She had short black hair, looked to be around her mid 30s, and a permanent scowl on her face. 

The woman looked up at me and tried her best to produce a smile; only to show me the best example of what a fake smile looks like. 

I took a seat beside my mother on the piano bench and smiled back at the woman. She told me her name was Ms. Wilson and she is my new piano tutor. She lives 4 houses down from us so she expects me to be at her hour 5 p.m. on the dot every Monday and Friday. 

Once the woman left around an hour later my mother explained to me that she was tired of feeling like she was being a drawback on my passion for music. So she looked around for a piano tutor we would be able to afford. The lady down the street contacted her yesterday telling her she would be able to teach me for 30 dollars a week. Once my mother heard that she used to perform for our town symphony 10 years ago she automatically accepted the offer. 

Three days later I went up to Ms. Wilsons house and knocked on her door. When Ms. Wilson opened the door I did a very visible double take. She looked completely different. Ms. Wilson was smiling a genuine smile and wearing a simple red skirt. She looked like she was 15 years younger than what she was and when she greeted me with a hug I felt a feeling of unease take over my body.

When she hugged me I knew for a fact that her hand grazed my butt, but I just figured it was on accident. She grabbed my right shoulder and guided me to her piano. It was in her living room but it was placed at an awkward place. The piano keys were facing the couch and the piano bench was right on the wall. 

When I took my seat I noticed that my back was right on the wall and I was facing the couch. Ms. Wilson took her seat on the couch and told me to take out my piano book and play the song I have been having difficulty on. 

I tried my very hardest and played the whole song with only two mistakes. I only made those mistakes because I noticed that every page I played perfectly Ms. Wilsons legs would start shaking up and down harder and harder, but when I made my first mistake I noticed that she would stop shaking her leg and start staring at me intently.

Once I finished the song she walked up to me and stared down at me. She started to stroke my forehead with her index and middle finger. In the softest voice I have ever heard she said Youre a fucking failure. I looked up at her and asked her what she said, but when I blinked my eyes I noticed she was back on her couch giving me a slow clap. She told me I only messed up twice and that with only a little bit of practice I would have this song down perfectly. 

After the lesson I went back home and told my mother what I thought she said. With a chuckle my mother told me that I probably heard her wrong and asked me to play the song we worked on. I played the song without a mistake and saw a huge smile spread across my mothers face. I knew that learning how to play the piano was a great gift for her so I continued to go to Ms. Wilsons house twice a week for my lessons. 

That Monday she sat on the bench with me while I practiced a new song. Every page I played right she would stroke my thighs, and with every wrong note I would feel a sharp pain in my leg. I knew she was pinching me, but I really just wanted her to stop rubbing me. 

After my lesson I played the new song I learned from my mother and she was even happier with the results. I wanted to stop learning how to play the piano from Ms. Wilson so I decided that from now on after my lessons I would completely butcher the song my mother asked me to play after my lesson. 

When the next Monday came Ms. Wilson opened the door before I knocked on her door. She was wearing a short black skirt and told me to come in for my lesson. I went inside and took my seat on the bench. She took her seat on the couch and watched me as I played. This time I played the new song without a single mistake. I closed my eyes while I played as I had memorized the song and only opened them when I had finished the song.

I heard the sound of Ms. Wilsons voice saying Bravo Excellent and Perfection! I looked at her only to find that she had taken her shirt and bra off to reveal her rib bones poking out of her midsection. Her chest was now a mixture of mashed up flesh and crushed up bones around her slowly beating heart. With every clap her face started to fall apart more and more. Her nose slid down to her chin and her eyes have started to melt out of the sockets. The skin on her cheeks started to peel off only to reveal rotting flesh underneath. 

That is when I bolted out of the bench and ran out of her door. 

I didnt stop running until I got into the front door of my house. 

I used my key to open the door, but the door wouldnt budge. 

After about 30 seconds of frantically knocking on the door a man answered the door with a confused look on his face; I screamed at him Who the fuck are you? Where the hell is my mother? 

With a surprised look on his face he took out his cellphone and called the police while going into our old laundry room.

I caught a couple of sentences, but I couldnt hear everything. 

Missing kid. 4 years ago. I do not see his mother. He is very confused. I dont know, maybe around 18 to 20.

Today has been three days since I ran out of Ms. Wilsons house. Ms. Wilson was found dead in her house. They say that she has been dead for the past 2 years. She died of a heart attack, and I have been missing for the past 4 years. My mother disappeared the same day I did. 

I was found, but my mother is [still missing] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).

Edit: Wilson not Watson sorry guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Regret Winning the Lottery With My Three Brothers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three years ago I won the lottery, and within 4 months later I learned to never trust anyone. My three brothers (Jerry, Paul, and Joseph) and I won the Power Ball lottery. We claimed it as anonymous, and split the 399.4 million dollars between the three of us. Of course, after taxes we took away around 71 million dollars each. 

Every week for 10 years we had been throwing in 50 dollars a person; some weeks we would win a couple of hundred dollars but others we would make a couple of dollars. Despite losing money, we would still throw in the same 50 dollars week after week without a second thought. The very hope that someday we might be able to just live comfortably without having a job was more than enough motivation for us; so that is why we never gave up or gave the fifty dollar expense a second thought.

We started the lottery pool when I was 24 years old. It became a thing one Christmas morning when we all realized that we were spending around 300 dollars a month on lottery tickets already. Before you judge all of us, I want you to know that since we were all very young our father spent almost all of his paycheck lottery tickets. We captured that same passion, but luckily for us, it was in a moderate way. 

Joseph and I have always been the closest since Paul and Jerry were both more than 7 years older than me. Joseph and I only had a 2 year gap between us. It meant that we argued and fought the most, but at the end of the day we never complained about having to share a bunk bed with each other. No matter how much we argued that day we would still talk to each other until we fell asleep every single night.  

We were the ones that actually got everything set up for the lottery pool, and he was the one that convinced Jerry and Paul to join in so that we could have a better chance. 

We made a couple of simple rules for in case we won and how we would go about getting the tickets.

1)	We always used randomized numbers. (Chance above luck)

2)	We would buy the tickets in turn based system. (Jerry, Joseph, Paul, then me)

3)	No matter who turned in the numbers; we would always split the winnings 25%,

4)	If someone was unable to participate that week they would not be involved with the winnings.

For 10 years we were facing constant failure. The most we won was around 1200 dollars, but if you added up all of the money we had spent until then it felt like we were just throwing our money away. For some reason we still kept doing it without any sort of hesitation. The person that was in charge for that week to purchase the tickets always found the 50 dollars from each person. 

Ten years later I went into the convenience store that was right by my house and purchased the 200 Quick-Pic lottery tickets. That Wednesday I sat in front of the tv while the numbers were being called. I wrote the numbers on a notepad and scanned through every single ticket. When I found one ticket that matched every single number and in the right order I stared at the two pieces of paper. I checked the ticket over a hundred times just to make sure that the ticket I was holding in my hand was the impossible goal my brothers and I were shooting for.

I called all of them within 10 minutes, and before an hour all of them were standing in front of me staring at the lottery ticket. Paul asked me if I was pranking them, but I convinced him that I really wasnt. Jerrys whole body was shaking with what seemed like absolute excitement, and Joseph walked up to me and gave me a hug while telling me that all of our lives will finally get better.

We all decided that the Cash option would be the best for us to split it equally, and once we got the cash the first thing we did was split four ways on a new house for our mother and father. I have never seen my mother and father so happy than the day that we surprised them to their new house. My father fell into tears while trying to explain how much it meant to him while my mother gave each of us hugs while telling us how great we were to them.

With all of the newfound money life was great to me until a month and a half later when Paul was found floating on his outdoor pool. His neck was sliced opened with the head of a rubber duck poking out of his open neck. 

Joseph came over to my house the next day to deliver the news, and when I heard about it I just wanted to cry over the loss of Paul. We may not have been close, but he was the one that always made sure we did our homework and made good decisions. Every time any of us thought about doing something reckless Paul wouldnt try to stop us, but he would try to talk to us and tell us what we thought about doing was absolutely foolish. 

The paranoia didnt really sink in until the death of Jerry 2 months later. He was found in the middle of our local park clutching a rubber duck. His stomach was ripped open with both of his feet stuck into his midsection. He had been dead for 8 hours until someone noticed that there was a dead body on the park bench. 

The day after Jerrys dead body was found on the park bench I noticed that Joseph had stopped talking to me all together. Just to make sure I texted him over 10 times and called him 3 times, but I did not get a response. 

I remembered playing with ducks with Joseph in the bathtub when we were younger and took baths together. I remember that Jerry and Paul would always make fun of us for playing with such childish toys in the bath, but we were never affected by their taunts. 

I didnt want to think it was Joseph actually killing both of our brothers, but I did not really have any other person to blame. I know I didnt do it, and I know that we claimed the lottery winnings anonymously so all of my worry was on Joseph.

I know that we were family, but you dont know what people will do for that extra bit of money. We all had more than enough money to live off of, but obviously Joseph didnt think it was enough for him.

For the next two weeks I double checked everything I did and everywhere I went. I was filled with paranoia since I knew that Joseph knew where I usually liked to go and what I liked to do. I kept staying vigilant until yesterday.

Yesterday, I woke up to the news of Josephs death. He was found a knife cut from his neck to the bottom of his midsection. The bottom half of a rubber duck was stapled to his stomach and the top half of the rubber duck was sewn over his lips. 

There were two words cut into his forehead. Little Ducky 

When I heard the news of his death my blood ran cold, and I found myself filling with an overwhelming sense of panic.

[That is exactly what my mother used to call us] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks). 





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Now Know Why My Best Friend Acted Creepy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have always been a scrawny person since I was in elementary school. Granted due to my semi decent sense of humor I was never bullied, but to the opposite sex I was never deemed attractive or dateable. Friendzone was the nation I inhabited and until the age of 25 I was completely fine with it. Of course, I craved the attention when it came time for the homecoming dance or prom, but I always managed to get a friend that went with me out of pity. 

After high school I went to a local college and graduated 5 years later. I ran out of funds so I worked in sales after my sophomore year to make enough money for my last two years. On my graduation day I looked back on the years I spent in college and immediately felt regret. Every day after my classes I would just go back home and eat dinner with my parents and go to my bedroom where I would spend the whole night surfing the web and reading. I made a couple of friends and had a date that ended terribly, but I just felt like I never truly utilized college for all of its worth. I was accepted into an out of state college, but I decided against it because I did not want to get out of my comfort zone.

After college I tried to find a job that went along with my major (English), and found that it is pretty much impossible to get a teaching job in the town I lived in. After four months of looking for a job I decided that any job was as good as any and went to the local Electronics store for my old job back. 

The manager was more than happy to take me back as I was the top seller every month I was there. I dont like to go out and make friends, but I was definitely good at making people spend their money. When I came back for my first day back 3 days later I realized that it was a completely different crew except the manager. There were three salesmen (Mack, Vance, and Jonathan) and the manager (Anthony). Before I came back in Mack was the top salesman for the past 6 months and we automatically did not like each other. Vance was the lowest salesman, but he always cleaned the store up and made sure all of the inventory was correct. Jonathan was the middle tier salesman, and we became fast friends. 

There really isnt much to talk about the world of sales. People come in looking for X object and we sell them X object while trying to add on accessories. Sometimes we would get them to loosen on their original budget and go for a higher end model. That is about as far as sales really go to me. It gets me a paycheck and I can pay the rent my mother and father suddenly started charging me. 

Three weeks into working there Jonathan asked if I wanted to come over to his house to hang out and drink a couple of beers. I agreed and after work we went there and turned on a couple of movies while downing beer after beer. After about 3 hours I decided it was time for me to go home, but Jonathan rationalized with me about the dangers of driving drunk. He brought out 2 pillows and a blanket. He pointed at the couch and I sat back down. He put the blanket and pillows beside me and told me goodnight while he walked back to his room.

I dont know when I fell asleep, but I remember snapping awake. I have this thing ever since I was young where I would slightly open my eyes in case its already bright, but I found the room to be completely dark. I slightly glanced up trying to figure out where I was but what I saw made me close my eyes completely and start shaking a little. Jonathan was standing in the hallway while staring at me. I waited about 10 minutes and slightly opened my eyes once more to see that he was going back into his room. 

The next morning I woke up to the smell of bacon. I quickly got out of bed and went into his kitchen. He was cooking and looking like his normal self so I just let my paranoia slide off and I asked him if he needed any help. With a wave of his hand he just told me to sit down and enjoy my hangover. I sat down on the couch until he was done cooking and we ate bacon and pancakes. We went to work right after breakfast, and by the end I completely forgot about him staring at me in the middle of the night.

The next weekend he asked me if I wanted to go out to a club an hour away from us and without a hesitation I told him yes. I told him I would wear my black suit to look extra spiffy, and while laughing he told me he would pick me up from my house at 10 pm. Around 1015 I heard him honking and I went outside and got into his car. When I saw him I had to take a double take. He was wearing the same exact thing as me. Black suit and a white button up shirt; I just decided to ignore it. 

We got to the club at 11, right as the doors were opening, and before it was midnight I was having the time of my life. For the first time in my life I was meeting girls that seemed to take an interest in me, and I even got to dance with a couple of them. The only thing that really threw me off was that Jonathan seemed to be staring down every single girl that even gave me a slight bit of interest. 

At 2 Jonathan came up to me and told me that it was time to go home so I went to the bar to pay off my tab. 

While I was paying my tab a girl that I danced with earlier came up to me and slipped a piece of paper in my pocket while giving me a light peck on my cheek. I know I blushed, but I maintained my composure enough to give her a wink and a little smile.

When I got into the car I took out the piece of paper and showed Jonathan. Nearly bouncing in my seat with my excitement I told him that she was definitely a girl that I would not mind dating. He asked me what she looked like so I told him that she was a little shorter than me, brown hair, and green eyes. Then I started to explain to him how pretty she was, but I noticed that he had changed his expression from happiness to what seemed like anger. The whole car ride was filled with awkward silences and sideway glances from Jonathan.

I felt like he had gotten a bit too weird for me so I started to avoid him at work. It worked for the first 3 days, but I noticed that he had started to follow me around. When I was driving home I would see his car from a distance away. Sometimes when I was lying in my bed I would spot a set of eyes coming from the set of trees in front of my house, but every single time I would walk up to the window I would see the eyes vanish. I didnt really know it was him until I saw a figure with bright green shoes run down the street. 

I know Jonathan is the only person I have ever seen wear bright green shoes. They were the shoes he wore whenever he went out running or whenever he exercised. 

I decided that the next day would be the best day to just approach him and tell him that I noticed him following me after work and looking into my window. I was going to tell my only and best friend that I would really appreciate it if he could just give me some space until I thought he was back to normal. 

That next day the store was closed. The store was closed because Jonathan was found in the middle of the night by the police with a giant gaping hole in his chest. His heart was removed and placed in his mouth. Where his heart should have been was a credit card from our store. The magnetic strip was rubbed off, and the name and card number was grinded off. On his stomach was a series of cuts to reveal a little note. 
 
Was it worth the sale?

I know I wanted him to give me some space, but I never wanted him to die. He was my only best friend, and the grief that filled my heart when my manager called and told me the news caused me to hang up on him and fall on my bed. With deep sobs I felt like the world was crashing down on me, and I never felt like he ever knew how much he really meant to me. 

Today is the day after Jonathan was found dead. I decided to go to the mall to clear my head.

I went outside to my car and found a letter stuck in my window. 

I grabbed the letter and read it in my car.

Hey subject8631,

Im sure youve noticed that I have been following you around, and that I have been acting weird around you. 

I know on the first night you spent the night over you saw me staring at you on the couch. 

I just want you to know that on the first week Mack convinced an older woman to make an $8100 tv purchase using our store credit card. 

The next day the woman came back with the tv. It had a big crack in the middle of the screen, but she told us all that it had come that way. Normally, we just return it and get our money back from the manufacturer, but Mack did not want to lose out on the commission. It was the last one we had in stock and he wanted to have an upper hand on you. 

She started to beg and plea to just take the tv back and let her buy a cheaper model. She told him that she didnt even have the money to pay the monthly bill. He just told her she was out of luck and made her take the tv back into her car. 

That night she killed herself. She was clutching a remote in her left hand and an empty bottle of pills in her right hand. 

The daughter came in 3 days later. It was your off day, but Mack was there. She went up to him and told him about the death of her mother. She didnt seem sad, but I could tell she was not here to ask about what can be done with the bill. With a smile she asked who the salesman was and the mother fucker told her it was you and described what you looked like. With a smile she skipped out the door and drove off in her red sedan.

When you spent the night I woke up to the sound of a car engine starting up around 2 am. I looked out the window and saw that same red sedan. When we were going to the club I saw the red sedan following us. When you described to me about the girl that gave you her number it matched what she looked like exactly. I just wanted to make sure you were safe so I followed you home and I kept watch over you.

Tonight I invited her over. I took the paper she wrote you her number on and texted her. She said she will be here at 2 am. I know I may not be alive when you read this, but I want you to know that I love you man. I know we havent been friends for long, but just know that I acted like a creep around you because I wanted to make sure [you were safe]  (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks) 







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cut up tongue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 10:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I heard the sound of my alarm going off I thought I hit snooze and fell back asleep again. About 1 hour later I bolted out of bed and checked the time. As soon as I saw that it was 8:45 I started to panic as it would be the 5th time I am late in the past month. I dont know why, but I just developed this habit of accidentally hitting Dismiss instead of Snooze. I know I should get up when I hear the alarm, but old habits really do die hard.

I rushed out of bed and texted my manager telling him Im sorry, but Im going to be about 15 minutes late today. I went into my bathroom and just threw some gel on my hair and got quickly dressed. About 5 minutes later I was in my car and on the road. Luckily, I was only about 8 minutes late so I knew it wouldnt be a huge deal.  I took off my shoes as soon as I got in threw on my slippers, (My company is big about keeping their floors clean) and scanned my finger on a security pad that is next to the door. When I heard the door unlock on my third try I rushed to the second floor and took my seat in the office. 

Usually we have a couple of people talking amongst each other while working on their projects, but today everyone in the office was quiet as they typed away on their computers. I checked my e-mails to see if there was any huge project that we suddenly got over the weekend, but I hadnt received any new e-mails since Friday. I walked into our break area and got a cup of coffee; when I walked back I noticed that Jim was writing extremely fast on a piece of paper. I glanced at his paper only to see a jumbled mass of scribbles everywhere. He stopped what he was doing when he noticed me staring and looked up at me with a blank stare. 

After a couple of seconds of awkward silence Jim finally said in the most monotone voice I think you should go back to your desk Greg. I nodded at him and quickly went back to my seat, and started to work on my project. I dont know what was wrong with Jim, but this guy really needs to work on his attitude. The more I sit in my chair working on my project the more I get mad at how Jim talked to me. I mean he just started 2 months ago. Im the one that is leading the project hes working on. What gave him the right to talk to me like that?

When I felt like I couldnt hold my anger any longer I got out of my chair and into my managers office. I knocked on the door and he told me to come in. When I walked in I saw that he was holding a letter opener in his left hand and a bottle of wine in his right hand. I started to tell him about how Jim just talked to me, and as his superior I felt like it was completely uncalled for. As I was ranting I saw the manager blankly stare at me as he kept trying to open the wine bottle with the letter opener. He stuck the letter opener in the cork finally and started to wiggle the letter opener around. When I finished speaking he put all of his attention on opening his wine bottle.

After about 3 minutes of trying with the letter opener he threw it on the ground and held the wine bottle with both of his hands. He brought his mouth the tip of the bottle and started to bite it as hard as he could.  With his fourth bite I heard a sharp crack and saw specks of blood splatter on his white desk. He spit the glass piece out of his mouth along with the tip of his tongue in the trash can beside his desk. He looked back at me and finally said in the same exact voice Jim used on me Jims right Greg, go back to your desk. I started to complain that I had no idea why Jim even thought he had the authority to talk to me like that, but my manager slammed his hand on his desk and glared at me. Go back to your desk Greg. Jim is right. Jim is right. So you need to go back to your desk. You need to be at your desk right now. Jim knows what is best. 

As blood started to drip out of his mouth and onto his shirt I asked him if he was okay, but he ignored my concerns and turned his chair around. I begged him to just call a doctor, but he refused to say a single word to me as he brought up the bottle and took a loud swig. I started to panic, but I left his office and walked towards my desk.

I kept trying to reassure myself that everything was completely normal, and that there wasnt anything for me to worry about. I started to feel better, but that only lasted a second. Every single desk I passed on my way back to my own desk I noticed that everyone was working furiously, but what they were doing made zero sense to me. One was just placing stamps all over the computer monitor, and another person was grabbing the phone and tapping random numbers without making a call. Mark, who has been a good friend of mine since I started working here, was continuously tapping the power button on his computer tower, and Jeff, who I hated, was on a word document typing complete nonsense. 

When I reached my desk I started to feel panic set in as I had no idea what the hell was going on, but I just brought up my project and tried my hardest to ignore everything going on and just get some work done. 

I was starting to get into my project when I noticed something. Everything was completely silent in the office. I looked up and the blood drained from my face; every single one of our 33 employees was staring at me. I tried asking what was wrong, but everyone started chanting in unison Stay in your seat Greg. Just work and dont get up.

Right at that moment I decided to just say screw it to the job, and went straight for the doors. Mark and Jim got up and stood in front of the doors, but I just barreled past them and went downstairs. I pressed the button on the side of the door and when it unlocked I kicked my slippers off and put on my shoes. 

I ran to my car and drove home as fast as I could. 

When I got home I took my phone out of my glove compartment to find a text message from my manager.

Greg you do know that today is a holiday right? Dont come in unless you want to work by yourself all day!

That message was sent to me 5 minutes after I ran into work.

Since I cant use my cell phone at work I really need to remember which days are holidays, because I know that I was not [working alone] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you so much everyone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a rough start when I first started writing here a little over a month ago, but through the help of other writers on the IRC and also the OOC I feel like I have definitely grown as a writer.

I know I'm still a pip squeek compared to most of you, but I promise I'll keep trying my hardest to contribute to my favorite subreddit of all. 

That's all. 

I'm going to go run around in a conference now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Last Trip To My Closed Down High School </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday my aunt died, and immediately I felt in my heart a gap that will never be filled again. My mother and father left me with them whenever they found the opportunity to make money; so I was stuck with my aunt and uncle for most of my childhood. So even now I see my aunt and uncle as more of my parents than anybody else. As soon as I received the news of her death I immediately told my boss to give me the next three days off and I drove two states over. On the ride there I turned on all of the songs we used to sing together whenever we went on long drives while I silently sobbed.

When I was close by I decided to drive by my old high school to try and recapture some old memories. As I got closer I noticed that something was off. It was 2:30 pm and that is usually the time that the school day ends, but no matter where I looked I did not see a single car driving away from the high school. When I arrived I knew why. My old high school has been shut down. I feel a small bit of grief since the building that introduced me to my first crush, my first best friend, and my absolute favorite teacher has now become a slab of concrete that held lost and forgotten memories. 

I sadly got back into my car and drove to my aunts house. As soon as I arrived I saw that there were several cars in her driveway. When I walked in the door the first thing I saw was the sight of my defeated uncle sipping on a glass of whisky while sitting in the sofa he has had for 20 years. Then I saw a bored looking man talking to my uncle about the debt that she had left him. My uncle was nodding as he was pretending to listen, but I know that my uncle never really cared about being in debt. Of course, everything else my aunt had was now his, but he still refused to give the lawyer any of his attention.

I walked up to my uncle and placed my hand on his shoulder.

As soon as he saw that he was me he smiled his 5 tooth smile and said I just knew you would come! I kept telling everyone you would come, but everyone told me you would be too busy to come, but I told everyone that you would be here for me and your mother. Though my uncle had fallen victim to mild Dementia he had always known that I would forever call him and his wife my mother and father. 

After we are done talking I walk to the kitchen and sit down as I revisit all of my older memories of my aunt cooking pancakes for me while she sang the little songs she loved so much, and how she would hold my hands telling me that I would always be something great. Feeling the need to cry again I went upstairs and in to my old bedroom. Seeing that everything was where it was the day I left made me break out into a sob once again. 

In the middle of my sobbing I slammed on the right corner of my bed and felt something hard. Only when I am done sobbing did I un-flip my covers and see my old high school yearbook laying there from when I was looking over it the day before I went to college. I was reminded that my old high school was now shut down, and before I became even more depressed I decided to do the most reckless thing I have ever done.

I am going to break into my high school.

When my uncles grandfather clock alerted me that it was midnight by ringing three times I hopped out of my bed and snuck outside. I got into my car and drove to my old high school. 

I noticed that the third window on the right side of the building was slightly opened earlier so that was the first place I checked. When I walked up to the window I felt a sudden rush of adrenaline.

It was still opened.

I raised the window and slowly slid my body in. 

As soon as I got into the room I recognized it completely. It was where I took my Spanish class my senior year. The teacher of the class was Mrs. Gomez and she was my absolute favorite teacher. I have never met a more patient person than her, and she always talked in a way that you would just want to pay attention the whole class. When I first came into the class I was struggling with the Spanish language, but with her patience and perseverance I quickly became one of her star pupils.

After a couple of minutes I left the room and walked down the hallways. I stopped in front of my old locker and put in my old combination. I was surprised when it opened, but realized that it was completely empty.

I went up to the first door on the left after the lockers ended and found myself in my old gymnasium. This is where I saw the face of my first crush the first time. While I was thinking about how she made fun of me in front of the whole history class for having a crush on her I heard a slam from the other side of the gym. I froze in fear for what felt like an eternity, but the sound of the second slam jolted me out of my paralyzed state. I didnt bother seeing what could have made the sounds. Instead I decided to get out of the gym as fast as I possibly could. When I was around 3 steps away I felt my feet jerking behind me as I fell forward. I have never been a clumsy person, and I knew for a fact I fell from what felt like something literally grabbing me by the ankles. My mouth landed on the corner of a book, and I felt one of my front teeth snapping in half in the process. I looked down to see a corner of a diary. 

On the cover of the diary was the name of my first best friend. The name Mike Stallworth was written on the cover, but when I looked on the first page I found myself staring at a blank page. I kept flipping until I got to the middle where a single sentence was written. You have forgotten about me. I grabbed the diary and tossed it to the other side of the gym and ran out. When I got to the room I entered through I realized the window was now shut. I tried opening every single window in the room but none of them would budge. 

I ran to the next room and tried the windows only to get the same exact result. For the next 30 minutes I ran around the school like a madman trying every single window and every single door, but did not find a single way out. I tried calling out from my phone, but every single call I tried to make failed to connect. 

So I ran into the restroom I used to go to every morning to meet with my best friend and trade our snacks we got for lunch. He always got a Snak Pak and I always got a Fruit Roll Up. Right when I ran in I felt the temperature around me start to feel like a mixture of hot and cold. I started to feel like I was suffocating, but I never truly ran out of breath. I ran into the second stall and sat on the toilet. 

I sat on the toilet for around 30 minutes, and I felt a sudden sense of calm so I walked out of the stall. I looked in the mirror and stopped dead in my tracks. I saw the face of Mike with his tongue hanging to the middle of his neck. His face was deathly pale and his shoulders were rising up and falling back down as he took every single breath. 

I turned around to avoid looking at his face, but I started to feel warm air brush across my neck. I turned to my right, but I saw there was nothing there. Then I decided to once again look in the mirror. It was Mike waving goodbye at me as he clutched the fruit roll up in his right hand. He was still smiling five minutes later when I entered into the restroom with three other boys. 

He stopped smiling when one of the boys grabbed him by the neck and slammed his face into the mirror or when he was punched in the face repeatedly while all five of us laughed. Yes, even I laughed so I could start to fit in with the others. At that time I thought Mike was holding me back, but he was the one that made me into the man that I am. 

After we left him lying on the ground I saw him pulling out his blood pressure pills. I saw him fill up the sink to the brim. I saw him put all of the pills in his mouth and dunk his head into the waters.

I saw him die. 

When his body stopped moving I heard a creak coming from the distance.

I looked back in the mirror and was met with the reflection of a heartless bitch that let his 18 year old best friend get to the point to where he just wanted to end his life. 

I opened the restroom door and went to the room with my Spanish teacher. I found that the window was now opened. 

I slid through the window and went to my car. When I looked back at the school I saw that it was gone. 

It was just an open plot of land, but I know why I had to go.

Mike needed to let me know that he never forgot, and I can never [forget] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/). 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch what you smoke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 11:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently, I am holding 5 pounds of maybe the most potent weed I have ever encountered. What am I doing with it? Im throwing that shit in to the bonfire I just made. A bonfire that consists of 4 pallets and 28 pieces of logs and a gallon of gasoline; you may be wondering why I am getting rid of $8500 dollars of product and I will tell you why. I just want to give you the background of what I do first.


I am a college dropout. I did really well my freshmen year, but decided halfway through my second year that college wasnt right for me. I got into the world of car sales, and I did really well the two years I worked there. I have smoked since high school and I never plan on quitting, and I have always bought it from my best friend since High School. One day I went over to my buddys house (Jay) and I bought an eighth off of him. When he was handing me the baggie he asked me So how much do you make a month man? I told him I made around $2900 a month. He scoffed and put his arm around me and told me to quit my job. 


Of course, I didnt quit my job right at that moment, but that same week our old manager quit and a new asshole manager took his place. Four days into the week he yelled at me for selling an old lady a used car instead of a brand new car so I just walked out and drove straight to Jays house. He invited me in with a knowing smile and from then on we became official business partners. I had 15k saved up and he had all of the connections. 


Within 6 months made 15k turn into 75k. Even though we have made a significant profit from my money we both felt like we should be making more at a faster rate so we started to branch out to other dealers with bigger quantities. We stopped selling anything smaller than half an ounce and with that strategy we started to make a lot more money. 


Four days ago Jay called me at 3 am and I groggily answered the phone. He told me that someone just gave him word that they just received in the best shit they have ever smoked, and that they would sell it to us at 1700 a pound. As soon as I heard the price I jumped out of bed and got dressed.  I picked Jay up from his house and he handed me a piece of paper with an address scribbled on it. 


I drove 35 minutes and when we arrived I had to double check to make sure we had the right address. For the past 9 months I was accustomed to going into rundown houses with a door always semi opened, but the house that we drove up to was a 3 story mansion with a gate in the front. We pulled up to the gate and Jay told me to press the Call button. As soon as I pressed it a voice asked who we were. Jay cleared his throat and said Jay, Im here for pickup. 


Before he could say anything else the gate opened up and I drove through the gates.


I pulled in about halfway past the gates so we wouldnt somehow get trapped and walked up to the front door. Jay held up a hand to knock, but before he could a man opened the door. He was in a simple t-shirt and shorts and looked to be about 24. 


He didnt say a single word. He just held out his hand. Jay took out 17k from his backpack and placed it on his hands. The man closed the door and came back out less than 10 seconds later holding 10 sacks of weed. As soon as he opened the door I felt the smell of absolute skunk hit me in the face. It literally brought tears to my eyes. We grabbed 5 bags each and threw it in my trunk. 


When we got home we were the most excited we had been in a long time. We didnt smoke any because we always had one single rule. We would not smoke any of our weed until we got near the end so that we can take in all of the profit before enjoying the product. So basically, whenever we start running out of one batch we can just smoke the remaining 2 ounces we have left over. It usually took us around 10 days to sell 5 pounds so the 10 pounds we bought would take around 20 days.


For the next three days we were selling the new batch faster than we have ever sold before. Within the 3 days we had sold 4 pounds and people kept coming back for more. The name Dizzy Melon caught on rather quickly so we started calling it Dizzy Melon too. 


The problem actually started this morning. We thought it was strange when we didnt have a single person come in even though it was already 1 pm. Jay already made a blunt with the Dizzy Melon and said we might as well try it, but I declined. I respect our rule, but I dont blame Jay for being curious about it. After he smoked the blunt we walked down the street where a guy that came by for a pick-up almost every day lived. When we got there he was being carted by paramedics. I fell to the ground when I saw the condition he was in. Half of his fingers looked to be completely chewed off while the other half were a mixture of mashed up meat and crushed up bones. They were hanging off his hands like defeated worms. His midsection has been torn into and some of his intestines were hanging out of his body and onto the gurney. 


We started running back to our house, but just before we got out of earshot the guy yelled out It lives inside of you. Once you smoke it. It wont fucking leave! We could hear his laughter even when we went inside Jays house. 


I turned on Jays tv as soon as we got in and put the news on. There have been 38 cases of self mutilation throughout our city, and I could recognize every single one of their faces from the last couple of days. 


I told Jay I was going to go home and think about what we should do about the weed, and he just grunted in response. 


I took the weed and went home. 


Three hours ago Jay was taken to the hospital. He damaged his midsection far too much to survive. My best friend since high school is dead all because of Dizzy Melon. 


So now I am standing in front of the glorious bonfire I made in my backyard. I plan to throw it in the fire and run right back into my house. I have a facemask on and I will hold my breath.


Im just here to warn everyone.


If you hear about a new strain of weed that smells far better than any weed you have ever smoked, and if that weed is far cheaper than the prices you are used to paying.


Dont fucking smoke [it] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Man Has Been Standing In Front Of The Same Urinal For Over 4 Hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to start off by saying that I have worked at the same job for 14 years. It is a great job where I just sit at the desk and make sure the e-mails that are sent out by us are readable and professional sounding. I kind of fell on to the job since my mother knew the CEO of the company, and since then I have moved up to a manager position with extremely good pay and great benefits. Alright, since you asked I make a little over 120k a year and my benefits include, all health, 30 vacation days (paid), and an apartment that the company pays monthly for. 

All in all, I simply couldnt be more content with where I am at in life. Ive never been married, but Im only 33 and it is the last thing that concerns me. I have had a couple of relationships here and there, but after a couple of months the love goes sour, and I begin to lose interest. Anyways, out of that semi-depressing topic and onto the more fun part. I live in one of the Eastern States, but I really dont want to tell you exactly which one. My apartment has a beautiful ocean side view, and I love drinking my coffee while I watch the waves go back and forth. I remember just 14 years ago when I was just a college drop-out and walking along side this very beach. Trying to find the nearest cheap food vendor so I could spend the last 5 dollars on something to fill my starving stomach.

Now I am staring down at that very spot I walked on and smiling to myself thinking of how lucky I am to have such a great mother. I give my mother a call every morning to tell her that I love her, and make sure she is doing fine. When she was 62 she decided to go live in a retirement village so that she could be with people around her age. I miss having her around, but when I visited her last year she seemed like she was truly having the time of her life. 

After my daily phone call to my mother I drive to work. Today was just like every other day but I had the intense urge to use the restroom. Waddling to the restroom with my bladder nearing its max capacity I burst through the doors only to find a man already using the urinal. So I walked into the stall and did my business. I started browsing on my phone and got distracted for about 15 minutes. Having only 5 minutes to get to my desk and clock in I quickly zipped up my pants and exited the stall. 

When I looked to my left I noticed that the same man was still standing in front of the urinal. Not really having any time to think about how weird that was I ran out the door and ran to my desk. After I was clocked in I started on my work. For a brief moment I thought about the man, but I quickly dismissed it to just a man having difficulty peeing. 

After I finished looking over 85 e-mails and sending them out I decided it was about time for my lunch. I went to the nearby sandwich shop and ate a roast beef sandwich with salt and vinegar chips. After I ate all that I could I folded the paper over the rest of the sandwich and carried it back with me.

When I got to my desk I placed the sandwich on my desk and took my daily after lunch restroom break. Basically just me sitting on the toilet and vaping for about 15 minutes since it is far too cold to stay outside and smoke. When I walked into the restroom I noticed the man was still standing in front of the urinal. Feeling a little uneasy I lightly tapped on his shoulder. He turned around to face me and gave me a smile that made me uneasy. His lips formed into a smile, but his eyes were bouncing all over the place in panic. His throat was making a strained noise, but his mouth just stayed in a closed lip smile. 

I asked him if he needed me to give him any help, but he shook his head no. Shrugging I just walked into the stall and played on my phone while I took a couple of hits from my vape. About ten minutes into my vape break I heard scratching coming from the direction of the man so I got up and opened the stall and peeked out. 

What the fuck.

Blood is now covering his hands as he has started to write out something on the wall in front of him. I shut the stall door and resist the urge to throw up. 

When I finally managed to calm myself down I walked out of the stall and stood behind the man to read what he wrote. It was just a single sentence. Can You Really See Me?

The man turned around with the same smile on his face as he stared me down with pleading eyes. I nodded my head yes at him and ran out the door and ran into the man that worked on the desk next to me. I told him there was a man that has been in front of the urinal for the past 5 hours and now he was writing on the wall with the blood from his fingers. He stared at me with a look of shock and pushed the door open. 

He took a quick look inside and called me an asshole while he walked away. 

I looked in there with him and saw that there was nothing but an empty room and clean blue walls. 

Knowing for a fact that I am going crazy now I open the doors again just to reassure myself, and I see that the man has turned his head completely around as he watches me read his new message. 

Dont Trust Anyone [Here] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).
 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend's ringtone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in an office with three other people in my section. We have all grown close through the past five years we have worked together. My name is Brad and we just call my three coworkers Jay, Kay, and El. We always hung out at my place and relaxed together every day after work. When Jay got married the three of us went to his wedding as his bachelors and I was the best man. When Kay proposed to his husband after the new law passed last year we helped him out by singing "Lean on Me in the background. When El was found murdered in the parking lot of an Olive Garden we all went to the funeral with grief taking over our hearts. This hit me the hardest as he was my closest friend out of all of them. We had been through so much, and I truly loved him like my brother and best friend. 


El was always the one that made us laugh when things got tense at work. He was the one that made sure we ate enough food throughout the day. The day he died was the day our office felt different. We had to bring in someone new into our section, and we immediately disliked him as he was rude and self entitled. Whenever I would try to tell him to make a correction he would just ignore me and continue working on his next project. We can call him Esohbee. 


We even tried to be nice by letting him come over to my house with Kay and Jay but all he did when he got there was insult everything about my apartment and drank almost all of my beer. When I asked him if he smoked weed he acted insulted and threatened to get us all fired. 


Fucking dumbass. 


We live in Colorado and as long as we dont smoke at work it is completely fine. So I just lit it and we all smoked it while skipping him out of rotation. When we got to around halfway through Esohbee snatched the blunt out of Jays hands and took about four deep and long hits. He let out a thick cloud of smoke with a satisfied smile on his face. He then told us that he just said he didnt to make sure we wouldnt rat him out for smoking. When Jay tried to take it back Esohbee jumped out of the circle and sat on the couch while smoking the rest of it. 


So after that night we have never invited him back to my house. 


Since then we havent had a problem with him as long as we just ignored anything he did and just handed him the work he was supposed to do. Once he finishes his work I would read it and make sure there arent any errors and then submit it in. If there are any errors I will just correct it and then proceed with my own work. 


So everything was fine until we started hearing Lean on Me playing from around Esohbees desk. That made me a little mad because it was the same ringtone that El used to have. So I turned around and asked Esohbee to put his phone on silent mode, but he looked at me with a confused look. I asked Jay and Kay if it was there phone, but both of them told me that they just had generic ringtones for their phone. 


I know it isnt mine because I always place my phone on silent. So I decided to make sure it isnt Esohbees by dialing his number and tapping call. Immediately the sound of some Electronic Dance song blared in the room and I quickly hung up the phone. Feeling a bit uneasy I walked up to his desk and started to find the source of the music. Jay and Kay started helping me while Esohbee sat at his chair staring at us. We searched for Els phone for the next 10 minutes, but we could not find it and the ringtone stopped going off. 


Over the next five days we kept hearing the ringtone going off between 4pm to 5pm for 15 minutes at a time. Every day it seemed like the ringtone was getting louder and louder. We were getting more and more frightened as each day the words would somehow change in the song. The third day of the ringtone playing it made the lyrics Lean on me when you're not strong to Fuck off me you piece of shit Then on the fourth day it made the lyrics I'll be your friend, I'll help you carry on to Mess with me fool, Ill end your sad life. Then yesterday it changed For it won't be long, 'Til I'm gonna need somebody to lean on to For it wont be long, till you take your last breath and find some inner peace. 



This morning when I woke up I realized that it has been 2 weeks since the death of El. I think of all of the little jokes he would make, and how he liked to just eat the frosting off of cupcakes and throwing the rest away. How he would always put his arm around my shoulder when I felt sad or stressed, and how he would always make a snarky remark about the people we all secretly hated. 


Then I remembered something and with that realization I got in my car and sped to the office. When I got there I saw Esohbee being carted out of the doors by two paramedics. He had a heart attack. 


I walked into the office and up to Els old desk. I bent down and looked behind the desk and saw the letter I gave El 3 years ago. I gave the letter to him because he seemed very depressed so I wrote all of the things that I could think of that were truly remarkable about him. It was really easy as he is easily the most amazing person I have ever had the pleasure of knowing. The night I gave him the letter he had a rope in his hand as he was mentally preparing to kill himself. Thank God he read the letter. I got a phone call that night from my sobbing best friend telling me that I had saved his life. 


Wiping a tear from my eyes I dig my hand deeper behind his desk and pull out a note that simply said To Brad on the front of the letter. This is what it said.


Hey Brad,


First off I want to say that I really love you man.


I not only owe you my life, but I owe you so much more as you have always been there for me.
You are my best friend and I will never forget you even after death. Two days ago I went to the doctor and he told me that I have a Glioblastoma tumor. I was too late going to the doctor and he told me that I basically only have 3 months to live. So for the next month I acted like nothing was happening and I kept making the jokes that I knew everyone loved. I wanted to be there with you guys till the last day.


About five days into the second month I started seeing a shadow in my room that was not mine. I ignored it for 3 days until curiosity got the better of me. So I asked him why he was there. He glided over to my bed and struck a deal with me. If I choose to accept death tomorrow I will have the opportunity to stay in one single location for the next 30 years. I took the deal and told him I would like to be by my desk so that I can make sure you guys are all taken care of. I can influence what happens around, but I will not be able to touch anyone. 


Today has been amazing. We all laughed at old memories as we made new memories. You seemed especially happy about your new promotion. Congrats by the way. I got to do what I always wanted to do. I got to spend the last day I have alive with all of you, and for that I will always be happy. 


I just want you to know that I will be there and make sure you guys will always be happy no matter what I have to do. Im going to go now. Today for my last meal I am going to eat my absolute favorite. A lasagna from Olive Garden. 


See you for the next 30 years bud.


p.s. remember that you can always Lean on Me Im just one call away. 


Love,


[El] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm 45 But I Have Only Lived Through 19 Years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 11:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As of right now I am 45 years old, but I have only really lived 19 years. Since I was young my life would jump forward every time something terrible would happen to me. The first time it happened was when I was 6 years old. That is the year that my father was involved in a hit and run. I remember wanting to cry, but before I knew it I felt like all of my grief was gone. I felt at piece, but I felt extremely different. My mother came in my room and told me to get ready for school. 

Somehow I knew where all of my clothes were, but they felt like they were much too big to fit me. When I put my shirt and pants on I realized they fit me perfectly. I went into the bathroom to wash my face and brush my teeth, but when I walked in I saw my own reflection. I was a lot taller than before, and my face looked a lot more different. When I ate my breakfast my mother dropped me off at a middle school. 

After 30 seconds of confusion I suddenly knew which class to go to, and who my friends were. I knew that I was in 7th grade since I was now 12. I knew that I had a bully, but he was never really that bad. His name was James, and he was always yelled at by his mother when she picked him up from school. My friends name was Brian and he was obsessed with his music. Everything was okay with my life for the next two years. I met my first crush, but she never liked me back. Brian and I grew closer every day since we had the same classes, and James ended up moving away. 

Everything was fine until my 14th birthday when my grandfather had a heart attack in our living room while I was blowing out my candles. After my mother received a call telling her that my grandfather didnt make it I started to cry. Just moments later I open my eyes to find myself sitting at a red light. I looked to my left expecting to see my mother driving, but found a steering wheel in front of me instead. 

That is when I had my first meltdown. I screamed at the mirrors that showed a face of a grown man, and I punched the steering wheel until my hands filled with pain. I looked outside the car window when I managed to calm down and realized that everything was different. I knew I was in the same city I always lived in, but there were stores I never even heard of. The park I used to go to all of the time was torn down and replaced with a mattress store. When I heard the car behind me honking I started to drive to my house. I dont know how I knew how to drive, but somehow I knew what to do and it felt completely natural.  I got to my house to see an old lady sitting outside of the house. When I approached her to ask her if she were lost I was struck with the realization that it was my mother. Fragile and old, but still sitting there with the smile she always had for me. She asked me how I did on the first year of college and I numbly told her that I received all As and made it to the Deans list. I told her I was feeling sick and she told me to go to my room with a worried look on her face.

When I got to my room I sat on my bed and began to remember everything that happened the last 7 years. Brian moved away when I was 13, and my favorite math teacher was found dead and lying on his desk completely still. He was dead for 8 hours before they found him. Not much happened afterwards. I graduated high school and went to my first year of college. The girl that I had a crush on is now my girlfriend. We havent had sex yet, but we both decided to wait until we were married. 

After four years I graduated college and immediately found a wonderful job as an editor. The day I graduated I got on one knee to propose to the love of my life and she said yes. We decided that the next September would be the best time for us to get married to get ourselves financially and emotionally prepared. Three months before our wedding my fianc passed away in a hospital. Knowing what would happen and the depression of her dying hit me at once and I unwillingly started to cry. 

I then found myself sitting in a coffee shop drinking a regular iced coffee. I look around to see where I am and found myself in the city I grew up in, but this time everything was different. People have started to look lifeless and uninterested with whatever they were doing. A baby was sitting at the table next to me just staring at me without any type of emotion. The mother took a look at me and said What the fuck are you looking at? I was blown away not by her statement but by how monotone she said it. 

I turned around and sat silently. I know that I am now 32 and I befriended James when he moved next door to me. The fact that he bullied me when we were so young did not affect how close we ended up getting. Two years after we became friends James was found in his living room with his intestines wrapped around his head and his organs spread around his body. 

Before I start remembering anything else I ran to my mothers house to make sure she was still alive. 

When I was 3 houses away I saw that my mother was rocking back and forth in her favorite chair outside. I go up to her and try to hug her, but she pushed me off and resumed rocking. I looked at her, but she refused to turn my way. When I turned her to face me I fell back onto the ground. Her face was the same but her lips were placed in a frown that immediately told me she hated everything about me. Her eyes were pure black as she said Dont fucking touch me again if you want to keep your hands. It was monotone, but it made me start to shake in fear. 

I went three streets over to my house and I laid in my bed for the next three days trying to figure out what the hell was happening. After three days I ran out of food so I went to the store. Again, everyone is expressionless and just going through the motions of shopping. One person was lying on the floor acting like he was walking. I stared at him for a couple of minutes thinking of a way to help him, but a lady hit him with the cart and started to drag him away. 

I decided right then and there to just live my life as if nothing was different. I got another job as a salesman and nothing happened for the next 5 years. 

After five years I decided to revisit my mother. I drove there and pulled into her driveway. She was still rocking on her chair and I walked up to her. I grabbed her shoulder and lifted her head thinking she just drifted off, but her head fell off her neck and into my hands. I screamed and dropped her head and it rolled to the side of my foot. I look down and see that her face is littered with holes all across her face. Maggots were going in and out of the holes and I turn around and go to my car. 

I start to cry and I know that I am about to lose even more of my life.

I woke up and found myself in a chair. The chair that is in front of the computer I am posting this on now. 

To tell you all that I remember everything now. 

About how I poisoned my math teachers apple I gave him at five pm after he tutored me. I dont know why I did it, but I was tired of seeing people I cared about dying all around me. I remember slicing Jamess stomach open and ripping out his intestines and wrapping them around his face. I took out his organs and spread them all around him. They never found his heart because I buried it beside the tree we would always sit at and drink beers together. I am just tired of seeing people dying all around me, and I dont know why people have stopped showing emotions. I dont know why my mother was dead for so long without anybody alerting the police or even an ambulance. 

All I know is that I am not going to lose any more of my life. 

Please dont get close to me, because I will try my very best to hold onto the last few years I [have] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Father Keeps Laughing At His Broken TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 07:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Around three years ago my father had to move in with me as he was unfit to live alone. Until the past week everything went perfectly. My wife and son adored my father as he is witty and easily likeable, and I have always loved my father with all of my heart. He was there for me whenever I needed someone to cry on, to talk to, and to get advice from. 

When he moved in with us our family wasnt doing too well financially. We barely made ends meet with the measly salary I received from my entry level office job, but when my wife and I heard about my father refusing to leave his bed after the death of my mother we decided to take him in. We had an extra room we used to store my sons toys so we moved all of his toys to his room and bought a cheap bed and mattress.

I found a tv at Goodwill for 20 dollars so I snatched it up before the lady beside me gave it a second thought. I lugged in the 80 pound monstrosity out of my car and into my fathers room. I stuck a paper clip into the coaxial port and managed to get around 12 local channels on his tv. After setting the tv up I went and drove the 45 miles to my fathers house.

When I got to his house I noticed everything about the house had started to fall apart. The front door was missing half its paint, the grass has grown about knee high, and the foundation of the house looked to be depressed. I knocked on the door and waited about 5 minutes before I saw the door opening and saw the face of a defeated man. His back was slightly hunched and his legs were shaking from the pressure of him standing up. The sight broke my heart; the once muscular and invincible father that would lift me up at the age of 13 and place me on his shoulder after I won the basketball game with a buzzer beater now looks like he wouldnt even be able to hold a spoon properly.

Once I got him into the car I grabbed the small bag of clothes he prepared for his stay and we headed back to my house. The whole car ride back we only spoke 7 words combined. Before it became too awkward we arrived back and I led him to his new room. 

He sat on the bed while I flipped through the channels till I reached the local news and left him to get acquainted to his new surroundings.

Things were quiet in the house until I heard the sound of my excited sons voice screaming Grandpa is here! I walked into the room to make sure my son wasnt disturbing him only to see my father smiling from ear to ear as he listened to my son talk about everything that happened at daycare. 

The first dinner was everything I could hope for. My father seemed to be going back to the man I once knew and my son and wife seemed to really enjoy all of the stories my father had to share. 

Over the course of the next three years our whole family has gotten much closer through the help of my father. 

We were all happy and nothing seemed to be off or wrong until my fathers tv went out. He called me to his room and told me that his tv wouldnt turn on. I came in and checked to see if it was still plugged into the outlet. Seeing that everything was plugged in I tried pressing in the power button. After three unsuccessful tries I unplugged the tv and told him I would get him a new one once I got my paycheck in two weeks. 

That night after I came back home from work I heard my father laughing in his room. Thinking it was just my son talking to him I sat in the living room and played around on the computer for an hour. After about an hour I went to my fathers room to get my son and take him to bed. I can still hear him laughing so I knock on the door. He said Come in! in the middle of his laughter and I walked in only to find my father staring at the blank tv screen laughing. 

I ask him what hes laughing about, but all he did was point at the tv while staring intently starting at the screen and laughing every 10 seconds or so.

I felt a little creeped out so I told my father to have a good rest of the night and check in my sons room. When I make sure he is already asleep I go into my room and laid next to my already asleep wife.

The whole night I woke up to the sound of my father laughing. I told myself that I will have to get rid of the tv first thing in the morning and finally managed to fall asleep for the rest of the night. 

When I woke up I went directly into my fathers room and started to lift it up when he started to scream at me. Leave the tv here I need it! I cant keep living without it! I tell him that I would get him a new tv that afternoon, but he kept begging me not to take it. 

The next five days was absolute hell. I barely got any sleep because of his laughter and because I was genuinely concerned my father was losing it. 

Last night I went into his room at 1 am to see what he was still doing up. I walked into his room without knocking and saw that he was an absolute wreck. His eyes have been sunken in and his skin appeared to be sickly gray. I stood next to him about to tell him that he will need to keep it down, but a shape on the screen caught my eye. I looked at the screen to see the reflection of my father, me, and my mother ticking his sides and kissing his cheeks. 

The blood drained from my face as I watched my mother walk up to my reflection and kissed me on the cheek which I know for a fact I felt. I rushed out of the room and ran back into my bed hoping it was all a dream. This morning when I woke up from a fitful sleep I walked into my fathers room only to see that he was absolutely still. I touched his forehead and only felt his cold skin. I put my fingers on his neck to check his pulse, but no matter how long I held down I couldnt feel one. 

With tears dripping from my cheek I looked at the tv screen. 

Only to see my mother lying next to my father and not making a single movement as [well] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Mother Wakes Up As A Different Person Every Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 07:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cautiously tiptoeing up to my mothers room I look into the crack of the door. I see her waking up and stretching with a smile and I know today is going to be a good day. 

I run into her room and give her a big hug telling her good morning. I know its weird that a person my size would run into his mothers room and throw a hug around her, but it is really rare for her to wake up as my actual mother. 

For longer than I could remember my mother has been waking up as a different person ever day. Some days she wakes up as the angry person who hates her son. On those days she will scream at me all day about how much of a waste I am. How I will never amount to anything. She never hit me, but the things she would say to me felt much worse than the pain I would feel from punches and kicks.

Some days she would wake up as a depressed person that didnt know why my father would ever leave my family. Why she was stuck taking care of me while my father is now always resting. This mother always made me feel depressed about my own life too.

Most of the days she would be a mellow person who would go about day to day things in a robot like way; she would make my breakfast and then clean up the kitchen and living room while I ate. After I was done eating she would go to her bedroom and lay down for her 4 hour nap. While she slept on those days I would just sit around and read a couple of books until she wakes up. Then we go to the living room and I practice my piano while she cooks dinner. We eat dinner together and then we both go to bed.

Then on very rare occasions the mother I once knew wakes up! This is the mother that would wake up every day until I was around 7 when my father left. On these days my mother will wake up with a smile and hug me right when she wakes up. She will call me her little piano master and ruffle my hair. Then she makes me the same delicious breakfast consisting of bacon, eggs, butter and toast, and sausages. After breakfast I will play the piano while my mother dances to the music and when we are both burnt our from dancing and playing I watch tv while my mother goes into her room to rest for an hour. 

Usually after her rest she comes down and we watch a couple of movies, but today she came down with a look of anger on her face. I ask her if she slept well, but she just told me to shut up and go into my room. Confused and sad I trudge up the stairs and hope that tomorrow I get lucky and my mother wakes up happy tomorrow.

I sit on my bed and read a couple of books until I start to drift off and wake up to the feeling of something on my stomach. I wake up to find the face of my mother right in front of me but her face has started to rot. Bits of her face fall on the bottom of my quivering lip and I try to flick them off of me, but every time I raise my hand my mother slaps my hand back and opens her mouth as wide as she can and acts like she is about to bite me. I notice that all of her teeth except for the two in the back are gone so I decide to raise up both of my arms and try to shove her down. 

Right when I push past her slaps I put a hand on each of her shoulders and push her off of me. Once I get her off I ran to her room and locked the door. 

I get on her bed and I try to calm myself down. When I finally managed to get myself to stop shivering I fell back asleep. 

I wake up to the sound of our next door neighbor cutting his grass. 

I prepare myself before I unlock and open the door to my mothers room and I exit glancing left and right. I notice that the door to my room is halfway opened and I see my mothers foot hanging off of the bed. 

I slowly walk into my room and approach my mother. She hasnt woken up yet so I lift her up and take her to her bed.  

I sit around in my room thinking about the night before. How her flesh was hanging off of her face and hitting my chin. 

It only takes me a few minutes to reason with myself that what happened is not possible. 

I go back into her room and flick off a piece of her cheek that was hanging down.

I loved my mother so much, but a year ago she told me that she wished she were dead instead of having to take care of her deadbeat 30 year old son. 

So I gave her what she wanted. 

I hope she can wake up happy [today] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Magpie That Saved My Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 05:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three years ago I woke up on a concrete floor next to my two best friends. We were sitting side to side handcuffed to the ground. 

I remember I panicked and tried jerking the handcuffs off of my hands by jerking it every which way until the skin started peeling away from my wrist.

Defeated, I sat on the ground and waited for the others to get up. 

I looked behind me and saw that there was a small opened window. Excitement is replaced with despair when I looked out to see only woods surrounding the building I was in.

I saw my friend next to me stirring so I grabbed his shoulder and whisper Brian get up, what the fuck happened last night? He looked at me with a dazed look and tried to fall back asleep. So I shook him even harder until he was completely awake. 

He looked like what me when I woke up; trying to rip the handcuffs off of him only to give up after a couple of seconds. Then he turned around to show a look of confusion as he glanced out the window wondering where we were. 

Brian grabbed Tim by the shirt and shook him for a couple of minutes until Tim opened his eyes. Before he started tugging on the handcuffs I told him that we were stuck in here and that there is an opened window. We just need to find a way to get rid of these handcuffs since tugging on them will not work. 

We quickly noticed that the room was almost empty except for a couple of boxes on the other side of the room. 

Collectively deciding that the best thing to do was to wait and try to recollect what happened the night before. 

We were out celebrating Brians new promotion so we went from bar to bar getting more drunk by the hour. All three of us could not remember what happened after we got to the fourth bar. 

Defeated and feeling completely lost I leaned on the wall and racked my brain for answers. 

That is when I felt a small peck on the back of my head.  I turned around to see a Magpie sitting on the window. The magpie stared at me for just a second before it shook its head as if to tell me the answer was no.

Then the Magpie flew away as I heard the sound of a door opening and closing. 

A regular looking woman with short red hair bounced down the stairs with a look of complete joy on her face. She had freckles all around her face and a chip on her right buck tooth. She was wearing a simple blue dress and purple shoes. 

She walked up to Tim and asked him Do you think Im pretty?

Tim spat on her shoes and told her Fuck No.

She walked past Brian and came to me with a smile on her face. Do you think Im pretty?

I remembered the magpie shaking its head no at me so I said No.

With a smirk she walked up to Brian last. 

She asked him the same question, and Brian without hesitation said Of course, youre absolutely beautiful. The girl shrieked with joy and gave Brian a deep kiss. When she pulled away Brian had the look of victory. She took out a key from her pocket and started to unlock Brians handcuffs. 

When she got them off she gave Brian a hug and when Brian hugged her back his whole body jerked forward dramatically. He started whimpering while she pet him on top of his head. When she turned him around he let out a groan of pain. 

I saw his exposed spine disconnecting with the flesh around it as she slowly cut up until she had a decent grip on his ribs and ripped the right ribs out and did the same to the left side of his back. She grabbed the ribs she tore out and happily bounced upstairs leaving Brain to die surrounded by his intestines and organs. 

Tim abandoned all reason and starting tugging on his handcuff with everything he had until I started to see the flesh ripping off the side of his right hand. When he started to grind the handcuff against his fragile bone he stopped while wincing in pain and started to sob. 

That was the first time the Magpie saved my life. 

For three days we waited around for her to come, but the only sign that she was still there was from the sound of happy humming from upstairs and the food that we woke up to every single morning. On the third day the Magpie came back and pecked on my head to alert me it was there. I handed it some bread as it nodded its head up and down. I tried petting it, but flew away before I got a finger on the bird. 

Tims right hand had started to become black with infection around his exposed bone. All he did when he woke up after seeing Brian die was repeatedly say What the fuck are we going to do? Then he would go back to sobbing for hours until he fell back asleep.

Around twenty minutes after the Magpie flew away the woman came downstairs and greeted us with a cheerful Hello! 

She walked up to me and gave me a peck on the cheek. While rubbing my forehead with her right palm she asked Would you reject me if I asked you to buy me a drink? Just as the Magpie showed me I looked at the woman and told her yes. 

After she gave me a light slap on my forehead she walked up to Tim. Asked him the same question, but she gave him a kiss on his chin instead. He told her that he would have definitely bought her a drink had she just asked him. 

She walked back to where I was sitting and gave me a kiss on my lips. 

That is when Tim started to laugh and kicked me on the side of my leg calling me a dumbass. 

As sweat started to cover my hands I started to beg her to let me answer differently. Feeling stupid for ever trusting a bird to make my decisions I went into a flurry of desperation; she ignored what I was saying and gave me another light peck on my lips. She then walked up to the boxes on the other side of the room and took out a small steak knife. 

I start to squirm away from her until I realize that she is standing over Tim. With a smile on her face she sat down on his ankles. With the steak knife she started to slowly cut right above his left knee. Tim was screaming at the top of his lungs while he tried to slap her hands away from his knee, but the cuffs made it to where he was only inches away. It took over 40 minutes for her to finish cutting both of his legs. It only took 16 minutes for Tim to stop screaming. 

That night I started to pray to anything out there. I just wanted to leave, and I felt like there was no way to escape. 

That is when the Magpie saved my life the third time. The feeling of something pecking my head woke me up in the middle of the night and I turned around quickly to see a key in the Magpies mouth. 

I grabbed the key out of the birds mouth and unlocked my cuffs. 

With each step I went up I could hear the creaking get louder and louder. I held my breath until I reached the top of the stairs and turned the knob on the door. 

It opened luckily so I turned to the left and walked towards the front door. Before I reached the door I saw a figure to my right and my body seized up in fear. I turned to my right and saw Tims lower legs and Brians ribs sewn onto other body parts. The only thing missing to make the body complete was the head. Above the body there was a piece of paper on the wall with just one sentence written down. From Liars I Will Make the Perfect Man.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Quit My Job To Participate In a Sleeping Experiment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three months ago I made the spontaneous decision to get myself involved in an experiment. I am required to lie on a bed for six straight months while sleeping at least twelve hours a day.

While I was walking down my street to catch a cab to work a man approached me with a big smile on his face. He told me if I wanted to make 150k in six months. Intrigued, I asked him what I had to do. With a smile he told me to go with him to his office about 3 minutes away walking distance.

I promise Im not one to just follow anyone to a location I know nothing about, but South Korea is equipped with cameras all over the streets and roads. Just to be safe I texted my buddy who worked right beside me to call the cops if I dont call him within the next 2 hours, and I texted him the address of the office once we got there.

Feeling assured that I had all of my bases covered I followed the man into the building. When we got inside I was amazed by how white everything was. The desks, floors, ceiling, wall, chairs, and even the outfits that the workers inside wore were all solid white. I couldnt help but stare at everything while we walked towards the back of the building. When we get to the back hallway of the building I notice everything is white here except for the doors.
There are 3 doors in the back and each door is a different color. 

The first door is blue, the second is yellow, and the last is red.

He stops in front of the blue door and opens it.

Holy shit, everything in the room is solid blue. I also notice that there is a huge bed with blankets, pillows, and frame which are all completely blue. It really looks like a normal bedroom with a tv in front of the bed and a laptop in the middle of the bed.

He pulled out two chairs and patted on one as he sat in the other. I sat down beside him and he pulled out a piece of paper.

Rules was written on the top with a list and a line for me to sign at the bottom.

The list stated the following:

1) You will not be able to leave your bed during the six months you are here.

2) You are to sleep for at least 12 hours a day.

3) You have access to the laptop and your phone, but you must never reveal what you are doing.

4) Every two months we will move your bed to another room. We will move you, but it is very important that you stay in the same position you were in while you were lying down.

5) When you receive your food you may put your head up to eat, but at least half of your back must be on the bed.

6) If you need to use the restroom press the button on the side of the bed. We have a way for you to use the restroom without you having to leave the bed.

7) If you feel sick press the button twice and we will send someone to assist you.

8) Once the six months is up you will be given the 150k on a card. If you lose the card we will not be able to replace it for you.

X________________________

I feel a little weird about having to stay in the bed for 6 months, 
but I do love to sleep and being paid to sleep for 12 hours seems like a complete luxury. Plus, I will still be able to use a laptop and my phone while Im lying down so I wont be bored at all. I can just log into my Netflix and watch every single show I have been meaning to watch.

I call up my buddy and tell him that I am quitting my job and that 

I found a better opportunity. He asked me what it was, but I had already hung up on him by then.

I let my manager know that I am quitting as well and hang up on him while he was cussing me out and screaming at me about how 

I completely screwed his team up.

I know I just ruined my chances of ever going back to my job and also getting another job in Korea, but once this 6 months is up Im going back to the states and finally starting my own restaurant.

Once I signed the contract the man handed me a pair of white pajamas. I changed into the pajamas and got on the bed.

The first 3 weeks go by and I start to run out of things to watch on the laptop. I dont have anyone I really talk to, and my buddy has stopped talking to me when I wouldnt tell him where I am working now. I have never been close to my family and whenever I try calling my mother and father they dont pick up the phone. The strange thing is; no matter how bored I am I still feel somewhat happy. I think about how much the money will change my life. I daydream about running a successful restaurant and making a successful chain after a couple of years.

I turn on the tv and start flipping through the channels. I get distracted watching this show about people flipping shit over having their cars towed for the next two hours and before I know it a person in white comes in and injects me with something that makes me fall asleep.

I havent dreamt in the past three weeks, but today I finally had a dream. I am standing next to my mother and father in a Flea Market. The same place I used to go with my parents once a week until I was thirteen. We are looking at a couple of turtles to get for my aquarium when the man behind the counter approaches us. He points at one particular turtle and tells me this is the turtle I should take home.

He turns it around to reveal the face of the turtle and I start to shake. It looks like a turtle everywhere else but the face; the face it had belonged to my old best friend who killed himself when he was 24. He overdosed on heroine in the dorm room we were staying at together the day before graduation. The turtle turned its face at me and slowly closed his eyes while his tongue slid out all the way to the middle of his shell.

I woke up in a cold sweat, but immediately felt a wave of peace as I knew it was all a dream.

For the rest of the first two months in the blue room I had the same exact dream, but for some reason as soon as I woke up I would automatically feel at peace.

When the timer went off signifying that it was the end of two months they took me to the Yellow Room. Two men came in and changed my diaper (embarrassing but true) and took me to the room while I stayed in the same position. The man that brought me here was sitting on the desk waiting for me. He smiles at me and tells me that I am doing perfectly. As long as I keep still on the bed it will all be over before I know it.

Everything was the same in this room as the previous room, but everything in here was solid yellow.

The first two weeks in the new room I did not have that horrible dream, but I felt a little sad that I had another 4 months to go. I just really wish I had followed what my father wanted me to do and go into law. He already had a firm set up, and he was willing to offer me a six figure salary on a silver platter. He offered to pay for my schooling, but my hard headed self decided to major in English.

I remember how betrayed I felt when my best friend died. He was my only friend and now hes gone. I have never found a woman that liked me making me still wait for my first date at the age of 24. I have successfully wasted the first third of my life on nonsense.

The night of the sixteenth day in this room I finally had a dream.
I am outside of my dorm room in college. I find the key to the room in my hand so I put it in the keyhole and open the door. My friend is sitting on the bed sobbing into his hands.

I walk up to him and start patting him on the shoulder and telling him everything will be okay.

He starts screaming No It Wont! Nothing Will Ever Get Better! Then he slowly lifts his face up at me, and I stand there in shock. His eyes are full of sadness, but he has an inhuman smile on his face. His lips are stretched out and ripped opened to reach the middle of his cheeks and the bottom of the lip is torn to his chin. He slowly licks the bottom of his teeth before he grabs me and screams at the top of his lungs at me as his blood hits me on the face.

This dream comes to me for the rest of the time I am in the yellow room, and each time I get more and more depressed about what he says. Nothing will ever get better, and I know thats the truth. I can make my own restaurant, but it will probably fail. I will be broke again, and now I wont have an opportunity to work in Korea now because I ruined the one reference I had.

After the two months is up the timer goes off once more and the same two workers lift me up and take me to the final room.
Once again I see the man sitting at the desk.

Last room my man, after this you are done. He says that and leaves the room.

I look around the room and see that it is identical to the other two rooms but red this time.

I did not dream for almost the whole two months I have been in here, but anger has completely taken over all of my emotions. Why the fuck would a father kick his son out of the house for not choosing the career he wanted? I was never a bad kid and I never got in trouble. Whenever I struggled in the past couple years and asked for some help all I got was the phone hung up on me.
Everyone that I have loved has left me or fucked me over. My first crush in high school laughed in my face when I asked her to prom.
I fucking hate everyone I know, and I just hope they can never feel happiness again.

Last night I had a dream. It was the last night I spend in here.

I am standing in front of my friend.

I know what just happened already by the smirk on his face. He has gone behind my back once again and has decided to go to law school and was just guaranteed the job my dad wanted to give me to him. He has just finished gloating in my face about how much more successful he would be than me, and how he just remained my friend through high school and college so that he could pursue his greatest passion. He told me how my father told him he was the son he wished he had.

I already knew about it all before I came into the room. My father called me while I was in the car driving to my dorm telling me how he has no more use for me, and for me to go ahead and get all of my stuff out of his house before the end of the week.

Once he is done bragging he lays on his bed and goes to sleep.
I creep to his bed with a needle completely filled with heroine and find a vein. I slide the needle in fast and inject all of the heroine in to the vein on his neck.

I woke back up with a smile on my face.

I think the red room was my favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Have Been Stuck In Our Office For 3 Days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 02:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After three days of being stuck in our office twenty-three of my coworkers and I are sitting quietly in our office chairs thinking of a plan to get out of this nightmare.

Let me give you some background information of our company since I have more than enough time to tell you everything that is going on. 


We are split into two businesses in our building. One side is a group of eighteen people that organizes conferences. We have four managers, three assistant managers, and eleven regular employees. The managers obtain the contracts for the conferences and lead a group of one assistant manager and four to five regular employees. Once we finish the conference we will go to the conference and make sure everything goes according to plan.

The other side is a group of sixteen people that develop chips and make the chips and distribute. Eight people develop the chips, five people will make the chips, and three people will contact companies looking for chips and create the order and send them out once the chips are made.

I know all of this may seem like useless information, and it really is useless information. I just really wanted to explain out everything before I tell you what happened three days ago. 

When the alarm went off signifying that it is 6 pm a manager and three regular employees from the conference organizing side packed their stuff up and headed downstairs. 

About ten seconds after they left we heard a low guttural sound proceeded by the sounds of screams from the four employees. Over the course of the next thirty seconds we heard the sound of bones crunching and flesh ripping until we heard four thuds on the second floor. 

Besides one person that was screaming from chip distribution all of us just stared at each other shaking with fear. I got out of my seat and walked to where I heard the four thuds right outside of our main office door. I looked to the left and then to the right and found the four heads of the four employees that went downstairs. The thing that scared me the most was the fact that the faces were ripped from each of their faces and put on the head of another employee.

After I got over the shock I closed the doors to the main office and locked the doors. 

I told everyone what I saw only to be met with a mixture of people screaming, people crying, and people just sitting in their chairs completely in shock. 

Someone called 911 and told them what was happening. The cops sent out three officers to our company. I know it was three because after twenty minutes we heard three wet thuds on the other side of our office door.

We called 911 again only to be hung up on this time. 

We just sat around the office and ate the little snacks we had stored in our desk until the next morning. One of the managers from the conference side decided to try his luck and he opened the door to our office. He stared at the heads of the officers in front of the door and the heads of the employees to the right of the door. With a shudder he walked to the stairs and headed down leaving the door opened. 

I walked up to the door and took a look down the stairs while the manager was slowly going down one step at a time. Right when he hit the second to the last step I saw his body jerk from side to side as his skin separated away from his body leaving him wailing in pain. He grabbed his skin and tried to put it back around his exposed flesh until each of his limbs were ripped from his body. His organs and intestines flung out of his body and literally disappeared along with his limbs. When his head was removed from the rest of his body everything except the skin of his face and the head disappeared. 

The skin slowly floated over his severed head and wrapped tightly around the skull before the head flew towards my head. Before it hit me I slammed the doors shut and locked the doors.

I told everyone that there was nothing we could do. I told them what is killing us is invisible and how it easily tore up the manager and made everything but his head disappear into thin air. 

For that day and the next day we drank water from the water fountain, ate the rest of the snacks that we had, and talked to each other about what we would do if we managed to get out of here. 

On the morning of the third day I woke up to see three of the chip developers and two of the chip makers getting ready to head out of the door. 

I jumped up and begged them not to leave. 

The guy who was leading the group, which was one of the developers, told me that they would all rather die than be stuck here for the rest of their lives.

Once they left I got on the computer on my desk and decided to send out a cry for help here. Please let me know if there is anything we can do to get out of this mess. Has anyone ever heard of something like this before?

The screaming of the five men have just stopped and I now hear the sound of heads hitting our office [doors] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Don't Care My Parents Never Really Cared About Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the second day of every month my friends and I go out to drink at the same bar at the same time. My group consists of 3 of my lifelong friends and myself. We have been friends since we were 8 years old and since we were 16 we have always made sure to gather together on the second of every month to share a 30 pack of beer. 

Whether the second day of the month be on a Tuesday or a Saturday we have always convinced our parents then and our wives or girlfriends now of how important this tradition was. Of course, when we were young we would just tell them that we were going to spend the night over at a friends house to enjoy a new game they just got. Parents were dumb that way; as long as they werent the parents to watch the group of hormone driven teens they were okay with wherever we were going as long as they knew where we were.

My first friends name was Evan. He was the type of person that felt he was right no matter what the topic was. Basically if he told us that the moon was made out of cocaine and litter we were forced to say he was right so that he would just stop fucking arguing with all of us. The next friend was Brian; who was the punching bag of the group. Let me tell you, Brian was not the smartest person in the world. He scored a 15 on his ACT and fucking celebrated because he felt like it wasnt a failing grade. Brian, however, did have a very big role with our group; no matter what kind of trouble we got into Brian would always say it was his fault. It didnt take long for all of our parents to stop trusting dumb ol Brian. Lastly, Jeremy, he was the person who never even took a second to think of the consequences of his or our actions. Thinking back, Jeremy should have been the one to take the blame for every single thing we got in trouble for. 

I was the last to fill the circle of friends. I provided almost nothing to the group, but my parents were the least caring by far. They just cared about how well their company was doing and how much money they were making that month. This was why my house became one of the hotspots for our group. We would drink a couple of beers in Brians house and then head over to my house after 10 pm. That was the time where my parents would fall asleep. They knew we were there, but they hardly cared about my well being so they never really said anything when they woke up to find empty cans of beer and empty bottles of liquor. 

They would just wake the lady that cleaned our house out of her slumber to take care of the mess. I guess that is why I never really learned to deal with any type of consequences. If I burned the food that I was preparing for my parents the cook of the house would whip up a delicious dish and tell my parents I cooked it on my own. When I made a mess the cleaner of the house would clean the mess up and tell my parents what a dependable and clean young man I was,

Okay, Im done talking about my childhood and the backgrounds of the friends that I have made a lifelong pact of friendship with. 

We were drinking together one day when I told my friends that we should go to my old house for old times sake. The house is now my own after both of my parents passed away, but I havent even set a foot in the house since I moved out of the house for college.

When we finished our beers and walked the half mile to my house. 

We find ourselves standing in front of maybe the shittiest looking half a million dollar house you have ever seen. The house has been vandalized with various words throughout the exterior of it. The front door looks like someone has chewed on the whole door with the teeth of a deranged meth addict. 
 
I dug into the ground of the third decoy rock in front of the door and pulled out the key. 

I opened the door and we went in.  

When we first went into the house we didnt see anything out of the ordinary so we sat on the floor of the living room and proceeded to drink the beer we bought on the way. After we drank 2 beers each we decided to reminisce about old times. We started off by talking about our old high school sweethearts and where they were. (We stalk our exes on social media) Then we talked about the group of kids that used to torment us throughout our middle school years, and how it was odd how every single one of the kids from the group of tormentors never showed up to our high school. Afterwards we talked about our parents. Every single one of my friends had something great and something bad about their parents. 

How they were there for them when they went through something rough, and how they revolved around their lives a little too much. I feel a tinge of sadness as I realize that I hardly knew my parents at all. They were there to talk to me for a couple of minutes, but once they got bored of me they would just walk away from me and act like I never existed.

I told my friends that I didnt really have any memories, but I would get back to it if I think of something.

After a couple more hours of drinking and talking about the goofy shit that happened to our lives we decided that this was the perfect time to end the night. With a hug farewell we went our separate ways. 

Evan went to the hotel he was staying at for the next three nights. Brian said he was going to meet up with a girl he met at a bar (He was too drunk to realize that she was a 55 year old prostitute), and Jeremy went to a nearby motel that had a couple of cop cars outside of and thought he would find some crazy shit before going to bed. 

I went down to the basement and walked past the familiar sight of 10 dolls of mine hanging by a noose from the ceiling. I walk past them and to the vent that was at the back of the basement. I open the vent to see the skeletons of my parents right where I left them. 

They were never there for me.

They never cared about what I did, and I never cared what happened to them.

I know my friends killed them so we could always have the ideal location to hang out.

I know this because I was there and because I helped [them] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> subject8631 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 06:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Have the Worst Hangover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 05:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waking up with a hangover is the worst possible thing. 

I found my wallet in my pocket, but my phone is still missing. I need my phone. For my job if you do not have a phone you might as well call it quits.

I think back to the various bars I went to the night before, but after the first bar my mind draws a blank.

Sighing, I decide to head out to the bar and see if I can retrace my steps. I go into the kitchen to grab my car keys, but quickly realize my car keys are nowhere to be found too. 

Hitting myself in the head for being such a drunk I run out my door and run the three miles to the bar. 

Despite my active drinking lifestyle I have managed to stay in shape by exercising 3 days a week. Plus, my job requires me to stay in shape as it requires a large amount of stamina at times. 

When I arrive at the bar I see 5 cop cars around the building. I see a body lying on the ground with the head smashed in. The bartender is still outside talking to the cops, and I approach him and ask him if he saw my phone in there. 

Met with weird and judgmental glances I realize I should have probably just waited before asking, but like I said, I really need my phone. 

Getting hit with the memory of going down about a quarter of a mile to the other bar I decide to head over there. 

When I got to the next bar I see 3 cop cars outside of that building. Curious I walk towards the voices and find 4 cops examining the body of a male that was stabbed in the chest and ditched on the side of the dumpster. The other 2 cops are talking to the owner of the bar. 

I know the last place I went to, but I had to mentally prepare myself before heading over there. It was an abandoned house that was in between the bar and my house. I went there with a good friend of mine to just drink as many beers as we can. We didnt want to go back to our house yet so our inebriated minds decided this was the best possible place to enjoy really cheap beer. 

When I got to the house I snuck my way in. I go to the bedroom to see the body of my buddy with his intestines exposed and spilling on the aged wooden floors. 

I find my phone lying next to his head and I pick it up and leave the house.

I need to stop working while Im drunk.

Im getting a little too messy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our New Parrot Is Teaching My Son Some Weird Phrases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 11:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When my son was 6 my wife and I decided to go the pet store to get him his favorite animal. After an hour and a half we left with some bird feed, a cage, and a bright yellow and green parrot. He was a year old and to our delight the workers there have already taught the parrot how to talk. 

Once we got home we were greeted by my son and brother. My brother looked a bit flustered from having to watch our very energetic son for the past 3 hours, but hes living with us while he finds a job so I dont feel bad whenever we make him watch our son from time to time.

My son screeches with joy whenever he sees his new friend, and immediately tries to talk with the parrot. I didnt think he would respond, but when my son said hi! he replied back with hi! Once I make sure my son isnt doing anything to get bitten by the parrot I decide to go to my room and do some work on my laptop.

While I am checking my work e-mails I hear my son laughing downstairs. After a couple of minutes my son runs upstairs and shouts Basement! and runs back downstairs laughing the whole way down. 

After around 30 more minutes my son runs into my room again and shouts Let me out! I tell my son to keep the parrot in his cage so he doesnt run away. He nods his head and runs back downstairs.

While I am shutting off my laptop 20 minutes later my son runs right back into my room. Go fuck yourself! surprised at what he said I hold him by his arms and tell him to never say that again. I explain to him that it is a very bad word, and with a sad look on his face he nods his head. 

I go downstairs with my son to look at the parrot and he is saying repeatedly Dont touch me." Not really knowing what else to do I place a sheet over the cage. I like how my son has taken such a liking to the parrot already, but I dont know if we can keep him around especially with my son copying whatever he says.  

I go to my wifes office and tell her what the parrot has been teaching him, and with a concerned look on her face tells me that she would go take the parrot back to the pet shop and get another one that looked similar. 

The next morning I tell my son that his parrot is sick and that mommy would take him to the doctor while he took a nap. After being reassured that the parrot wont die he happily finishes his breakfast and plays with the parrot. 

I go into the bedroom to wake my wife up, but she is fast asleep and would not wake up no matter how much I shook her. Leaving my snoring wife in bed I walk back into the living room where my brother is asleep on the couch. I ask him to watch my kid while I go to the pet shop, but he insisted on taking the parrot and letting me stay home. 

At 12 pm I put my son down for his nap and my brother gets ready to head out. Once he is done getting ready I hand him my car keys. My brother looks at me for a second and said Man, I never told you how much I appreciate you letting me stay here. I love you man. I really hope I can repay you back somehow. I give him a hug and he heads out. 

After waiting for a little over 3 hours and having to explain to my concerned son that his uncle and parrot would be back soon I decide to give him a call. When he doesnt pick up after the 5th call I take my son into my wifes office and tell her Im taking her car to the pet store to see if hes there.

I go to the pet store and notice my car is not there. I go into the store and show the worker a photo of my brother and ask them if he came in. She tells me that Im the first one to come into the store today, and she would let me know if he comes in. I thank her and hand her my business card. 

I go back to the house and tell my son everything is fine and they will be back soon. 

I go into my wifes office and tell her that my brother is nowhere to be found. We decide to call the cops and tell them about the whole situation. They told me they would look into it, but chances are unlikely to find him as he could have just decided to leave on his own. I give them my license plate number and tell them I have a bright red Chevrolet Malibu. 

Five days later I open the door to be greeted by two cops and my sons parrot. 

According to a witness that lived across the street from the incident, he saw a woman flagging down a red Malibu. My brother rolled down his window and talked to her for a second and pulled into her driveway. He got out of the car with the parrot and went into her house. He noticed the car never left the driveway after a couple of days and saw on the news about someone going missing in a red Malibu. After he made the connection he contacted the police department, and shortly after the cops arrived at the house where my car was.

They found 9 mutilated bodies in the basement of the house. The parrot was right next to the bed where my brothers mutilated body was placed. 

The house was owned by the woman who owned the pet store. All of the employees when later questioned by the cops said they found it odd that the same parrot was returned to the store 9 times, but they never really questioned it. 

After I am done talking to the cops I take the parrot from them and I place him in the living room. 

The parrot looks up at me and tells me love you man.

I wish I could go back in time to tell him I loved him [too] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I Will Never Trust A Tickle Me Elmo Again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 02:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the small town I live in we have around 4,000 people. Our town being so small and containing so little people our options for stores are very limited. If we want to go to a major store we would have to drive 30 minutes out to the closest mall or 45 minutes out for the closest Wal-Mart. When it came time to buy gifts whether it be for Christmas or a birthday most of our residents would go to the local small market which sold a couple of electronics and a small selection of jewelry. 

Gifts for children were an easy fix as we had a decent toy store owned by one of our older residents. He was an 86 year old man and we all called him Papa Bear. He was loved by all of the children and he always made sure he stocked the newest and best toys in his store. Another thing, he always made sure to keep prices lower than all of the major toy stores and even Wal-Mart. Our town was very lucky to have Papa Bear and even at the age of 17 I visited him at least once a week.

On the day of my 18th birthday I received my first laptop from my mother. My father gave me the keys to his old Chevrolet Camaro. My aunt and uncle gave me a check for $300 (which when I tried to cash was declined by my bank), and my poor old grandmother bought me a Tickle Me Elmo from Papa Bears Toy Shop. I did not have the heart to return the gift or to tell my grandmother I was far too old to play with the toy she got me so with a grin I hugged my grandmother and thanked her. 

I placed the Elmo on my side table beside my bed and got comfortable on my bed to watch some dumb videos online after my birthday celebrations. After around 2 hours of watching videos I dozed off. 

I was brought out of my slumber to the sound of Elmo giggling. After giggling it said Hug me and dont let go! Thinking what the hell I grab the Elmo and give it a hug. When I stopped hugging it; the doll said Now hug me tighter till your arms get tired! Getting a little annoyed as it was the middle of the night I turned the doll off and placed it on the side of my bed once again. 

I quickly forgot about the toy for the next couple of days as I was busy packing all of my stuff to get ready for college. 

Around 4 days later I was having trouble falling asleep. My mind was racing from the anticipation of moving to one state over to attend college. This is the first time I am ever leaving the town I live in, and I am filled with both fear and excitement. 

After about 30 minutes of lying down I hear the Elmo doll talking to me again. I bring him to the bed where I hear him telling me Hug me, Hug me, I love being hugged! Getting a little annoyed that he is turned on I decide to take the batteries out. 

When I open the back flap I notice that there is a small vial placed underneath the battery pack. I carefully take it out and place it in the drawer in my side table. 

The next morning at 6 am I head over to the police station with the Elmo and the vial. When I go inside I show them the vial and the doll. They take the vial from me and tell me they would look into what it was.

Eighteen hours later Im unpacking all of my stuff in my dorm room. 

I get a phone call and I answer it. 

My mother and father are in custody for the attempted murder of me. 

The vial contained Ricin, and my parents confessed to placing the vial in the doll and telling my grandmother to gift the doll to me. 

They did not want me to leave their side, and they felt the only way to stop me from going was to kill me and have me by their side permanently.

To this day I will never trust my parents again, and I will never buy a Tickle Me Elmo no matter how much my son wants [one] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks). 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Son Has Been Talking To The Walls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 11:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My father went missing when I was 19 years old. It was after a week-long argument with my mother resulting in my father being there the night before and gone by the morning. I was home during the summer break of my freshman year when it happened, and I have never felt so betrayed my whole life. He was supposed to be there to see me graduate college, to be there when I was feeling down and I needed to talk to someone, but all of those hopes were sliced away when I found out he took the easy way out.

It really wasnt any different not having him around though; throughout my childhood he would go back and forth from Korea to America. He would be with us for a couple of months before finding another great opportunity and having to fly back to Korea. So when he decided to run away from our home I decided the best thing to do is to forget about that man in general. 

When I went back to college I focused on my studies, and after three years I graduated with a degree in Criminal Justice. I met a lovely lady my sophomore year and once we both graduated we decided to get married. After we got married we settled into a cozy 2 bedroom apartment and lived our lives happily for the next 2 years. 

I worked at a retail job because the job market was shit at the time so I had to take whatever was available, but come to find out I had  a real gift in sales. After a year I reached management, and after another 6 months of bringing my store numbers up by 30% each month they decided that I deserved to be promoted to regional manager. When I got home and told my wife the wonderful news she was very excited to tell me her wonderful news. We are having a baby!

Filled with excitement we started to get everything ready in the 2nd bedroom during the next 40 weeks. On the day that she was supposed to have the baby I took a month off and waited patiently by her side. 3 days later I was being shaken by my wife and I knew immediately what it meant. 11 hours later I was looking into the eyes of my beautiful son for the first time. We named him Gabriel and he was everything I ever hoped for.

He was certainly a smart child too! He stopped using pacifiers on his own at 3 months, and he started to walk by 10 months. At a year and a half he started to use words in the right context, and by 2 he was speaking to us in short sentences. He knew both Korean and English and was beginning to take a liking to singing.

When my son was three I heard the unfortunate news that my mother had passed away. I took my wife and child 3 miles down the road where the funeral was being held. As I gazed into the hole where they placed the body of my only parent I fell to ground and started to sob. My son stood by my side and rubbed my shoulder and told me Its okay daddy, you still have me and mommy. With that statement I regained my composure and looked at the family I had now. Feeling happy once again I stood there for the rest of the funeral with my child and my wife in my arms.

The next day I was told that my mothers house was fully paid for and I was the one to receive the house at the time of her death. Her life insurance also left us 100k and with that we paid for everything we needed to set up the house to our liking and put a sizable chunk into Gabriels college fund.

The first three nights in the house went by smoothly and I felt completely at home. My wife loves the size of the house and how it has 3 bedrooms with 2 full bathrooms. My son likes the fact that he now has a second room to place all of his toys in. 

The only strange thing about the whole house is that my son has now started talking to the wall that is by his bed. It started off by him just staring at the wall and giggling, and then he proceeded to start saying little things like how old are you? What is your favorite color? I like cupcakes what is yours? Thinking he just had an imaginary friend I let him talk to whatever he wanted to.

On the fifth day I was jolted awake at 5 a.m. to the sound of my son screaming. I run out of my room and into his when I see him pointing at the wall and saying Dont show me the bloody face show me the nice face. I dont like the bloody face.

Panicking I pick him up and put him in between me and my wife and he falls back asleep shortly after. The next morning while we are eating our breakfast I ask him who he has been talking to. He responds back with James I ask him if James is a friend of his and he tells me he is; then I ask him what he was talking about when he told James not to show his bloody face. His answer makes me gag on my piece of toast. James will sometimes come to the room with his face covered in blood, and he told me to tell you that he never left you.

I call a crew to come to my house to tear down the wall that my mother put up when I went back to college for my sophomore year. We used to have a 2 bedroom house, but my mother told me that she wanted to make a third bedroom in case I decide to move back in with my family. I normally wouldnt be so drastic and tear down a whole wall, but my fathers name was James.

When the wall came down I noticed a bag in the corner. I opened the bag to see a pile of bones and skull right on top.

My father never left me.

My mother was just tired of arguing every [day] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).

Edit: can't spell bag -.-
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I Will Never Quit My Job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 01:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seven years of working at the same department store and selling the same shoes year after year I have slumped in what you would call a salesman depression. Well, that is what my manager called it when he sent me to the back warehouse to give me a talk after he saw me cussing out a customer for asking if he could use other shoelaces instead of the original ones. I mean, who doesnt know that changing out the shoelaces is probably the easiest thing to change on shoes? 

So I am just walking around the dusty and overstocked warehouse waiting on my manager when I stumbled on a series of sentences written on the back side of the wall. The first sentence was Help me Im being chased. About twenty paces later I think theyre just toying with me was written, and on the corner Im sorry for making you mad, I promise I wont come back again was scribbled in an almost unreadable way. 

Thinking it was just a prank I continue to wait. 

Honestly, when I first started working here I was probably the best worker in the store. For five years, five fucking years I gave this store everything my body could handle to place value on myself. I was never late, I received the most positive reviews from customers, and I always came into work if they ever needed someone on my off day. Month after month, my portrait stood proud in the employee break room publicly stating that, once again, I was the employee of the month.

Its just after the five year mark; every question the customer asked me started to seem really dumb to me. I did not see a point in showing up to work every day on time when almost no one else did, and when they called me on my off day I would reject the call as soon as it came in. 

I honestly wanted to get fired so I could find something else, but I have never been one to quit so since they never fired me I tortured myself day after day helping these helpless customers. 

I got a little more reckless with my customers day after day. It all started off with very sly smart comments, to giving the customers the wrong product on purpose and seeing if they would just buy the product to avoid any awkward situation, to snapping back at the customers that were rude to me. Then finally today was the day I decided to start cussing out a customer for the stupid question. It wasnt a complete vulgar stream of words or anything. Just Why the fuck did you ask me that when youre standing right beside the replacement shoelaces dumbass? I mean a completely valid point, but of course since it was contaminated with forbidden words Im stuck in the warehouse waiting to get bitched at by my manager. 

After waiting around 30 minutes I finally see my manager walking through the doors, and what joy! The customer is walking right behind him with a smirk on his stupid ass face. 

The manager slows down for a second while the customer keeps walking past him and the manager proceeds to lock the door with his key.

Thats when I started to get worried. 

The customer was probably his brother or friend or some shit. Bracing myself to get beaten down by two fully grown men I watched them approach. 

The customer was the first one to speak. Do you even know who the fuck you just cussed out little bitch? Im the number one salesman at Electric Emporium. Im a fucking salesman too, and just because I asked you a question you decided to shame me in front of everyone else? Youre fucking worthless dude, and I cant wait to see you get fired for being a dumbass. I worked in sales for 4 and a half years dude. I know how to do sales. How long did you work in sales? Probably just a fucking seasonal worker or some shit. Have fun with unemployment.

For the first time ever, I saw my manager smiling behind the customer. 

Feeling humiliated I stare down at the ground and wait for my manager to fire me.

I keep staring at the ground until I hear the customer shouting and start running. When I look up I see the customer running towards the door with a bloody arm. My manager with a smile hands me a bloody knife and tells me that this will get me out of the funk I have been in. 

With rage pumping in my veins I run after the customer; hes a little faster than me as he runs past me and to the back of the warehouse. 

Oh well, I know Ill catch him sooner or later.

I just want to thank the store I work at and more than anything else my amazing manager.

I cant wait to continue working here now that my funk is [gone] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please Don't Eat At A Place Called Tenderized For You </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 09:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work at a semi-popular restaurant in the Midwest section of America. We serve probably the best tasting onion rings you will ever eat. I, personally, eat at least 2 orders worth of these onion rings a day. Believe it or not the ingredients are the same as any other onion rings, but we just add a little sprinkle of garlic powder.

I have worked here as the manager for around 2 years and as a cook for 8 years making it 10 years in total. So of course, if my store is doing good I feel like I am properly doing my job, and when the store is doing bad I feel like I should do anything possible to make more customers come in through the door. I am a fair manager, and I never ask my employees to do too much. Ive been in their shoes and the previous manager was a complete ass hole. It made me not want to keep working at times, and that is the reason why I have decided to be a lenient manager while still managing to get my employees to get all of the work done.

This being Christmas season we expect to receive in around a little over 120 thousand dollars of profit after the margins. If I hit the margin I feel good about the work Ive done; plus the extra bonus makes it even sweeter for me. 

The only thing is we have been completely dead. Around a week before Christmas we havent even broken the 50 thousand dollar mark. I knew it was the new restaurant that just opened up down the street from us around two months ago. Its called Tenderized For You and its been packed every single time I have even drove or walked past it. Over the two months they have been opened we have steadily lost business. Our once loyal customers have stopped showing up all of a sudden. 

So being the good manager I was I told my employees that they were all doing an amazing job despite the numbers, and I closed the restaurant down at 11 p.m. then walked to the other restaurant to see why they were so successful while we were completely failing. 


When I walked in I noticed the cheesy dcor of a stereotypical fast food restaurant. Red plushy chairs set in front of white thick plastic tables. The person behind the counter greets me with the generic Welcome to Tenderized For You would you care to try the Deluxe Patty Cheesy Melt? Astonished by how ridiculously the name of the sandwich sounds I ordered it with the combo. I asked for onion rings instead of the fries. 

Once they placed the tray of food on the counter I took a seat on the cheap red chair. I try an onion ring first to be immediately disappointed. Its somewhat soggy from the over use of oil and the onion is still somehow hard. Throwing the uneaten half onion ring back on my tray I took a bite of the burger. 

Holy. Fucking. Shit. 

It felt like I took a bite out of the meaning of life. The flavor of the burger immediately captured the attention of my taste buds, and before I knew it I have finished the whole burger in less than 5 minutes.

Completely bewildered by the taste of the burger I went back to the counter and ordered another one. After they placed my newly made burger on my tray I went back to my seat and scarfed it down before even giving it a second thought.

For the next five days I have ordered 2 of the Deluxe Patty Cheesy Melts after I got off of work. I have yet to figure out why the burger tastes so good, but like a traitor I have gone day after day without giving a second of regret. 

Today is the day that I know now why the burgers taste so good, but today is also the day that I will never eat a fucking burger from here again. 

When I went into the restaurant today I ordered the usual 2 burgers and decided to use the restroom before I start eating. As I am about to go through the bathroom door I notice the employee only door is open.

After debating with myself for 2 seconds I slowly open the door fully. There doesnt seem to be anyone there so I sneak past the grills in to the deep freezer in the back of the restaurant. 

When I peeked through the window on the freezer door I saw the guy that usually takes my order sitting in the middle of the floor cutting the fat off of a chunk of meat. When he turned it around I wasnt quite sure what kind of meat it was, but I kept watching. After he finished peeling all of the fat from the first hunk he brought out the next piece of meat. 

Vomit starts rushing through my throat as I notice that he has a human arm in his hands.

Running out of the restaurant I notice that the man is now in the front of the counter with a smile on his face waving at me. 

So here I am to warn everyone.

Dont every fucking eat at Tenderized For You.

They are using human fat to make their burgers taste so good.

I see the man standing outside of my window, and I know that a part of me will soon be in the mouths of their loyal customers.

Tenderized For You. Tenderized By Me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Am Struggling To Live For More Than A Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 06:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was nineteen and my brother was twenty-five when he disappeared out of thin air. There wasnt a trace of him until around two months after he disappeared. He was found in the backyard of a house around 300 feet from the hotel we lived in by four men. He was found with his legs and arms torn off and circled around his body to form a gory heart with his head stuck in the gaping hole of his stomach and a smile on his face. 

My brother and I have been always close, and I truly loved him more than the rest of my family. Our father ran away when I was just seven and was never heard from again, and due to the stress of having two kids to care for and working 2 jobs back to back my mother was always a little too hard on us. Which made my brother and I form a strong bond that lasted all of the way to his death.

He has always been there for me no matter what, and when I found out that I had a bad liver at the age of 14 my doctor told me they had one available but because we did not have any insurance we would have to pay out of pocket. I knew we had zero chance to come up with 577 thousand dollars so I started to give up hope. Little did I know that my brother worked his ass off to fundraise every single dollar and come into the hospital with the proud smile I loved and after 6 days I was out of the hospital supported by my loving brother. When my mother died my brother took on 3 part time jobs so we could live in a hotel and have food to eat.

That is why when I found out how my brother was killed I wanted to get my revenge on the ass holes that took the only family I had. The police did not want to press charges on anyone until they had solid proof, but I knew that the house he was found at was the house of 4 men that he always had problems with. Ever since we were in school they kept tormenting us and like 4 ass holes no one wants to live with they got a house together so they could live jerking each other off.

With the gun in our safe I went to the house. Knocked on the door and when the 16 year old brother of one of the men opened the door I knocked him out with the butt of the gun. Entered in to the living room and placed bullets in each of their pathetic heads. After I admired the sight of their blood and brain matter on the wall and back of the couch I took my cell phone out and called the cops and reported my murder. 

I was charged the death sentence in court, and after a two year wait I was put to death through lethal injection.

Of course, I was sent to hell, but after walking towards the screams and wails from the fiery pit I was stopped by an angel. He told me he had a deal for me. The deal is that I will be placed in a body to live out whatever amount of life they have left. If I die in one body I will be placed in another body. The people are chosen through how suicidal they are so whatever body I jump into I will live with all of their depression and guilt. I dont know what happens to their soul, but I figure it is better than having to live with wanting to end your life constantly.

The first body I go into is the body of a 36 year old business man. Immediately Im hit with the guilt of killing my wife. The way I folded my fingers over her throat and watched the life drain slowly from her eyes. This just happened a little over ten minutes ago, and I have a gun in my hand. With the guilt bearing down on me I placed the gun in my mouth and squeezed the trigger. 

Before I know it I am now in the body of a 27 year old woman. I see myself coming into my house to finding my best friend having sex with my father. I remember the way my mother was hanging from the ceiling fan after she heard from me how my dad cheated on her. I remember how my father killed my best friend and then himself 2 months after my mother killed herself. With a sigh I place the rope down and try to go about living. I go outside and enjoy a cup of caramel macchiato. I watch a movie and laugh at all of the funny parts, but when I get back home the depression hits full force once again and I swallow a bottle of pills I use for my blood pressure. 

I find myself dreaming and it is a most beautiful dream. I am in the body of a 19 year old man and he is running through the fields with the love of his life. We go to a beautiful field full of flowers and I pluck one out and place it behind her ear. We kiss and I tell her how much I truly love her. I wake up feeling refreshed and to my horror see my fianc with her neck sliced open. The memory hit me of slicing her neck over an argument and then not wanting to believe what I did I placed her on the bed and went to bed hoping it was all a dream. Now realizing what i did i get hit with the feeling of both depression and guilt so hard that before I know it I have sliced each wrist and placed them into the rushing faucet water.

With the next body I write to you all before I kill myself once again. Please dont ever think you can justify killing anyone. No matter how right you think you are please dont think you can ever pass judgment of this caliber.

I sit here typing to you in the body of an 18 year old male. I am the brother of one of the men I killed, and the first memory I received was cutting the arms and legs of my brother. I remember using a tiny pocket knife to slowly slice the neck of my brother until his screams cease when I get halfway. I remember once I finish decapitating his head I tore his stomach open and shoved his head in the hole I created. With my index and middle finger I pulled each side of his lips up to form a smile. With his arms and legs I form a heart around his body,

For the first time I will end the life of my new body for the guilt and depression of both of our actions.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Can Call It Vandalism, But I Love All Of My Writings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 03:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive always said that I wanted to be an author when I grew up, and with that in mind throughout almost my whole childhood I carried a pen and a notebook around wherever I went. My passion started to bring in attention when I was in college. It wasnt my papers that I turned into my English Professor, nor was it my submissions I made to the college newspaper. It was the stories I would leave in various hallways throughout campus for everyone to see, but I always kept my writings anonymous. 

In total I have created six writings all over campus, and with each story it definitely captures the attention of everyone.  I dont make a pattern of when I write, honestly, it is just when I am feeling inspired and when that feeling comes is when I know it is time to post another story. 

 I always have a helper, of course, to make sure there isnt anyone there when I post the stories, and to always make sure my writings have that extra kick by putting their input into it. I never use the same helper twice, never; I dont want them thinking they are a huge role in what I do. Thats how I stay anonymous and I still have yet to be caught. 

As you can see, no matter where I post the story it is still violating campus rules as they do not authorize my writings. They say what I write is far too gory, made from a disturbed individual, not suitable for the public, the list goes on, but so will my writings until I get caught. 

These past six months I was feeling extremely uninspired. So I decided to take a break, and I also need to find the perfect helper to help me post the story. Its almost impossible to find a helper that you know wont rat you out to the campus officials, and the helper must be very good at being quiet as we have to be as stealthy as humanly possible. 

Today my helper is Todd. He is in three of my classes this semester, and we have shared quite a bit of laughs and he has proven to be more than suitable for this job. As we walk together down the empty east side of campus I notice that there is just the most wonderful spot to place my new writing. 

We speed up towards the location and thats when Todd turns to me and finally says his first words to me tonight What the hell L, you scared the shit out of me dude! I thought I was being stalked by a lunatic! 

With a chuckle I tell him that I was just going to the hallway to grab the story I wrote this afternoon, and then ask him if he would like to proofread it for me really quickly. Like that nice guy Todd is he nods his head and once again we are walking together in to the hallway.

As he opens the door I use my knife to slowly penetrate the back of his head, and with my hand I cover his mouth to ensure he does not make too much noise. 

Now for my writing. 

With my knife that is my pen, and his face that is my blank piece of paper.

I write down.

Im Todd, and I have sex with helpless animals.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People are Getting Murdered Everyday, But I Just Want to Keep Singing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 06:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the most popular things you can do in Korea is called Noraebangs which just means Singing Room in English. You pay 20 dollars an hour in the more prestigious locations or just 50 cents a song if you go to one of the ones in an arcade. 

The reason why it is so popular is because no matter how shitty you sing you will not get judged by others. Dont get me wrong. Im sure they judge you, but not in a way where you will see. I like to go to these rooms myself to just release stress by drinking and singing. 

Well I used to until a week ago. Two weeks ago the police have started finding dead people in those rooms with a random body part missing. Not really thinking much of it I decided to still go. I mean Id much rather face a slight risk than be stressed out of my mind the next day. 

So the next day I still head to my favorite singing room. For only 5 dollars at this location I can sing for an hour and they provide free popcorn as well. Plus they have 3 dollar bottles of cheap Korean liquor called Soju. Tastes like ass but gets me drunk from just one bottle so why the hell not?

Once I hand the 8 dollars to the guy in the front I head to the room that they assigned me. After logging in 9 codes to my favorite songs I pick up the microphone and start the night off with singing Mr. Brightside. 

Right when I am about to get halfway through the song a confused looking woman is standing in my doorway. Not wanting to stop singing I just gesture towards the part of the door that has the room number written on it and the number of the key that she is given. Shes just the next door over so I just put it off to her being confused. With a nod of her head and an embarrassed smile she closes my door and heads to the next room.

Before the next song starts I crap open the bottle of Soju and take a big swig. I smile when I hear that she is singing All Star in the next room as I remember when I used to sing it when I was much younger. After I finish my drink and the remaining songs I slightly stumble out of the room, and I head towards the subway station. 

The next morning I wake up with a slight headache so I go into the kitchen looking for a Tylenol and some water. I realize I left the TV on for god knows for how long, but its on the news so I leave it on wanting to see if anything else developed from these killings. 

Not really much in terms of them finding anything out, but they have found another body in one of the arcade ones. A male college student who was about to graduate this year was found with a stab in between his eyes and the lips have been cut off of his face. 

As the segment ends and moves on to Korean Baseball I know its about time I head off to work. 

Just another stressful and boring day of sitting in front of a computer and typing out whatever everyone else wants me to type out in English. Getting bitched out for being a worthless piece of shit is also another great fucking benefit I have working here as well!

 Another day at work makes it another day for a trip to my favorite spot in Korea. Well the only fucking place in Korea that still manages to give me joy now. I go back to my spot and make the same 8 dollar transaction I do every day and head to my room.

While walking to my room I notice the girl is singing in the room beside me again so I pop my head in and give her a smile. With a slight giggle she waves to me and keeps singing. I dont want to look like a fucking creep so I head to my room immediately after I wave back.

Just like today went the next three days went almost identically. 

The two things that changed, however, is the body counts. The first of the three days, there were 2 bodies in the same room. Both slashed from the neck to the top of their stomach and the left leg taken from one of them and the right leg taken from the other. All they knew about the two people was that they were coworkers for the same company.

The next day there were 8 people found with ripped open chests and 4 different teeth pulled out of their mouths. 

The last of the three days was the tamest with just one person. However, he was completely skinned from head to toe. The anchor said that when the police found him lying on the ground he realized that nothing else was missing from him. There was also nothing wrong with the state of his flesh so whoever did this is very skilled with the knife.

The Second thing that changed over the course of the three days is the girl that I keep bumping into at the Noraebang has decided to go on a date with me tonight. Of course, I kept going at the same time just to bump into her, and I finally got the courage to ask her out for tonight.

I put my very best suit on and I head off to her house. When I see her my jaw drops. I mean this lady is definitely beautiful. 

When we arrive at the restaurant we order simple salads and we rush through with the eating. We both know that what we really want to do together is finally sing together for the first time. We go to the spot where we first met and I pay the normal fee plus another 8 dollars for her fee as well. I nod at the man behind the counter as he smiles at me and we head to the room that she normally uses.

I suggest singing All Star and I see her face light up. So I plug the code in and we each take a microphone. The next 30 minutes is filled with joy as we keep taking turns picking songs until the 7th song ends and she gives me a face filled with such hatred.

You fucking stupid bitch. Is all she manages to say before stumbling onto my lap with a knife stuck in her chest.  I sit back and really marvel at how beautiful her eyes are. Pulling the knife out I carefully cut around her sockets until I can grab her eyes and rip them off of the optical nerves. 

As I leave the room I flash the eyes to the worker as he nods his head and hurries in to my room to make sure I did not leave even a spot of evidence. 

Now dont blame me for doing all of those killings.

This was just my contribution to our cause. We each provide a piece of a body, and we are given enough money to live a lot more comfortably than we all normally would be able to. 

I dont know who our boss is. I dont know why he/she would need the exact body parts to recreate another human. I just know where to leave the part that was assigned to me. 

We never know when we have another job or what general type of location we need to acquire it from, but what I do know is that we will always get it done. 





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Christmas Present </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 04:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has been a toy that has caught the attention of millions of people across the world. They are called hatchimals and are these toy eggs that you interact with until the actual toy animal pops out of the egg, and they are now almost impossible to find in stores. 

Flipping through Amazon only frustrates me more as I realize that the cheapest ones are going for around $180, and there is no way that my meager salesman salary will be able to cover that expense. Its just that my son really wants one, and I need to keep looking for one that I will be able to afford no matter how long it takes. 

Im about to give up for the night until I find a craigslist ad for a hatchimal for just $59 dollars. I look through the ad and find out that its some Good Samaritan that has bought 50 of them knowing that they will sell out quickly, and is now selling them for the same price he got them for.  Filled with joy I text the number that was listed on the page, and with my laptop I head to my bedroom to show my wife the great deal I managed to find. 

The person does not text me until the next morning. While Im eating breakfast I see a text from him saying that he does indeed have some left, and he is willing to meet me at the Red Lobster that is just down the road from me. So I text him back saying I can be there with the cash in 20 minutes. Once Im done getting ready for work I head out and park at the Red Lobster. 

After waiting for about 7 minutes I see a man in his 40s step out of a bright yellow truck. I get out of my car to greet him and notice that he has a prosthetic right arm and his face is littered with cuts. I mind my manners and shake his left arm thanking him for being so generous at this time of year. With minimal words he states that I should get my money out as he pulls the box with the green hatchimal out of his truck and extends his prosthetic arm out signifying that he wants my money.

Im feeling just a bit confused, but I take my wallet out and give him three twenties and told him to keep the one dollar change. With a nod and a quick thank you he gets back in to his truck and drives out of the parking lot. 

I cant help but feel like it was some sort of scam, but Im already running late for work now so I just head off to store I work at. 

With it being holiday season our store is bustling with business, and before I know it I have met the sales goals for today and its time to go back home. While Im driving back home I realize that I completely forgot to wrap the present so I stop by the local Walmart and get a Christmas bag with some Christmas themed tissue paper. 

Before I put the hatchimal into the bag I check it over to make sure that its real. Comparing to what I have in my hand and what is on the picture on my phone I quickly determine that its real and the guy was just fucking creepy. 

Once I got home I showed my wife the toy and she insisted that we just give our son the gift now. I mean hes eight and its all hes been talking about for the last month so we know he would appreciate getting his toy quicker, and on Christmas we can just give him the little gifts that we had already gotten him. When he received his toy his face lit up and he gave us both a hug and kisses on the cheek. Ripping open the box he started petting the egg and the egg was making slight interactions with him back. 

Five days before Christmas was when it finally hatched revealing a tiny purple and blue owl with a tiny horn on top of its head. He automatically started petting it and caring for it as if it were a pet and we knew that he truly loved it. 

After a couple of days of him petting it and carrying it around everywhere we heard the hatchimal start singing happy birthday, and we knew that it was finally getting to the Toddler stage of the toy. This is the stage that you will teach it how to walk, play games, and just a bit more functionalities. 

Thats when I started noticing that the toy has now started to follow my son everywhere he goes. Tonight I told him we were eating dinner in the living room to watch a Christmas movie he raced down and took a seat at the couch. When my wife and I came into the living room with our dinner we noticed the hatchimal was halfway up the couch. I asked my son if he brought it downstairs with him, but all he said was it followed him down. So I just grabbed the toy and placed him in the kitchen out of reach from my son and came back in to the living room. 

Once the movie ended I took him upstairs and brushed his teeth then sent him to bed. It wasnt until around 1 in the morning when my wife and I decided to head to bed. As Im passing my sons bedroom I notice hes still up and carrying on a conversation. I open the door and peek in to see him petting his hatchimal and talking to him in the dark. Sneaking in I hear the hatchimal telling my son to sneak out of his house and to go to the end of the street. That scares me, but rage fills every part of my body as I realize that the voice is of the man that sold me the fucking toy.

Ill head out the fucking door.

Ill be at the end of the street.

Merry Christmas Mother Fucker.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm 12 and I Met a Nice Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the sound of change jingling in my pockets I race out of my mommas car and into the best cookie store in the whole wide world! 

Every day if I am a good boy and I do all of my chores my papa gives me a quarter, and at the end of the month they take me to the cookie store where I can spend all day eating cookies and reading the books I take to the store! The owner of the cookie store sees me come in once a month so he brings me free lemonade throughout the day too!

As I start getting into my book a man sits in front of me and tells me Im a very good looking young man. So I remember my manners and tell the man thank you. Im twelve years old, but a lot of people have already called me a very good looking person so the compliment does not make me as happy as it used to. 

I ask the man what his name is, and he tells me that his name is Jonah and that he has a wonderful game room in his house. He said he has all of the newest game systems and all of the games, with a humongous TV, and all the snacks I could possibly want! Wow! He must be very rich to have all of that stuff. I only have a small TV at home, and I only get around 5 channels on it so thats why I read a lot of books.

Im only halfway through my second cookie so I offered the man one of my other cookies. He declines my cookie saying that he has plenty of snacks to eat back at home, and he offers to take me over to his house to play video games and eat as many cookies with ice cream as I would like.

I dont want to waste any of the cookies I already have so I ask the man if he can give me around an hour so I can finish my book and the rest of my cookies. He says its fine and that he can wait for me to finish.

He keeps telling me what a good looking boy I am while Im trying to read and it gets a little annoying so I tell him that I am happy to get compliments, but I would like some time to read my book and that he is distracting me. After being quiet for around 20 minutes he starts to try and hold my hand, but every time he brings his hand to mine I act like Im flipping the page in my book.

After he manages to grab my hand and starts rubbing it with his finger is when I tell him to stop touching me or I will not be going over to his house. I guess he finally understood that I would like to have some type of privacy while I read and eat my cookies because he finally decided to do something on his phone. 

When I am finally done with my book and cookies I notice that it was 4 p.m. so I tell the man that I am ready to go over to his house now. 

He jumps out of his chair excitedly and talks about how much fun we are going to have while we exit the store. The owner of the cookie shop gives me a questionable look but I just give him a smile and a nod.

I smile while I think to myself how much fun I will have with him while we walk out of the store. I laugh when I know today is going to be a good day while we walk onto the parking lot. I scream with glee when my daddy comes behind the man and shoves him into our van. 

Does not take long for us to be on the road as my momma is a very good driver and we manage to peel out of the parking lot and onto the streets. By the time we get on the highway we already have the mans mouth taped over and the skin of his arms peeled off. The rest of the skin is easy to peel off now so we both grab our knives and make sure all of his skin is gone by the time we get home. 

Once we get home my daddy and I chop the hands and the feet off because we dont like eating those parts so I threw them in to the fire. Then we have to cut right in the middle of each elbow, then shoulder, take the guts and organs out of his midsection, pull the ribs out. That all goes into the stew that we make. The meat found on the back, chest area (with the heart and organs taken out of course), and legs all make for a wonder pan fried meal. 

I may be twelve, but I know what a fucking creep is. I know that he is evil for wanting to do unspeakable things to me. That is why every month I go to the cookie store. That is why the cookie store owner is a very good friend of ours. He has the same taste as us. So he finds people that are looking for good looking boys like me and tells them to come to his shop so they can take me home with them. 

Yes we like human flesh, but arent we making the world a better [place] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks)?
 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Town is Blessed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 11:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is Jeremy and I live in a small town in Mississippi. Im just your average sized male at 5 foot 11 inches. I own a farm where I am blessed with an abundance of animals. They are all well fed, and I make sure they are as happy as can be.

We have around 200 to 225 people living in our community. Unlike the rest of the world we live by a certain set of rules. We do not condone to any kind of adultery, women listen to what the man says, and children stay quiet until they are asked a question. We have other rules, but its all pretty much common sense from there. If the sin is harsh enough they must be punished with death. 

We still have technology in our community, but we are not able to have anything that allows us to communicate to anyone on the outside of our town. Cars are allowed but no one has a car due to the fact that you can walk anywhere you want to in less than half an hour. Last but not least at the end of the month we all gather together to the great fire pit for our sacrifice. As all of the great people in the Bible the Lord requires us to give up some portion of our earnings. I have always tossed my largest animal so that He may keep bestowing upon me His blessings. 

I have a beautiful 3 bedroom ranch right in the middle of the town. My animals are all in the backyard fenced in so they are not able to leave my farm or get stolen. Every morning when I wake up I pray to the Lord thanking him for everything he has done for me, afterwards I go to my kitchen where I use only the best cuts of meat to eat with my eggs and toast. The butcher shows up usually right when I finish breakfast to pick up any animal of his choosing. Then I go for my daily walk around town. After my walk I go back to care for my animals and take an afternoon nap. 

Once I wake up I wait till the butcher arrives with a large loaf of bread and enough meat cooked to complete perfection to last till tomorrow afternoon. Once I am finished eating I go outside and I throw an assortment of vegetables provided by my wonderful garden and watch as the animals fight over the food. Now it is time for our towns mandatory 2 hour prayer to the Lord.   Where we must sit outside of our house no matter what weather and spend the time praying for forgiveness of whatever bad thoughts or wrong doings we have done throughout the day.

When the prayer time is over I go back inside and reheat the meat and make a salad for dinner. Bed time for me comes right after I finish my dinner as I need to get up early in the morning. 

That is what I do every day, and it is the perfect life for me. 

The only day that is different is the last Saturday of every month. This is the day we give the Lord our sacrifice. As I have said before I go to my farm and pick the biggest animal I have and walk it to the fire pit. The animal always put up a fight and makes this horrid high pitch noise, but I have always managed to throw it in month after month. As I watch the eyeballs of the beast burst into liquefied goo I laugh, as the skin melts off of the flesh I join in the dancing with the other townspeople. Just when it turns into a black piece of stump is when the sacrifice is over and we head back to our houses to rest.

One fine day I step out of my house to realize that I am extremely low on animals. I start to worry about what I am going to say to the butcher as he will definitely notice how low I am. Everyone in our town will be ashamed to know that I have failed them as a provider of meat for them all. I know God must have a plan so I kneel in front of my farm and I pray for a miracle.

As I open my eyes I am filled with joy! I see a multitude of animals coming right up to my farm! They make their normal noises like Sir, our bus is being repaired by your mechanic, but we are all very hungry. The mechanic told me to go to you and you could give us a meal. I nod my head yes and lead them into my house. Just a bit of Rohypnol mixed into each of their bowls of meat stew and I see every single one of them droop their heads and begin to drop their bowls and spoon on the ground. 

This gives me 45 minutes to get them ready for my farm. First the tongues must be sliced off so that they may not proceed with their evil sayings and produce further blasphemy to the Lord. Then I must drive a metal rod from the front side of their thighs to the ankle and bend each part down so that they may not walk astray from the Lord anymore. Lastly, a smaller metal rod will start from the bottom of the wrist to the bottom of the bicep and bent down each way to avoid them from further sins the twisted animals mind can think up of doing.

The Lord has provided us for months all because we do as he asks. We are not lead down the path of sin, and we always keep our faith to the Lord. The animals may sound like I do, but I know that deep down inside it is merely an animal. That is why I have my farm. 

So that they may produce something good out of their lives.

I am blessed, my town is blessed, are you blessed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be Careful What You Pray For </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 11:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive always been a semi religious person. Basically, I share the same belief as Christians, but refuse to go to church. I just never saw the need to be forced to sing, pray, and converse with people that I would usually avoid like the plague in public. 

Plus the fact that I whole heartedly believe in evolution and that there are beings beyond Earth cause most Christians to cringe. Having a whole Sunday off for myself has always been completely fine by me.

Unfortunately, next week is this special service for my mother and father because they are getting ordained or some shit. Being the good son I am I decided to go with them. 

The service is just like every other service. Sing the same songs about how much we are in love with Jesus; which makes me seriously wonder whether its a religious song or just some sappy love song. Then time for everyone to turn to John 45: I dont fucking remember and read it out loud all together. Then my favorite part! The time where we all listen to a person on a podium and talk about how if we dont take Jesus show of love we are all going to get our skin and flesh melted off of in some endless pool of molten lava. 

After the sermon is over we all bow our heads and get time to pray for our own prayer requests. That is when I first laid my eyes on what has made me obsessed with going to every single church I possibly can. Its really hard to describe what it looked like even though he was floating right on top of the person in front of me, but just think an angel with tattered clothing. 

His body was completely normal except he had a swirling mass of black goo for a right hand, and a small shining body of light instead of a left hand. His face was stretched out longer than anyone I have ever seen. His lips were impossibly stretched out to produce the saddest look I have ever seen.  His eyes were solid white on his left side while his right eye was the darkest black you could imagine. His forehead ended in a curve making his face end touching the middle of his back. As the man started asking for the new promotion he really wanted the being slowly touched his head with his right hand and with a look of great depression passed to the next person.

He proceeded to pass by everyone and touched them with his right hand or his left hand. When he got to my parents he touched both of them with his left hand. Once he got to me he just stayed in front of me for around 2 seconds and proceeded to pass me without touching me with his left hand or his right. Made me wonder why he just passed by me I realized I was not praying. I looked around the church to see if anyone else noticed this ugly piece of shit touching everyone, but even the people that have stopped praying did not seem to notice a thing out of the ordinary.

Once the service is over I decide to go back home and research about what I just saw, but all I got out of Google is that Im some delusional fuck. Absolutely nothing about it, and I decided to just completely ignore what I just saw. 

The next week is complete agony for me as I cant even take my mind off of what I just saw. The impossibility of the shape of his face and the look of pure sadness puts me at a constant depressed mood. I know for a fact that he was there listening to everyones prayers and either approving them or disapproving them with a touch of either his left of right hand. In the middle of the week my parents got approved for a much needed loan for them to set up a new church so I know that the being has some sort of ability to make peoples prayers come true.  

I dont know much else about it, but I know my mind wont be at rest until I figure out exactly why its doing what it does and what is leading it to receive such torment doing so. So when Sunday rolls around I decide to go to a different church to see if I can see him once again. After the singing and the sermon is over this pastor allows people to come to the front of the church to kneel down and pray. Once again, I see the figure come in and with the same look of depression goes by each person and touches them with one of his deciding hands.

I see one of my work colleagues in the front and I wait to see which hand he will be touched by. Once I see him touched by his left hand I start to wonder what exactly he was praying for. After the sermon I go out to greet him and he looks surprised to see me at his church. We go through the formalities and we say our goodbyes and I head back home. 

I decide to just stop thinking about everything and relax before having to go spend another week at work. So I just order some food and pop in some movies. Before I know it morning has arrived and I start getting ready to work. Once I reach the store that has graced me with the opportunity to sell electronics I notice 4 police cars parked outside. 

I look inside to see my manager has been literally torn to shreds by God knows what. The only way I can tell it was my manager was by the name tag that was attached to a piece of our uniform accompanied by a bit of skin and chunks of meat on top of the camera display. What was identified as his head looked like a deflated red dodge ball. His eyes were torn out of his socket, his nose just a crushed mush, and mouth gaping open as if he was stuck in a permanent blind scream. 

I cant bear to look any longer so I just head back home knowing that we will not be working at all. Our store was closed for the next three days, and all I did during that period of time was lie on the couch and order pizza continuously.

On Thursday I go back to work, and we have a little team meeting before we open. The new announcement was that the coworker I saw at church has now become the new manager. He looks deathly pale as he hears the news and looks as if hes about to faint. After the meeting I go up to him and congratulate him as well as ask if he would like to go get lunch with me on break. He accepts luckily.

While we are at lunch I ask him why he looked like he was about to faint. His response to me brought chills all over my body. Well the thing is, remember last Sunday? Okay, that day I was at the front of the church and I prayed that I can somehow get a better position or get a raise. I just never expected that to happen like that. I tell him maybe it was just a coincidence it happened like that. I wanted to tell him what i saw but I just dont want him to think Im crazy when I tell him what I started seeing at church. We resume our lunch and right as we are about to finish he looks up at me and tells me one last thing. You know after I was done praying I felt a warm presence in front of me. I honestly thought it was God giving me the assurance that what i was asking for will indeed happen.

Thats when I decided to make it a personal mission of mine to figure this shit out. 

Once the work day ends I go back home to see my mother parked outside of my house sobbing in her car. I go up to the car and she flies out and clings on to me as if her life depended on it. Once I manage to calm her down we go inside and she sits quietly on my couch. After 5 minutes of awkward silence she looks up at me and tells me that after just 10 days of getting approved for the loan. My father was so overcome by the stress of everything he decided that his one dream was just an impossibility. Knowing he had no turning back from it he decided to shoot himself in his bedroom. My mom came in after a prayer meeting to my find my fathers blown out skull and brain matter all over the bed sheets.

I have yet to figure out what this demented little bitch is, but I will figure it out.

Just please take my warning.

Be careful what you pray for.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you Tried Vaping? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 10:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you had asked me three weeks ago I would have told you that vaping is by far the dumbest fad to hit the stores. Well not as bad as those so called hoverboards, but pretty damn close. 

I did not see the point in sucking on a metal stick and blowing out far more smoke than is necessary. The only real reason why I bought it two weeks ago was to smoke it indoors when I dont feel like going outside and braving the harsh cold winter. Plus everyone I know started to get vapes so I thought. What the hell, and decided to use it just during the winter and keep it in my closet till the next winter.

It really didnt take me long to become completely infatuated by this device. I mean the flavors you can get for this thing is absolutely incredible! Blueberry cheesecake and vanilla make smoking feel like youre merely eating desert rather than taking in the much needed nicotine my body craves. I started smoking more of my vape and far less cigarettes. 

After a week of smoking the vape it has gotten to where I no longer need to smoke cigarettes. It feels like complete freedom when I can go into my restroom at work and smoke to my hearts content and leave the restroom with it smelling better than when I got in it.

I cant help but continuously talk about vaping to everyone I know now. I will talk about it with my family members telling them that I am no longer taking in anything that is harmful to my body other than nicotine and how my life is starting to get better. 

I know its starting to become an obsession when I bought my 11th vape, but I have yet to regret any of those purchases. Its a good obsession, and I am just so glad to have found out about it instead of living with such a closed mind.

 I mean I dont smell like cigarettes anymore so my boss is much happier to stand around and talk to me now. So I just had to tell him how amazing it is that I am now vaping. He seemed confused by what that was so I took him outside and took a hit from my vape and blew it right in his face. After getting over the shock he was surprised by how good it smelled so I did not get into any trouble for doing that.

He allows me to smoke my vape in my office now, and I simply couldnt be happier. My friends that started vaping before me are now applauding at the fact that I have started too, and we now get together and one of our houses and watch movies and just vape the night away.

Imagine my surprise when my boss came into my office blowing a thick cloud of smoke! Simply amazing when I see someone doing something I am so passionate about. He said that he just could not stop thinking about how amazing it smelt and he was so curious about how it tastes he decided to go out and buy one himself. Which, of course, he does not regret doing at all!

Its been two months since I start vaping and I realized that every single breath I take now I am breathing out smoke. Which I dont mind at all because I can now constantly taste the wonderful caramel and coffee mix I started using. I just hope people dont get insulted with having smoke blown in their face every time they talk to me.

The only thing that pisses me right the fuck off is the fact that my so called friends are now excluding me from every little gathering they are having. I mean Im doing everything they like to do with them! I laugh, scream, cry, or freak out over the same scenes they do, and most of all I blow out vape smoke with them constantly. 

Inconsiderate as fuck.

I know exactly why they stopped asking me to come over. They are probably weirded out about the smoke that continuously comes out of my mouth. 

Another thing, my fucking boss fired me after telling me that he is tired of being reminded about how amazing vaping is continuously. Just another person tired of seeing me expelling vape smoke out of my mouth. 

So it is due time I get back at everyone for not only insulting me, but for insulting the very thing I love. I go up to my ex bosses car after getting fired and I wait for him to get into the car. Six whole hours but its worth it. When he gets into his car I shove a vape all the way down his throat and tape his mouth shut. Afterwards ripping his throat open with his tie clip and grab a bottle of vape juice and proceed to pour it in his exposed throat drip by drip. Take out my pocket knife and slowly slice down from his throat to where his chest meets his stomach. Rip out his right ribs and once I spot his exposed heart I shove another vape into it. Maybe now he can love vapes as much as I do.

My three friends shortened my time for any type of fun, because once I rammed into their house one of them had the fucking genius idea to automatically call the cops. Quickly and swiftly use the knife to pounce on my first friend as the other two run out the door and I start taking hits off my vape and CPR style blowing it into his mouth as I slowly cut both of his ears off. I remember he always told me that he was starting to get annoyed at how much I talked about vaping. After I slice his ears off and is expelling smoke continuously like me I slowly shove the knife in each canal of his ears and shove it in as far as the knife goes to make sure I rip his eardrums. 

Before I leave I grab a vape and shove it in to his right ear and use the knife to shove it into the middle of his head. Grab his ears with another vape and shove the items right into his mouth and tape it all in. 

Ill get to my other two friends soon. 

Dont insult what people love. Its just completely rude. 

Just have an open mind.

While youre at it. Why not start vaping too? Its just the greatest thing in the world!

I truly promise you will not regret it.

Not even one bit.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fun Challenges in Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 10:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I have any type of free time I like to indulge in my favorite hobby of all time. Seeing what people will do for money. Ive gotten quite good at convincing people to do things by offering a good amount of money while having a camera and a microphone claiming its for a YouTube Video.

Im currently in South Korea so the only hard part is to find a foreigner that is good at speaking English. Luckily, there is a park nearby my house where a lot of foreign teachers will walk around and meet other people that speak their native tongue.

Today a man in his late 20s caught my eye so I decided to approach him. 

Hows it going man? My name is B and Im filming for a YouTube video. Do you have some spare time?

Of course he says yes and asks which channel Im posting the video. I give him my business card with my YouTube channel name on it and we are ready to proceed with the fun!

Alright sir what is your name?

James. 

Great! The first challenge for $50 is extremely easy just tell a random person you love them.

Its silly but there are people who are not able to complete this challenge. 

However, he without hesitation goes up to the closest woman and tells her he loves her. Afterwards, he quickly explains that this was for a YouTube video which makes it annoying because its just another thing for me to edit out.

On to the next challenge!

For $200 dollars the challenge varies depending on the person. For him I decided to make him go up to a random guy and hold his hand for at least 10 seconds. 

Without giving it a second thought he goes up to the first guy that walks past him and grabs his hand. Out of pure shock the guy holds onto James hand without trying to let go of his hand for seven seconds. After that the man tries to struggle out of James hand, but James manages to hold on for the remainder three seconds.

When I hand James the money he quickly gives the man a hundred dollars out of it and the man seems completely satisfied about the extra hundred dollars.

Its crazy what people will do for money.

Good job James! Now for the third challenge for $500 you have to remove an article of clothing from anyone that passes us. 

This time he is not so quick with the challenge. While people pass by I can see the hesitation on his face as he tries to quickly think what would be the easiest thing to take off.

After 10 minutes of waiting I tell him he needs to find someone in the next 2 minutes as I believe he has had several great opportunities hes passed by.

Lucky for him the third person to pass by after that was a lady wearing a scarf so without second thought he rips the scarf off of her. 

Stunned, she just stares at James while I hand him $500 dollars. James, the nice guy he is hands her a hundred dollars and explains it was just for a YouTube video.

Youre fucking killing me James. Thats another spot for me to edit out but at least he completed the challenge. It is now time for the final challenge.

M- Hey James, are you free all day tomorrow?

J- Yeah, I have an off day at work today and tomorrow.

M- Well the last challenge will take some time so we will have to go tomorrow if youre up for it!

J-Alright man, whats the challenge?

M-  There is a mountain called the Namsan about 3 miles away from us. Im sure you have heard of it. Well I want you to wear some shorts and a t-shirt and climb that mountain with me!

J- Ah fuck that dude. Im not trying to freeze to death man.

M- I can assure you that you wont freeze to death! Plus its the last challenge. This is for $5000. I know you cant turn down that money!

The money always helps. People will pretty much do anything for $5000. They may say they never will, but when they are put in that position they will always take the deal.

The next morning I meet James at the same spot and we get in my car and head off to the mountain. Its only a 15 minute drive through traffic so I just share some small talk with him. 

Learned quite a bit about him.

He moved to Korea to teach English. 

He moved here with his wife, but they dont have any kids yet.

His wife also teaches English, but for some extra cash she works some hours at a local coffee shop.

Thats why he decided to do these challenges as well as climb the mountain in summer wear. So she can quit her job and they can spend some more time together.

Stories like his completely warm me up. I mean he loves his wife so much that he is willing to sacrifice his own body and health. 

Well we start heading up the mountain and right away I can see how cold he is. We are at the bottom of the mountain and its already 28F. 

I start to feel bad for him so I decide to break my own rules and give him my extra coat. When we start reaching the top is when I turn the camera back on while I take the coat back from James. 

Once we reach the top we exchange high fives, and I tell him to do some jumping jacks to warm up while I get a fire started. I always take a bag with three logs and several boxes of matches. He takes my suggestion and starts doing some exercises to get him warmed up.

I take that opportunity to take out my hunting knife and jam it in the middle of his back. Slicing down I can see how his spinal cord is separating away from the back muscles and ribs. I cant look him in the face as I do it because I can feel the look of betrayal on his face. 

Once I reach the bottom of his back I slice his neck to make sure he dies quickly. Once, I make sure hes dead I cut a small piece of his bicep off. Put it on a stick and place it over the fire. While thats cooking I have to skin him and separate the skin from his face from the rest. Then take a picture of the facial skin placed over my face as I take a bite of his cooked bicep.

Cut up the rest of his body that can be eaten and bury the rest of the scraps.

Am I a cannibal? No. 

I do have a delivery I have to make tomorrow.

Like I said. 

Its crazy what people will do for money.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook Problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So today started like every other day. Woke up, got out of bed, brushed my teeth, stared at myself in the mirror for about 3 minutes, made breakfast, ate the breakfast, used my key to unlock my front door, locked my front door, and headed to work. I live in a pretty unsafe neighborhood so I have to always remember to lock my doors and make sure all of my windows (which are luckily pretty much unbreakable unless you fire a pistol directly at it) are locked as well.

I work at an office so the mundane schedule of my life continues throughout the whole day.

I am currently mapping out how a website needs to look, and then sending those to the design team so they can start creating the website. Its kind of weird how theyre called the design team, but they actually dont really do any designing themselves.

Anyways, I work on that all the way till its time for lunch. Our lunch takes place in a cafeteria type setting where every little business that works around it gets to eat there for a low price of roughly 3 dollars. (I work in Korea so its hard to guess the exchange rate right.) The food there is always shitty, but I cant really complain because of the price.

We get an hour off during our lunch break so after lunch I always check my phone for the remaining 25 minutes of my break. As soon as I turn on my phone I notice I have a notification for a picture uploaded to my Facebook account.

Strange. I honestly dont remember uploading any pictures so I open up Facebook to see which picture uploaded.
What the fuck.

Its just a picture of my living room.

When I get back to my office I get another notification for a picture uploaded to my account.

Its a picture of my bedroom with what looks to be blood on my bed sheets.

It doesnt take long before people start messaging me asking what the hell is going on, and it takes over an hour to explain to everyone that Im fine. Im in my office, and Ill figure out everything when I get home. My mother messaged me asking if she should call the cops, and I tell her its fine. Its probably some prankster who was in my house before and decided to spook me while Im at work.

I decide that Ive had enough of these uploads so I change the id and password to my account. Luckily for me I only have Facebook. Ive never really gotten into the other Social Media Websites.
I know most people would panic at this point, but for me there really is no reason for me to panic. I mean, I have an ungodly amount of locks on my doors, and all of my windows are completely bulletproof. I swear I could get through the purge in this house. So theres no way anyone could get in.

Its 2 p.m. now so only four more hours to go before I can go home. There hasnt been another disturbance on my Facebook in the past two hours so I start to calm down.

Get back to work on the website and before I know it 6 p.m. has arrived. I need to pick up some milk and eggs on the way home so I stop by my local grocery store.

Its 7:30 by the time I get home and as I unlock the door I see a figure in the doorway. I cant help but gasp at a man missing both hands and feet. The wrists are oozing out blood but the scabs around the blood are old. His nose has been stapled downwards and each side of his mouth has been sewn together leaving only a small space to open his mouth. Ears have been cut off only to be replaced by the ears of a stuffed animal.

Im fucking shocked. I mean what the fuck.

How did my pet fucking manage to get out of the basement?

I swear pets are getting smarter every day.

Like I said.

Im safe inside of my house.

No one can sneak into my house or sneak out of my house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Trust Glenn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 12:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I have been working with mentally ill patients here in Jeju Island, South Korea for around 20 years now. The patient that was rushed through the doors here recently is by far the most disturbed individual I have ever worked with. I am posting on his account, because I am deeply disturbed by everything he has written. 


The first day he came in after his life saving surgery was a meeting full of awkward glances and silence. Im a therapist. I know. I should be able to deduce something out of the silence, but Im at a complete loss. 


Towards the end of the session he starts muttering some sort of gibberish that I simply cant understand. I sigh inwardly and write what the fuck in my notebook to completely summarize this meeting. 


I thank him for his time and he just proceeds to lay back down onto his hospital bed. 


This is what I know about him so far. His name is Glenn. He works for a company that organizes conferences and events. He killed his manager that was staying at the same room as him. He came into the hospital yelling and screaming about deaths and a strange itch. 


The only death that has occurred during that conference was his manager, and he shows zero signs of skin irritation. Besides the massive hole and the missing man parts there was nothing wrong with him when he came into the hospital.


Completely horrible what he did to his manager though. 


His manager was nothing but a mass of flesh when the paramedics arrived. The throat was torn out of him and his spine was halfway out of his backside. His midsection was a jumbled mess of smashed organs and intestines. His thighs were mostly sliced off by a pocket knife. The meat that was sliced off his thighs was then stuck on top of the spinal cord.


The worst part of it all was that his eyes were both taken out and he used that as an entry port to his brain. His head was gashed open utilizing that entry point, and the brain was removed from his skull. 


They found the brain hanging from the inside door knob.


Thats why Im here. I have by far the most experience out of anyone else here and I also know English at a competent level. 


Second Day of our sessions and hes still blankly staring down at the floor. So I start asking him random questions about his job, his family life, his favorite food, anything to get him to talk. I have realized that the most basic questions tend to make anyone talk. No matter how fucking psychotic they are. Yet, he still keeps staring down at the floor and whispering gibberish to himself quietly.


Im about to give up hope so I just write my final comments down on my notepad when I look up to see him staring at me as if Im some slice of thigh meat that failed to stake myself on top of a spinal cord. Not saying anything to me at all but just staring at me blankly and still muttering to himself.


I still see that as some type of progress so I end the session there and once again thank him for his most valuable time. He goes back to his bed and proceeds to lie down.


His nurse comes in and lays a tray of food on his bed and tells him its lunch time. He keeps staring at his food blankly without any thought of picking up the spoon to begin eating. His nurse then tells me that he has not eaten a single thing or has drunk a single thing. 


I guess her telling me this information has angered him because he grabs the tray of food and flings it at the TV screaming one single word. DIRTY! Then laying back down acting as if nothing happened at all. 


Fucking weird kid.


Third Session he is completely fixated with me. He has not taken his eyes off of me for even a single millisecond. He keeps muttering, but this time I thought ahead and brought a little microphone to clip on to his collar. This way even though he doesnt respond back to me I can still maybe get a couple of my questions answered. 


I still, however, try to get him to talk by giving him some more generic questions, but of course I am not getting a single response. I did notice that he has started to obsessively scratch his right arm, and hes beginning to bleed where hes scratching so hard so I make a note for his nurse. While Im writing down the note Glenn finally says a phrase that makes sense to me.


You do not know whats going to happen.


I ask him what he meant by that, but he just closed his mouth and started shaking his head at me. I write down what hes said and told him that this session is over and we will continue the next session tomorrow. 


I give his nurse the note when she gets back with his food and I leave before he chucks his dinner anywhere near me. 


I go back home and watch some TV while I eat my leftovers from the night before. I cant help but keep thinking about what he said earlier. What does he honestly think will happen? If I can just figure that out I can easily put together why he did those horrific acts.


I wake up to a series of texts coming into my phone.


These are the texts from the nurse. 


Hey are you awake? I went into Glenns room and his restrictions are torn off. Hes in the restroom now just curled up into a ball.


Can you come over here? Hes not moving at all. He just keeps saying I found a new body over and over again.


Ive called the cops. Theyre coming now, but I really think you should get over here. Hes acting really strange but I feel like hes trying to tell me something.


Fuck. I get out of my pajamas and get into a shirt and some pants and rush out to the hospital. There are cop cars littered about the hospital, and I cant help but fear the worst.


As I step out of the elevator I see cops standing outside of his room. I walk up to the room and look inside. The nurse is lying in the middle of the room with chunks taken out of her. There are two doctors sitting next to her telling her she will be fine and to stay calm. Listen is all she can do as her eyes are sitting right next to her on the floor. The oddest thing about it all is that on her chest there is a series of deep gashes to spell out. Not good, Dirty.


Where the fuck is Glenn?


I ask the police officers and they are saying that they are still trying to find him. When they got there all they saw was the nurse lying on the floor with a scalpel lodged in the right side of her chest. 


No one can seem to find him, and theyve had people searching for him everywhere. They only had a skeleton crew at the time so security was at a minimum. Of course, when they look on the cameras they can see Glenn as he rushes past each camera and finally going past the camera that is pointing towards the entrance.


Not much for me to do here now. So I head back home. I just want to sleep and get this night out of my head.


I get to my house and I go into my kitchen to grab some cereal, but what stops me dead in my tracks is that on the counter I found a bloody plastic spoon.


For Glenns account of last week.


Part one: https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5fv6ie/please_help_me/


Part two: https://wh.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5g1y1l/please_help_me_part_2/


Part three: https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5g92uz/please_help_me_part_3/


Part four: https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5gf39j/please_help_mefinal/


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please Help Me-Final </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 12:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For Part 3 : https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5g92uz/please_help_me_part_3/

This is finally the last day of the conference and I cant begin to explain how happy I am to finally get through this hellish week. One can only stomach so many deaths.

Today we had by far the smallest turnout. The total participants now totaling a pathetic count of 361 people. 

We are going with a lighter schedule due to the fact that the participant count is so low as well as people fucking dying left and right, but you know half day. Yay.

Today seems like it's going to be somewhat of a decent day. The only thing bugging me now is that I have this annoying itch on the top section of my forehead. A quick scratch will make it go away, but within twenty minutes that same spot will be disturbed by the same itch. Not really a big deal since I'm not scratching as bad as the other remaining participants, and I'm not really sure the itching even had anything to do with the intestine cuisine lovers.

 After the first two meetings it's time for the coffee break. I take the meager amount of participants to the coffee break area, and I grab a coffee for myself. Coffee has been a very big reason why I haven't fucking lost my shit after everything that happened in the past week.

I go back to the office after I finish my coffee and make sure all of the participants are happy with their coffee and tea. 

God this fucking itch.

It's starting to get really annoying.

It has gotten to the point to where scratching will make the itch go away. Seriously. No. Matter. How. Much. I. Fucking. Scratch. it stays there and it will not go away. 

Have you ever had an itch on your eyelid that is so bad that you have to rub the everlasting shit out of your whole upper face region?

I have even tried the good ol open my eye as much as my little Korean eyes can open and poke the area that is causing me this grief and torment.

So now Im going to do the only rational thing I can think of.

Luckily I have a pair of scissors and two perfectly good hands to complete this little operation.

Good news.

The itch is finally gone.

Bad news.

My face is not as symmetrical as it once was.

But seriously.

Who gives a flying fuck.

I got rid of the itch!

I start to finally feel like I see the light at the end of the tunnel. One more meeting and we are finally over. 

FInal meeting is finally over, and the conference is finally over without me having to see the insides of another person. 

Time to finally go back to the hotel and finally relax.

The manager and I get into our car and drive back to the hotel. Some people are staring at me because i have a mini hole on my face, but luckily I'm now living in plastic surgery central.

Finally back in the hotel. 

You know what I just noticed is the fact that the manager has not said a single word to me. Maybe he's just in a bad mood. 

Okay.

What the hell.

What the actual HELL.

The itch is back, and its now migrated to my eyebrow.

Well I know exactly how to solve this simple problem.

So i just use my index and middle finger to pinch my eyebrow and use my pocket knife to slice off my eyebrow. To make it feel extra gratifying I sliced it little by little to feel every centimeter of the itch slowly disappear away. 

Good as new and I can proceed to relax!

Well its time for bed.

The manager is already asleep.

Only thing is. I cannot sleep for the life of me.

Why?

I think you know exactly why.

The itch is back and its so much worse.

It has now migrated away from my head and is now disrupting my very manhood.

The very tip of it and I know its only a matter of time before I go insane from this so Caitlyn Jenner 
welcome me to the club!

Back to my handy danndy pocketknife.

Two questions.

Have you ever sliced your own dick off? If you have answered yes to the first question my follow up question is. Why the fuck does it take so damn long?

I swear there is more to the penis than I have ever expected. As Im sawing through bits of tissue and veins I start to finally feel the itch going away slowly. I have been cutting for about 5 minutes and I havent even cut through half of it, but that doesn't matter one bit. It feels amazing. Pure Bliss. Every drop of blood is helping me forget this conference one day at a time.

Well I finally got it off and man does it feel good to be itch free.

I don't know how I'm going to dispose of it. I mean I can flush it down, but I feel like that would just be disrespectful to men all around the world. So I think I'm going to hold on to it. Just as a souvenir or something.

Come to think of it I really did like that coffee I had earlier during the coffee break. I hope no one noticed me grabbing a coffee. It was honestly just to calm myself down after this stressful conference week.

I grab some gauze from the health kit and bandage myself up and finally lay myself down to enjoy some much needed sleep.

So I want to sleep, but I still can't seem to fall asleep. It's just I have this feeling. A feeling that I have something inside of me that needs to leave my body. If it doesn't leave this itch will keep occurring. 

I just need to make an exit point for whatever needs to exit, but I'm really not sure how big I should make it. 

Cut.

Cut.

Itch. 

Scratch. 

Cut.

I don't need to think.

It's getting too hard to anyways.

Cut.

Stomach.

Manager.

Neck.

Cut.

Throat.

Rip out.

Eat.

Adams apples do not in fact taste like apples.

My large 

intestines.

Manager.

Mouth.

Coffee.

Last thought guys.

Whatever is inside of me right now.

They are in every participant that was here.

Some dead.

Some alive.

From every country around the world.

They like to move from body to body.

I need to eat whatever is blocking them from exiting.

They are not visible.

They are there.

Cut manager.

Rip stomach.

Shove face in.

Need.

Find.

Need.

Help.

Leave.

My body.

Not good enough.

Manager's body.

Not good enough.

Need new.

Eat.

Intestines.

Found

Stomach

adkdfj

daienene

adslkmdmd

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please Help Me Part 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 11:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fourth day of the conference.



There is nothing I wish more than for this conference to end. 



Fourth day of the conference and our attendance has now dropped down to 724 participants.



68 reported deaths so far, and 600 participants that have either gone to a hospital to get themselves checked or have fled the fuck out of dodge.



I wish i wouldn't have to be here, but let me explain something to you. If you either get fired or quit a job in South Korea you are basically fucked. The chances of you finding a job before you run out of your funds and find yourself sharing beans outside of a convenience store with Mr Lee is very fucking low. Mr. Lee does not smell good or have decent manners because he's a salty, homeless, piece of shit that latches on to legs of anyone that passes him by begging for Korean Wine money. So that is why i'm still here.



Shit. I'd rather die than be stuck being Mr. Lee's latch buddy.



So back to this shit storm of a conference.



Everyone is on edge. Participants are now whispering to the people they trust, and the other workers and I have pretty much secluded ourselves to our office.



The only time we leave the office is to prepare for the next part of the conference. When it is time for them to go to another room one of us leaves the office to guide them to the other room and bolt back to the office. Moe, Larry, and Curly have already done their turn so it's my turn to lead them to the coffee break area. 



Stress is overwhelming me so i grab a coffee to settle myself down and fight back the desire to sleep. I see the participants leaving the other room so i guide them to the coffee area. The first thing i notice about them is that they continue scratching various parts of their bodies. 



Fucking gross when most of the participants are now riddled with scabs throughout their bodies. Making it seem like we are now in an elementary class that has been struck by the chicken pox virus. Super, mega, fucking gross when I see some of the participants ripping off their scabs and putting it in their mouths and eating it. Like why the hell are they doing that?



Okay Dr. Fernstein your dick isn't going anywhere. There's no need for all the scratching and grabbing it like a baseball stadium hotdog. I fucking hope he isn't ripping scabs off of his dick and eating it. Like the most bizarre blow job and hand job combined activity ever.



Well I'm about to go back to the office because I've had enough of this shit. 



Why is Moe and the manager coming out?



Damn it.



Before they even come talk to me I run to the office and oh fucking joy!



It looks like a fucked up blood bath love scene.



Larry is now gnawing on his own fingers while Curly is doing the most logical things by using a pair of scissors to cut his ears off and eating them like an entree at red lobsters. (I like entrees from Red Lobsters) 



I'm done just fucking staring so I run up to them and try to get them to stop.



What i get in return is a big hefty bite to my stomach by Curly.



What the hell Curly?



He broke through skin, but (thank God) did not get a bite off of me.



I definitely don't want to look like I got attacked by a midget shark everytime i go to a swimming pool. 



So yeah fuck that I'm not doing shit for them anymore.



Let them eat themselves. 



I use my phone to once again call 119.



Good news.



The police are on their way accompanied by the paramedics.



Bad news.



Larry has already taken out his own eyes and devoured them like they were his last meal. Afterwards, using his pocket knife to rip into his chest area. Curly has noticed this new-found meal and has proceeded to gnaw on his exposed ribs. then tearing out two of his lower ribs and slashing  Larry's midsection and his own midsection. 



Now what creeps me out the second most is the fact that they have both proceeded to tie anything they can with each other. I'm talking intestines (of course, and anything that is connecting their organs to their bodies. What creeps me out the most is that Larry is doing this fucking blind.



Well the cops have finally shown up with the paramedics and they have to send them in with one ambulance. For one blind guy and one deranged guy they have really done a good job with those knots. 



Word spread about what happened. (I came out of the office in hysterics screaming out what just fucking happened) , and that resulted in over 200 participants just turning around and exiting the conference building.



What brings everlasting joy in my heart is that the Local Organizing Committee has made the selfless decision to just finish the conference out. 



I mean who fucking cares that two of our employees just had a buffet of each other?



Me?



I can't fucking quit.



I can't leave either. 



I still need this job.



The job market sucks.



Please give me suggestions on how to deal with this.



One more fucking day.

Just one more fucking day.

Link to Part Two: https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5g1y1l/please_help_me_part_2/

Link to Part One:https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5fv6ie/please_help_me/


Link to the Final Part: https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5gf39j/please_help_mefinal/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please Help Me Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 07:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the first two days.
https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5fv6ie/please_help_me/

Well its now the third day of the conference and I have just woken up.

Its 5:30 in the morning so that gives me around 20 minutes to get ready and head out. 

So I just do the regular early morning stuff. Hop in the shower, brush my teeth, dry my hair, and put my suit on. Normal every day stuff. 

The only thing is. Every single time I start doing anything my mind keeps flashing back at the gore I witnessed last night resulting in 3 throw up sessions in between my morning routine. 

I still taste the disgusting bile in my mouth as I rush out of the hotel room.

The manager is already outside waiting on me so I hop in the car and we start driving to the conference site. It was a relatively regular car ride except for the fact that my manager would not stop scratching his hair. I mean how fucking hard is it to just wash your hair? The last thing people want to see in a formal conference setting is someone going ape shit all over their hair and have dandruff mixed into their atmosphere.

Anyways, we finally reached the conference site, and of course its completely empty because the conference doesnt start back up until 9. So we start setting up everything for the day. 

The other workers are running a bit late, but my manager and I manage to get most of it knocked out before they even arrive over an hour late. 

We have 3 other guys working with us. Ill call them Moe, Larry, and Curly for privacy sake. Moe is the guy that has by far the most experience in the conference business out of all five of us. Larry is the guy who has a decent amount of experience but is lazy as hell, and lastly Curly who is just a dumbass.


They come in and they tell us to go take a break since we got most of it done anyways so we, without complaining, go to our little office space to rest. The only thing I couldnt help but notice was that Larry has a pretty long cut alongside his eyebrow. I hope it wasnt a waxing mistake because that would be completely embarrassing. 

So we just lounge around until its time for participants to start spilling into the building. I told my manager to rest some more while I guide them into the first room. Im a nice guy plus the manager has not stopped scratching that dandruff infested hair of his. 

I start bringing in the participants and show them to the room where they will be having a little morning meeting. The speaker that was supposed to lead this meeting was the intestine eater from last night so we quickly replaced him with another speaker. 

The meeting ends well without any hiccups and now its time for their coffee break. Now that everyone has grabbed their coffees I have a second look around, and I realize that we have a lot of people scratching random parts of their bodies really roughly. 

Its far too cold for us to have a mosquito outbreak, and the chance of 80% of our participants having an allergic reaction to the same thing is really unlikely.

Ah fuck it. 

I really dont care how many guys are casually scratching their ball sacks while talking to each other. 

Second meeting. 

Goes without any problems.

Lunch.

Not a problem.

2nd Coffee break?

According to plan.

Third and Fourth Meeting?

Nothing.

So we are now finished and we all go back to the front section of the conference building and wait on the bus.

All participants present?

Check.

Buses are finally here so we start boarding all of our participants in to our buses. Each bus can hold up to 90 people so we only put 75 people in each bus so they can be as comfortable as possible. 

We get everyone loaded up and we are now ready to go back to the hotel. 

I start getting in to the passenger side of the car until I hear screaming coming from the 3rd bus.

Fuck my life. 

So I go up to the 3rd bus to see what all of the commotion is about.

Remember when I told you that the man eating his own intestines and shit was the worst thing I ever saw in my life?

Well this completely blows everything out of the fucking water.

The first thing I notice is the amount of blood that has covered the interior of the bus. 

The next thing I notice is that there are 8 people in the bus still alive, but what they are doing is giving me flashbacks from last night. They are digging in to the bodies of the dead participants and have now proceeded to rip out their large intestines and their small intestines. 

I mean its really nice seeing a group of 8 people working together so well. They have made a pile of all the small intestines and, of course, feasted on the large intestines. The bus driver makes a little gurgling sound and I look at him to see if hes still alive.

Good news.

Hes still alive.

Bad news.

He wont be for long.

His stomach is completely ripped open, and I can see the bite marks all around his intestines. What really bothered me is the fact that all of his fingers and toes have been bitten off and used as plugs for the various organs and intestines that have been left exposed by the chunks they have feasted off of. 

Well thats just fucked up so I cant keep looking, and I turn around to see what the other guys are doing. They have ingested the rest of the large intestines and have started twirling the small intestine around their bodies. 

So.

Fuck that.

I get off the bus and call 119. (Korean Emergency Number)

Then get in the car with my manager and wait for the cops.

The police and ambulance finally arrive, and arrest the intestine covered participants and take the dead participants in the ambulance.

Nothing else to do but go back to the hotel.

We called the Local Organizing Committee when we got back and explained out everything and asking if we can just stop this conference and try again next year. 

They want us to keep going because after all. They paid money, and if the other participants are still okay to keep going they will continue the conference.

The other participants just think it was some satanic ritual performed by 8 fucked up people, and they are all completely willing to continue the conference.

Two more days to go and I have none of my questions answered.

What the fuck is causing all of this.

Why is everyone scratching themselves so much?

Does it have anything to do with the scratching?

I dont know.

Fuck it.

Two more days.

Link to Part Three: https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5g92uz/please_help_me_part_3/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please Help Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 07:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the 3rd Day
https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5g1y1l/please_help_me_part_2/

Alright guys, 
Im going to need a little bit of help on this one. You can call me Glenn since everyone messes up my name anyways, and I am a run of the mill Korean male. I work in an office, I have a child, a wife, and I am neither great nor bad at what I do. I work for an office that organizes conferences, and after we are organizing said conference we go to that conference and basically make sure everything is run smoothly and efficiently.

So we have finished organizing a conference for aeronautical sciences, and we have now arrived at the conference site which is around 3 hours from our office. So, after the conference we stay at the same hotel most of our participants reside in for the next 5 days. 

The first day of the conference goes by without a hiccup. We have the same bullshit welcome reception where basically old people try to get a bunch of young enthusiasts pumped up for the next week. Then a coffee and tea break where participants make mindless chitchat about the countries they are from and what they do in their amazing new la-di-da fucking job. Then a bunch of lectures and then another coffee break, and then more lectures, then done.
 
Simple.

Seriously, as long as it has been well organized prior to the conference it is a relatively simple week. Minus moving a bunch of stuff and working off of around 5 hours of sleep.

We all get back to the hotel and celebrate by drinking cheap Korean liquor called Soju which is only around a dollar here, and commend each other for a job well done. 

Then sleep.

The rest of the week should go the same way the first day went.
I didnt even notice that there was anything off until lunch the next day.

I mean Im tired and the lack of sleep is already affecting me the second day of the conference, but the first thing I noticed was the absolute lack of conversation. I mean there is well over 1300 people here and the room where lunch is taking place is completely quiet.

I look around the room and I cant help but stare.

Everyone is in perfect sync. They are all chewing at the same exact time. Then raising their fork, and then lowering the fork into the bowl of salad. Putting the salad in their mouth and chewing at the Same. Exact. Time. 

What the actual fuck.

I dont know whats going on but Im absolutely starving so I shove whatever is left on my plate in my mouth and leave.
I go out to where the organizers office is and I see my coworkers steadily tapping away at their computers. Relief floods me because I notice theyre all working at a completely different pace so I know theyre unaffected by whatever the fucks going on.

So I go up to the manager and describe out the scene I just witnessed. 

He thinks its odd but nothing to get completely worried over so I let it slide for now. 

The rest of the day goes by and I have dismissed what happened at lunch as just an odd coincidence.

Back at the hotel now and the manager and I are just relaxing with the TV on. 

My eyes are starting to feel heavy so Im about to fall asleep until I hear a loud scream down the hall on our floor. 

I look at the manager and hes already giving me a weird look signifying he heard the scream too.

So we go outside of our room and what I see next was the worst thing I have ever seen in my life.

One of the speakers for the conference is lying on the hotel floor literally ripping the side of his mouth. His stomach is already ripped open with a pool of intestines spilling out of his open suit. We try to stop him, but every time we get close he kicks us back and proceeds to slowly split the right side of his mouth. Im now just frantically begging him to stop, but he just wont. He has now ripped his mouth to the point to where the rip has reached the bottom of his earlobe and has now started on the other side of his mouth.

Good news. 

The police and paramedics arrived shortly after him starting on the second rip. 

Bad news.

Before they could even stop him he has started to eat the intestines that were protruding out from his stomach, and by the time they did stop him he already chewed through a lot of his large intestines.

After he is carted away by frantic paramedics the manager and I have decided to go back to our room.

So thats what has happened so far. Its only the second day of the conference and we have 3 more days to go. 

So why exactly did he do that?

Is it connected to the lunch scene I witnessed earlier?

Is there anything I can fucking do?

What the fuck is going on?

Help me please.


Next Day
https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5g1y1l/please_help_me_part_2/

Edit: Placed link for the next day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
