<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8542</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 14:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sort of, yes. It was actually originally called "borderline" because psychiatrists thought that people with BPD straddled the border between psychosis and neurosis, but we now know that BPD is largely caused by one's childhood environment (abusive parents, caregiver neglect, sexual trauma, you get the idea). 

For instance, I was raised in a radically pentecostal home (almost a cult; think "Jesus Camp" type of stuff). Being brought up with the belief that heaven is this supremely unattainable prize and that hell is a place of unimaginable suffering (a place where all of my friends were supposedly going, no less) caused me to think in very black-and-white terms from the time I was a toddler.

Black-and-white thinking is a hallmark symptom of BPD (hence the popular BPD book title, "I Hate You, Don't Leave Me!"), and so my own personal diagnosis of this illness can be traced back to those childhood beliefs. You get the idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 14:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! I have BPD. I was formally diagnosed around 2 years ago, but have lived with its symptoms for about a decade. 

The psychiatric community is actually moving away from the "borderline" terminology; the more accurate and up-and-coming title is "emotional intensity disorder." 

Put simply, a popular metaphor to describe BPD is to imagine that we have 3rd-degree burns covering our "emotional skin," and so we are very sensitive to the world around us. We feel emotions very deeply, rapidly, and intensely; both good AND bad ones. This intensity makes the good feel VERY good (i.e., I cry when I see a cute dog) and the bad feel VERY bad (i.e., I thought I wanted to die when my 9th grade crush didn't like me back.)

Interestingly enough, dialectical behavioral therapy (the most widely-used method of treating BPD) is what really brought me to Buddhism. DBT teaches us to use mindfulness to examine these very severe emotions, so that we are better able to control them. So, it promotes mindful thinking, meditation, analyzing the inner workings of ourselves, and a lot of other habits that align with Buddhism. 

I hope this helped a bit. I am actually currently studying to be a mental health counselor, and have been in DBT therapy for over a year. Let me know if any of this does not make sense. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I do suppose that 21 years of experience would make you credible on this, lol. I'm definitely keeping them in mind. I will say that I felt very "right" being there, for lack of a better word. The Dharma talk deeply resonated with me and with some of my personal experiences. 

I'm only living in NYC for a couple more weeks, so I plan on visiting a few other places. But NKT did have a lot of things that I liked, and I know that they're quite easy to find in metropolitan areas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's super helpful to know. I actually found out that they have "Meditation 101" classes tonight for people to get acquainted with their practices and the center. I'm going to head there after work. Will definitely share my thoughts. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Will definitely do some research on that. I know that I'll most likely be in NYC and Boston over the next year, and both of those places seem to have a relatively large amount of resources. It's just a matter of sifting through all of them and finding the one that feels best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 16:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if this is consistent with all of their centers, but I did some more research into the NYC branch and they offer a "generosity policy" that allows you to pay a smaller fee/no fee, if your financial circumstances otherwise prevent you from attending. And in my case, full-time volunteer work leaves a lot to be desired when it comes to income, so I'd be interested in utilizing such a policy. 

Of course, once I do find a community that seems to feel right for me, I also plan on offering volunteer work as compensation. I have professional training in photography and graphic design, so I'm hoping that I can use those skills wherever I end up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 16:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair point; that's kind of where I'm torn. Like I said in another comment, I really enjoyed the NKT service that I attended this past weekend, but it's difficult to ignore all of the dissenting material that exists against them.

Do you have personal experience with any of these organizations? Just curious. The firsthand accounts I've found are very polarizing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 04:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right; it actually seems to carry the least negative stigma of the examples I listed. A few questionable articles here and there, but I imagine that to be typical for just about any tradition. 

My only issue is that the NYC center's classes are pretty expensive, but I don't believe their meditation and Dharma talks are anymore than a $10 suggested donation. I'm thinking of going to one of their beginner sessions tomorrow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 23:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not entirely positive, to be honest. So far, Tibetan Buddhism seems to be the best fit for me from what I know about it.

I actually tried the New Kadampa Center in NYC and really enjoyed the dharma talk, the structure of the service, the atmosphere, etc. But again, there seems to be a lot of negativity surrounding the NKT (and any other modern, Westernized Buddhist tradition, really), so I'm hesitant to commit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to find a consistent Buddhist community when you travel a lot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 19:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, everyone. So, I travel all over the United States doing volunteer and humanitarian work for a living. I've been studying Buddhism independently on and off for the past couple of years, and am starting to become serious about making it a central focus in my life. I'm stationed in New York City for the next month, and so I'm trying to take advantage of all the different resources that are available to me, but I've run into a problem: I don't know which community or temple to join, just because I travel so much. 

I know that centers like New Kadampa, Shambhala, Diamond Way, etc. are easy to find across the country, but these very large organizations don't seem to be without considerable negative controversy that I'm not sure I want to get involved in, and I don't know if I'm willing to overlook some of their more questionable politics just for the sake of convenience. 

Does anyone know of any other large groups that are easy to find throughout the country? I'm not quite sure which particular tradition I would like to study yet, so I'm open to any and all suggestion. This is my first post, and I've only recently begun to seriously look into Buddhism, so I'm still learning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
