<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9680</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 05:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You owe me five! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 05:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know he's a postman, don't you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 02:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got one of these and I can't wait for it arrive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 02:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was able to get the price down! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 12:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I hadn't thought about it but I suppose I'd be open to hearing any trade offers. The Miller is a size medium but my others are larges.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 03:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More than I'd like to pay for sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legit Check - Lemieux jersey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 04:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 04:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright I'll get ya a Mounds bar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 04:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think people will still be using napkins in the year two-thousand? Or is this mouth-vacuum thing for real? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 03:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picked up the complete series Amazon deal of the day that was posted in the sub recently. Glad to finally have the dvd's, lots of cool extras.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 17:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minnesota has awesome jerseys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 16:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was pretty excited when he was traded to the Sabres. He's started to really turn it on lately after a slower start to the season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 16:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome! Great gift. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 15:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great collection! I love the old Pens jerseys. I see those older Lemieux jerseys on eBay all the time for cheap but it makes me worried it might not be legit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 15:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!! I was glad it was available, you wouldn't believe how many Seinfeld names are taken on here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 07:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wondered where the fresh bun came from for the extremely old hot dog  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 07:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you'rrree the ass man?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 07:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gave someone the Kramer for Christmas, they loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 07:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 06:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like most Sabres fans I've always been a big fan of the blue and gold jerseys, but as I've gotten older I grew to appreciate the goat head jerseys much more. My only aud experience was actually the unveiling of those jerseys since I was still pretty young when they were playing there. The alternate red jersey with the swords was awesome, I wish they would have kept it even after they got rid of the goat jerseys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 00:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Once I got it in the mail I knew something was off with it. Wish I knew about this sub before making the purchase.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 00:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got that one pretty cheap fortunately. Disappointed to hear this is a fake though!  Have you seen fakes with the fighting strap before?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 22:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I began collecting hockey jerseys in the last year and have put a respectable collection together. Would like to get some more 90's jerseys into the collection. 

Can anyone help confirm whether the team USA Kane jersey is legit? I got it on eBay earlier this year and have some doubts whether it's legit or not. The sizing seems to be off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hockey jersey collection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 22:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 20:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That 4xl was in the store forever. It's an awesome jersey but I just didn't want to spend too much on a blank Americans jersey when they had more sizes in stock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 05:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also recall him eating a giant sucker in "The Betrayal".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 05:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How ya like your bagels now?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 01:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking Charlize Theron possibly for Sue Ellen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 01:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely agree. I've been thinking about this throughout the season and I think it's become pretty clear O'Reilly is next in line. Last season I was wondering if Girgensons may get the C at some time in the next couple years, but it doesn't look that way anymore. I don't really think there's a great choice afterward, players like Gorges or Moulson are not realistic. The others that might be good are still a few years off in their careers from reaching that level.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 23:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful landscaping  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 06:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the homeless don't want them, the homeless don't have to eat them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 04:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh come on Clarkman!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 04:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's got a lot of time on his hands these days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 05:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two races of flavor living side by side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 03:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a fan of how he pronounces "Geergensons" myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bylsma Shootout Choices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 21:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else notice Bylsma consistently making questionable shootout choices this year? I've seen a lot of Moulson and Gionta. In today's game, he puts in Girgensons as the last shooter to tie the shootout when Eichel, Kane and Reinhart hadn't even shot yet. I really like Girgensons, but there were much better shooters available.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 20:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mind Ray, I'm kind of indifferent with him. He's serviceable. I think Brad May is pretty terrible but has gotten a little better from when he started. The game when Marty Biron took his place was great, I wish he could just take over for May.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 18:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gender Studies major </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 17:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm also in the minority of people that think the last episode was great. They brought back so many of the great minor characters that the group had wronged throughout the series. Jerry and George are on the merge of having a successful TV show, only to have it taken away. Great references to situations they encountered throughout the series. I also wasn't left feeling as though there could have been more to offer fans, they wrapped up the series on their owns terms and without leaving a lot of unanswered questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 05:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never saw someone possessed before?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 05:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still don't get why people were so upset over him holding a stack of money next to his ear in Vegas. Glad to have him on the Sabres.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 05:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that Meryl Streep, she's such a phony bologny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 04:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother used to see Enroth around Buffalo frequently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 04:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horrifying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bullet Proof? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 04:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 04:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some were original airings, I think others were reruns but while the show was still on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 03:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks awesome. Wish they would set this up somewhere closer so I could check it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 03:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The syndicated episodes sometimes don't have all the content that was in the original episodes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 03:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ordered. Sent this deal to about a dozen other people too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 02:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may still have all the VHS tapes my brother taped all the episodes off TV with if you're interested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 20:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an awesome deal. I can stream the series with Hulu now, but it might be worth it just to pick this up in case they get rid of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 20:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do the karate, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 13:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe spacing the posts out a bit would be a good approach. Gives people something to look forward to!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 12:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the talent we have and prospects in the system, I'm not sure we could afford to make another big splash and pick up someone like Stamkos without hurting our future a bit. I'd prefer to stay patient by developing who we have and continue to draft well. Stamkos' contract could hurt us down the road when we have to sign Risto, Eichel, Reinhart, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 12:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bit too young I think. We had Rob Reiner lined up but I'm sure there's some other options out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good luck on the pilot, Jerry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 05:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 04:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 04:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was the best part of that trade! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 04:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer he upper 100's and the 200's based on the view. Lower 300's are good too. You can honestly see well anywhere you are in the arena though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 04:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have, it looks terrible. I contributed to that though?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 04:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For what Murray gave up for Lehner, there's no way he's not going to play the bulk of the games. Agreed on Ullmark being sent down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 04:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pardon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 04:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome game from Johnson. Will this be the loss when Boudreau finally gets fired? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 23:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad lighting on the porch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 20:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was tough finding a good Sue Ellen. We did cast Danny Devito for Mickey, but Warwick would be a great choice too. 

Still looking for a Slippery Pete!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who would be cast in a Seinfeld movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 12:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Years ago my brother and I talked about if a Seinfeld movie were ever made, what "bigger" actors/actresses would potentially be cast to play minor roles. We came up with this list of potential actors that could play minor parts of characters who either appeared in episodes or were referenced throughout the series. Did we get any of them wrong? Help us fill in the blanks.    
Ray/Cedric, street toughs - Antonio Banderas and Rick Moranis  
OTB employees - James Woods and Jack Black  
Joe from Joe's Fruit Stand - Robert de Niro  
Jean Paul - Dave Chapelle  
Seth, Jerrys friend from college - Louis CK  
Lloyd Braun - Pierce Brosnan  
Cousin Jeffrey - John Kerry  
Sid the car parker - Sherman Helmsley  
Joe Davola - Gary Busey or Mel Gibson  
Jeffrey Harharwood- Ian McKellen  
Bob Sacamano - Steve Buscemi  
Lomez - Cheech Marin  
Martin Jerry's neighbor - Danny Trejo  
Mickey - Danny Devito  
Jiffy Park/Jiffy Dump employee - Sylvester Stallone  
Alec Berg - Alec Baldwin  
The sidler - Bill Paxton  
Mr. Morgan - Tim Meadows  
Conrad, Connie or Con - Kurt Russel  
Mario the Pizza Parlor owner - Frank Vincent  
Babu Bhatt - Gerry Bednob  
Maroon Golf - Denzel Washington  
Sue Ellen Mischke - Jennifer Aniston  
Joe Mayo - Matthew Perry  
Franklin Delano Romanowski - Meat Loaf  
Karl, the exterminator - Danny Glover  
Deena, Georges childhood friend - Kirstie Alley  
The Drake - Luke Wilson  
Marcelino - Miguel Sandoval (same actor, he was perfect)  
Nana - Betty White  
Ping - Jet Li or Ken Jeong  
Rabbi Glickman - David Schwimmer  
Shlomo - Rob Reiner  
Rebecca DeMornay - Queen Latifah  
Jimmy - Woody Harrelson or Michael Keaton  
Mr. Pitt - Michael Caine  
Paisanos employee - Al Pacino  
Craig (Elaines former boyfriend) - Jason Statham  
Simon (Elaines sleazy British boyfriend) - Sting  
Stan the Caddy - Steve Martin   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
