<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4153</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 06:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reliability, if it's going to break without me enjoying the product than why bother ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 06:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Less about money and more about who you've let go and why.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 06:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you suck on rocks when no ones looking, don't leave (insert name here) alone outside. They'll suck on rocks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 06:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't trust your self, periodically self evaluate your self from the least bias position you possibility can or have some one else do it if you're not capable. You're blind to your own faults, and that's okay. Just remember to check your self on a regular basis.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 18:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the truth, my partner makes me strong because we challenge each other to be better. She is strong where i am weak and vice versa, that'w why we chose eachother. Because picking some one to burn out the rest of your years with is so much deeper than the bull shot romantic comedeys let on. And yea, the Cinderella nod was punny purposefully.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 13:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disney lied to you, none of us are these cookie cutter puppets here to save you. We want partners. Happily after doesn't just happen, Cinderella probably got on the Prince over leaving his shoes lying around. Small disagreements will happen and that's fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 06:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand what you meant in the first place. I'm unfamiliar, elaborate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 06:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be jealous of no one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 06:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand, I never said I served in any kind of military. Just some target shooter with a hunting license.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 06:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an excellent example. Once you see proof of intent it kind of makes the action.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 06:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot, you see awful people donating to sound foundations. Donating their time and effort and lending a hand to some one in need. But there is always a hidden intention or something ti gain. Some one to impress, wool to hide the wolf.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 06:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally had to take a break from reddit after posting that. My cursor hovered over cancel for a minute before I hit save.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 05:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Re-live implies that i lived it to begin with. I lost a brother back in 2012 April 1st. A few months before his passing we had a pretty good bonfire with friends and family. I hate that he went into the darkness alone, how ever strong he was for me he was afraid of the dark more than he'd like to admit. I'd relive a fantastic day with him and follow him into the darkness, what ever waits for me on the other side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 05:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, but kindness is such a broad answer. There are plenty of bad people that can display kindness. To easy to fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 05:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be an amazing moment to travel back to. Imagine witnessing an early human find rhythm and sing the first tunes to another. The emotion coming from that interaction is so priceless, they could never have imagined everything that came after. Gold and the garbage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 05:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people are taking this as a question regarding what attributes make up a good partner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 05:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> another good one, the right thing to do often times isn't easy. Watching someone make the hard choice at their own cost in the name of what is right is a pretty good indicator.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 05:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, often times you see people so blindly caught up in them selves that they fail to see that there is an entirely different mindset behind every action that they contest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 05:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also a good one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 05:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this one, any new person you meet diserves respect until they loose that right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 05:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some times after a good look in the mirror I go through a sort of.. self evaluation. I look at my atributes and my actions and I really don't know if I can classify my self as a good person.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 05:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've made a killing shot on a pig with a long gun at close to two hundred yards. If some one irreparably assaulted or killed a loved one. I'd claim them in plain sight where they felt safe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What are qualities that you believe make a genuinely good person ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 05:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 01:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to lie. I studied the new testament from age 15-17 reluctantly. outside of that i have only bites of information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 00:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea... but than we have to validate the mormons.. and the protestants... and the Jehovah's witnesses... they all clash. it's tough  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 23:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> try..  ZOMBEH MOOSE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> plus jesus wasn't immortal. If i could do that i'd start there.. jesus didn't have to square off with missiles or high powered rifles.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That could have been one of the choices jesus had, he had god's powers but never exercised the wrath. I wanted to see the wrath.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if a choice needed to be made within the decade ?  you either needed to bring about earth's end, or die for our sins.  or maybe find another suitable way to pay for our sins.. annual human sacrifice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wut.. ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> above all else i want to see a jesus that exercises the wrath of god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, i want it to be dark and gritty...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right ? I feel like bruce almighty made a good comedy out of this concept, but i want a gritty mini-series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a stoner messiah, that would be unlucky hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets say that the sacrifice of jesus has expired and you now have to choose to either bring about the end of the remaining humans. Or find a suitable sacrifice so that our sins are "paid for" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what do you mean ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's not the point, the point is that you your self present day have been born the sibling of christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (you can either answer from a religious standpoint or entertain the thought of being another theist being the sibling of christ)  I haven't studied the bible in for ever, but God spoke to jesus in his early twenties. Before that he was just your average shmuck living day to day, just like you or me. But after god spoke to him he began to display the powers of god. Which we have seen first hand can either be full of wrath or love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If god spoke to you and let you know that you were to sibling of Jesus Christ, would you be the next savior ? or the Antichrist ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see why you would make that comparison. But it would be so much more interesting in a galaxy not so far away. I'd make it stray away from the happenings of jesus but similar plot points would be there. 

Maybe you reveal to a friend that later turns out to be a judas, the US military would serve as perfect stand in for the romans. and at the end they can choose to end the world right here and now, or die for us so that we may continue existing in our cycle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take it back, i'd like to get a text message at an unimportant part of their day once a week and than be able to control their body for five seconds. 

Girlfriend excuses herself to the bathroom during a dinner and BAM !! I pour my beverage into her purse. Toss my phone over a balcony, take the steak knife and cut off a lock of hair, than shit myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right ?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that cold actually lead to serious issues with your feet. that may even end up crippling them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> once a year they lose control of a bowel movement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said i didn't want an opinion, i was just stating that yours wasn't a fact. and i offered and opposing view to provoke further conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 22:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M16oW9idZbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ The Second Coming ] (forgive me because it's been a long time since i've studied the bible)

Jesus was in his early twenties when god revealed to him that he was his son right ?  Well through drunken bondfire talk we've gathered that there is really nothing stopping god from choosing another child right ?  

the story follows a random twenty something (male or female) that wakes up one day to the booming voice of god. This person is told that they will be granted more and more of god's powers as the days pass. and that they have to decide if the fate of humanity. 

the salvation from the act of jesus has expired and time has come again to decide whether or not we are worthy. So the story follows this character and they can choose to become the second comming of Jesus or the Antichrist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd max out on happiness, if i've stripped everyone of their wealth i'd summon the greatest minds to see if I could coral these humans into a state of mind where we can stop share, co-operate, and move forward as a species. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vanity my friend, there is no better fuel for the ego than a horde of sheeple giving you an encouraging  "bahh !" every time you show your self publicly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend and I share an apartment. Biggest animal I can get is a cat, I she'd appreciate that project when we buy a home though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right ? just because it CAN eat an animal that big doesn't mean that it's the appropriate food source for regular feeding. The only big difference i've seen with the piranha is that the mouse does tend to typically drown before a killing blow is struck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Convince them that they'll get likes and retweets. that tactic is working all around every first world right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheese cake is love, cheese cake is life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm both, a woman can be put in a multitude of situations where abortion is the rational choice to salvage a quality life for herself and loved ones. And death can only be paid with death, I wouldn't even mind if violent sex offenders got the death penalty for the murder of innocence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what i was waiting for. I used to feed my snake and i was always worried that if he landed a miss on a mouse head that he'd loose an eye in the fight. I'm less worried about the piranha though. the numbers definitely make it a one sided fight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean.. that's an opinion, and don't get me wrong. I can see where it comes from, it's just that the fish naturally would feed on a live animal. They like it, you can see the difference between a frozen feeding and a live one. Nature is a cruel shrew.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people will beat a pop song like a dead horse than pretend they never liked a year later after 50+ have taken its place.I love to check out the local scene, california is good for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont feed my bearded dragon frozen or dried crickets/superworms. He loves live food, it's dinner and entertainment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, store bought feeders are almost never a risk. maybe you can argue that a frozen mice doesn't contaminate the water with fur but a strong tank filter will take care of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pop music, the masses go bananas over some garbage song and I can't go anywhere without drowning in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're illegal in my state, but why are they weird ? as far as fish go i'd say they're pretty cool. I'm not really a fish guy my self.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where does that thought process come from ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been raising a bearded dragon so youtube recommended a video where a piranha owner feeds his fish live mice. Now I have friends with snakes, lizards, and frogs so a live feeding isn't really taboo. But the the whole  comments section on this feeding video blew up.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think it's ethical to feed a live feeder mouse to pet piranhas ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 21:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 20:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you have a steam account ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 20:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a mask for airsoft originally to protect my face after a witnessed a friend get a tooth shot out. Now I wont wear anything else because I am vicious with it on. Every now and again some one will look my way and shrink back into cover because they can't see my eyes and assumed i spotted them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 20:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "The Devil is real and hes not some little red man with horns and a tail. He can be beautiful because he's a fallen angel and he used to be God's favorite."
 - American Horror Story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 20:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm out of california. my steamtag is zombehmoose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 20:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pacific standard time
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 20:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> message me with your steam accounts if you guys still play
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 20:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a friend of mine and i were talking about a game type where 5+ players use the yacht with mini guns and rpgs. while fighting off hydras with non-lock missiles and chain-gun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 20:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do either of you have mics ? I just ditched my 360 and GTAV is the best. but i need gtav buddies with mics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PC] Does anyone have an active crew that is available from 5pm to 9pm for heists and shenanigans ? and that use mics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 20:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Built my PC up after ditching my 360 and GTAV is currently my most active game. is anyone a member of a crew or know of any active crews that use mics ?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 06:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This world has tought me that fair is not always necessarily fair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 04:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> History has taught us that the strong man doesn't let evil deeds go uncontested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 04:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calm, cool, collected, and patient are the traits that mark the victor. Keep it smart and wait for the right moment and i'm sure you'll be fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 04:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some things can be done to you that make life not worth living.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 04:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right ? My childhood entertainment forms of media taught me that the bad get what's coming to them. Than I grow and time and time again i see the good guy getting shafted by the douche bag with little to no repercussion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 04:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fine, but if the law failed to catch up with some one and they've wronged your irreparably why should they just get off free ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 04:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've personally always felt that the whole "eye for an eye makes the whole world blind" motto lacked the blanket affect for every day situations. If you purposefully put out one of my eyes I want your whole head, not just one eye.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Do you feel that revenge is worth pursuing ? Why or why not ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 04:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 06:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are all assuming that you're in the passenger seat. when it comes to my safety around my friends and anyone that i let drive me i dont mind taking their phone and tossing it in the back seat. I'm talking about a driver you encounter in a separate car while you yourself are driving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 06:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly why i wanted to talk about this. I lost an ex to a drunk driver and it seems like the drunks coupled with the smart phone zombies make driving one a friday through sunday a game of russian roulette.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 06:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea but the punch to the neck might drive home a lesson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 06:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feels like i'd be doing it all day. How often do you encounter it ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 06:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's sad but this would make a great bumper sticker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 06:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would not believe how poorly recieved that is. No matter how civil you go about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 06:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish, a 22 to the rear tire might teach them a lesson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 06:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was behind a woman at a red light earlier this week when I noticed she was on her phone. I honked and she looked up and around with an expression that said "He must be honking at some one else, i'm clearly doing nothing wrong,".

When the light turned green she didn't make it much more that 100m before she pulled into her left lane so much so that the driver next to her had to get out of the way so that they didn't get mashed into a concrete divider. When we got to the next red light i honked at her and motioned for her to roll down her window. I tried to maintain my composure and said " hey, you need to get off your phone ! you nearly killed some one!".

This didn't sit well with her "fuck you ! don't tell me how to drive faggot !!," she replied.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What is a socially acceptable way to get some one to get off their phone while they're driving ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 06:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 23:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An ex of mine practically lived off of take out and microwave meals. She flaunted me in front of her friends constantly as a chef. Each and every time I'd say something like "I can make spaghetti and I know how not to burn a steak i guess" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What has been the most redeeming moment in your life so far ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 22:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 22:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to send in for these book order catalogs in elementary school. and the week long waiting period for them to arive seemed to last for ever. I still get that feeling anytime i order anything that's entertainment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
