<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3080</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today's delivery. Jameson Caskmates. Limited edition Jameson aged in stout barrels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 01:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American cant handle bad review of local food. "You. You're an example of an obnoxious Irish piece of shit. Don't think for one second that you're better than me because you're Irish." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 13:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did you know that Christopher Hitchens did not like Dracula? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 01:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Club: October Discussion god is not Great: How religion Poisons Everything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 00:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the delay folks. Real life and all that jazz.

Original thread with full timeline is here: http://www.reddit.com/r/ChristopherHitchens/comments/2orcp8/hitchens_book_club_proposed_timetable_input/

This month we are focusing on god is not Great: How religion Poisons Everything, a book that actually needs no introduction.

If you haven't read this book before, you're in for a real treat.

This is one of my favorite books written by Christopher, and it's his best seller. He toured the bible belt debating every person who challenged him, and destroyed all of them. 

His chapter on Islam is timeless, and is really needed presently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd fight to the death. It's a right that they should not have the power to take from me. It's symbolic in my mind also </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 13:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any opinions on this Danby 50 bottle wine cooler? Model # DWC508BLS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 23:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link here: http://www.bestbuy.com/site/danby-wine-cooler/4580021.p?id=1218492389818 skuId=4580021

My budget is around $600.

I'm looking to store wine for 4 - 5 years, before building my own cellar. 

Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm as far from a connoisseur as you can get. I just found this chart. Does this mean I've been drinking wine I should be aging? (2014/13/12 Chteauneuf-du-Pape) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 04:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are all the BBQ places around here absolutely awful? Is there anything comparable to BBQ in Texas? I'm almost sick of looking at this stage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 02:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jihad in the Workplace: Looking Back on the Fort Hood Shooting by Alexander Hitchens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 00:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got 30 sods of turf delivered to my gaff in the USA. Decent sods too. Fucking delighted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 19:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ian Madigan hails fantastic reception from Irish supporters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 16:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made some Hitchens Wallpapers (one more in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 15:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello Kurds! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 01:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christopher Hitchens was a big supporter of Kurdistan. He would often wear a Kurdistan flag on his lapel. Being a fan of Christopher's writing, I started doing this when I moved to America from Ireland in 2011. Whenever I go out to dinner, I wear the flag of the Kurds in solidarity with Kurdistan's fight for independence. 

I'm currently reading a book by Aliza Marcus titled "Blood and Belief: The PKK and the Kurdish Fight for Independence".

I'm about half way through, and the book is interesting to say the least. Up until now I was not too familiar with the PKK, or Ocalan.

I have some questions which I hope you will help me by answering:  

1. Have any of you read this book? 
2. If yes, how accurate is it? 
3. Can you recommend any other books on Kurdistan's history to help me familiarize myself with you wonderful people   culture.

Thanks for listening. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something that people do on Reddit that annoys you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 14:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I finally got my act together. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 18:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I moved to America in 2011 I was in the shape of my life. I was 140lbs and fairly ripped. Due to a car crash in 2003, I have pretty bad arthritis in my back which has prevented me from working out as much as I would like. I used to run 10km (6.2 miles) per day, box 5 times a week, and lift 5 times a week. 

That was all blown away, and I gained 40lbs from 2011 up to August of this year. My drinking increased, as did eating crappy food. I was a mess and depressed because I couldn't work out anymore.

Anyway, I cut out the booze completely, cleaned up my diet and I'm back in the gym. The only thing I can do without setting off my arthritis right now is cycling, so I'm doing that but once the gut is lifted I'll be able to do more.

I've lost 11 pounds since September 1st and I'm feeling amazing. This is something I've wanted to do for ages but I kept putting it off because I like whiskey, wine and beer a lot haha.

But as of now I am off the booze, and not allowed to touch it again until I'm back down at 140 pounds, and even then it will be a very strict intake.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Lord works in mysterious ways" -- response to church shooting in Alabama. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 03:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL 22 US veterans kill themselves every day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 02:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a town in Tennessee hung a 5 ton elephant in 1916 for killing a trainer at a Circus (thanks to /u/Kjfitz) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 19:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the craziest true story from your home town? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 16:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minimalist photo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 21:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any love for P.G. Wodehouse's Bertie Wooster and Jeeves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 18:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Luke Skywalker joins locals in Irish bar while taking time out from filming Star Wars 8. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 16:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by taking 3 times the recommended daily dose of miralax in one go </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 06:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a fucked up back. Pretty bad degenerative arthritis. My doctor has me on some strong opiates to help with the pain. Opiates, if you're familiar with them, cause constipation. 

Today my doctor told me to try miralax to help soften things up and get things moving again. 

For whatever fucking reason, I misread the instructions and put 3 generous cap fulls into a pint of orange juice.

Within ten minutes things were moving alright, and haven't fucking stopped since. That was over eight hours ago. I haven't eaten in an attempt to stop this (no digestion should equal no shit).

I've literally been pissing out of my ass for what can be described as a full working day. I just hope it stops by tomorrow night because I'm supposed to be taking my wife to the theatre. I'm really lucky I can work from home. 

If I do manage to sleep tonight I really hope I don't fucking shit in the bed. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens on Charlie Rose - "god is not Great"   Iraq war (May 4, 2007) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 00:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm no longer banned from playing in magic tournaments. I have risen from the ashes to defend my honor against the scrubs of Earth. Prepare yourselves. [r/pics by u/OB1FBM] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 21:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made some Hitchens Wallpapers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 03:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walmart is getting a gas station. If you get a Walmart credit card you'll get 15 cents off every gallon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 01:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/LifeWithoutIgor should redirect to Reddit's main page </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 01:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greg Grandin "The Trial of Henry Kissinger isnt very useful and is actually counterproductive; righteous indignation doesnt provide much room for understanding" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 01:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL according to a CNN politics poll, 29% of Americans say they think the President is a Muslim, including 43% of Republicans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 01:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Carolina magistrates opt out of performing same-sex marriages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 03:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great essay by Lawrence Krauss regarding Kim Davis and religious freedom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 01:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great essay by Lawrence Krauss regarding Kim Davis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 01:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salman Rushdie on his latest book: It might be the funniest of my novels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 01:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You pronounce the 's' in Kansas. Why don't you pronounce the 's' in Arkansas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 23:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man described by judge as "nightmare on the streets" with 96 previous convictions breaks cops nose and only gets 8 months in jail. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 19:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sharia Law is a tautology. It's just sharia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 05:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats your favourite snack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 01:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never be afraid of stridency: Richard Dawkins last interview with Christopher Hitchens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 20:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went to see Jim Jeffries last night.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 14:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping this makes his DVD as he said they were recording. A yank shouted that the Australians were only free because of America.

Jim schooled him so bad the guy fucking ran away. It was glorious.

"You cunts showed up late to WW2 and are responsible for the deaths of thousands, if not more. Morally reprehensible.". 

"One percent of your population is behind bars. Higher than anywhere else. That's not freedom.". 

"In Holland I can fuck a prostitute and do lines of coke off her back while talking to a cop. Holland has more freedom than America.". 

He said a lot more but i dont want to ruin the DVD. 

Best bit was when he ran off with his wife following. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Club: September Discussion Thomas Paine's "Rights of Man" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 00:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original thread with full timeline is here: http://www.reddit.com/r/ChristopherHitchens/comments/2orcp8/hitchens_book_club_proposed_timetable_input/

This month we are focusing on Hitch's book on Thomas Paine's "Rights of Man".

This is a wonderful follow up to last months book about Jefferson. Like last month, this is a quick read but deeply fascinating. 

I don't have time for much more of a write up as I'm working like crazy for the next while.

As always - enjoy!

P.S god is not Great next month! :D

P.P.S enjoy this lecture: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MWxpkcQUCeo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stay classy North Carolina. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 04:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Atheist Son of a Jewish Rabbi Created One of the Greatest Libraries of Socialist Literature </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 04:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In response to 40,000 people dying yearly due to being unable to afford medical treatment; "It was their own ignorance that made them not get medical attention" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 03:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most fucked up thing you saw in a sorority or fraternity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 02:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jesus was a Palestinian. Given that US Christians support what Israel is doing in Palestine (stealing land, etc).... is this not hypocritical? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 19:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manslaughter is mans-laughter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 21:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best name you can think of for a music band/group? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 19:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's an instant turn off for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 01:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rock Harbor Grill in Apex is being forced to close. The owner of the building gave the lease to someone else. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 16:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rock Harbor Grill in Apex is being forced to close. The owner of the building gave the lease to someone else. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 16:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TWC Maxx is available in Apex from October 2nd. Go here to request a new modem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 22:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check this gorgeous fella out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 18:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens - Diana The Mourning After [1998] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 06:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher HItchens on Firing Line with William F. Buckley Jr. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 05:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens on the Death of Diana, Princess of Wales (1997) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 05:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> College Students Refuse To Read Award-Winning Novel Because It Violates Their Christian Beliefs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 00:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> College Students Refuse To Read Award-Winning Novel Because It Violates Their Christian Beliefs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 00:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An appeal for sanity! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 17:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been said when a butterfly flaps its wings in one part of the world it can cause a hurricane in another part of the world... what do you think is happening when all the Gentlesirs tip their fedoras? 

Are the present day neckbeards responsible for the rise in natural disasters?

Do the responsible thing. Steal the next fedora you see! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A picture of the rail network in Ireland, demonstrating the impact partition can have on a tiny island. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 17:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's things I look back on from my religious days and I just fucking cringe so bad. Looking back on when you were religious, what's something that happened that makes you feel that way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 01:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm so hungover me hair hurts. Registered fuckcromwell.net when drunk last night. Awkward. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 15:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most fucked up thing you observed or experienced at school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 03:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Ma is visiting from Ireland. Some surprise she brought with her. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 20:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Family Values Activist Josh Duggar Had a Paid Ashley Madison Account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 23:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Holland - Hay Festival. The Christopher Hitchens Lecture: De-radicalising Muhammad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 23:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Holland - Hay Festival. The Christopher Hitchens Lecture: De-radicalising Muhammad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 23:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Holland - Hay Festival. The Christopher Hitchens Lecture: De-radicalising Muhammad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 22:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens reading about Joyce at the Hay Festival. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 01:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Church in Llanelli today. Sorry for the potato quality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 22:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Church in Llanelli today. Sorry for the potato quality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 22:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2008 Audi A4 2.0T Rear Tail Light Removal -- are these bolts damaged? (Two Images) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 15:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What jabber client do you folks use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 14:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ah lads, the media is a fucking disaster. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 13:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday, this story was doing the rounds on Yahoo, Irish Times, BreakingNews.ie -- http://www.breakingnews.ie/world/dont-freak-out-but-scientists-think-octopuses-might-be-aliens-after-dna-study-690779.html

"Don't freak out, but scientists think octopuses 'might be aliens' after DNA study"

Typical bullshit hyperbolic drivel we've been seeing for the past few years. They can't have a headline without injecting feelings and emotion into it.

Anyway, I read the whole fucking report which is here: http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v524/n7564/full/nature14668.html

**TLDR;** Overall, not only is it not alien, apparently, at least in some ways, it is more similar to other organisms than people expected.

Don't get me wrong, these are very exciting results. For example that the octopus evolved its sophisticated nervous system using similar approaches to mammals is very, very interesting. And some of the new genes appear to be related to some unique abilities octopuses have that scientists (and engineers hoping to copy them) have been trying to figure out. But its genome is very clearly related to its close relatives, such as the squid.

The media reports are simply wrong. That, unfortunately, is not uncommon. Media sources want clicks or subscriptions, and sensationalist reports encourage that. On top of that, most people writing science articles for media sources don't know anything about science, and many of them get their information third-hand or worse which means these stories tend to get more and more embellished. Overall, it is never a good idea to trust the popular media on scientific topics. If a media report about a scientific topic doesn't seem to make any sense, there is a good chance that is because they got it fundamentally wrong.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Norway has out-flegged the fleggers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 03:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A similar story to the woman in Dubai: Cavan Orphanage Fire in 1943, 35 children   1 adult died apparently because the Poor Clares (Nuns) did not want the Fire Brigade to see the children in their pyjamas. The remains of the 35 girls were placed in 8 coffins. (x-post from /r/ireland) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 01:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL in North Carolina the Wage and Hour Act does not require mandatory rest breaks or meal breaks for employees 16 years of age or older. The only required rest breaks or meal breaks are for youths under 16 years of age. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 03:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relevant now more than ever: The United States should be squeezing Turkey, not the other way around. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 02:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nostalgia (x-post from /r/pics) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 02:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite hangover food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 16:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you there Dad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 02:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An unexpected conversation... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 21:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I moved to the south in May of 2014. I've been an atheist most of my thinking life. As a child I was actually an altar boy and served at my grandfather's funeral. Even though I'm atheist now I'm kind of proud of that moment. 

My wife is Christian, knows I'm atheist and it's not an issue for us at all. Her family have no idea I'm atheist though, and I'd rather not have to bother with that confrontation.

Anyways. I was in a bar on Thursday, and these two goons started getting into a heated argument over the Confederate flag, and how the US was a Christian nation and all that jazz. Now, one of the guys was fucking carrying so I just let them at it. I wasn't even sure you were allowed to carry and drink alcohol and just chose to keep my trap shut.

After the guys left the barman, visibly pissed off, spoke up about it. I did my usual spiel (which is sourced from Hitchens) stating 99.9% of all species are extinct - some design isn't it? We talk for a good while, and another bar man comes over and joins in and talks about how he's thought the whole thing was shit but hasn't been able to speak to anyone about it.

Two customers come in and they share our views as well.

It was kind of cool, not something I expected to happen in the south.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were allowed to punch one person in the face without any repercussions, who would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 20:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens - Playing 'What if' on Wretched Radio [2009] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 20:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M'thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 05:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This was a week... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 04:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a week when a blogger in Bangladesh was killed for asking questions about two cricket teams who pray to Allah during a game, wondering who he could possibly choose to win.

A week when a Brazilian radio host famous for exposing corruption in his city was murdered while broadcasting live on the air by two gunmen.

A week when Denis O'Brien threatened to sue a satirical news website for posting satire about him.

Freedom of speech is almost nonexistent these days. We call the suppression Orwellian. I beseech you to watch the following video and not take this shit lying down.


https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jyoOfRog1EM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NostrilShorts] Denis O'Brien's Message to Waterford Whispers News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 03:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This was a week... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 02:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I spoke with Lawrence Krauss and Alexander Hitchens today. Alexander is expecting his book to be released next year (depending on the publishers). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 03:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alexander wrote a few essays/articles here: http://www.huffingtonpost.com/alexander-meleagrouhitchens/

If you're unfamiliar with him you should check out his work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Supreme Leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 22:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 99.9% of all species are extinct which means we are all part of the 0.1% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 03:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the most fucked up thing that happened in the 90s? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 00:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite Limerick? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 19:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't judge me. I love carrots! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 13:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friends food kept tasting funny. She bought new saucepans and was about to buy a new dishwasher....then I saw what she was cooking with. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 14:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitchens   John Lennox pre-debate conversation (full video of the Don't Bow to Islam clip posted earlier). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 22:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitchens   John Lennox pre-debate conversation (full video of the Don't Bow to Islam clip posted earlier). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 22:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orwell's use of 'presently'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 20:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on a bit of an Orwell binge as of late, focusing on his lesser known novels. I just finished Keep the Aspidistra Flying, which I found to be a very agreeable book. However, I couldn't help but notice how often Orwell used the word 'presently' to start a lot of his sentences. At one stage he used it twice in one paragraph.

I just started reading Down and Out in Paris and London, and there he is at it again. I try to skim over it and ignore it, as it can be bothersome.

Has anyone else noticed this? Does it bother you at all?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could pick one quote which helped "wake you up", helped you lose your faith, what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 17:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's mine, from Christopher Hitchens: http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1572150/quotes

Let's say that the consensus is that our species, being the higher primates, Homo Sapiens, has been on the planet for at least 100,000 years, maybe more. Francis Collins says maybe 100,000. Richard Dawkins thinks maybe a quarter-of-a-million. I'll take 100,000. In order to be a Christian, you have to believe that for 98,000 years, our species suffered and died, most of its children dying in childbirth, most other people having a life expectancy of about 25 years, dying of their teeth. Famine, struggle, bitterness, war, suffering, misery, all of that for 98,000 years. Heaven watches this with complete indifference. And then 2000 years ago, thinks "That's enough of that. It's time to intervene," and the best way to do this would be by condemning someone to a human sacrifice somewhere in the less literate parts of the Middle East. Don't lets appeal to the Chinese, for example, where people can read and study evidence and have a civilization. Let's go to the desert and have another revelation there. This is nonsense. It can't be believed by a thinking person. Why am I glad this is the case? To get to the point of the wrongness of Christianity, because I think the teachings of Christianity are immoral. The central one is the most immoral of all, and that is the one of vicarious redemption. You can throw your sins onto somebody else, vulgarly known as scapegoating. In fact, originating as scapegoating in the same area, the same desert. I can pay your debt if I love you. I can serve your term in prison if I love you very much. I can volunteer to do that. I can't take your sins away, because I can't abolish your responsibility, and I shouldn't offer to do so. Your responsibility has to stay with you. There's no vicarious redemption. There very probably, in fact, is no redemption at all. It's just a part of wish-thinking, and I don't think wish-thinking is good for people either. It even manages to pollute the central question, the word I just employed, the most important word of all: the word love, by making love compulsory, by saying you MUST love. You must love your neighbour as yourself, something you can't actually do. You'll always fall short, so you can always be found guilty. By saying you must love someone who you also must fear. That's to say a supreme being, an eternal father, someone of whom you must be afraid, but you must love him, too. If you fail in this duty, you're again a wretched sinner. This is not mentally or morally or intellectually healthy. And that brings me to the final objection - I'll condense it, Dr. Orlafsky - which is, this is a totalitarian system. If there was a God who could do these things and demand these things of us, and he was eternal and unchanging, we'd be living under a dictatorship from which there is no appeal, and one that can never change and one that knows our thoughts and can convict us of thought crime, and condemn us to eternal punishment for actions that we are condemned in advance to be taking. All this in the round, and I could say more, it's an excellent thing that we have absolutely no reason to believe any of it to be true.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best thing that happened to you so far this year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 03:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Club: August Discussion Thomas Jefferson: Author of America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 20:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original thread with full timeline is here: http://www.reddit.com/r/ChristopherHitchens/comments/2orcp8/hitchens_book_club_proposed_timetable_input/

This month we are focusing on Thomas Jefferson: Author of America, part of the Eminent Lives series.

If you have not done so, you really ought to listen to Hitchens speak about the book in a library he oftentimes visited in La Jolla here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g_iOJtAuzk4

The book itself is a quick enough read, but Hitchens vast knowledge of Jefferson can truly be seen in the above video. This video is also how I came across The Black Jacobins, a book by C.L.R James which is well worth reading. 

I've rambled enough - time to shut up. Happy reading folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TWC Maxx is coming. Has your service been upgraded yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 21:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Websphere library hell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 01:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a maven web app, using WAS 8.5.5.

On app startup I'm getting the following error:
Caused by: java.lang.NoSuchFieldError: org/apache/http/message/BasicLineFormatter.INSTANCE

This means there's some sort of mismatch of jars (httpclient   httpcore) in my classpath.

To get more info, I ran the following code:

    ClassLoader classLoader = Test.class.getClassLoader();
    URL resource = classLoader.getResource("org/apache/http/message/BasicLineFormatter.class");
    log.info("Outputting resoure info: " + resource.getFile() + " " + resource.getPath() + " " + resource.getRef());
              try {
                     log.info(FileLocator.resolve(resource));
                     log.info(FileLocator.toFileURL(resource));
              } catch (IOException e) {
                     // TODO Auto-generated catch block
                     e.printStackTrace();
              }

This gave me the following output:

 start Outputting resoure info: /org/apache/http/message/BasicLineFormatter.class /org/apache/http/message/BasicLineFormatter.class null
 start jar:file:/C:/RAD9.0/IBM/WebSphere/AppServer_2/plugins/com.ibm.ws.prereq.jaxrs.jar!/org/apache/http/message/BasicLineFormatter.class
start file:/C:/RAD9.0/IBM/WebSphere/AppServer_2/profiles/AppSrv01/servers/server1/configuration/org.eclipse.osgi/bundles/105/1/.cp/org/apache/http/message/BasicLineFormatter.class


These are both obviously loaded to WAS on startup - how do I stop this from happening? I tried changing the priority of the module loading in the app settings - by setting load parent last, but that stopped the app from coming up at all.

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New License Plate Cover (x-post from /r/pics) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 03:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the last movie you watched? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 00:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You've somehow ended up on death row. It's your last meal before the execution. What do you order? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 16:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [repost] Don't bow to Islam. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 03:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens - Don't bow to Islam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 04:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seanus Ennis - god of the uilleann pipes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 03:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Sunday lads. What's the craic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 05:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JAX-RPC to JAX-WS: wsimport not generating all classes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 23:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're going from JAX-RPC to JAX-WS.

When using JAX-RPC we used the com.ibm.websphere.ant.tasks.WSDL2Java class to generate our classes.

For JAX-WS we're using wsimport. I've notice some of the classes that are generted using the old method don't exist when using wsimport.

Has anyone else come across this before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your most prized possession? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 01:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I haven't touched this since Christmas but I felt the urge to have a dram tonight - Midleton Barry Crockett Legacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 02:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gentlesir planting some seeds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 04:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend found this at a southern flea market. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 01:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hanging with m'lady </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Illinois teen accidentally kills himself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leave mckenna alone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 21:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Christians   Jews Wake Up. Obama is MUSLIM!" -- I saw this sign outside some lunatics house on the way home today. Couldn't take a picture as I was driving. Will try to snap a picture tomorrow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not quite sure why they didn't address non-religious people, or why it would even matter considering it's the same god but a different messenger. Probably not worth trying to use logic when it comes to this sort of anti-intellectualism.

Hilarious all the same though. North Carolina I love ya! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Christians   Jews Wake Up. Obama is MUSLIM!" -- anyone else see this sign outside some lunatics house on the way into Apex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Christians   Jews Wake Up. Obama is MUSLIM!" -- anyone else see this sign outside some lunatics house on the way into Apex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 23:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alright, we need a bit of a lift with all the bullshit that's going on lately. Lets focus on the good things. What's your favourite thing about Northern Ireland? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Kavanagh posts a video of him and McGregor in 2013 with a similar escape that Conor used last Saturday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corkman who crashed McGregor party: 'If I rushed it or pulled a camera I was gone -- check out Conor's shiner. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Bastille Day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy Bastille Day, a day which celebrates the storming of Bastille and the start of the French revolution which saw a monarchy overthrown. As Paine described it -- "a glorious sequel to Americas".

If it wasn't for the French revolution, the San Domingo revolution may not have been a success. The French revolution helped emancipate the slaves on that French colony, however it must be recognized that Toussaint L'Ouverture's men had to rely on their own strengths and abilities to pull it off.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bastille_Day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cocky in prediction. Confident in preparation. But always humble in victory or defeat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 09:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens: What Did Margaret Thatcher Do for Britain? Iron Lady   British Politics (1987) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 08:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For anyone wondering about Dana's comments about more Irish living in the UK than in Ireland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 08:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Conor missing for the post fight conference? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 08:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/goblin_skeleton to get Irish flag tattooed on forehead after tonight's fight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 07:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pendred gracious in defeat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else's UFC.TV stream "loading" every now and again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 04:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chad Mendes has a new set of wheels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 05:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite Hitchens essay or polemic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 16:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's quite a difficult question to answer, and it's almost self defeating in a way. It's like asking someone what their favourite book or movie is. Our attitude changes over time, as does our mood, so it's extremely subjective but it's certainly not a pointless discussion.

For a long time I have loved his essay on Churchill whereby Hitchens discusses being raised on "the cult of Winston Churchill" and America's obsession with him, but I shouldn't stop there. 

Hitchens could be extremely funny, and one only has to look as far as Joyce in Bloom to see multiple examples of this. This is an essay that's mostly about wanking, and Joyce's obsession with it. He even jokes about it impacting Joyce's eye sight.

Another favourite of mine is Prisoner of Shelves; Hitchens talks about the available shelf space in his apartment, which is considerable, continuing to be outrun by the appearance of new books and he explains why he has decided to stack them vertically (a suggestion from a Vanity Fair colleage). This actually led to me doing the same, and buying lots of vertical shelves which ended up saving enormous space at home.

Stand up for Denmark is a great polemic calling for everyone to get behind the country after the cartoon incident. I try to read this every few months to remind me of the need for free speech (as well as listening to the debate in Toronto).

What is your favourite Hitchens essay or polemic, and why?



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is how I've been spending my evenings this month. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 02:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember "Why Religion is Immoral: And Other Interventions" which has yet to be released? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 21:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The publisher of this volume is Simon   Schuster.

Does that ring a bell with any of you? No?

Well, Michael Korda is their editor-in-chief, and he just happens to be Henry Kissinger's publisher as well.

If that still isn't registering with you, then you should read the Introduction to The Trials of Henry Kissinger.

I find this connection very interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kingsley Amis - Lucky Jim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 19:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have any of you read Lucky Jim by Kingsley Amis?

I just finished it, and I found it extremely hard to put down. It was a real page turner. I've read reviews on GoodReads, and it appears people either love it or hate it. They either got the humour, or they didn't, and I guess that makes sense because humour is subjective.

I loved the writing style, it wasn't just that the book was funny but it was because it was *so* funny.

Christopher Hitchens wrote a review of the book here, and he can say it better than I can. http://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2002/05/the-man-of-feeling/302486/

Have any of you read it? If so did you like it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was wondering where Mumbles was, when suddenly this appeared from under the couch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 18:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Club July Discussion: Love, Poverty and War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 01:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original thread with full timeline is here: http://www.reddit.com/r/ChristopherHitchens/comments/2orcp8/hitchens_book_club_proposed_timetable_input/


This month we are focusing on Love, Poverty and War a book which is a bit of a monster to tackle in a month. I'm actually not sure many of you are following along anymore, as discussion has been almost nonexistent. However, I'll soldier on because I feel this is worthwhile. This is a book that might be hard to finish in a month, as it's tough reading a variety of essays on different subjects. An activity which made it easier for me was tackling All Art is Propaganda and also Facing Unpleasant Facts; both are collections of Orwell's essays put together by George Packer.

If you are still involved, I encourage you to discuss the essays in this text. My favourite is the opening essay on Churchill. 


Don't forget to ask questions about anything Christopher says. This goes for all books we will encounter. One of reasons we are taking part in the book club is to encourage discourse, to question everything, to discuss the contents and also make note of the recommendations for further reading. Happy reading folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Redditors who tried to commit suicide, what led you to the attempt to take your life, why did it fail, and are you glad you're still here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada is burning. This was taken shortly after noon in Saskatchewan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 20:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Man of Feeling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What a wonderful gift. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ant to Maven question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 15:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi folks,

I'm in the middle of an ant to maven migration for one of our applications (a web service). Our build.xml isn't too big - around 400 lines of code or thereabouts.

I have almost everything working. The part I'm stuck on is as follows:

In ant we have:  

    target name="gen.wsdl"
       echo message="generating WSDL for ${service}"/
       java taskname="WSDLGenerator" classname="com.wsdlgenerator.WSDLGenerator"
          classpathref="gen.wsdl.classpath"  fork="true" failonerror="true" dir="${wsdl.dir}"
          arg line="${opargs}"/
       /java
    /target

I'm trying to do this in Maven like so:

    plugin
	groupIdorg.apache.maven.plugins/groupId
	artifactIdmaven-antrun-plugin/artifactId
	version1.8/version
	executions
	  execution
	    idcompile/id
	    phasecompile/phase
	    configuration
	         target
                 echo taskname="WSDLGenerator" message="generating WSDL for ${service}"/
	                  java classname="com.wsdlgenerator.WSDLGenerator" classpathref="${gen.wsdl.classpath}" fork="true" failonerror="true" dir="${wsdl.dir}"/
	            		argline${opargs}/argline
	         /target
	   /configuration
	   goals
	      goalrun/goal
	   /goals
	/execution
	/executions
    /plugin	    

This is not working and I'm getting the following error:

[WSDLGenerator] generating WSDL for ${service}
     [java] java.lang.NoClassDefFoundError: com/wsdlgenerator/WSDLGenerator

Now, firstly - I've removed the full package name so I'm not breaking any NDA at my company, it's a bit longer than com.wsdlgenerator.WSDLGenerator. I have this included as a dependency in the pom, and when I type "com.wsdlgenerator.WSDLGenerator" in any of the classes it is recognized, so I'm not entirely sure why Maven is falling over here.

Have any of you run into this before? Am I even doing this the correct way?

**EDIT** I resolved this by using the maven.compile.classpath instead of the custom gen.wsdl.classpath. I'm not running into issues with the argline parameters but that's a separate issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Backs of front seat falling off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 02:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else have this issue? The backs of my front seats are falling off in my 2008 Audi A4 2.0T, looks like some sort of glue issue. Unfortunately it's probably related to it being 100F here these days, and I can't keep the car in the shade until our office has a covered garage built next month so it gets ridiculously hot. 

Any idea how much this would cost to repair? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy crap I'm so excited </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens: Why Does the Media Lie to Us? Media and Reporting Bias (1997) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 08:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carol Blue and Martin Amis 2012 On panel discussing 'Mortality' and Christopher Hitchens' life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 07:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In light of the recent debate around the confederate flag, here's Hitchens' thoughts on the matter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 15:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You've been tasked with writing a novel. What is your opening line? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 23:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin Amis - The Rachel Papers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Rachel Papers is Martin's first book written when he was in his early twenties, published in 1973.

This is the third book of Martin's I have read (the first two being Experience [his autobiography] and The Zone of Interest).

I probably should have started with The Rachel Papers. I was happy to see him talk about things like "experience" in the novel, so I can see that was a constant theme throughout his life and why he gave that the name of his autobiography.

The Rachel Papers was excellent, kind of like a mature Catcher in the Rye. I found it very easy to read, very hard to put that, and I was done with it after several hours. I haven't been that captivated by a book in a while.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something that made you cringe lately? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 13:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Author of That Horrible Snowden Article Has Even Worse CNN Interview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitchens lays the smack down on a gay Christian, and a bunch of callers who hate the gay Christian for what he is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 02:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long do you usually wait before re-watching the show again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've watched the show three times now, with my third re-watch finishing about a week ago.

Just wondering how long you lads/ladies usually wait until watching the show again? 

I don't want to jump in too soon, if such a thing is even possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oscar Pistorius release in August to be recommended - CNN.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 15:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would anyone else love to see a spin off show in the sideways world with Sawyer as a cop, and Miles with crazy-seeing-how-dead-people-died powers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 16:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another "OMG nothing will ever be as good as Lost" thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished Lost for the third time with my wife. It was her second viewing.

It's kind of mad for me to think about how long ago the show first aired.

I'm at that point where no other show is interesting to me. I've tried to start a few other shows and I'm bored within 5 minutes and just cannot get into them - I'm just not able to give them the attention they deserve right now.

I'm actually considering watching Lost a 4th time, but I'm also thinking I should wait a bit.

I'm seriously suffering from post-Lost fever. I've even read the pilot, and holy crap the detail in there is insane. It's worth reading if you have not read it yet.

Why cant I connect to television like I did with Lost? i think it's a combination of the characters and the island. Almost every island scene was beautiful, and almost all characters were loveable. I think Kate was the only one I did not like.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lovely day for a dram. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 00:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Java Rules Engine (possibly spring based) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 16:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to implement a rules engine for an application I'm in the middle of creating.

Having no experience with rules engines, I figured I would open up a discussion here for you more knowledgeable folks.

I've been looking at Drools Guvnor (http://guvnor.jboss.org/) which appears to have everything I need.

Have any of you used Drools Guvnor, or do any of you have experience with other rules engines?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WANTED] Video of Christopher Hitchens vs Michael Moore debate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitchens wrote about it in his polemic "The lies of Michael Moore", whereby he said he engaged in "an onstage debate with Michael Moore at the Telluride Film Festival".

Here's an image from the debate: http://www.overcast.pwp.blueyonder.co.uk/f911/media/telluride1b.jpg

I NEED THIS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Club June Discussion: Why Orwell Matters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 20:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original thread with full timeline is here: http://www.reddit.com/r/ChristopherHitchens/comments/2orcp8/hitchens_book_club_proposed_timetable_input/

This month we are focusing on Why Orwell Matters, a book which took me two or three attempts before I could read it all, mainly due to not being too familiar with Orwell's writing. After reading Orwell's Diaries, and a few of his novels I found this easier to tackle. 

Please don't forget to ask questions about anything Christopher says. This goes for all books we will encounter. One of reasons we are taking part in the book club is to encourage discourse, to question everything, to discuss the contents and also make note of the recommendations for further reading. Happy reading folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone on here was looking for a photo of a touchdown bar ages ago. Here ya go. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 17:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it OK to bring a kettle and my french press into the office at work? Do other people do this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 01:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **UPDATE** 

So I grew some balls and brought in my french press today. Only good comments so far - people love the smell.

Result! Thanks folks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As promised - messed up train incident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 00:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spent a weekend in Dublin on the lash with my friends, and I was a bit sore on the Sunday as I'm sure you can imagine. I picked up a few cans of beer in Heuston station, and boarded the last train that night. It was around 9pm and it was pitch black outside, and had been dark since around 5pm.

I get on one of the front carriages and just walk all the way to the back. I don't want to be near anyone and wouldn't mind a carriage all to myself so off I go to the back. I get to the last carriage and sure enough there's nobody in it. Lovely job. 

If you're unfamiliar with the carriages, they have a table with 4 seats around it. Something like this: http://citytransport.info/Digi/P1160991.jpg

So I make myself comfortable, crack open a beer, and the train starts to move. About five minutes into the journey, this fella in his 50s or thereabouts comes in and sits a few seats up from me. He makes eye contact with me and I nod as if to say "hello", but I get no reaction. He's just staring at me, really weird like. His eyes are fairly large, as if he's mad in the head or something.

I look away anyway, and try to focus on the outside of the train hoping that he'll either go away or just stop looking at me.

I go into my bag for a book, hoping that will give him the idea that I don't want to fucking deal with the cunt. My bag is on the floor so I bend down and root around in it, find my book, and when I sit back up straight with the book in my head he's sitting down at my table right across from me. 

Every hair on my body stands up at this point. I'm not even joking like. I'd say the look I had on my face must have been hilarious. He was there across from me, with the big stupid look on his face.

"Well how're ya? Have you any sisters have ya?"

I says I have yeah, I have one sister.

"I bet you'd love to fuck her wouldn't ya? Does she have a smelly pussy does she? I bet she does yeah"

He says that to me really quickly... with this deep dirty voice.

So obviously I'm dealing with a fucking nutter of some sort, a demented perverted fuck anyway.

"If you think I'm going to let anyone talk about my sister like that, you're a big fucken eejit. Take that back - I don't think those sorts of things because I'm not fucked up in the head".

I'm not quite sure why I said that. I probably should have just got up and left, or told him to fuck off. 

He says sorry and sits there in silence. Looking at the window, then me, then window. When looks at me he's really staring at me like, studying me, thinking of something. It's quite clear.

A few minutes go by and I'm fucking dying for yer man to come along who checks the tickets because I did not think there were many people on the train to begin with.

Just as I finish my can, and get another from my bag he lunges at me with those eyes of his all fucking crazy like. He starts choking me with both his hands, and he hops up on the table so he's kneeling on it with both hands squeezing the shit out of my neck.

Now, it's a cliche to say time went as if it was in slow motion but that really is how it felt. Despite it feeling like time slowed down I felt like I didn't have time to think about the situation that much because I couldn't focus on anything but the pain my neck. My windpipe was fully closed, with the front of it touching the back. My fuck the pain was brutal and I couldn't catch my breath at all.

I studied self defense as a teenager, and there's a move you can do to get your arm over one of his arms, and under the other one, and then if you turn you'll disrupt his grip.

I did that and it worked, and I had about 1 or 2 seconds to react, so as i'm pushing him off his hold on my neck is released and I'm able to connect with his chin and knock him back a bit. I jump up, still trying to catch my breath and get over the awful pain in my throat, and I just lay into him. Punch after punch, and he still has that stupid fucking look on his face. 

I stop hitting him, and I'm fucking exhausted man. Heart is going 90, so I sit back down across from the table where we were just trying to think like. He gets up and goes into one of the other carriages, and I'm still in disbelief... did this really happen?

I go to the rest room to clean myself up a bit, and I come back to my seat. The ticket fella comes around and I let him know the story and I give a description of who did it. The ticket fella asks if I could point him out and I said I could, so we walk through the carriage and I see him sitting across from a group of girls and I point him out. He has his back to us, and the girls see me pointing him out and they recognize there's something up.

The cops are called and they're waiting at the first stop which is Portlaoise station. I go back to my seat and the ticket inspector stays there watching yer man in case he moves. He tells me to be ready to meet with the cops when the train stops, and I tell him I'll stay put and they can come to get me and he agrees.

The train stops anyway, and people get off the train and he's one of them. He's grabbed by the police, handcuffed and led away. I can see all this out my window, because when he got off the train he started to walk up towards where I was - everyone who got off the train was leaving that way.

A cop comes into my carriage and asks me to come to the station with him so I can make a formal statement. This is the last fucking train though, so if I do that I'm fucked.

He says he'll ensure I'm brought home safely after I give the statement. So I do that, I explain the whole story, and true to his word the fella who took my statement drove me all the way from Portlaoise to Shannon, to my front door.

I never found out what happened to him, because I moved to the states soon after the incident and I never followed up with it. I haven't a clue who the fuck he was or what his deal was. It was a very strange experience for me, and I'm glad I was able to defend myself with one of the only fucking moves I remember from self defense. When I think back on it, it's as if it was a different life or something. It's just so bizarre and I never thought anything like that would happen to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you know anyone who went missing or was murdered? If so, what's their story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 04:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird event leaving UL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 02:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife, who was my girlfriend at the time, was studying in the University of Limerick, in Limerick City, Ireland. She's from the states and was studying abroad, and that is how we met. She was living on campus (I think the place was called Cappa, or something like that).

At the time I had a very flashy convertible, a real head turner. I worked doing operations support for a big multinational at the time, and some times I'd start work at 5am. So I was leaving her place around 4am to get back home to Shannon to start work - it was a remote job when I was on the 5am shift.

Anyways, I'm coming out of UL and it's ridiculously foggy. Like, I can see about 10 - 15 feet in front of me. There's a roundabout just around the corner, so I slow down and then I see some lad run out in front of the car and hold his hand out to stop me. His face is covered with a balaclava. I'm like, what the fuck. Right at this time, someone runs up and tries to open my driver-side door, but for whatever reason I had locked the door.... I NEVER LOCK THE DOOR... but I did it then for some reason... I just felt it was a really early time and there could be freaks around and you'd never know what could happen being at a red light in the city with a car like this.

Anyway, when that happened I just floored it, and I was in such a rage that I aimed for the cunt standing in front of me and luckily I missed him.

My heart was fucking racing, hair standing up all over me. I got home and told a friend of mine about it who was online on Facebook, and he lived close enough to UL so he took a trip over in his car but didn't find anyone.

The guy who tried to open my drivers door had a hatchet in his hand.

Fucking madness. I completely forgot about this until I started reading through the sub.

It's not the most fucked up thing to happen to me, I'll post another thread a bit later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arnie is in the Mac Mansion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 23:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Cows get sunburn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tell us your moving story. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 23:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is for the people who moved to Hawaii, either from the mainland or elsewhere.

1. How did you end up on Hawaii - what made you decide to live in Hawaii?  
2. What did you bring with you?  
3. Did you have a job lined up before moving?  
4. Where was the first place you lived - how much did it cost?  
5. What was your anxiety level like when you moved here?  
6. Were there differences (culture or otherwise) that you found interesting or noteworthy?  
7. Did you find it tough to make friends here?  
8. Did you stay in your first job or are you still looking?  
9. How did you manage the first few months (being away from friends and family)?  
10. In restrospect, was it a good decision and would you consider doing it again knowng everything that you know now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we talk about Tsarnaev? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 04:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd love to hear what Christopher would say about Tsarnaev. Here's his thoughts on the hanging of Saddam. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 02:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I buy a really nice whiskey cabinet? Budget is $500 - $2500. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 02:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update: Decided to go with something like this: http://www.cooperagecabinets.com/liquor-barrel-cabinets/

Thanks for the suggestions everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone tried the Apex Farmers Market yet? Is it good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 15:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/Aigis-the-Aeon calls out an OP who pretended his daughter committed suicide and donater her organs to charity for upvotes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is regularly feeding your kids fast food (McDonalds, Wendys, etc) child abuse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 14:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You've woken up with the ability to see 10 seconds into the future. What creative ways can you think of using this new found ability? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 04:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A flow chart that defeats No voters who use religion as an excuse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 04:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should we create a fat person tax to help reduce obesity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 22:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, your significant other is out of town for the weekend. What is the plan to pass the time while they are away? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 16:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's the story behind the first time you were drunk? How did it happen and what age were you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 16:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the 4FM cheating man who tricked the nation with his elaborate prank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 16:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL today is Victory Day, a holiday celebrated by most former Soviet Union countries. The holiday marks the defeat of the Nazis which happened 70 years ago in 1945. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 11:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tomorrow I am celebrating 70 years since the Russians beat the Nazis with my friend Oleg. Does Igor celebrate Victory Day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 22:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scottish National Party wins 56 of 59 seats in UK General Election, up 50 from the 6 seats they won in 2011. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 14:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House owners of Reddit, what do you wish you knew before buying your house? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 02:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Long Long Way by Sebastian Barry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 14:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone else read this book? I saw a few posts from 4 years ago but nothing recent.

This book was written in 2005, and I came across it by way of Christopher Hitchens who, when asked what he was reading about ten years ago gave this title.

I'm about half way through and I'm absolutely loving it. If you like war books, or are a Catch-22 fan then I'm sure you'll enjoy this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst experience you've had involving a house mate or a tenant? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 02:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most restrictive thing you've seen a parent enforce on their kids? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 17:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stroke victims of Reddit, tell us your story. When did it happen and how has your recovery been? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 19:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the greatest experience available to mankind? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 14:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Club May Discussion: No One Left to Lie To: The Triangulations of William Jefferson Clinton. Verso. Reissued as No One Left to Lie To: The Values of the Worst Family in 2000. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 03:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original thread with full timeline is here: http://www.reddit.com/r/ChristopherHitchens/comments/2orcp8/hitchens_book_club_proposed_timetable_input/

This month we are focusing on No One Left to Lie To: The Triangulations of William Jefferson Clinton. Verso. Reissued as No One Left to Lie To: The Values of the Worst Family in 2000.

This book is a scathing attack on Clinton, and one which hasn't drawn enough attention. If I recall correctly, Christopher's deal with his publisher was for 5 grand for this book.

Please don't forget to ask questions about anything Christopher says. This goes for all books we will encounter. One of reasons we are taking part in the book club is to encourage discourse, to question everything, to discuss the contents and also make note of the recommendations for further reading.
Happy reading folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is Angel Falls, the world's highest uninterrupted waterfall. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 02:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any of you parsed WSDL files before. Which parser did you use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 15:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there,

I've been tasked with creating a WSDL parser, which checks for specific requirements our team has which are not covered by the current parsers out there. We run our WSDL files through things like the WS-I parser prior to parsing it for our needs, and it's that final piece that I am working on.

Anyway, I'm using javax.wsdl to parse the WSDL file, and also using XSOM to parse the XSD files.

This is working really well and I'm almost finished, however I wanted to know if the APIs I'm using are ones you guys have used before, or if there are better alternatives out there?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walking down an isle in the local 711 when I saw this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 02:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walking down the isle at a 711 when I saw this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 02:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few more pictures of the Kerry coast from this past weekend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 15:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
