<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1563</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 21:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cough cough Boston Cough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the last book you read that had almost no filler? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 21:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 17:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This novel hopefully will be published. I think it is good enough. After that I  do not know. I have the next novel in my head as well as 5 scripts I am working on. But I really don't know. It all seems about extreme luck or knowing people. I am not lucky and live a fairly isolated life. And I am getting old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is your favourite 'that guy' actor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 04:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J.K. Rowling and the Chamber of Literary Fame - Rowlings spectacular career is likely more a fluke of history than a consequence of her unique genius. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 01:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 16:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If your wife or girlfriend dressed you what would you look like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 16:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 05:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2nd response with this. Now I am scared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 01:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a way. But I think I had a slight break from reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the weirdest scene in the history of cinema? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 01:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever felt apologetic or uneasy about what you have written? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 17:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If so, why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [XPost from /r/pics] - This bookstore is getting creative. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 00:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 15:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found it amusing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 15:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone writes at some point, but I guess I was thinking more about the critics who are not themselves fiction writers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stuff non writers say. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 14:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the best critics non writers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 14:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously, Everyone writes at some point, but I guess I was thinking more about the critics who are not themselves fiction writers?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Jerome Flynn (Bronn from Game of Thrones) spent many years in a religious cult. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 17:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 13:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the question but good going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 13:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But your press would disappear too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 19:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to just say it as it is, but no, it is not already dead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 19:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We will be replaced with robots soon enough. That is the end product. But in terms of adaptation in the short term, it has pushed past saturation point into the absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 18:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and this is why I brought up the question. If it were to happen literature as a valid form of human expression would die even earlier than before.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 18:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Opportunity involves the open submission to an agent these days. Or a smaller publisher. I think a lot of this is about what you write. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 18:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an element of talent in certain types of writing, in most art, in most functions in life. I don't think that can be denied. Again, if you are all Paris Hilton level actors (easily interchangeable blondes for example) you might luck out. If you are Daniel Day Lewis or Robert De Niro you will get noticed for your talent.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 18:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like you care little about writing, or the future of literature. It comes across that you are quite bitter for some reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 16:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> History shows that many great writers never had a break and suffered in obscurity until old age or after death.

In terms of genre fiction it is probably 99% luck. Literary or non fiction I would imagine there are elements of talent involved which do not apply to other works.

Hard work is necessary for most. Not all, there are people who have one in a million chances, we saw one post recently. Sometimes things fall into peoples laps. That is just how it is. 

It is the bad actor who makes millions when there are hundreds better than him versus would Pacino have eventually made it due to his talent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Traditional Publishing died would you care? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 13:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 13:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the world regressed to only having fiction the level of this man then I think it would be better if none was produced at all. Possibly one of the worst successful writers I have ever encountered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 00:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do not like the literary fiction? What do you like to write? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 00:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really would depend what my staff was happy with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your next project after you finish your current one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 19:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 19:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can get welfare working full time while studying?

or is this all nonsense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 03:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were you allowed any contact with anyone who could let people at home know you were alive? Red Cross ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 20:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi!

Why are you against the Anti-Counterfeiting Trade Agreement?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 03:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No mine is completely irrational, has no basis whatsoever in any rational thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 03:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In many countries you need to have proof of applying and being rejected to maintain social welfare. If you apply on paper and get no response you could be cut off and that might end up fucking your life up. Keep in mind not everyone on reddit is an IT specialist computer scientist engineer. Many live week to week. Or day to day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 19:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> never heard of it

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brazil_(novel) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 11:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 10:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, happens, this is why many of us are alcoholics. We need to drink to feel good again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 10:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once you write something that actually moves you. It might not move anyone else, but if your script makes you feel something that's beyond pride then you're achieving something as a writer. And you might just be writing something that other people might be emotionally engaged by.

Well then 99% of screenwriters on the planet must never pat themselves on the back ever so (or have really low expectations)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 10:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take your meds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 04:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get a neuroscience degree before if you are serious

psychology is a joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some titles that you wished you had come up with first? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 02:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 17:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sent you a critique I think not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 17:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have I asked for any of that? no

bringing up my history is a low move comment reported </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 14:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously you are getting into a deep argument.

And seeing from the few upvotes I got on a different thread mentioning the competition I feel I am not alone.

The work put into the contest, perhaps it should have been more open. Who are making the decisions? Internet randoms for the most part and one known person. 

Deserved to win? In your opinion. When the runners up and honourable mentions posted on the sub that time were that bad makes you wonder about the competency of the judges.

I believe you have good intentions with the FAQ but my point still stands. 5 books and links to 5 script sites and maybe what 5 competition/board pages. That is all that it is. 

All other advice on here is just the same old hat, devolving into pissing contests for the insecure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 14:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On this sub hardly a problem at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 12:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. It is the sad truth that the colossally bad now have a forum where they can actually believe they are writers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 12:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no it did not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 12:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I asked it and it got hundreds of responses I think I and others knew very clearly what it meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 12:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no my family doesn't so fuck you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 12:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not at all. One can admire the prose and dislike the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 03:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are three - five links and maybe 4 or 5 'Bibles' referenced on here in total.

Link them on the side.

Stop putting work on yourself mate.

It's probably a dead sub and I can't see it growing too far. 14K users my ass. Very little responses in general and those who do seem to be angry and full of bile.

And I repeat reading the highlighted competition lists made me reconsider ever even commenting on here. And I am sure I am not alone.

Ten pages with nothing. Shortlisted.

Bad Tarantino rip off. Shortlisted. 

Not saying terrible but if anyone posted the same on here openly they would be ripped to pieces. Pissed on is the word. Yes, I have read them. Pissed on. 

Sort that problem out first. Don't bother with FAQs for a sub where no one really cares and those involved don't seem to offer any better advice than can be posted with 5 amazon links and 5 links to script sites.

Save the effort I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 03:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no.2 is reddit

any attempt to dismiss that is against the site </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the last book you read - in terms of writing - that blew you away? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 17:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am not a bad person but I can't do anything right. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 15:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything I do backfires or just falls limp and turns to dust. All the work I have done gets me nowhere. I am surrounded by success. I have been open about my intentions but not nearly as open as I should be. 

I assume you can understand what those intentions are. 

Everyone who cares or pretends to I don't know. It is not fair I continue to worry about that.

I am very tired.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are some of us meant to suffer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 14:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that just our misfortune in life? Nothing works out for me. I seem to be surrounded by people with great success and it seems to come easy. 

I struggle to do the basic. All my potential is spent now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think you could make it as a professional criminal and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 23:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the stupidest thing you do on a regular basis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 18:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think every chapter has to be as good as the others? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 23:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or can some be better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone on here found an agent or publisher as a direct result of publishing short stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 13:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the agent read one and contact you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you picked the best day of your life and the worst day of your life and combined and halved them - would that mix be better or worse than your average day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 00:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favourite food to eat when sick? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-20 21:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you feel working for a director who was not as technically competent as you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 14:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If someone was to come from a writing/theatre background, who had more experience in those areas, but had an interest and some knowledge of the technical side.

Would it be a problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are these hard rice shaped growths that are on my dogs skin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 23:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are only occasional. One I found on his back leg.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your thoughts and opinions on J. M. G. Le Clzio? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 18:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is required to set up a production company? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-03 15:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much failure can you take before ending it? Serious question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-02 13:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to know others opinions. When is the cut off point? I am trying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the general Reddit community/Hivemind becoming nastier in the past 6 months and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 20:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your honest opinions on shorts which have large budgets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 11:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many smaller, excellent films seem to be made with a bit of talent (rare I know) and dedication. It seems to me that blowing 30-40k on a beautiful looking but ultimately crappy short is a waste of money.

What do you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When should you be researching agents? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 21:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like I am drowning in others success. Can anyone relate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 13:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everywhere I look people are getting places. Often without any hard work. I say that because I know them. They told me what they had do. What am I doing wrong?

Is it the depression? The clock I have set still exists. I am trying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Offered $250,000 for my script. I think I will turn it down. What do you think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 16:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you honestly rate your writing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 11:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gloves off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate everything I put on paper. So how am I supposed to continue? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 17:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the favourite opening line that you wrote? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 16:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going insane with this right now. I can't go on until I have it fixed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Considering your current work, who is the single biggest influence on your writing right now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 16:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not overall in your history but right now, for this work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you rate the level of writing on here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 05:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever collaborated on a piece? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-15 16:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems it could be quite easy for 3-4 users on here to map out a YA book and throw it up on Amazon no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you ever look at your work and think if that was under a known authors name you would accept it and read on... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 19:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But because it's under yours you think it is awful? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the possible titles of your next work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-10 19:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am thinking of two. 

And worried by both.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think is the most beautifully written novel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-09 13:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever dug out an old manuscript, completely rewrote it and sent it out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 22:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone got any stories to tell? I am considering doing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else feel like an absolute failure surrounded by success?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 16:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exhausted, to my core, but my anxiety keeps me awake? Any tips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 01:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I happily go to my death on the 1st of March 2014. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 18:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing can stop me. Life is pointless. Just wanted to vent, which is pointless, maybe some people can be saved from the comments I don't know.

edit: Thank you all for the replies. It does mean something. I hope people know that.

edit 2: I am sorry this post is just whining. I hope someone maybe sees it and gets help. Everyone deserves to be happy but some of us never will.

edit 3: whomever sent me reddit gold thank you - it was anonymous so I cannot thank you directly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you take chances in your script or stick to the formulaic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-19 15:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to me that many on here follow those screenwriting bibles and the set formulas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So rejection of novel number 50 - what next?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-02 20:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am working on another as we speak but what should I do?

Bin it? Fire? Paper plane war? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Contemporary but lesser known Literary Fiction I should be reading right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-02 13:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do you think is the most overrated playwright of recent years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 20:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What low budget features have you made? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 21:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many of us are really and truly alone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 18:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on Michael Mann's The Keep? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 12:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A strange film. Potential and all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do any of you feel like you were born in the wrong time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 02:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I was born even 10, 15 years earlier I think I would be happy and successful. I mean this to my core. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you have one main trigger for your nerves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 00:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should we even expect to have a relationship? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 21:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why put the pain onto another?

We are selfish enough creatures at the best of times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it actually possible for everyone to be happy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 22:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the creepiest police composite sketch that you know of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 18:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My anxiety is going to kill me. Anyone relate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 13:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think you will die of old age? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 01:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think 2013 will be a good year for you?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 14:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What has been your good news lately? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 20:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is more important career wise - the novel or the short story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 13:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a half dozen short stories on the go. Various lengths 5k -15k. I was thinking that I could spend that time on a novel instead. Would it be more practical? 

What do agents want? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It was my birthday this week..... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 14:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... I am in my early 30's. So officially I have spent over 50% of my life dealing with constant and persistent thoughts of ending it all.

I don't know it this is a good thing or a bad thing.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favourite political/legal thrillers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-30 21:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A genre under appreciated by many I believe but I love them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most overrated food that you have ever had? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 18:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How has depression destroyed your promise and ambitions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 19:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe talking about it could help. I don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is illegal in your area that should be immediately made legal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-24 20:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many scripts have you been able to get produced? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-24 18:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What were they ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan's ninjas heading for extinction. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 12:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think it is wrong to set a date? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 10:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What food products do you think have reached the pinnacle of their kind? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-17 20:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfection or thereabouts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What playwrights do you absolutely hate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 14:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you deal with Envy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 11:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long term goals seem impossible so I don't try. Am I alone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 14:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A career? Why bother? Probably suicide.

A house? Why even start? Won't be around to enjoy it.

A relationship? Enjoy them while you can, and I do, but if taken away what difference will it make?

Frustrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else find the idea of suicide rather comforting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 22:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the sense that it actually saves you at times? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you cope with being a failure? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 20:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And no I am not saying everyone is.

But for those of us who are it might help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone not care if their 'end' upsets their parents? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 04:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What First World country are you happy that you were not born in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-25 19:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> List your reasons if you wish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is David Foster Wallace overrated?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 15:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to hear your opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I was successful I would not be feeling like this. Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 18:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I read a lot of biographies of writers. Why does it seem so easy for the majority of them to succeed?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 13:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are talking a good 80%. And not even the world famous prize winners. I'm talking the average.

They get grants and teaching positions after publishing a few stories.

Although nearly every agent says they do not want short story collections they go about publishing a collection before the novel.

They come out of college and into a super job at a major paper or magazine.

They get agents with unfinished manuscripts. Producers appear and ask to see their scripts.

Everything seems so easy. I know for everyone of these there is a Joyce or McCarthy but I just don't see the angles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starting now and finishing a novel by New Years Eve? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-09 17:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feasible?

Crazy?

1st draft?

Anyone have any advice?

I am not working at the moment, unless some retail job pops up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regarding the front page video - Why don't juries in America convict police officers who are caught on tape assaulting civilians?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 14:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_cases_of_police_brutality_in_the_United_States

Often times they are acquitted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does one get over small mistakes which grow in your mind to become unbearable?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-30 22:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those slight memories or misspoken words or deeds which can ruin your life?

Anyone have any answers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italy upholds verdict on CIA agents in rendition case says the BBC. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 19:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there are websites or links that discuss budgets for filmmaking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 15:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Features or shorts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't some agents and publishers respond at all? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 13:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You send your probably formatted manuscript or letter. You provide postage for it to be returned. You provide an email as well.

What is the thinking behind this?

If they don't want submissions say it on their website. If they want to read submissions they have a duty to respond to you within a certain time.

Am I in the wrong here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Higgs - You can't touch me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 03:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does one get to write those Star Trek novels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 10:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the best genres to make money from short stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-20 18:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Publishing a short story which forms part of a novel : Are there any problems doing this?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-18 00:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The short is a self contained piece. It is published in a magazine. 

Say a year later a book comes out and it is a chapter of a novel for example.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you feel you have to sacrifice other things in your life to write? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-15 18:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is Friday, evening approaching. Part of me wants to get out into the city and chill. The other part says no, sit down and do some work.

EDIT: Thanks folks for all your responses. Most enlightening :-)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is $19 per story too high for a short story competition? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 17:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wanted to see what the opinions on here are like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think there are writers you should avoid?

Or perhaps particular books that are not worth the effort? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-11 17:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or do all writers have some value? I was thinking this regarding Vollman. A few hundred pages into Imperial and I was thinking to myself:

1: Do I like this? - no.

2: Am I learning anything from it? - no.

3: Would I recommend it to others? - no.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you get over the crippling self-doubt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-10 21:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever written a long work in bullet points? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 21:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Nabokov did something similar.

Most people say write first draft then pare back 20% or so.

What about the other way, write the main thrust of the work, perhaps even as much as 50% and then when you go to rewrite it expand upon it?

Does this even make sense at all?

I'm just lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
