<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7338</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are no effects of being born on Friday the 13th: The Empirics of Bad Luck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 13:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research: More violence, more knowledge and engagement in politics (The Longterm Effects of Political Violence on Political Attitudes: Evidence from the Spanish Civil War) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 21:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 13:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not only Delhi's children who deserve quality education. Take a look at the current economist http://www.economist.com/news/leaders/21660113-private-schools-are-booming-poor-countries-governments-should-either-help-them-or-get-out on "$1-a-week school". Perhaps that's a solution to improve schooling in poorer countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 12:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an old but great article... It has still relevance today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Economic Development and the Effectiveness of Foreign Aid: A Historical Perspective Edwards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 09:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bounded rationality matter: Paper on "Bounded Rationality and Voting Decisions over 160 Years: Voter Behavior and Increasing Complexity in Decision-Making" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 08:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 00:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is interesting to note that the slightly improving Greek economy in late 2014 fell back into a deep recession as Syriza (and Yanis Varoufakis) took power. Syriza is largely responsible for the banking crises and the forced banking holidays and the devastating current economic situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research paper on "Military careers of politicians matter for national security policy" with special data from Switzerland (video summary available) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 00:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 15:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is interesting that you need a complicated model to explain a simple phenomenon. Supply and demand analysis would most likely be sufficient too, i.e. there are some costs of "working as a prostitute", e.g. marriage chances, social stigma, etc. Interestingly Arunachalam, Raj, and Manisha Shah. "Prostitutes and brides?." The American Economic Review (2008): 516-522. http://www.jstor.org/stable/29730074 do not find any evidence for the mechanism suggested by Edlund   Korn (2002). In fact, they find the opposite: Prostitutes are more likely to be married...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 14:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be great if the stars also looked at the scientific results on the effectiveness of aid... most aid is not very effective and further research instead of gospels are required. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now paper on "Economic Development and the Effectiveness of Foreign Aid: A Historical Perspective" by Sebastian Edwards (NBER, Worlbank, ...) in Kyklos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 14:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New scientific paper on "Why Democracies Outgrow Autocracies in the Long Run: Civil Liberties, Information Flows and Technological Change" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 12:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those born on a Friday the 13th, don't fret! Everything is fine... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 21:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a new paper in Kyklos Review the authors find little evidence that people born on the 13th or those born on Friday the 13th are significantly less likely to be employed, earn lower wages or that they are more likely to stay unmarried compared to people born on other days. See: http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/resolve/doi?DOI=10.1111%2Fkykl.12085#.Vb5qKwmgf5Y.reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
