<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2561</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Clinton: Resurgent nationalism taking us to the edge of our destruction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no, don't take away the sacred ground that is already at r/butter. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, what's step 3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have the Delta amex card or any Delta medallion status, they're offering it discounted for $79 / year.

https://clearme.com/delta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it's 2k spend for 25K, but ditto that this is a great card to store your MR points with no AF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, and if you don't have the no fee Everyday card, now's a good time to get one. 25K/$2k offer via incognito, or if you can't get that then there's the usual 15K/$1k referral offer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure! The best offer is for points that you (personally) would use.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A: The US did not actually land astronauts on the moon in 1969. Rather, it was all a plot to one-up the Soviets in the space race. President Kennedy had promised in 1962 that we would reach the moon by the end of that decade, ahead of the others. With Cold War tensions reaching a zenith during this decade (Bay of Pigs, Vietnam), the US had to find a way to show that it had the scientific and technological advantage over the USSR. However, with the current level of technology, it was impossible to successfully bring humans to the moon and back, as suggested by former Rocketdyne engineer Bill Kaysing and others. Thus, the government and NASA staged a fake launch and moon landing, just in the nick of time before the decade ran out.

B: The Apollo program was designed and carried out throughout the 1960s with the precise goal of landing Americans on the moon's surface. With the Space Race ongoing during the Cold War, the government pumped money into NASA's R D to make this happen. American ingenuity and engineering has never been wanting, we're only constrained my money, and by God we were able to do it. The Apollo ship and capsule design was rapidly iterated over the various Apollo missions. 11 missions were made in 3 years, each fixing the problems faced by the last one and slowly getting closer to reaching the moon. Apollo 8 reached the moon and made several orbits of it. Apollo 10 made it to just 50km above the lunar surface. And finally, in July 1969, Apollo 11 and its astronauts made the landing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just a hazy blur of static when you try to look into the future? If so, that's probably accurate... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *it was apple grab-a-tree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The DASH Diet, 20 Years Later </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the article they're going to start deploying the ARM-based hardware to Microsoft data centers first. I agree for the prosumer and high end market Intel will continue to be the top choice, but I could see the ARM servers start to be "silently" used in cloud computing / VMs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft unveils new ARM server designs, threatening Intels dominance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No White House likes it when intelligence agencies  such as the National Security Agency, the Central Intelligence Agency or the Defense Intelligence Agency  deliver bad news, or when that information undercuts the executives preferred policies or political positions. But I cant remember another White House so quick to dismiss those agencies judgments or so willing to discredit them as dishonest or incompetent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former CIA and NSA Director OpEd: How Trump Undermines Intelligence Gathering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Magnetic hard drives go atomic: Physicists demonstrate the first single-atom magnetic storage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the upgrade offer have any lifetime restrictions similar to a new card sign up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try generating one through this link, it gave the 50K bonus offer, whereas going through the Amex account page gave me the 35k.

https://www262.americanexpress.com/business-card-application/raf/200552-OPEN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah bummer, didn't realize you couldn't combine those. Hope something works out friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep like that. You can redeem blocks 5000 skymiles for $50 off the cash price of your ticket.

http://www.delta.com/content/www/en_US/skymiles/use-miles/pay-with-miles.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a Delta Amex? If so, you can use the Pay With Miles option which lets you pay the cash price using Skymiles at a rate of 1cpp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www262.americanexpress.com/business-card-application/flexapp/platinum-delta-skymiles-business-credit-card/apply/45282-9-0-C1CD61DFC0ABFEEB0022A8EF0D24A09AF630B68437904BAA-201045-o4AuoeISx2TucBLPQ0djwPT*mLs=?cellid= cellid= om_rid=NwsyP9 om_mid=_BY3yXAB9MGjLX. om_lid=axp6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of retention offer was it, if I may ask? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intro: Here's looking specifically at one of the differences between it and the Affordable Care Act (ACA), regarding the individual mandate. The ACA required that all Americans purchase health insurance, either through employer, through the individual marketplace, or access it through Medicare/Medicaid. If the individual lived in a state that did not expand Medicaid access (19 states), they were exempt from the mandate. The new bill removes this mandate, allowing people to go without insurance. However, if someone has no insurance and then decides to get insurance, they can be charged up to a 30% premium.

Paragraph A: The new bill provides more financial freedom to people who do not wish to purchase health insurance. For example, young and healthy people will likely not need to get much health work done, and so can save money by not getting insurance. If someone does have a chronic illness, or acutely becomes sick, they can always sign up for insurance with no more than a 30% surcharge.

Paragraph B: Requiring everyone to have insurance is a way to ensure the sustainability of insurance programs. Even though young, healthy people will likely not need to undergo much care, their payments would support those who do need it. Removing the mandate will cause insurance premiums to increase, since those needing healthcare will be more likely to actually purchase insurance, and not people who are healthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drives straight through the competition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CSP and the Green Card? What is this, TPG? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I got a D on my acid/base chemistry exam, does that mean I got a pHD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the Camera Inside Apple? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If i should be able to buy healthcare instead of a new iPhone, then does phone insurance count as health insurance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy guacamole! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will post within 24 hours of completing the flight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Factual if actual </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes you do, unfortunately. The once per lifetime refers to you ever having that card, not actually receiving a bonus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The study looked at taxis of different colors and corrected for other factors besides color, suggesting that it is indeed the color (yellow being easier to see) that improves safety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flickr tags could help predict floods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No issues, though it might be worth letting chase know that you plan to make a large transaction so they don't flag it as fraud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I had done something similar with my BCE, they told me the minimum was $500 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You certainly could get both </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://refer.discover.com/s/ipnek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yellow taxis safer than blue ones, study concludes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the main tenets of the ACA is to improve preventive care, which will lower the cost of healthcare over the course of decades. It is not really designed to ameliorate catastrophic care.

An article in the New England Journal looked at ER visits in Massachusetts after the state passed insurance reform (which is what the ACA is modeled after). The authors found there was no real significant change in ER utilization when compared to two other states which did not have similar reform.

http://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMp1109273#t=article </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The silver lining of this bill is that it may not get full support from the GOP. Many will want to have more cuts while simultaneously having to live up to Trump's rhetoric that no one will lose insurance.

Though I'm sure that if this doesn't get passed, there will just be another version coming up shortly, and this saga will continue... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sens. Rob Portman (R-Ohio), Shelley Moore Capito (R. W.Va.), Cory Gardner (R-Colo.) and Lisa Murkowski (R-Alaska) said they would vote against any reform bill that fails to protect Americans who became eligible for coverage under the ACAs expansion of Medicaid. 

 With 52 Republicans, McConnell would not have enough votes to pass repeal without the support of at least two of those senators.

If you live in any of those 4 states, it is especially important to call and speak to these Senators' offices. They could be a make it or break it for this bill (whatever variation ultimately comes to a Senate vote) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Republicans release long-awaited plan to repeal and replace Obamacare // This is supposed to come up for a House vote later this week. Call your representatives (both House and Senate) let them know your thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah sorry, expires next month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a flyer for the Chase Total Checking $300 / Chase Savings $200 bonuses. Lemme know if you want the code.

Edit: and it's gone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, username doesn't quite check out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This poo shall pass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *recursive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine and Russia face off in U.N. court over separatist conflict </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump states his 'total confidence' in AG Sessions despite bipartisan calls for Sessions to recuse himself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico economy minister to meet with Ford, GM in Detroit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Left threatens Trump-friendly senators with primary challenges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abuse survivor quits pope's commission citing 'shameful' resistance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders rips Trump for 'stirring up fear and hatred' with speech guests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia, China block U.N. sanctions on Syria over gas attacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oscars envelope handler was too busy tweeting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oscars envelope handler responsible for Best Picture mix-up was too busy tweeting to do their job properly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Believes Obama, Former Aides Are Behind Leaks, Protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC chief doesnt plan to review AT TTime Warner merger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Bush on NBC: media is "indispensable to democracy" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Oscar statuettes legally cannot be sold by winners or their heirs unless first offered back to the Academy for $1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump administration re-evaluating self-driving car guidance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYT executive editor: Trump is the best thing to happen to our subscriptions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blackberry's new KEYone phone has a physical keyboard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fasting diet may help regenerate a diabetic pancreas (Mouse study) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC to halt rule that protects your private data from security breaches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CDC Report] Death from drug-overdose has increased in all age groups between 1991 and 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico says does not need U.S. aid under review by Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State Dept. memo - on dangers of leaks - leaks to media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC votes to lift net neutrality transparency rules for smaller internet providers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not best of times for US - Supreme Court Justice Ginsburg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA Telescope Reveals Largest Batch of Earth-Size, Habitable-Zone Planets Around Single Star </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Washington Post: 'Democracy dies in darkness' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verizon is planning 5G tests in 11 cities this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May hosts French presidential candidate Emmanuel Macron </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verizon Hacks $350 Million From Yahoo Deal After Massive Data Breaches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kasich tentatively slated to meet with Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not My President! declare anti-Trump protesters in Atlanta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists arent happy with Trump. So what are they going to do about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 33 questions about Donald Trump and Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Impeach President Bannon' signs pop up around country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: the Trump administration is planning to tweak its travel ban  but maybe not enough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schiff: Trumps attacks on intelligence community are 'deeply counterproductive' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pentagon chief: NATO now has Trump's 'full support' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Zuckerberg is worried about sensationalism in news. He should look in the mirror. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans need to protect themselves from Trump  now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House denies Flynn replacement pick turned down job over staffing dispute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump tweets: Retired general a candidate to replace Flynn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung chief Lee Jae-yong arrested for bribery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The frontrunner to be the next national security adviser is basically the anti-Flynn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 23:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Dems want Pruitt vote delayed over emails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York Times, Newsmax fall victim to fake Flynn Twitter account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feds cite D.C. charters for high suspension rates, particularly for black students </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pelosi to Trump: Time to tell Flynn 'you're fired!' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warren hammers Labor nominee with 83 questions ahead of hearing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former GOP rep to Trump: 'Stop complaining and do your job' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Obama official: Repealing Obamacare will hurt seniors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's official inauguration poster has glaring typo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'SNL' scores highest ratings in 6 years with Alec Baldwin as host </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> States are gambling with law enforcement safety </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Senate bill aims to make sure federal scientists arent muzzled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can now get Amazons Alexa to order your usual drink at Starbucks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congressional Hispanic Caucus requests meeting with ICE officials after raids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP bill would gut EPA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-spy chief: I don't know of any intel that proves need for travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC should retain net neutrality for sake of consumers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump blasts CNN: Cuomo never asked Blumenthal about 'long-term lie' of serving in Vietnam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blumenthal: We're careening 'toward a constitutional crisis' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intel, Trump tout new $7 billion investment to create 10K jobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders: Vote to silence Warren is an 'outrage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP senator on Warren: People need to be called out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> C-SPAN: DeVos confirmed as Secretary of Education 51-50 with VP voting as tie breaker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A dollar bill goes up to a Euro note </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 20:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and starts making self-depreciating jokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OPCW Won the Nobel Peace Prize </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 17:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first reaction was "Syriasly??" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a med student's favorite romance novel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 17:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fifty Shades of Gray's Anatomy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
