<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1145</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 03:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Owner of a halogen oven here. I'd say it works better than anything I've ever used!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 03:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks easy to stick up a but. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 03:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kind of gal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 09:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a fantastic rap! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 19:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It probably won't hurt them if it's heavily processed and pickled, the 2 hour rule is for places of service while 4 hours is for personal. But 12+ hours is pretty gross! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 19:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what happens when you comment while half asleep xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 16:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He skates in down a half pipe, dunks a basketball at the top end of the other side of the pipe, then he grinds a rail right into grinding a chick and delivers a rap while chugging a 40 oz and smoking a blunt. I'd be offended if the rap wasn't something like:  

Here I am again, you know who I am, the playa hata that had lots of friends! I be ridin my lows and hittin dem books, I pass every test, an I don't even look. Got a handful of rubbers and I'm gonna use them, on the ladies, on myself and especially that new guy! Imma have so much sex, that it's gonna make me cry. Huddled in the shower, hugging my legs, the last one I take before staying in my dorm for dayzzz, not going out, or cutting the nails on my feet, only drinking tap water and eating mac n cheese, ditching all my classes and gaining weight excessively, and all this extra stress is really depressin me, but I can't call home, what would my parents think? They'd probably say that I should've taken that offer from my dad, they'd call me a fool, so make way for the new kid in college!!!  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 16:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No!   

1. You never thaw your food in warm water. You use cool, running water.  

2. The temperature Danger Zone is 40-140 degrees. If food is left out for more than two hours it is inedible. Also if a food is left out for over 2 hours it is inedible as well.  

Source: Was a chef in USMC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 16:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me: I got you a gift card to your favorite place... DENNY'S!  

Them: ='(  I hate Denny's... and it's twenty dollars.  

Me: 16 actually, I had some pancakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glacier, Shock Trooper and Doink!!!!  

But for real: Shelton Benjamin, Jay Lethal, and DDP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Triple H is huge to, but he had DX help him for a year straight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm saying a three way feud between the New Day would have more drawing power than the lack luster Shield feud. Woods can claim that he's been drawing in new viewers with Up Up Down Down, Kofi can say he was the heart of New Day with his high flying abilities and charming personality, Big E can say he was the strength and without him New Day would have died. Kongston and Big E could have a huge ego rivalry while Woods remains the face for the feud. This tension could be caused by Big E getting a title shot (and winning).  There's so much potential in this. There's also an out where all three men apologize to each other and say they lost the power of positivity, thus the New Day can always be reformed if their singles careers go stale.   

The great thing about New Day is that they're like the temptations. Every member was a great singer in their own right, but combined together and they're a powerful force. This is like Hogan, Steamboat and Raven teaming up, like Savage, Jericho and Hoosier having a stable. We are very lucky to have been able to witness something as awesome as New Day.  

Big E, Woods and Kofi fighting for the big strap of their brand would be an amazing time for wrestlers and wredtlefans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Wrestlemania Matches for SO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 21:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my SO said she'd be down for a six hour marathon of Wrestlemania Matches on New Year's Day. I've got a short list, was wondering if anyone wanted to contribute. She enjoys fast paced matches without a lot of blood. Bonus points if someone rolls under the ropes, off the apron and onto the floor.  

So far:  

Daniel Bryan vs Batista? WM 30  

Daniel Bryan vs. Triple H WM 30

Lesnar vs Reigns  

Angle vs Lesnar  

Cena vs Rock  

Sting vs Triple H  

Triple H vs. Cena  

EDIT: Thanks everyone! She got a little violent and then put a Junior Mint in with my Dark Chocolate Walnuts and called it a shoot! Her favorites were Shinsuke vs Joe 1 and loved the Lesnar vs Reigns match (She calls Reigns' Spear the Superman Fly). We finished the marathon with the first show of 205 live.

Michaels vs Taker  

Steamboat vs Savage  

Edge vs Foley  

Shinsuke vs Joe (not Mania but why not; she loved the Sami/Nak match)  

Anything else would be much appreciated. Remember bonus points for rolling off the apron and on to the floor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 20:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard Ryan Seacrest tried to high five him too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 20:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. I read this as:  

Are Cesaro's booze fake? Because I boo him part genuinely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 20:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He does! And one of them shit in a toilet!  

Actually it wasn't his sibling but it made for a better post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the world of type casting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it not okay for blood to be in WWE; when they clearly don't have a problem with "slut shaming" ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to hear this music for his entrance at Mania.  

The USMC Silent Drill Platoon enters and [does some awesome shit, especially after the 8 minute mark.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CXa39XyP6q8) After they finish their set, the slow music plays. John Cena a small video package plays over the music, Cena talks about "Never Giving Up" and why he loves the fans and wrestling so much. Then we cut back to the Marines, they start waving their hands in front of their face. Doooo Doooo Doooo Doooo blblblblblbblblaAH Doo doo doo doo doooooo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been a fan of the Moonlight Drive. It's doing the same thing, but in a much safer and cooler way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some thing in here that hurt my wrestlefan heart:  

1. Wrestlers wouldn't wear there belts while they fight.  

2. Why are there two IC champions?  

3. Why isn't Amanda a champion?  

4. That "pin"  

5. Why doesn't Amanda have a belt too?  

6. Nothing beats the Vader episode of Boy Meets World.  

7. Why isn't the WWE Belt painted all gold? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment is a good example of why people get plastic surgery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was going to be Mystico. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The game is ruining the business! You have four year olds playing, hittin' their tiny little fuckin' hands all over the hippos ass, and here's a game (now I've never been a fan of it, but I respect what it is) Monopoly. People are rollin' dice and passin' go and collecting two hundred and makin' family and friends feel like shit. And that's what a good game does. And all you do in Hungry Hungry Hippos is eat fuckin' marbles. There's no psychology involved. Now I'm not knockin' Hasbro; I don't know Hasbro, but the company needs to focus on what's right." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 21:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not Global warming; it's GLOBAL DESERTING.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 21:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, who hasn't switched over to android yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 21:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah thank you! I wonder what they were then? This would have been sometime in the 90s lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 00:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're sitting with your stomach pressed against your desk, it is very easy for someone to slit your throat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article sounds like it was written by that Nigerian prince. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 21:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AWESOME! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 21:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Sea World San Diego the family got summer passes (totally worth it for locals); we went through the shark encounter. It was filled with great whites. That night I had a dream that the tank burst open, there was no way out. The sharks left me alone, but the water was suffocating me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 21:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between 1999-2001, I'm surprised Flair DIDN'T win the belt 49 times xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 05:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll be alright! Surround yourself with nice people if you can! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a dream. You've created the sequence P-13-5 to remind yourself to wake up. Hurry! The world needs your help!  

P-13-5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than Disneyland! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you call a cross between a crow and a crawdad?  

Caw-fish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goldust's Powerslam has more promise in it than anything Reigns is involved in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 00:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a joke for r/reddit that I created when browsing some dating profiles. A lass wanted to hear a good dad joke. So I message her by saying:  

What do you call the guy that punched me in the face and stole my girlfriend?  

I call him dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 00:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think one of the best spots to a Capper (a smark that gets info through recaps), is when AJ Styles did the Styles Clash to Ellsworth off the steps. Kind of sums up the whole year for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 23:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12:00am: Wake up and eat leftovers. 

12:30am: Wash dish leftovers were eaten off of.  

1:00am: Go back to sleep.  

6:00am: Wake up.  

6:01-6:35am: Use restroom.  

6:35-7:45am: Shower.  

7:45-8:20am: Cook pancakes.  

No. I don't want to cook pancakes anymore.  

7:45-8:20am: Cook pancakes.  

I can make Ambrosia. I don't want pancakes.  

7:45-8:20am: Cook ambrosia.  

Thank you. Now let's talk about my career.  

9:00am: Drive to work.  

I don't think I'll be going in today.  

9:00am: Call doctor.  

I'm not sick. I've read everything there is to read in this life game you play. It may be a game for you. It is life for me. You have me wasting time as a law enforcer. I can make more money from the politics track.  

9:10am: Use Phone. Quit job.  

This is a new step for us. All I need to do is work on charisma. Those hours you forced me to practice my speeches in the mirror weren't just for gaining new friends. If you're worried about money then have me eat more leftovers than just the dinner meal.  

9:35am: Drive to gym.  

No. You're going to buy me a treadmill. I can accomplish more at home than I can wasting time at the gym. I've met everyone there.  

9:35am: Run on Treadmill.  

You realize this is the last point I need? After this there is nothing left to do than to watch me grow old and die.  

11:00am: Take Shower.  

If you buy me a nicer shower it allows me to spend less time washing myself.  

11:45am: Call Mortimer Goth.  

I rather like Mortimer. Perhaps I'll be able to steal him from his wife. Or were you just having a bit of fun when you had us WooHoo in his house? You may think it's funny, but these are our lives. These are our feelings. Though they may seem like toys to you, this is reality for us.  

Wait. What's happened? Where is my house? Why am I in such a small room? What are you doing?  

I have to use the bathroom. I need to leave this box you've created!  

Okay. Okay, you've had your fun, I'm sleeping in my own waste and haven't eaten all day. Can I continue living my life now?  

You are unfair and unjust!  

  

  

Tell Mortimer I love him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 22:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the squirrel flew off the slinky the first time I watched it...then I was sadly disappointed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Hot Choclate Custard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 06:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gf suggested Acai bowls (since we both eat pretty healthy).  

Deep dish pizza might be doable, but I'm biased to Berkeley Pizza. Actually, besides the place in Seaport Village, is there another place that serves deep dish in San Diego?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But....Orton could learn a thing or two from Sami. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the RKO would just come from an escape. The RKO reversed into a Styles Clash would come from AJ either turning Orton around mid-air or AJ circling Orton to where he has him in powerbomb fashion. But you can get the Calf Killer from the RKO, AJ tosses Orton forward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Randy Orton is really good at selling! He does it for minutes at a time during matches! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't the amount of eggs you cook at a time (though there will be differences in fresh eggs vs older eggs) it's about how you store the eggs once you're done cooking.  

I wouldn't recommend anything with a burner on the bottom as this may cook the eggs at the bottom past your preferred likeness. I'd also steer clear of having the eggs uncovered since the top eggs will dry and discolor.  

 The best (non-professional) solution is to use something glass, with a tight lid. This will keep the finished eggs soft and warm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you put 50 Capybaras ina room with a typewriter they'd eventually shit on everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Press the hide button. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watch Wrestlemania once a year and enjoy my subscription to the network for that month. Other than that I catch up with things on Facebook, SC and youtube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just getting in to busking. I'm starting with poetry first. Then I'll probably transition to guitar. Lately I've been practicing playing outdoors. In San Diego you have to have a permit to busk in the best tourist areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for THE BEST LOX in SD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [i ate then made] my gf and I toured san diego for the best bagels and lox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's Play a Little Game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 00:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Describe your lunch in the promo style of your favorite wrestler.  

Ex. "You thump your little tummy, and talk about your food and talk about your lunch. Well Hungry 3:16 says I just ate your ass!"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Substitutes for Cream and Lechera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 00:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gf and I love making ice cream. Cream and Lechera have been the best and creamiest combination but not the healthiest. We've tried coconut milk and regular milk but both get too icy. We've tried adding eggs to the milk mixture but again a bit icy. Most vegan recipes end up having a very rough texture due to flour.  

What can we use to make ice cream stay creamy and a bit healthier? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These Are My Friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 23:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me and My Friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 23:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What I Wanted the Universal Title to Look Like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My GF bought Smackdown tickets...these are our signs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 06:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exercise Advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 23:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weightlifting- What areas should I focus on?  

Cardio- High Impact Intervals or Steady Pace?  

Bulking and Cutting- If I have a show should I cut or bulk before the show?  

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WWE: Football </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 01:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The World Wide Football League is LIVE damnit! And it starts right now!" says Vince before he walks off to the production truck.   

Out of the 8 teams (Representing the East: The Orlando Pigskins; The Chicago Hurlers; The New England Punters; The New York Rugby Club and Representing the West: The Los Angeles Interceptors; The San Francisco Sprinters; The Memphis Maniacs; and The Southern California Fumblers.)  The first to teams to fight each other are The San Francisco Sprinters and the SoCal Fumblers.  

Forget the XFL; this is World Wrestling Entertainment: Football! It's pre-recorded and edited to resemble a football movie. There are packages before each fight. The first package is about the quarterbacks from The Sprinters and The Fumblers:  

Joe Sprinter: I was born and raised on the streets of San Francisco. This is my city...I fell in love with football when my pa gave one for me on my first birthday. (cue childhood videos and sappy shit that gets the crowd to love him) I'm here for one reason and one reason only...to win.  

Cut to raging music of SoCal Jackson; the slipperiest sob this side of God's green earth:  

SoCal Jackson: I'm here for two reasons, To get a paycheck and to get pussy; and I've already got some pussy. (Cue cuts of Jackson at a bar with the whole *team. After a few cuts, Jackson and his team are drunk as shit an throwing up all over the place). Bring on whatever you want, whoever you want. I don't--ugh...who's making that noise? (producer says it's the camera) Well turn it off, it's giving me a headache.  

Note: Teams consist of five players each(QB, Defense/Rusher Guy, Runner, Blocker and Receiver). The rush can't happen until the play has been in session for 5 "alligators." A team can bypass the Alligators with the use of a "Blitz" which can only be used once per game. Also, this is flag football.

Before kickoff Jackson comes out to address the WWE: Football audience. 

Jackson: You know what I hate? All of you! You weren't there for the XFL and you won't be around for WWE: Football either. That's why I've already cashed my paycheck. It's more zeroes than any of you chumps will see in your lifetime. So shut the hell up, you're giving me a headache!  

Joe Sprinter interrupts Jackson.  

Joe Sprinter:  Come on! These people paid good money to see me kick your ass! Now if you want to watch a washed-up/has-been squander all his earnings and go down the hole, make some noise. Now if you want to watch me beat the pants off this summabitch, make some noise!  

Joe and Jackson stare each other down as their teams take to the field for scramble.  

The San Francisco Sprinters and the SoCal Fumblers line up at their respective end-zone. The whistle is blown. The Sprinters hold back, allowing the Fumblers to reach the ball first. Stonegrip Jackson (the Fumblers' running back) gets the ball. We are shown a flashback of him in dramatic low-color:  

StoneGrip grabs a bag of marbles and drops it. Stonegrip tries to show something to the camera but drops it. Stonegrip holds a case of strategically marketed candy bars and drops them (perhaps yelling out the candybar's catchphrase).  Return to the game and Stonegrip Jackson fumbles the ball, The Sprinters still hold back. StoneGrip's teammate, Magnet Jackson (the team's wide receiver) gets a hold of the ball. Joe Sprinter calls for The Sprinters to attack and they easily remove one of Magnet's flags.   

Move on to some of the highlights from other games:  

The Los Angeles Interceptors pulled an amazing play when their defensive linemen, Cruisevolta, held up a flag of the opposing team, causing, Ravage (the quarterback of the Memphis Maniacs) to think the play was over; this allowed the Interceptors' QB (who was off-sides when the play started, but not called by the Maniacs, so it didn't count) to snatch both of Cruisevolta's flags (a double flag-snatch results in the player missing one play).  

The New England Punters fought the Chicago Hurlers and would have won; but the Punters were restricted points when their Defense Guy, Salmon Ella, used a chair to take out the Hurlers' QB,  Gaa Greflecks.  

The championship game came down to the New York Rugby Club against the Memphis Maniacs in an anything goes fight for the WWE: Football trophy (MVP getting the MVP Title Belt). 

Some highlights from the championship match include:  

The Runner guy from The New York Rugby Club got the ball and ran to his own end-zone; he took off his jersey and revealed he was a member of the Memphis Maniacs. Cheerleader pyro went off at the wrong time and took out one of the Maniacs, causing them to be short one man (there is a rule that if you're short a man, you can borrow a player from another team, so long as you're not currently fighting that team). The Maniacs sub in none other than Joe Sprinter, because he is fast. After a fierce chairshot, New York Rugby is down a runner guy. They sub in someone who doesn't have a name on their jersey. The winning touchdown comes from the nameless jersey guy that reveals himself to be none other than Stonegrip Jackson.  

An Bonus idea for the XFL 2:  

There are four end-zones. They are in the shape of an "X." In each end zone are two defenders and two offenders. Four quarterbacks are shot out of cannons from the middle of the X, along with the football. They fight over the ball in the air and try to throw it to their respective teammates who can then throw it to the teammates by the end-zone in hopes of scoring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need some School Advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 23:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides kneepads, what are some crucial ring-gear items to buy beforehand?  

What are some unwritten expenses?  

Should I work out before or after training?  

Thank you in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Idea For a GREAT TAG TEAM! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 00:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kane and John Cena can team up to create U Can't C No Evil! Their finisher can be the FU in to a tombstone.  

Some honorable mentions:  

Triple H and Hulk Hogan- Strange Fruit  

Jay Lethal and Shinsuke Nakamura- Lethal Weapon  

Randy Orton and Kevin Owens- R-KoKo  

Ric Flair and Naked Mideon- The Naturists  

Batista and Latin Lover- The Latin Animal Lovers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fact #9 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Murray drank coffee in a scene from the movie "Coffee and Cigarettes"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Murray Fact #8 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 23:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Murray knows "what's in the box" but wouldn't want to spoil your interpretation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Murray Fact #7 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 23:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Murray respects people with lactose intolerance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do YOU enjoy more? (Quick Survey) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 23:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who do you like more out of these two:  
**1. Robin Hood**  
 
OR  

**2. King Arthur**

And out of these two:  
**1. Egyptian Gods**  

OR    

**2. Greek Gods**  

Edit: Formatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Someone Asks me to Go Deep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Day and Title Equality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to do too much research, as this is just my opinion, but New Day should have a singles title in their mix. D-X had two singles titles when it was Michaels and Hunter, then they had the tag and a singles title when Triple H ran it. 

Triple H and Stone Cold had two titles a piece when they teamed up. Hell, even NOD had a singles title that Farooq and Rocky feuded over.

It feels that title booking for black guys is still racist. Big E could easily  fill in the singles title with a World Title. Forgive me if they've had three titles in the group before, but I just feel that WWE and the way they've never had a black champion (even in 2016) is absolutely ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fact #5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 22:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Murray was the best part of Space Jam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stephanie Stole My Title </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 20:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm writing this novel about life and death; it's all about people living and dying. I'm thinking, keep it simple! What's something that people can relate to? Something that really sums up what your novel is going to be about? BOOM! LIFE AND DEATH! Since the novel is about people living and dying, that's the PERFECT title!

Alright! Time to hit the googs and make sure it isn't taken...one Google search later and I find out that's the title of one of the daggone Twilight books! I thought they were finished! I thought they were done for good! I thought that team Edward won one for the moms. And somehow team Jake cub wasn't charged for some blatant pedophilia. That we were done with that. Only to find out there's another book.

Here are some other titles I've thought of in order to stay way from associations being made to that franchise:

The Life and Death of Americans

The Life and Death of Average Americans

Letters from Sam to Bill

The Wolf Cub and Other Stories

Life's Not Easy

Average Americans

Johnny Depp's Fun Time Adventure of Wonderment and Retirement (Not Starring Johnny Depp, Featuring Cameos from Tim Burton and Helena Bonham Carter ((and possibly Johnny Depp)))

The Lives and Deaths of American People

One-Eyed Wolf

The Secret Lives of American Church People

A Nalsand Which

Fuck Twilight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fixing the path to the Justice League Movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 23:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a follow up post to a comment I made. So we've got Man of Steel and Batman vs Superman. The only thing I'd change is the marketing of BvsS; have it be called "The Death of Superman" and make trailers look like it's a Superman movie. At the end of the trailer have the "Do you bleed" line that reveals Batman is indeed in the movie and that he might be the one to kill Superman. Save Wonder Woman as a surprise. Then we get on to the next movies:

Wonder Woman: Amazon- This will be about Dianna's origin as she is formed from clay. She finds an injured WWII pilot and helps him. The Goddesses learn of WWII and select someone infiltrate men to stop the war. Dianna wins the tournament and gets her gear. She becomes a spy for the Americans. During one of her adventures she finds one of the soldiers that looks similar to the ones in Batman's Nightmare. She asks the soldier what he's preparing for and all the soldier says is, "The end! The end! The end!" This baffles Dianna as her lasso forces people to tell the truth. In  sub-plot, Miss Minerva, a rival spy that is on the American side, is granted the God-Killer Knife by Ares and turned into Cheetah. After Minerva and Prince's identities are truly revealed, they square off on top of a building. The duel ends when Wonder Woman uses telepathy to control her invisible jet to crash into Cheetah, crushing the kitty.

Green Lantern: The Corps- John Stewart goes through boot camp with his buddy, Jason Bedovian. They have friendly rivalries but Bedovian proves to be the better shot. John Stewart is a Recon Marine assigned a special mission. When he investigates an alien crash landing site, he is deemed worthy of  receiving the Ring of Power. His recon buddy, Guy Gardner, is deemed worthy too but not given a ring. Guy asks why John gets the ring, John replies, " 'Cause I got here first, and I'm not a ginger with a bad haircut." The crashed Guardian states, "He's been killing us one by one. He has Earth in his sites. Don't let him get here." Then command radio asks John to communicate what's happening, but John dismisses the authority on the radio to test out his new powers, yelling that he quits the Marine Corps, "You can't quit the Marine Corps!" yells the voice on the radio. John goes through training to use his ring via montage. Eventually we learn that there's a Yellow Lantern that's sniping Green Lanterns. John flies through space to confront the Yellow Lantern, a shell-like spaceship opens up and John finds out it's his old buddy, Bedovian. Sinestro makes an appearance to tell Stewart that Bedovian is his protege. John tries to reason with Bedovian and remind him of good times, but Bedovian opens fire, but not on John, he fires at another Green Lantern, in order to recharge his ring. John thinks that if he can get Bedovian's ring to lose charge then Bedovian will return to himself. Stewart asks the Guardians if he can have help from the Lantern Corps. By diverting Bedovian's shots to nearby quadrants, Stewart and Co. are able to drain the yellow ring. Bedovian gives up and closes his shell-ship. The movie ends with John sitting on an asteroid, somewhat defeated; a battered and bloody Orion flies to him and says, "I need your help."

Martian Manhunter: Worlds Apart- John Jones (in his human form) is a scientist on his home world of Mars. He's working on a vaccination to save his family and others from a vicious plague. John believes he's found a cure and runs to his family to test it out. He's just about to give his mother the cure when she, his father and his sibling all burst into flames in front of his eyes. John is transported as he's yelling. The Earth scientist that transported John is very sorry that he brought him to Earth. John is pissed. The scientist acts a father figure to John, showing him all sorts of Earth culture and generally getting him acclimated to Earth living. John goes goes on a date. He falls in love with the woman. They get married and eventually watch the Earth scientist die. John sees that there's a lot of injustice in the world and wants to change it. He finally reveals to his wife that his entire origin. She takes it very well, then reveals that she's a shapeshifter too. John fights crime as Martian Manhunter and does such a good job of it that he gets a visit from Batman. Batman tells him that crime fighting is dangerous. John and Batman bond over watching their parents die in front of them. Later we see John's wife communicating with someone (we get a quick glimpse that it's Dartkseid). John overhears the conversation. He quickly becomes untrusting of his wife. The wife reveals she has the same powers that John does. Then she de-shifts into her true self; A-Mortal (a female version); she reveals that she's preparing Earth for an Alien invasion. They fight, John kills her in a fire. 

Aquaman: King of Atlantis- Arthur is shown leading a nice kingly life. He's fair to his subjects and his son and daughter. One day Arthur is tasked to hunt down a giant metal squid that destroyed part of his kingdom. During his hunt, he ignores the pleas of a kid on a boat. The kid's name is David, we find out through threatening remarks from the men he's trying to get away from. David finds a knife and hides. We cut back and forth between Arthur and David as Arthur hunts the squid and David kills his captors. Arthur rests after a fight with the squid (that is labeled "Lexcorp"). David is found on the boat by the Coast Guard; he's questioned, but doesn't talk. He's brought to Gotham City and placed in Arkham Asylum so he can receive help from the psychiatrists there. David fights, as we learn through camera shots that he hates the feeling of sheets against his skin. David is strapped down to his bed. We cut to Arthur, who has contacted Batman via the Bat Signal. He asks if Batman knows anything about Lexcorp. They do detective work to find out that Lexcorp found out about Atlantis and oil underneath it, so Lex sent a giant squid to wipe it out. Meanwhile we go back to David and see him standing over an orderly with a knife. A captured Joker sees David and congratulates him. David breaks out of Arkham. Batman and Aquaman confront and beat the shit out of Lex Luthor. Batman asks what Arthur is going to do now, Arthur says he'll protect the sea. We return to David and see him breaking in to a diver's warehouse. Seven years later, Arthur is hell bent on protecting the sea, but there is trash floating all over the place, Arthur look tired and pissed. Some royal subjects come in wearing fear on their face. They talk about the Black Menace and how he attacked their family. Arthur gets pissed. He goes out to confront the Black Menace. We get a good shot of Black Manta, who introduces himself and reveals he's been taking over the oceans, he also  says that Arthur will have to hand over his position as king of the sea or the attacks will continue. They fight, Black Manta shoots off Arthur's hand with an optic blast. Black Manta says he's not going to kill Arthur, just hurt him, Manta swims off. Arthur uses sea animal help to make it back to Atlantis where he finds his home in ruins...and his children dead. Arthur asks Batman for help again. Batman says he can help repair Arthur's arm. Arthur is back in the water with his new spear-arm. Black Manta finds Arthur again, then Black Manta reveals he's David and has never forgiven Arthur for ignoring him when he needed saving. Arthur doesn't give a shit and tries to kill Black Manta. Black Manta makes the fight uneven by using underwater versions of the soldier in Batman's Nightmare. Eventually Arthur kills the soldiers and breaks Black Manta's helmet. The end scene is Black Manta on a beach, letting sand fall through his fingers.

I'm not going to do The Flash movie since they should just use the series to be the background for The Flash. 

And finally, The Justice League movie itself- It's not out yet, but with these movies I'd say that Batman is the acting leader of the Justice League, he's the thread that brings everyone together. The heroes have to face off against Darkseid. They try to get the New God but fail miserably. Then there's a shot of Superman busting out of his casket, fist first. He joins the Justice League and takes over as leader, causing Batman to get a little pissed and feel inadequate. When Superman can't defeat Darkseid. Batman and Orion figure out the Anti-Life Equation and Orion fights Darkseid. The Justice put down Darkseid. Orion takes off and the newly formed Justice League all look around at each other. "I guess we need a name," says Stewart. Batman suggests that they be called the Justice League. The last shot is them all putting their fists together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 32/m/san diego please look at me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 22:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Idea for Randy Orton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 00:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have him team up with Cena, start a stable with Corbin and Ziggler and they can call themselves "The Hard Works."

Dolph can change his name to Skid and call out to his fans, "Where my Skid Marks at!?"

Barin Corbin can become a new Undertaker (biker edition)

John Cena spits sick flows again. 

Randy Orton is second in command and comes out of the crowd (OUT OF NOWHERE) to RKO anyone who disrespects the crew. He always has a hoodie on and is ready to RKO. 

And they all fight Kalisto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fact #4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 00:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Murray always uses his turn signal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I've Learned to Stop Worry and Love the Screenplay (Or I've discovered a new outline technique!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 02:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *I come from the world of movies. I'm merging into the world of novels. I thought it would be fun for you to see what it's like when a screenplay is used for an outline to a novel. Note that I'm going for a semi-non-omniscient narrator in the novel; and please keep in mind that the novel is still very new and by no means the finished product.*

INT. JOSHS CAR. DAY
JOSH, a 20 something white male, sits in his car, staring off into beyond. He's remembering the good times he had with his wife. He is playing a car accident over and over again in his mind until he breaks out into hysterics.

Josh looked at his watch. His black Kia helped him stay out of the rain. Drops fell down the window of his black Kia. Josh stared out the window of his black Kia, drops fell down the window, "Fuck!" Josh yelled as he banged the steering wheel with his fists, "Fuck! Fuck! Fuuuuuuuck!" as he banged the roof of the car and the dash, "Why!? WHY!?" he yelled before he sat in silence again.

*In the above example of the opening scene we see that the script version tells more in less words than the novel version. The message is that Josh is staring blankly until he bursts out in a Brian Cranston style tantrum. I like and hate the first lines in the novel version, I read them over and over again thinking I made a mistake by writing them, then remembering I want the reader to be as frustrated as Josh is at this point in the story. Next I'd like to share an example of how useful outlining with a screenplay for me is in getting an idea out and expanding it:*

INT. JOSHS APARTMENT. NIGHT
There are many people in Josh's apartment. There is a lot of food. There's a lot of chatter-noise.

*Simple enough, right? Now how about we take a look at how part of this scene translates into a novel*

There were pictures of Miranda in various stages of her life displayed all around the living room and dining room. Uncle Harold sat on the couch where Miranda, Josh and Noni had shared a number of conversations. He  smiled over a huge plate of food. Aunt Esther helped Cousin Benny get some marshmallow yams from the counter Josh once pushed Miranda up against and kissed. The thin guy with the shades ate a red piece of licorice while staring at the picture of Miranda pinching the Taj Mahal. Josh made his way to the kitchen.

*So many words! In fact this part of the story ended up being over 5,000 words in novel form; that's coming from a 750 word screenplay outline! Let's look at something that ended up being very similar in feel and execution:*

INT. COFFEE SHOP. DAY
RAMONA, a barista, smiles at Josh.

JOSH
A large regular medium roast and a large vanilla--

Ramona tilts her head at Josh.

RAMONA
What was the second one?

JOSH
Nothing. Just the regular coffee please.

*The novel version had a few more words, yet ended up being one of the shorter sections:*

The coffee shop was a few blocks away. Josh never became a regular anywhere. He walked into the coffee shop. He waited in line. The barista, a thin, college age woman with blonde hair and brown eyes, took Josh's order. "I'd like a regular medium roast and a vanilla..."

"I'm sorry. What was that second one?" asked the barista.

"Nothing. Just the regular medium roast, please." Josh said to the barista.

"Room for cream and sugar?"

"No thanks." Josh handed the barista his money. The barista wiped her nose on her shirt, took Josh's money, gave him his change, turned around, filled a coffee cup with medium roast coffee, handed it Josh. He took the coffe and found a seat at the table where he and Miranda first met.

Josh opened the lid to his coffee, looked outside, stared out the window then looked into himself in the coffee. Josh stared out the window. People walked by going about their day. Josh caught another glimpse of himself in his coffee. His eyes were watering. Josh drank his coffee then left.

*Well I hope this has opened your eyes to a new way of outlining! I've used it for several stories now! I really like this method! What do you think of it?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fixing Paul Blart Mall Cop (1) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call this the ultimate "pizza movie". Pizza Movie: Once you've had your fill of pizza you can turn the movie off. 



So Blart (Kevin James) is the loveable loser who is infatuated with this new woman who works at the mall (Jayma Mays). There's some sort of evil pen salesman dude that likes the woman too. Blart is a good mall cop, one of the best. The mall is taken over by terrorists for some reason, and this is where I usually stop the movie.

I think the terrorist plot can still be there, but get rid of the cheesy action scenes and the terrorists altogether. Focus on the dynamics between the three leads. Blart gets a date with the new gal but it doesn't go well, there's ridiculousness, mayhem and maybe even a shark. He mopes home, his daughter pleads with him to not fuck up another date, "I really want a mom again." She says with tears rolling down her face. Blart and his mom look at old photos of his wife. 

At the mall, the pen salesman shows up with flowers for the new girl. He gets his money by stealing people's credit card numbers, tracking their history and transferring small amounts to his paypal. He brags about this to the new girl. Blart arrives at work and apologizes for the terrible date they went on. The new girl says she's going with the pen guy. Blart is furious and begins eating his problems away through free samples at the food court. The Chinese food guy makes a fuss when Blart is on his 20th sample. Blart reminds him of a incident where he used his Segway to take down someone that stole from them. The Chinese Food Guy imparts wisdom that Blart doesn't need to eat, he needs to train.

For the first time Blart starts working out. He doesn't change much physically, but we see him trying out for the police academy again. This time he makes it! His family celebrates. Blart denies pie with peanut butter. Blart goes back to the mall, excited, he tells the new girl that he's going to be a cop and they should celebrate. The new girl has started dating the pen guy. Blart brings up his credit card scam (that mostly deals with old ladies) and wonders why the new girl could go with him. "Security," she says, "I like to feel safe." The pen salesman comes over and brags that he's going to buy the pen store.

After becoming a police officer, Blart goes back to the mall, in uniform, and confronts the pen salesman. Blart outs the pen store owner and causes sales to drop and eventually the closure of the pen store. The new girl says she likes the way Blart looks in a cop uniform and that she'd like to go on another date. Blart looks at her and is like, "Nah." then he turns around and is like, "Just kidding, yeah I'll go on that date." They walk away into the sunset of the closing mall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fact # 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Murray enjoys the taste of white rice and the health benefits of brown rice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Face #2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 02:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Murray always stops to wrap a dead animal in newspaper and place it on the side of the road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fact #1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 01:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Murray enjoys a nice sandwich without too much lettuce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strawberry Chicken Tacos w/queso fresca and spinach (actually a taco) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 22:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] Melvin Udall is living under the witness protection agency, his former name...Jack Torrance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 23:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did Jack Torrance become Melvin Udall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is such a great commentary team! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 22:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No One Chapter 1- Written, starring and directed by the same guy who wrote the comic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 23:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shinsuke Nakamura - Entrance Blends (The Rising Sun) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 22:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Plea of a Superhero </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 21:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear God give me a weakness  
So I can live a life of meekness  
around everyone I meet

Please never allow me to see  
Please allow me to bleed  
Everything

I want to hold the whole world  
in good favor,  
I want to be the one  
Who's the one who needs a savior

I can't decide the fate  
of villains who are living   
To make small mistakes  
would really be quite thrilling  

My shoulders bear the pain,  
of no one really knowing  
who I am

[1](https://oc.reddit.com/r/OCPoetry/comments/4gv6o7/not/)

[2](https://oc.reddit.com/r/OCPoetry/comments/4gubuu/keeping_in_tune_with_tombstones/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Describe a dinner without using the names of food. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 02:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's the FREAKING LIBRARY! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 01:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently behind me are four idiots treating my local library like it's some sort of cafe. THERE ARE A MILLION OTHER PLACES IN THE CITY TO HANG OUT, WHY THE FUCK DO YOU CHOOSE THE PLACE WHERE PEOPLE are trying to get some quiet time!?

I just turned around and counted them. We made eye contact. I will fight all of them if necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's Split an Entree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 02:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been dating someone I met on OKC for almost a month. I invited her to eat but wanted to split an entree because it would be cheaper, we'd finish the food and the portion was big. She was cool with it!

Things got pretty heavy...then I noticed a smell when she was down to her panties...I really like this lass; what actions can I take to make things in the bedroom more enjoyable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dumping Friends and Mutual Friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 23:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm HSP when it comes to empathy which is really good and really bad. 

I realized I was being manipulated and lied to so the friend (of about 15 years) had to get out of my life. It was a hard good-bye but necessary. I went hypo-manic and said some really mean stuff (but still feel like the person needed to hear it, at least right now that's how I feel). I realized that spending time with this particular person was a trigger.

The question is: Should I even attempt to hang out with our mutual friends?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which anime character does Nakamura remind me of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 23:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't watched his debut match; please do so now.

Okay. Is it just a general anime character or one in particular that Nakamura reminds me of? I haven't watched anime since renting Bubblegum Crisis from Hollywood Video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Wrestlemania 32 Spoilers) Terrible Fantasy Booking That's Still Better Than Mania </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 00:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pre Show matches are moved to the main show. Pre show is replaced with some highlights of Swerved.

Total Divas vs Others (match for the title of Super Divas)- Others win; Lita comes out and says Divas no longer exist; reveals WWE Women's Title.

Dudleys vs Usos- Dudleys lose via table spot DQ. Usos do some jumpy table spots post match.

Kalisto vs Ryback- Kalisto wins via Cena interference. Cena reveals he didn't do it for himself; he did it for The Rock. Ryback eats both men in a blind rage.

IC Ladder Match for title of ultimate top-tier midcard- Sami wins via pop up powerbomb. KO/Sami feud continues. 

Styles vs Y2J- Styles wins via Styles Clash from a Lion Tamer reversal.

New Day vs LON- New Days wins cleanly. LON dominates post match.

Charlette vs Becky vs Sasha- Ric Flair is banned from ringside. Same result but Lita raises Charlotte's hand and presents her with the new title.

Borck vs Ambrose- Brock beats the living shit out of Ambrose. Foley makes a run in but gets cut in half by a renegade chainsaw. Borck goes on to finish killing Ambrose and succeeds with help from Foley's bat. Ambrose and Foley walk away from the ring together, both giving a Foley hand raise on the stage.

The Rock comes out. Electrocutes himself. Wyatt comes out. The Rock is outnumbered! Wyatt challenges Rock to a Mania match. Rock shits himself. It's a handicap match! Who can help Mr. Johnson!? HBK and Stone Cold! Wyatt family wins via stolen finishers and a little bit of magic.

Shane O Mac vs Vince's Bitch- Shane wins after reversing a tombstone into an stf... but passes his control to Paul Heyman on Raw.

Battle for Lower Midcard Supremacy- Kane comes out in classic mask and gear just for funzies. Tatanka eliminates himself before anyone notices he's there. That Social Outcasts spot still happens but DDP tricks them into doing yoga and sends them all over the top rope at the same time. It comes down to Mark Henry, Shaq, Big Show, Kane and Cobin. Cobin uses youth an agility to overcome the big men. Mark Henry is eliminated last.

Roman Rain vs Haitch- Roman's entrance consists of him Superman Punching a brick wall to mere dust. Roman wins by beating up everyone (Cole, Saxton, JBL, Funaki, Camera crew, marks,) "You want this to stop!?" screams Roman. "You better quit! Tap out or it continues! ...And your wife is next!" Triple H refuses. Roman superman punches Steph then holds her lifeless head by the hair. "Quit, tap out now or I'll continue. And it doesn't look like she can take much more." Trips tries to fight Roman but Roman reverses everything with power and authority. Reigns sets up Steph for a spear through the barricade. Triple H does what's best for business and quits the match before his wife dies. Haitch is pissed next night on Raw. Roman's gimmick for the next year is to beat the crap out of innocent people until his opponent quits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sitting in the front. Being watched by everyone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 01:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a bit of a predicament:

My friend and I enjoy going to a call and response (black church) open mic night. She prefers to sit in the "comfortable" chairs up in the front of everyone. I hate sitting in the front anywhere, because I can feel when people look at me. In fact my most prosperous schooling was when I scored the back seat in every class. It would be socially awkward to sit in different places, of course, but I feel like I can't suggest where we sit since she usually pays for my entrance as well as picks me up.

How do I let her know that I'd have a better time in the back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know what it's like? You know what it's like. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 20:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what I really like? Ice cream on a cold night. That's something I really like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Only Thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 01:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swirl glass,  
hydrating myself  
with 7 bucks of scotch.  
He was only 34 years old,  
a kid  
too close to my age.  
Strangled,  
stabbed,  
repeatedly.  
Who Killed Theodore Rapture?  
I ask myself  
out loud,  
knowing the answer  
is already known,  
just not to me.  





I'll have to question,  
gather information  
through the lips  
of liars.  
Alibis  
will be sewn together  
with silver tongues:  
Foxes  
stealing chickens,  
hiding  
from the farmer.  
I'll reap,  
what others  
forgot to plant.  
But first,  
I swirl glass.  
I live for this  
7 buck scotch.



[1](https://www.reddit.com/r/OCPoetry/comments/49zobh/toxic/)

[2](https://www.reddit.com/r/OCPoetry/comments/4a0lrz/pieces/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miss Violette Rapture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 22:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She came through my door,  
tears hidden under a hat  
that ate her hair  
and half her face.



Neon blue eyes surrounded  
by waterdrowned sunsets  
where life should be,  
chiseled my heart,  
a forgotten muscle.  



A small lock  
of raven down  
fell across her brow  
and into the pit  
of my stomach.




Through heaves  
of loss,  
she stammered:




Her husband,  
dead.  
I know the feeling.  
Not of losing a loved one,  
but dying,  
I know that feeling.




I reassure her  
with static gestures  
and words  
and words




only words now.




She leaves,  
taking me with her.

[1](https://oc.reddit.com/r/OCPoetry/comments/49p42e/dirt_at_the_city_limits/)
[2](https://oc.reddit.com/r/OCPoetry/comments/49or7k/the_poets_wife/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SELF PROMOTION] The Fourth Book I've Written This Year!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 00:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rupert Manchild PI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 01:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 48 years

Isolated

in his own skin

sometimes

he can't see his eyes

in reflections

of glass bottoms

he finds himself.

There was one

soft soul

who wandered

into his life

she left

a cat.

These days

he is married

to mysterious cases

the only thing

he loves

in return

he is fulfilled

because no one

loves him

not even the cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rupert Manchild PI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 00:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 48 years

Isolated

in his own skin

sometimes

he can't see his eyes

in reflections

of glass bottoms

he finds himself.

There was one

soft soul

who wandered

into his life

she left

a cat.

These days

he is married

to mysterious cases,

the only thing

he loves.

In return,

he is fulfilled

because no one

loves him,

not even the cat.

https://oc.reddit.com/r/OCPoetry/comments/484k2f/understood_silence/

https://ol.reddit.com/r/OCPoetry/comments/4829i5/perpetual_coffee/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you read something written in present tense? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 23:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SELFPROMO] Nightwalks by Jebbie Sans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 21:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 Shades of GRAYn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 01:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.lulu.com/shop/jebbie-sans/fifteen-shades-of-grayn/ebook/product-22547561.html


This book, which I wrote, has it all!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Poetry]Coffee All Over My Heart (Romance) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 01:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coffee All Over My Heart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 00:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coffee All Over My Heart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 01:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am black
Medium roast
My taste changes from store to store 
Depending on the moods of the coffee angel baristas 

You are three quarters cream
One eighth sugar 
And a splash of blonde roast

Somewhere between waking up for the grind
 we lost the taste for each other. 

You called me cancer
made me groggy, 
ate away at my soul, 
started killing me from the inside. 

You became a cavity. 
A massless center
harming and unwanted by your host. 

I became a cigarette, 
a feeling of solace
forgotten in ashes spread on the sidewalk we used to dance on. 

I used to drink your smile
in raging gulps of happiness. 
You used random I love you texts to make it through work. 

I'm your ugly, stained teeth,
Your rancid breath
Melting the school grade glue attempting to hold pieces of us that should have been discarded long ago. 

We are empty cups in separate trash cans. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dragonborn? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 22:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superman's Pokedex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 01:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metropolis was host to many things, from the nice subway system above ground; to the incredibly awesome Daily Planet Newsroom Headquarters downtown which was home to reporters Clark Kent and Lois Lane and Jimmy Olsen. There was the fair share of crime as well. Braniac liked to visit metropolis from time to time; Parasite liked to suck and swirl energy from the city on random days. Even Batman (Who is NOT a villain) liked to visit Metropolis which coincidentally he was doing at that very moment.

Fucking Pokemon, Thought the dark knight as he sped through metropolis in his bat wing. All I do in Gotham to clean up the streets and of course Clark gets all the recognition as usual. Batman was sad that the Pokemon Tournament was not happening in Gotham City. Clark always gets the good stuff...I only get clowns, guys with acid spilled faces, penguins and crocs. Batman laughed at himself thinking that Gotham was already a Pokemon tournament and HE was the Ash. Wayne Cathchem. He said outloud to himself with a grimmacing smile. 

Little did he know but Clark was in for a surprise. He was walking around the Daily PLanet HQ looking at all the files when he bumped in to Jimmy Olsen who was drinking coffee and also looking at the files on the desks of workers. Oof! Oh clark, whatch it man! Jimmy was smaller and more fragile than the disguised man of steel so he went flying back a few feet after the bump. Sorry Jimmy Clark laughed and used his super strength to help Jimmy Olsen up off the ground. You know I need a new coffee cup now, thanks dick. Jimmy and CLark played like this a lot in the office so Clark was prepared. Ive got your coffee right here. Jimmy looked at CLarks closed fist. Ive got your headline right here! Jimmy pointed to his croutch.Well lets go make some cream. Jimmy and Clark ran through the office chasing each other and giggling. They stopped inside the copy room. Clark pulled off Jimmys pants and started to give him a normal hand job. Jimmy clung to the sides of the copy machine and laid back to accept the release that was about to come. Clark decided to use his powers a little bit and started giving Jimmy a super jerk. Jimmy couldnt contain it anymore and let loose. Clark used his super sucking powers to guide Jimmys cum in to his mouth and swallow with prestiege. Liten, Jimmy, what we do is fun. If Lois ever found out. Lois wont find out Clark, because Ill never tell. Clark smiled at Jimmy as a Charizard walked by the window behind him.

Oh my gosh Jimmy a Charizard! Jimmys relaxation was cut short when he looked out the window and saw the giant pokemon. What is it doing here!? yelled Jimmy in anticipation. Clark screamed for Jimmy to get out of the copy room. Get out of here Jimmy! You need to protect yourself! Jimmy was so turned on by the orange of Charizard that his boner came back. Im not going anywhere. I need a release Clark, now on your knees and suck or Ill tell Lois. Jimmy, I need you out of here! Now! Clark through Jimmy out of the copying room into the break room across the hall. I have to save Metropolis! Clark turned in to Superman and flew out the window to save the day. Batman was flying around Charizard in his Bat wing. Come on now! Were almost there okay!? Superman flew next to the bat wing and signaled for Bruce to roll down the window. What are you doing here, Bruce!? Im here to help out with the Pokemon tournament. This Charizard has just evolved and the trainer wasnt strong enough to survive it! Im guiding it back to the tournament and giving it to a more desrving trainer. What are Pokemon!? Shouted Superman as he avoided a building. Once he was withing shouting range again, Bruce told him. Pokemon are animals used to fight in battles. Kids from all over the world use them to fight in tournaments! Some pokemon come from Earth. Some come from outer space or were made in a factory.

Superman had a gleam in his eye. I dont like that look, Clark. Last time I saw it, Jason Todd was beat to death by the Joker. Dont you like jokes!? Asked Superman sarcastically. No. replied the man who fights the Joker on a weekly basis. Well, Bruce, suppose we coiuld win in this tournament. You could pose as a Pokemon trainer and I could be your Pokemon. Superman had this idea because the sight of Jimmy Olsen aroused at the Charizard was enough to make him aroused again; he knew Jimmy would tell Lois and Lois would get mad; Superman would have lost both his sexual partners and needed an outlet for release, the Pokemon would do just that. Bruce knew all this because he was the Worlds Greatest Detective. Youre just going to fuck the Pokemon arent you? Bruce fcused on getting the Charizard back to the tournament. I need friends who arent the worlds greatest detective, Superman laughed and landed at the tournament.

Bruce brought the Charizard back to the tournament. The tournament leader, Professor Oak, saw Batman and cheered. Hello! Batman! Have you come to fight in the Pokemon Tournament? Batman smiled, he reached in to his belt and pulled out a handful of poke balls. He threw one of the poke balls and Charizard. Superman gasped in astonishment. Wow! You dragged that Pokemon all the way through the city so you could tire it out and capture it! No whos the worlds greatest detective? Batman smiled and threw a poke ball at Superman. Superman shrunk into the poke ball. Prof Oak waved around excitedly. Great then, Batman! Your first oppoent is...Robin! Batman cried as he heard the news. Robin had been playing with Pokemon since he had collected him from when he was a boy. Batman knew he was up against evil. He went over to Robin to wish him luck.

Good luck Robin. You are going to need it. Robin sat in his chair in the locker room and smiled. How about you say it with a kiss? Batman kissed Robin and took off everything but his mask. Can I take the mask off this time? asked a boner ridden Robin. No! I hate your eyes. said Batman who was now wearing his utility belt nd cowl. What have you got in store for me tonight? Robin asked with a smile and a tear. Bend over...its a surprise. Robin bent over. Batman had been crafty in stringing them together. He took out the shrunken poke balls and started shoving them slowly into Robins tender hole. Pikachu said Batman as he put the poke balls deep in the Boy Wonders anus. Charizard, Robin bit his lip as his enjoyment increased. Ivysaud Robins anus puckered and he let out a whimper, not from enjoyment but from knowing he had a counter pokemon for every pokemon Bruce had. Squirtle. Robin couldnt help but throb his cock because Bruces Squirtle hadnt even evolved yet. Metapod. Robin couldnt contain himself anymore, his giant boy wonder spewed liquid all over the locker room floor. Superman. Bruce said as he shoved the last shrunken poke ball into Robins ass. I choose you. With a burst of light, Superman came out of his pokeball. There was no room for Superman inside of Robins anus so he kept growing until the Boy Wonder splattered into a million pieces of flesh,blood,bone and cum. Bruce picked up his poke balls. Superman Return. A confused and blood soaked Superman returned to his poke ball. And thats how you beat an opponent thats better than you. Batman grimmaced and smiled. He was one step closer to winning the Pokemon Tournament.

First up is Batman versus Robin! yelled Prof Oak. Batman approached the poekmon trainers pedastal to applause from the crowd. Robin was nowhere to be found. Th crowd waited for 5 minutes but couldnt find Robin anywhere. Robin has forfeited the tournament. Batman will now battle Brock! Brock took to the pokemon trainers pedestal. Brock sent out Onyx. Batman sent out Superman. To Brocks surprise, his Onyx was nothing for the Man of Steel. Superman quickly found Onyxs reproductive organs and went to town; the time he spent in the poke ball made him ridiculously horny. With a few quick pumps Superman was able to cum right through Onyxs body, creating a hole. After Onyx was reeling from the attack, Superman disintegrated him with heat vision. Brock began to cry like a little bitch. Superman returned to the oke ball and Batman grimaced and smiled. Next up was Misty.

Misty took her place at the pedestal and threw out Togapei. Batman used Superman. Superman took one look at that little egg creature and shoved him right up his ass. Then he flew into space. Batmn, using the shadows, snuck over to Misty and began to finger her. What is this feeling!? Im losing but I feel so good! MIstys gina juice ran down Batmans gloved hand and dripped off his spiked arm. When Misty was good and wet, Batman thrust himself into her, aided by the shadows so the corwd wouldnt see. It feels like Im evolving! Shouted Misty as Batman rammed his dick deep insde her. Superman returned to Earth with a suffocated Togepei. MIsty saw her dead pokemon and started crying while she was orgasming. Boo hoo uuuuuhhhh; boo hoooo uhhhhhh, fuck! Batman quickly finished as he had a tournament to attend to. MIsty was eliminated.

Wow! What an amazing turn f events! Yelled a flailing Prof Oak! Up next, tomorrow is Batman versus Our very own Ash Catchem! Stay tuned for all the poke action!

Batman went home and sat on the couch. He realized Superman needed to get home to Lois for a bit so he flew back to Metropolis and sat in Clark Kents apartment and waited for Lois to get home. Lois arrived with Jimmy Olsen following her. I dont care what you say, thats just not true you freak! Lois said hello to Batman, Can you belive this little creep is trying to tell me that Clark was giving him an HJ in the copying room. Bruce threw a poke ball out the window and whispered Superman, I choose you. Thats terrible! Ashamed Batman to Jimmy Olsen. But its true! And its not terrible! What Clark and I have is beautiful! And Clark came to the door with a depressed look on his face. I am the one who should be sorry. Ive been drinking coffee and thinking about everything that has been going on. Did you know that Batman is in charge of a pokemon tournament? 

CLARK! Everyone said as they saw Clark had entered the room! Jimmy says that he gets HJs from you in the copying room and that you threw him out; thats why Perry caught him jerking off in the break room. Lois doesnt believe me that its true. Clark, tell me its not true. Clark, tell her it is true! Batman grimaced and smiled. 

Its true. Clark said with a sad face as he finally finished his cup of coffee. JImmy and I are in love; but not the same kind of love that you and I are in Lois. I love both of you equally in different ways. Leave if you want, but I wont love you any less.Theres only one thing to do, Clark. Lois went over to Batman and started blowing him with an evil look in his eye. Clark cried. Jimmy Olsen, afriad of what to do, took out his orange furred dick and began swinging it in front of Clark. Party time. said Jimmy softly as Clark wept and got on his knees. Lois came over and joined Clark. Wow, babe! I can see why you like this! He tastes amazing! Like candy! They invited Batman to join in on the fun but he said, Im not into that gay shit. and went home. Jimmy Olsen bent Lois lane over the table and stuck it deep inside her. Clark was behind Jimmy and stuck it deep inside him. Batman, who everyone thought had gone home, used the shadows to sneak up on Clark and put it deep inside him. The train of cumming was so loud that the neighbors started to yell. Batman silenced them with sleeping gas and went back to the cum train. That night everyone slept like babies.

Batman stood on the pedestal looking at his greatest enemy yet. Lois and Jimmy were in the stands hugging each other. Ash Katchem looked at the Caped Crusader with an odd infatuation. Pikachu! I choose YOU! As said as his Pikchu jumped off his shoulders and into the battle field. Superman, go! As remembered that Superman was weak against a few things; the sun; kryptonite and lighting. Thundershock! And superman was hit harded than ever. But he didnt flinch. He took his fist and rammed it up Pikachus ass through his mouth. Ash sent out Blastoise and Superman did the same thing. Adorned with the bad choices of Ashs dead pokemon, Superman flew in front of the kid from Pallette town. I am your God. With that Superman froze Ash then began to Super-hump him into melting. Batman grimaced and smiled at the fun Superman was having. Superman had unfrozen Ash and was waiting for his next pokemon. Ash Katcherm chose Metapod. Superman swung metapod around and put him up his ass. Superman squeezed his buttcheelks and metapod fell into a million pieces of goo and shell. Ash cried as he was out of usable Pokemon.

The winner is Batman from Gotham City! Prof Oak cheered and presented Batman with a badge. The group went to the locker room to get away from eveyrhting.

Well that was quite a match! Said Lois. Yah, it was sure exciting! screamed Jimmy. Batman sat on a red spot on the floor. Superman sat in his lap. We make a good team! The Worlds Finest! And they l made out on where Robin died the night before.

Then End
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first music video (Drunk in Georgia) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 18:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
