<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject16</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This situation contributes to unrealistic, costly, and harmful drug policies. If the real problem with drug addiction, for example, is the interaction between the drug itself and an individual's brain, then the solution to this problem lies in one of two approaches. Either remove the drug from society through policies and law enforcement (for example, drug-free societies) or focus exclusively on the addicted individual's brain as the problem. In both cases, there is neither need for nor interest in understanding the role of socioeconomic factors in maintaining drug use or mediating drug addiction.

The detrimental effects of using law enforcement as a primary means to deal with drug use are well documented. Millions are arrested annually for drug possession and the abhorrent practice of racism flourishes in the enforcement of such policies. In the United States, for example, cannabis possession accounts for nearly half of the 1.5 million annual drug arrests, and blacks are four times more likely to be arrested for cannabis possession than whites, even though both groups use cannabis at similar rates.

An insidious assumption of the diseased brain theory is that any use of certain drugs is considered pathological, even the non-problematic, recreational use that characterizes the experience of the overwhelming majority who ingest these drugs. For example, in a popular US anti-drug campaign, it is implied that one hit of methamphetamine is enough to cause irrevocable damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Viewing addiction as a brain disease promotes social injustice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This situation contributes to unrealistic, costly, and harmful drug policies. If the real problem with drug addiction, for example, is the interaction between the drug itself and an individual's brain, then the solution to this problem lies in one of two approaches. Either remove the drug from society through policies and law enforcement (for example, drug-free societies) or focus exclusively on the addicted individual's brain as the problem. In both cases, there is neither need for nor interest in understanding the role of socioeconomic factors in maintaining drug use or mediating drug addiction.

The detrimental effects of using law enforcement as a primary means to deal with drug use are well documented. Millions are arrested annually for drug possession and the abhorrent practice of racism flourishes in the enforcement of such policies. In the United States, for example, cannabis possession accounts for nearly half of the 1.5 million annual drug arrests, and blacks are four times more likely to be arrested for cannabis possession than whites, even though both groups use cannabis at similar rates.

An insidious assumption of the diseased brain theory is that any use of certain drugs is considered pathological, even the non-problematic, recreational use that characterizes the experience of the overwhelming majority who ingest these drugs. For example, in a popular US anti-drug campaign, it is implied that one hit of methamphetamine is enough to cause irrevocable damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Viewing addiction as a brain disease promotes social injustice argues Professor Carl L. Hart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe this is how Trump Voters can be reached. Show that the personalities they adore use certain policies that benefit everyone. 

Hopefully they can see that Pence did something good here that gets acknowledged by the media.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bit sciency, but very interesting read. 

Most interesting I found these parts:

One result of this is that consumers never really know what theyre buying, even in states where cannabis is legal. Cannabis is sold under names  Sour Diesel, Girl Scout Cookies  that imply standardized varieties, the same way you can buy Xtra Sweet corn or a Bushel Boy tomato. But the science doesnt really work that way, Holmes, Vergara and other scientists said.

Holmess company has an online data visualization showing genetic relationships between samples of cannabis DNA that have been submitted to it by people from all over the world. About 20 percent to 30 percent of the time, he told me, the samples they test wont be even remotely related to other samples sold under the same variety name. Thats similar to results that a Canadian research team got in 2015, when it found that **35 percent of its samples were more genetically similar to samples with a different name than to samples with the same name**. Holmes said that these distinctions can matter to recreational consumers who had a bad experience on a certain variety and want to avoid it in the future.

That also applies to people who are picking their weed based on the broad family categories of sativa and indica. The former is often said to produce highs that make you feel energetic and creative, while the latter is supposedly the stuff that makes you fall asleep on the couch after 15 minutes. But its all just a big myth, Holmes said. And other scientists agreed. The 2015 Canadian study, for instance, found that even though there is some evidence that cannabis could be organized into two families with distinct traits (and even that is the subject of scientific debate), those sativa and indica designations arent really meaningful to the consumer market, because of both cross-breeding that muddies the distinction and simple mistaken identity. **In one case, a variety called Jamaican Lambs Bread, which was supposed to be a sativa, was nearly genetically identical to a supposed indica variety from Afghanistan. Both the names of cannabis varieties and the indica/sativa division should be thought of as fungible marketing, not accurate biology.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why That Maui Wowie Doesnt Hit You The Same Way Every Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, but it seems to be just one server and the Website in question is:
secure2.donaldjtrump.com

and not 

donaldjtrump.com

Reading the article shows you it is less sensational then the Headline suggests. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hunched Over a Microscope, He Sketched the Secrets of How the Brain Works (Ramn y Cajal, Great Article and Beautiful Illustrations) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bit sciency, but very interesting read. 

Most interesting I found these parts:

One result of this is that consumers never really know what theyre buying, even in states where cannabis is legal. Cannabis is sold under names  Sour Diesel, Girl Scout Cookies  that imply standardized varieties, the same way you can buy Xtra Sweet corn or a Bushel Boy tomato. But the science doesnt really work that way, Holmes, Vergara and other scientists said.

Holmess company has an online data visualization showing genetic relationships between samples of cannabis DNA that have been submitted to it by people from all over the world. About 20 percent to 30 percent of the time, he told me, the samples they test wont be even remotely related to other samples sold under the same variety name. Thats similar to results that a Canadian research team got in 2015, when it found that **35 percent of its samples were more genetically similar to samples with a different name than to samples with the same name**. Holmes said that these distinctions can matter to recreational consumers who had a bad experience on a certain variety and want to avoid it in the future.

That also applies to people who are picking their weed based on the broad family categories of sativa and indica. The former is often said to produce highs that make you feel energetic and creative, while the latter is supposedly the stuff that makes you fall asleep on the couch after 15 minutes. But its all just a big myth, Holmes said. And other scientists agreed. The 2015 Canadian study, for instance, found that even though there is some evidence that cannabis could be organized into two families with distinct traits (and even that is the subject of scientific debate), those sativa and indica designations arent really meaningful to the consumer market, because of both cross-breeding that muddies the distinction and simple mistaken identity. **In one case, a variety called Jamaican Lambs Bread, which was supposed to be a sativa, was nearly genetically identical to a supposed indica variety from Afghanistan. Both the names of cannabis varieties and the indica/sativa division should be thought of as fungible marketing, not accurate biology.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Your Weed Doesnt Hit You The Same Way Every Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the article before you comment people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Tulsi Gabbard

Die ist in der Demokratischen Partei vollkommen bedeutungslos. Die wurde nur von Trump Anhngern die sich als Bernie Supporter darstellen haben mega auf Reddit gepusht.

Und zwar nur deswegen weil sie von allen Demokraten mit Abstand am hufigsten mit den Republikanern gestimmt hat, gegen Hillary hatet und mit Trump zusammenarbeiten wollte.

Hier ein tiefgehender Artikel ber sie:
[She was mentioned as Trumps likely choice for U.S. ambassador to the UNthe job ultimately went to South Carolina Governor Nikki Haleyand even met with him after the November election. Gabbard is reportedly a favorite of Steve Bannon, the former CEO of Breitbart News who now is the president-elects chief strategist. Bannon, who has described Breitbart as a platform for alt-right views, which combine white nationalism and economic populism, has praised Gabbards views on gunsshe supports some gun restrictions, but not others; her alignment with Republican senators on Syrian refugees coming to the U.S.; and, of course, Islamist terrorism. Indeed, Gabbards name was not among the 169 Democratic lawmakers who wrote to Trump criticizing his hiring of Bannon.](https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2017/01/tulsi-gabbard-syria/508367/)

Auf gar keinen Fall wird die einzige Person in der Demokratischen Partei die auf Trumps Seite steht als nchster Prsidentschaftskandidat aufgestellt. 

Edit:
Sie wurde wahrscheinlich auch deswegen so gepusht von Trump Anhngern, da sie einen Keil zwischen Hillary Anhnger und Bernie Anhnger getrieben hat. 
Zuflligerweise hat sie einige Beziehungen zu Sheldon Adelson der auch Millionen in die Kampagne von Trump versenkt hat und einige Super PACs gegrndet hat. Vielleicht wird ihr Name deswegen von gewissen Kreisen so positiv verwendet:

[Reps. Jason Chaffetz, a Utah Republican, and Tulsi Gabbard, a Hawaii Democrat, reintroduced an Adelson-backed bill Wednesday, provoking another battle within the deep-pocketed gaming community pitting Adelsons Las Vegas Sands against MGM Resorts and Caesars Entertainment, which hope to make money online.](http://time.com/3695948/sheldon-adelson-online-gambling/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only reason for the existence of this survey is to saw doubt in the minds of people who oppose Trump and reinforce his supporters.

So the ones who share it to "skew the results" play right into their hand. 

All they want you to do is read their "arguments" in the description of the extremely loaded questions. 

Nobody seriously thinks they will bother to release the results? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just need some double think then it is easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes stop all leaking. Prosecute them. 

Throw those leakers into cells. Shut down treacherous organizations like wikileaks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Shes just saying things just to get in front of the TV to prove her relevance because behind the scenes shes not in these meetings"

It is not because of her lies, but because she is irrelevant and has no access to information. 
So why book her if she can not tell you something new? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I dont even think shes saying something she knows to be untrue, Scarborough said. "Shes just saying things just to get in front of the TV to prove her relevance because behind the scenes shes not in these meetings and any reporter can ask anybody in that White House and they will say the same thing. Shes not in these meetings. So why does the president allow her to keep going out and spreading false information?" 

I mean why should they book her if she is obviously out of the loop and most stuff she says turns out to be wrong?

Either she lies or she genuinely just has no idea what is going. In both cases there is no use in having her on TV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice that even fox news reports it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the alleged victims was not even in Frankfurt at the time the allegations are said to have taken place.

Before the Bild report, no sexual assaults were reported to police from Fressgass over New Year.

The sad thing is that obvious bullshit gets picked up by newspapers because right-wingers demand it. 

How about only reporting the truth and not what some people want to hear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how he calls it simultaneously ["fake news"](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/831830548565852160) and ["illegal leaks"](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/831840306161123328). 

How can it be both? Either the story is incorrect, then it can not be a leak, or it is truely leaked then it can not be "fake news". 

It is logically impossible for both his statements to be true. So one has to be a lie. Maybe even both. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sci-hub.cc

[more info](http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2016/04/whos-downloading-pirated-papers-everyone) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so that is settled. Nothing to see here. Please move on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 11:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He talked to Russian intelligence officers who were obviously wiretapped. So I guess noone ordered a wiretap on Flynn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 11:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do not get rewarded for it from their audience.

 Whenever you see a story like this give clicks and likes to the conservative papers. Show them it is worth their while to report on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is physiological (in)tolerance.

See the article:

Our sample (48.6% female) is drawn from the Han Chinese undergraduate population at a leading Chinese university. Members of our sample are similar in age and background: homogeneity of the participant pool is the reason we use this population. We are aware of no evidence that alcohol intolerance is associated with personality or preferences, and in our sample we find no evidence that this polymorphism systematically predicts personality type, attitudes toward risk, or prosociality. Other than alcohol intolerance and gender, both of which are expected to impact systematically use of self-control, we are aware of no other reason or evidence that practice of self-control would differ systematically among this population. 

**Alcohol intolerance arises because of the presence of the ALDH2 Lys487 allele (see SI Appendix for details).** Since there is an equal chance that either parental allele will be passed on to offspring, alcohol intolerance can be understood as occurring randomly in the population (22). This randomization across our sample is crucial for the causal inferences we report below. Note that our research strategy connects to the Mendelian randomization literature (2326), which also takes advantage of natural experiments implied by random assignments of genes from parents to offspring. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 10:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me google that for you:

http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/donald-trump-saudi-arabia-911-business-deals-a7038991.html

http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/306990-trump-appeared-to-register-eight-companies-in-saudi-arabia

An overview on all his conflict of interests:
http://www.theatlantic.com/business/archive/2017/01/donald-trump-conflicts-of-interests/508382/
(Includes for example his stake in the pipelines that just went forward)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 16:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it is highly correlated with people who vote AfD, which are at about 15 percent at the moment. 
Some people are really unhappy with the current state and look to Russia as an alternative. 
Furthermore, there are a lot of German people with Russian roots:
https://de.wikipedia.org/wiki/Russlanddeutsche </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anybody who expected anything else is a fool. 

Trump has extensive business dealings with Saudi Arabia, that are much more pronounced than Clinton's. 

It was clear that he will not get rid of that, despite all his statements. He just does not care about the optics at all. His own financial well-being is more important than his political promise. And money is one thing the Saudis have way more of than he has.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How nice would it have been if Kasich had said yes? 
Then we had him in control instead Bannon, Kushner and Pence. 

He is somebody who could have united the country. Trump could do all the ceremonial stuff while Kasich runs the country. Man what a nice dream.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 13:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Senate Democrats will unveil a $1 trillion infrastructure plan  and offer President Trump their support if he backs it.

From our largest cities to our smallest towns, communities across the country are struggling to meet the challenges of aging infrastructure, Senator Chuck Schumer of New York, the Democratic leader, will say. Our urban and rural communities have their own unique set of infrastructure priorities, and this proposal would provide funding to address those needed upgrades that go beyond the traditional road and bridge repair.

Republicans resisted President Barack Obamas push for an infrastructure surge for eight years, arguing that the federal government couldnt afford it and that state and local governments should shoulder more responsibility for improvements. But Mr. Trump has taken up the Democratic cause.

We will build new roads, and highways, and bridges, and airports, and tunnels, and railways all across our wonderful nation, he vowed in his Inaugural Address.


Let's see what his answer is. Republicans will hate this plan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 11:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conspiracy theory is widely acknowledged to be a loaded term. Politicians use it to mock and dismiss allegations against them, while philosophers and political scientists warn that it could be used as a rhetorical weapon to pathologize dissent. In two empirical studies conducted on Amazon Mechanical Turk, I present an initial examination of whether this concern is justified. In Experiment 1, 150 participants judged a list of historical and speculative theories to be no less likely when they were labeled conspiracy theories than when they were labeled ideas. In Experiment 2 (N=802), participants who read a news article about fictitious corruption allegations endorsed those allegations no more than participants who saw them labeled conspiracy theories. The lack of an effect of the conspiracy-theory label in both experiments was unexpected and may be due to a romanticized image of conspiracy theories in popular media or a dilution of the term to include mundane speculation regarding corruption and political intrigue.

Article is Open Access, so you should be able to read it, if you are interested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Dare Call It Conspiracy: Labeling Something a Conspiracy Theory Does Not Reduce Belief in It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 11:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
