<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9013</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Guardian's mobile visits overtake desktop visits between 6am and 7am -- overall, smartphones and tablets now account for nearly 35% of their traffic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 14:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 50-page report, Losing Humanity: The Case Against Killer Robots, outlines concerns about fully autonomous weapons, which would inherently lack human qualities that provide legal and non-legal checks on the killing of civilians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-19 19:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 18:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, typo in the submission.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now new research has, for the first time, identified a common gene variant that influences when you will wake up each day  and helps determine the time of day you will most likely to die </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 15:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New injectable gels developed by MIT chemical engineers toughen up after entering the body, could find applications in drug delivery and tissue engineering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 22:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study examines the financial costs of sadness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 14:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Theres nothing more dangerous than a scientifically illiterate adult who is trying to make decisions about the world where science literacy matters." - Neil deGrasse Tyson on the Harvard Kennedy School PolicyCast (x-post from r/politics) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 19:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 Colleges Dishing Out the Best Grub in New England </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 14:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marine animals inspire researchers to invent a device that can detect, capture and release rare cancer cells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 14:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study shows that meditation training can have measurable effects on how your brain functions, even when you're not actively meditating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 22:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Panel of experts examine how the election results will affect education reform at the federal, state, and local levels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 20:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bioengineers develop a gel-based sponge that can be molded to any shape, loaded with drugs or stem cells, compressed to a fraction of its size, and delivered via injection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 20:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 01:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hosted a bourbon tasting party with my wife (our first) in September. Just a few tips:

* Bought some [whiskey glasses](http://www.amazon.com/Stolzle-Glencairn-Whiskey-Glass-Boxed/dp/B003TMCNI8/) before the tasting event - they were totally worth it.

* For snacks, we had an assortment of cheeses, grapes, pretzels, nuts, and dark chocolate

* Also made some [gougres](http://www.google.com/url?sa=t rct=j q= esrc=s source=web cd=1 cad=rja ved=0CEAQFjAA url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.davidlebovitz.com%2F2009%2F01%2Fgougeres-french-cheese-puffs%2F ei=cZihUJiAEqrC0AGHg4GIBg usg=AFQjCNF1nWLSaN4FX_RIhsFp1OQxi99xaA sig2=q5FGTDfUTwb77lfUWhWOzQ) (French cheese puffs) - they were delicious and helped fill up guests between tastings

* Read a quick description of each bourbon before each tasting. I thought it would be cheesy, but the guests really enjoyed it.

* We tasted 6 bourbons over the course of about 2.5 hours. No one was liquored up. Bottles of water at the table helped.

* Print sheets (or send a follow-up email) to the group with the names/years of each bourbon. 

Enjoy your tasting night - hope it goes well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 14:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dinner was delicious. Highly recommend it. Start with the spicy lobster bisque if you can (soup of the day). I had the haddock (incredible) and my wife had the steak (asked for.medium, got medium-well, but still great)
The blueberry dessert is really good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 18:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people understand that a goal of a restaurant is to make you spend more. I believe the article is just trying to expose some of the marketing tactics used on menus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 18:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting dinner at 22 Bowens tonight so I'll add some comments soon. It'll be my first time in Newport.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early treatment sparks striking brain changes in autism (Yale School of Medicine) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 18:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 17:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can find Eagle Rare 17yr, I highly recommend it. My wife got me a bottle last Christmas -- best gift ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A look at the tricks restaurant menus use to get you to spend more </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 17:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HootSuite privacy fail sees hundreds of emails sent to users in an hour, complete with other peoples details </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 17:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 17:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTA: 
As the planet shifts on its axis, stress on the tectonic plates that make up Earths crust increases, Mitrovica explained. That increased stress acts like a stretched rubber band, gradually pulling the planet back to its original rotation axis, even after millions of years of rotation at a different angle.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once its axis tilts, how does the Earth know to return to its normal orientation? Researchers explain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 16:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 23:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My band is [Eleventh Hour Sunrise](http://eleventhhoursunrise.com/). Alt rock/acoustic/prog rock from New Hampshire. I'm the drummer, so I'm always picked on. Hope you enjoy:

http://soundcloud.com/eleventh-hour-sunrise/sets/ordinary-life-locket-ep/

Our new 2-song album free to download.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers from Harvard and MIT use our inner ear's 'natural battery' (a chamber filled with ions that produces an electrical potential to drive neural signals) to power power an implantable electronic device </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 15:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Note-Takings Past, Deciphered Today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 14:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super-Earth in 6-planet system may have oceans, life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 20:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers quantify how many years of life are gained by being physically active at different levels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 20:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 18:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Direct link to their research article on this topic at: [Science Translation Medicine](http://stm.sciencemag.org/content/4/159/159ra147) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Living, breathing lung-on-a-chip, made using human lung and blood vessel cells, acts much like a lung in a human body </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 14:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 23:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Really appreciate that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Election Results 2012: Nate Silver on How He Got It Right [video interview with NY Times] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 14:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google search data sheds light on likely voters, Harvard Ph.D. student finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 20:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Alt Acoustic/Prog Rock] Eleventh Hour Sunrise - Ordinary Life   Locket. I'm really proud of the new 2-song EP my band just finished. Both free downloads. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 00:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Harvard Students Are Running New York City Marathon in Boston to Raise Money For Disaster Relief </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 16:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Music can reduce the perception of effort during a workout and can also measurably improve endurance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 16:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rare specimens from a world-class skull collection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 16:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A research team has invented a quick-release tape that has the strong adhesion properties of commercial medical tape, but without the ouch factor upon removal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 20:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-01 20:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's [a turkey chillin' on a bench](http://statigr.am/p/300650390783601174_448913) - I saw this guy outside Holyoke Center a couple weeks ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huge tree falls on a car in Cambridge, MA [photo] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 22:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the lowest mass black holes ever observed in the middle of a galaxy has been identified </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 21:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 18:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full text of their research article is available here:  [Making the Moon from a Fast-Spinning Earth: A Giant Impact Followed by Resonant Despinning](http://www.sciencemag.org/content/early/2012/10/16/science.1225542.full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Pay-Per-Click Ad Costs Rise, Small Businesses Search for Alternatives - NYTimes.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 16:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists offer a new spin on the origins of Earths moon -- propose that prior to the collision and creation of the moon, an Earth day was only two to three hours long </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 16:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earth-Sized Planet Discovered Orbiting Around Nearest Star </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 15:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The rise of "medical tourism" - Ethical, legal issues when people travel to other nations for health care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 15:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers spray-paint ultrathin coatings that change color with only a few atoms' difference in thickness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 17:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paleontologists reveal the identity of Predator X  an immense, big-headed marine reptile said to have a bite four times stronger than Tyrannosaurus rex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 17:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four Harvard experts  on voice, movement, public speaking, and trial law  critique the last presidential debate and offer the candidates their tips for the next matchup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 17:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-15 16:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the [Harvard Gazette](http://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2012/10/roth-shares-economics-nobel/) article on Alvin Roth:
I was sleeping, he said of the 4 a.m. wake-up call. When asked how he planned to celebrate, the sleepy Roth simply responded, Coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 18:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Direct link to the ScienceMag.org research article - http://stm.sciencemag.org/content/4/155/155ra137 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have safely transplanted human neural stem cells into the brains of four boys with a rare, fatal brain condition. The preliminary trial paves the way for future research into potential stem cell treatments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 17:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I guess Facebook doesn't watch baseball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 16:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At todays rate, global population would skyrocket to 27 billion by 2100, from todays 7 billion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-09 17:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Mapping the World's Friendships" is a new interactive map from Facebook that explores the factors that connect countries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 03:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 00:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, basically a new design for playlists? Here's an example: [CS50: Intro To Computer Science](http://www.youtube.com/course?category=University%2FEngineering list=ECF8A834F810575A94 feature=edu) from Harvard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 00:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But really, hooves counting?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven Lions EP Teaser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 16:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A NASA telescope got a glimpse of a dying star called Helix Nebula located 650 light years from Earth [video] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 01:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do exercise programs help children stay fit? The programs just didnt work, at least in terms of getting young people to move more, says researcher. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-05 18:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time, an international team of astronomers measure a black holes "point of no return" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 15:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 ways that edX could change education </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 14:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bring Us Your Innovative Ed-Tech Ideas, Education Dept. Says at Meeting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 20:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter has automatically opted you into more email notifications; heres how to reduce the spam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 18:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obesity-related hormone discovered in fruit flies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 18:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 17:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full report is available in Cell Reports - http://www.cell.com/cell-reports/fulltext/S2211-1247(12)00265-3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers find molecular link between two fatal diseases, amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS) and spinal muscular atrophy (SMA) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 15:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using ultrasound waves, MIT engineers have found a way to enhance the permeability of the skin to drugs [video] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-27 19:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers use precise lasers to manipulate neurons in worms brains, instructing them to turn in any direction and even implanting false sensory information </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 14:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NBC unpacks trove of data from Olympics, shows vast shifts in how people watch television, especially with second devices like tablets or smartphones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 14:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Measurements of stress hormones and self-reports of anxiety show that leaders in stable organizations experience less stress than their subordinates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-25 14:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese police shut down one of Foxconns largest plants after a brawl involving over 2,000 workers broke out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 22:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 19:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting method of research, from the article:
Unlike many psychology studies, which use small numbers of college students, these experiments tested thousands of people from around the world using Amazon Mechanical Turk, an online labor market thats becoming an increasingly popular tool for social science research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a series of experiments, researchers found that people who make quick decisions act less selfishly than those who deliberate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 19:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google has taken what its officials call an experimental first step into online education, releasing open-source software called Course Builder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 14:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7 scholastic DIY projects to customize your study space, including a glass globe desk lamp and a map-shaped cork board </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 14:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research indicates that a complex clash between countries gender norms and changing economic realities could explain why, in many developed nations, fewer women are having children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 14:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 01:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love that you have Eagle Rare 17yr in your collection. That was the bourbon that really got me hooked on trying new whiskeys. Awesome selection you've got there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alton Brown of Food Network replies to fans on Twitter using photos of Post-it note sketches and scribbles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 15:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 17:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure thing. The report was published in Cell.com - summary: "Loss of 5-Hydroxymethylcytosine Is an Epigenetic Hallmark of Melanoma" http://www.cell.com/abstract/S0092-8674(12)01012-4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MIT team has managed to create three-dimensional movies of electron behavior in a topological insulator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 17:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have pinpointed when seemingly innocuous skin pigment cells mutate into melanoma, big breakthrough in skin cancer detection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 17:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> September 17, 2012 - Drew Faust, President of Harvard University </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 14:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thiel Fellowships pay young people to forgo college and to plunge into real-world projects </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-16 15:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvard offers a new dramatic arts class -  Hip Hop and Spoken Word: Theater Performance Laboratory  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-16 15:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NDSU and University of Texas at Austin being evacuated because of bomb threats - 9/14/2012 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 17:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 14:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a direct link to the research article: "Young Children Consider Merit when Sharing Resources with Others" - http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0043979 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study at Harvard suggests that children may have a far more advanced concept of "fairness" than previously thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 22:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvard students build the worlds largest cardboard box fort </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 22:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robotic tentacles gently pick up a flower [video]  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 15:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sleep apnea among health problems hitting the poor hardest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 15:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hows this for a mind-bender: Lou Gehrig may not have had Lou Gehrigs disease.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 15:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the most expensive penny in the Universe. It's now on Mars, after an exciting $2.5 billion ride.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 14:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 14:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll know once I have my first few glasses. I bought it because it was good, but also since I don't make it out to that area too often.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 03:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure I could really pick that out if they didn't tell me, but it is really smooth. Not sweet. More of an oak finish to it. Compares with Vintage 17yr for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 02:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried their rye as part of the tasting too. Pretty spicy - definitely hits your nose hard. Good though. I just preferred the bourbon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 01:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the distillery link for more info: http://www.fingerlakesdistilling.com/index.php/our-products </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tried some McKenzie Bourbon Whiskey last weekend at Finger Lakes Distilling (Seneca Lake - NY).. good stuff. Ended up buying a bottle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 01:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Team of experts in mechanics, materials science, and tissue engineering has created an extremely stretchy and tough gel that may suggest a new method for replacing damaged cartilage in human joints </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-06 21:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new brain-computer interface allows a person to walk using a pair of mechanical leg braces controlled by brain signals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-06 04:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazing composite image shows a superbubble in the Large Magellanic Cloud (LMC), a small satellite galaxy of the Milky Way, located about 160,000 light years from Earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-05 15:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So when will smartphones finally replace our wallets? Not for a long time, unfortunately  at least a decade. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-05 14:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it imaginable that a computer-agent team-member could behave, over the long-term and in uncertain, dynamic environments, in such a way that people on the team will not notice it is not human? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 15:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By studying strange coiling behavior in the grasping tendrils of the cucumber plant, researchers have characterized a new type of spring that is soft when pulled gently and stiff when pulled strongly
 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 15:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 21:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noted for future submissions - thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A swollen star near the end if its life has been caught devouring one of its own planets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 16:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Arctic ice cap is on course for a record-breaking melt session following a summer of unstable conditions, according to National Snow and Ice Data Center </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 16:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research casts doubts on key aspect of dissociative identity disorder - the amnesia barrier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 16:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research showed vitamin D supplementation decreased risk of respiratory infections among children during winter (when daily sunlight is limited) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 02:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri's Ozarks Technical Community College website drops the clutter, new design inspired by Google search </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 16:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pea aphids may have an unprecedented ability to harvest sunlight, and use the energy for metabolic purposes -- making it the only species of animal known to have photosynthesis-like powers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 18:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A view of synthetic biologists is that biology is essentially modular. Understood well enough, its building blocks  organs, cells, genes, proteins  could be assembled in plug-and-play fashion, like electrical elements on a circuit board. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 18:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers encoded an entire book into the genetic molecules of DNA, and then accurately read back the text </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 14:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harvard researchers demonstrate a "dynamic coloration" system for soft robots, allowing the robots to camouflage themselves [video] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 20:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Students at the University of Middle Tennessee have installed a full plug-in hybrid kit in a stock 1994 Honda Accord for $3,000 (and can be applied to almost any car) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 20:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Instagram adds a photo map that lets members plot their pictures on an interactive world map </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 20:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a world gone online, always on, and viral, what are the implications for communities of faith? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 19:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-12 04:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy. I wish I still lived close to Magouns. Rented a place a couple blocks away for about 3 years - loved that bar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 20:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a free Harvard Yard tour app you can download if you want to take your own quick tour: http://www.harvard.edu/visitors/mobile-tour -- enjoy your visit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 23:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast of Champions = great example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 17:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fee = 1 bottle not on the list. What are you bringing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 15:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. Here's some more info about the clinic they ran while at Harvard: http://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2012/07/liverpool-f-c-wins-over-local-youth/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 02:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd suggest a cichlid tank. It's freshwater so it'll be cheaper than saltwater. Dedicate your time into getting the right setup (substrate, rocks / providing territories for your fish, # of fish to buy, etc). Stick to one lake if you buy African cichlids (Malawi, Tanganyika) or get 2-3 American cichlids. Go with fishless cycling if you can, or get some giant danios as dither fish and to aid in cycling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 21:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could it be a product of the surface area of the fast skin suit? More material covering human skin? Just throwing ideas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 21:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing too new, but it does try to get the readers to understand that there's still some really good work being done in tech in Silicon Valley -- not just those creating derivative social platforms and mashups, looking for quick acquisitions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-22 20:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, to be more literal (from the researcher) - What we have shown conclusively is that the surface properties themselves, which the manufacturer has in the past claimed to be biomimetic, dont do anything for propulsion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 22:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree. I feel like playing to a click track (at practice) in headphones helps me with my timing at live shows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 22:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, right? Weird how you swear the bpm bumps up or down 5 clicks and everyone thinks you're crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 20:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a drummer, I've always wondered why my brain tricks me to think the metronome is speeding up or slowing down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 20:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not really the purpose of the research. They are trying map the "rhythms inherent in the human brain, which may affect our musical rhythm". It's not about perfection of our internal metronome. It's about the biological factors that influence it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-10 20:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I make a costume for Halloween every year, but my Yip Yip costume is still my favorite. The kids thought I was Cookie Monster, but the adults knew what was up. [Video](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lbD-3MM5SSI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-16 22:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did see that post - I think it's a good idea to promote during move-in / orientation week. Have you talked to Sharon Duffy about promotion yet? She'd be the first person I'd contact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-10 17:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome that you got this started. I'm not sure how much you want Emerson staff involved here (I'm the web manager for enrollment / one of the people behind @emersoncollege and Emerson's other social media). 

If I can help, let me know. I've been a redditor for a while (more for just browsing new stuff, not really submitting or commenting) but I'd be up for helping promote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
