<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3989</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 14:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've already responded to this, i'm aussie myself not like we need 100x posts about it
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 23:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 10:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just do donuts in my hot pink faggio to represent my neutrality but i still get shot at lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When i see someone approaching me on the map </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 05:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 01:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but it is good for the newbies starting out :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 01:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure man but if you know where the helicopter spawn is (not the police station) i think its the closest tower to the east. when you buy it theres an option for the ground floor level one or the top floor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 22:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not bad but tbh i'd rather go and do missions and shit instead of just running in and out of a shop collecting money, you earn RP and it's a lot more fun tbh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 22:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha thanks :D it's better because you still get a 10 car garage, it's only like 270k or something which is cheaper than the 400k and theres not griefers always waiting outside your place to blow shit up etc.
and the helicopter spawn :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 22:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mhm kinda defeats the purpose of working your way up in online etc, but thats your decision you can play the game however you want i guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 22:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought the apt next to the helicopter spawn + a nice new car :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your favourite/best money making methods? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 12:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a lot of you guys won't want to give away your shooper shecret methods but I was just wondering what/how others people make their money or if they have any tips they want to share.
For me, the best I've found is doing the briefcase missions for martin, then storing the car that the guy is driving to sell to the Los Santos Customs after finishing/failing the mission. The only other decent way I've found is repeating 'Down the drain' races over and over, if you have 4+ people playing with you, if you win you can get up to 13.6k and even if you lose your still getting some decent money.

/thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 00:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :O The money has finally come? When I get home i'm going to buy the $270k apartment or whatever that's right next to the helicopter spawn, it still has a 10 car garage so it's all good :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joining a game and trying to talk to people.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 12:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
