<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7382</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 01:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this from meatspin.com??? Nsfw  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 01:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adding you. Fallingbuckets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Squad up. XBONE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 01:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's up folks, I'm looking for some active squad mates and friends for bat 4 on xbox one. My gamer tag is FallingBuckets. I spot like crazy, can fly any helicopter proficiently and drive just about every other vehicle very skillfully. Hit me up for a good time. You guys rule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 06:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the difference between that, and, flammable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 05:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We call the dirt-daubers here in Alabama. And for some reason my phone would rather them be called "dirt-daybeds." Fuck you autocorrect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 05:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in HS- I stayed home from school to play hookie( COD4 ). After my morning shower I put on a bathrobe. TWO MOTHERFUCKEN WASPS inside it. Bit/stung like crazy, ditched to robe and bolted around the house buck-nekkid. Didn't know they were wasps until I investigated the robe and was promptly hit by them a couple more times. I then killt them.
  
After this encounter, went over to Le Home Depot for TWO CANS OF WASP KILLER. These cans had raaaaange I tell ya. 12 feet accurately. 
  
Went onto the roof and had a blast, one can in each hand. Must have killed a couple dozen outside my room and on the roof. Eventually ran out of juice, with a couple stragglers floating around in despair. So I flipped the can over for dramatic effect, swatted the wasp onto the ground and CURB STOMPED THE SHIT OUT OF THE WASP.

TL;DR - FUCK WASPS, call me if you got a problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 21:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just tryna do hood rat shit wit his Grammy aaiiight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 21:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't. Stahp. Watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 06:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it, too. Find it odd and peculiar, but it feels fresh and creamy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 07:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how people attempt new strategies in wars rather than, say, multiplayer or campaign. Clan mates always try and a co normally stops them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 02:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like having a few DGB spaces but with only a single in them, to mess with people. But DGBs are not entirely necessary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 05:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one goes to eleven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I love Waffle House... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the atmosphere, and hashbrowns. Just had some gentleman hold the door for me and then ask if I'd like to purchase some heroin. Got me thinking- what about Waffle House do you love and hold dear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 19:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it goes. I try to work that into normal conversation to see if I catch anyone's literary attention. Slaughterhouse-five. Sometimes it works, so it goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 18:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Gordon! You rule. 
  
My question for you - what would be your last supper? Your last meal if you saw it coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 22:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the drugs part is what unnerves people and cities, naturally.
  
In Essen, Germany, they had blue lights in the interior of public restrooms- to make it more difficult to locate veins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 23:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Architecture, urban design. With centuries of experience under your belt, and the knowledge of how the built environment has changed and reacted through your designs, we would get some pretty exceptional stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 02:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Auburn University's Rural Studio. 20k house and other community projects in and around Hale County, Alabama.
  
Might not be exactly what you're looking for as far as scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 02:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sketchup's exterior application called layout is pretty good at compiling drawings from the scenes you great in sketchup. Features like rasterizing/vector, line thicknesses. It streamlines the documentation for post-processing.
  
I've been using sketchup for 6 years and just fired up layout today. Hah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 02:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monolithic architecture. It certainly is a hell hole fo real doe. I don't want to be there or anywhere in view of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 19:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are the key to your own success. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 19:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I moved a lot in the formative years-
  
Brooklyn, NY. Great for understanding diversity, urbanity, and the collective whole of a community. Bad for crazy people, nature is pretty distant (Appalachia). Always something to do.
  
Lake Tahoe, NY/CA. Great for nature, backyard was a mountain. Lack of diversity, both in race and $$. Beautiful mountains and beaches. Lots of outdoor activity and happy, chill people. May dump 4ft of snow overnight. School still in session.
  
Atlanta, GA. A mix of both worlds. Great people, urban feel(still sprawled) but with a huge density of foliage and trees. And chic-fil-a. Bad for the occasional racism. Shitty suburban cops. No beaches. Great pools.
  
About to head back to one of those three for a professional career. Guess which. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 19:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tame Impala, arguably. Very similar sound throughout, but with a clear progression in their musical capabilities, sensibility, etc.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 22:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks homie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WAR] who leads in wins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 20:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious- what clan has the most war wins? My clan just hit 100 in the year wars have been around. I've seen it as high as 133. (We beat em) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 04:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not kitten! Resisting arrest can be Catastrophic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> David Bowie's "Life on Mars" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 05:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like where you're heads at- my clan looks at total stars in wars at the very bottom of the player profile to gauge how efficient they may be while we are recruiting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 05:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, pepper the loons along the perimeter surgically. 10-14 loons. Then kill the AQ with the troops you used to kill the CC- Like your heroes, and possibly a high level golem you requested from a teammate. Which will soak damage and hopefully distract the bows while your hogs go to town. Watch out for giant bombs, so don't bunch them up when you drop them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 22:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easy goho with your troop levels. Request a lvl 4-5 golem in CC. Drop by the gold storage near queen. Kill her with your CC kill squad and heroes. Drop hogs en masse. Profit.
  
Edit- forgot to mention. ADs are really close to core. Drop 2 bloons on perimeter structures to clear out all the trash. Bring 10-12ish bloons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 22:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen high lvl gowiwi/wipe 3 star these bases. Haven't seen it 3 star this developed of a base, however.
  
I'm a early-mid th10. Used this base for 1 war and got 3 starred with a max gowiwi lvl 25 heroes. 
  
This base pops up a lot in masters 2 and 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 21:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah man, I got 56 seconds.
  
Felt so damn good.
  
Been waiting all day to press it. But have been AFK. Finally pressed it. Feels like when I first lost my virginity. Not much like the second or third though.
  
I really want to press it again.
  
Love,
  
Assmaster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 15:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few clan mates request this - 2 witches a wiz 2 barbs. Barbs walk in front of everything so witches don't get shot in face. Wiz there for moral support and killing enemy skullies meeting your kill squad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 16:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knights of the old republic- and not some MMO bullshit pay per month.
  
Also- fallout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 20:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How far off is the thickness of the wood from the slot? If it's not much (a few sixteenths of an inch) sanding it down would be your best bet. Or use a planer if that's accessible. 
  
As far as painting or staining- sand down the material from a course grit (80) to fine (220) with a step somewhere in the middle (150) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 03:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ok buddy. More trees will grow in the years to come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 05:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Change the "GO AWAY" to "PLS," and you might have luck with that particular base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 04:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People from the Greek island of Lesbos are known as lesbians. 
  
Heard it's quite beautiful out there, with really nice people.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 23:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even as a Greek I'm faced with this dilemma. 
  
But, most of the time the staff isn't greek, so it hardly matters. 
  
Quesadiller.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 03:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nazis on a tank! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 03:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's dissscuuuussssiiiiinnnnnn' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 02:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's really peculiar about this is that the skull was found perched on a shelf. As if someone had placed it there.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 00:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bueller?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 21:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simple layout/ringus. Our clan uses mostly hogs. Thoughts as strategies appreciated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HWYA/WAR] opposing clan has about ten of these layouts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 21:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 16:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your other air defense and then your wiz towers. Wiz towers are huge at your stage in the game. Wouldn't worry about being having 2 air d's upgrading. Only have 2 days at 50% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 05:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explanation? Context? Information? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 22:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weldwood contact cement maybe?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mounting EMT pipe to plywood face? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 04:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like part of a joke.

I have 2 inch diameter EMT aluminum and am attempting to adhere/attach it somehow to the face of stained plywood. Inserting globe lights inside. 
  
Suggestions would be greatly appreciated!
  
I was planning on cutting a sort of notch in the face of the wood to give more surface area for gorilla glue(?) to do its work. Depth 1/8" and enough of an opening to grip the tube. Pipes will be around 3" long so not much of a cantilever.


I'm basically creating a marquee letter in the shape of the letter A. This is my second one so I'm trying out the pipe method rather than sheathing 6" flashing around the edges- finishing this method with the letter k currently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hate Mosquitos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 00:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not new.. But can provide years of entertainment. 
  
Clash of clans
  
Sub /r/clashofclans

You can really get into this game. In every way possible. Clan wars. Micro/macro strategy. Cool stuff throughout. Updates and new game elements are fairly frequent. It's free but has in-app purchases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 22:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cancel that! Did the ol South Park trick on the circuit breaker. All is seemingly good. Will cut more holes now. Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drill press shorted out! Help pls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 22:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was cutting some 6 inch holes out of this art piece I'm making for a client to make it lighter. At the very end of the cut out the motor stopped and an electric spark flew out of the side opposite the control arm/wheel.


The drill press is an older Sears Craftsman model 15 1/2 inch. Model # 113 21310.

The pulleys and such still rotate. Light won't turn on. Definitely electrical. Any help appreciated! Google searches led to no avail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 02:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dag nabbit!!! I miss this place so much. I spent my adolescence in incline. Went to middle/high school there. Now I'm in alabama.... Found some mountains cough hills here though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 20:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Early-mid TH10 here, L 109. How come the RCS gets matched up with one another so frequently? My clan always matches up with Eastern European and Asian nationals. Kinda funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 19:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a younging I wanted to be a rockstar, still do actually. 
  
  
Currently I'm finishing up my final year(5th) of architecture school. Werkin' at a residential architecture firm now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 20:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  !!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 06:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your mother should have swallowed you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 23:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An axe. Was a lumberjack for Halloween one year. Had 17 shots of jack daniels( open bar ) and blacked out. Now I have no axe. Apparently I also pissed on an ottoman in one house and pissed on another in a different house. Or so it goes...


So an axe, or jack daniels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 06:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just an office dog? Even then he's a poor fella, has to smell the remains of his brethren everyday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poor guy! (Avondale, Birmingham, AL) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 01:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 07:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 6-ft tall house cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did it anyway... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 21:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 05:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a bunch of my number 1's
  
Smile 
  
Say please and thank you
  
Don't be an asshole
  
Stand up when meeting someone if seated, say there name while looking into their eyes- You won't forget their name and you automatically start the connection process.
  
Ask questions. Be interested.
  
If you're not very outgoing.... Pretend you're a celebrity. Sounds ridiculous but the false confident aura you're fabricating emanates pheromones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 19:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad brains! 
  

Check out this band: Death.
  
Protopunk early 70's, documentary on netflix "band called death" main hit is "politicians in my eyes." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 19:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Mr. Hawk, huge fan of your skating, games, and movies. Particularly THPS2 and the Bones brigade. 
  

Probably had a better question for you when I was 12 (22 now) but here it goes:
  
  
If you were to choose any sport to be exceptional at, like Tiger is to golf or Tony is to skating, what would it be? 
  
  
How do your conversations with Rodney Mullen go? Creativity is skateboarding as a focus.
  

PS I sat behind your family at boom boom huck jam in NY  back in the early 2000's. Unbelievably awesome show. Social D!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 03:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two cannibals are eating the body of a clown. One says to the other- "does this taste funny to you?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 16:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emperor Impala of Mustafar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors, what makes Reddit a beautiful thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 16:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In your opinion, why is Reddit so interesting? Post meant to be general and up for interpretation. Subreddits, comments, users, social commentary, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 06:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Architecture record for magazine subscription, without a doubt. Archdaily.com as a free alternative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 01:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very well put together response sir, you've already been immensely helpful. The particle board was an arbitrarily made decision(10$ cheaper than MDF) and that under layer is only to provide some stability to the thin 1/4" walnut ply. The reason why I didn't use another walnut ply is to be economical as it is the underside of the table. The glass will either be held in place by its own static friction or may use silicone at the corners to raise it slightly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 00:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your post is what I originally mean't by "meaningful comments." You haven't acknowledged any aspect of this post in regards to woodworking. But, I am thankful for the check, have a lot to learn about reddiquette-getting a lot of down votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 22:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks bud. A quality aesthetic is absolutely a requirement, I'll post the the updated iterations of the legs once I get to rendering this weekend. The technical drawings and programming are critical, but the tolerance may be problematic with the seasonal expansions. 
The table is as follows:
1/4" walnut veneered plywood and 1/4" inch cherry(inset)
5/8" particle board

What kind of expansion can I expect to see? How to alter design with this in mind? Any tips on laminating/connecting walnut plywood to particle board to structure of table?

Thanks again everyone!

Edit: i's to I's and 86'ed an extra word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 22:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is bold, I like bold. I'll elaborate-the majority of furniture designs I've seen that are heavy on the CNC router are focused on flat-packing or complete CNC fabrication. The process of cutting out a pattern and fitting it with its infill counterpart isn't seen as much(in the scope of CNC routing furniture). The overall process of pattern/infill in furniture design has been around for ages; what makes this special is the tolerance of the CNC's measure- something like a 10,000th of an inch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 21:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will be glass in those portions. I acknowledge your gut reaction of it being 'too busy,' but I like it so, and respectfully disregard it (happens pretty often in design conversation) The figure ground between pattern and wood type is what makes the project, how the pattern is created and infilled using a CNC router is also something not really done before... Ever.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 21:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This render is from about 3 weeks ago. The pattern in plan has changed very slightly, and the legs are now less bulky and taper to a square at the bottom. The outline in the pattern is 1/4" walnut plywood and the infill panels are cherry. The legs are walnut and the stringers(beams) between them are cherry. 
    
The panels, infill and pattern, are CNC routed, the connections to the legs are all mortise and tenon.
    
I am a fourth-year architecture student in a furniture studio. Any meaningful comments or general thoughts are appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A table I am designing and about to build. Tell me what you think Reddit!{First Reddit Post} </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 20:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 01:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Are you an interior decorator? Because when you walked in the room became beautiful."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
