<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6464</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Cousin's Wedding, Part II </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 05:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We left home at 6:30pm. When we were 600-700 from the restaurant, the traffic was so heavy that it went at a crawling speed. This is the result of heavy development in Flushing. My grandma's phone is ringing constantly.

When we went inside, we were told to sit at our designated tables. Then the wedding was about to start, I found out that the ratio of Asians to non-Asians was 7 to 1, with only one black guest. These people are the bride and groom's college classmates, coworkers, friends, and in-laws. During the wedding, I thought that if Hillary was here, she would think that this is unity and say, "Our society should be like this," while Trump would feel butthurt and would throw some racist rant.

Before the beginning of the wedding, we were served dim sum appetizers. They have char siu pastry, spring roll, hargow, and shumai. There was also alcohol.

The wedding consists of a 9-course meal, wedding games, dances, and an introduction video. The meal is similar to what we had this afternoon. By the sixth course, everyone started to feel full. 

By 10pm, everyone started to leave. By 10:30pm, it's only us and my cousin's college students and coworkers. My cousin is seen taking a high number of tequila shots. 15 minutes late, he became drunk. It took 30 minutes to wake him up. By 11:30pm, we all left.

When we were on the way home, it was fast until we got to 101th St due to road construction and a biker gang parking on the street. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Cousin's Wedding, Part I </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today is my cousin's wedding. We left home at 10:30 am and went to my cousin's home in Rego Park, NY. When we arrived I saw my cousin's uncle and aunt and my in-laws at the home.

The aunt-in-law was making vegetables for the feast. My dad and I was given a receipt for some food we have to pick up. We then went to the restaurant in Elmhurst, NY to pick up the food. After picking up the food, we went to the nearby supermarket and bought some tangerines. When I peeked inside the supermarket, I can tell that it is in renovation status.

When we went back to the home, we started to prepare the feast and waited for the bride and groom to enter. When they entered, they went to the room, as part of the Chinese traditions. My relatives were given cups of tea to drink before eating. The staples were the usual. There were some seafood yi mein noodles, chow main, and vegetable noodles.

After eating, we cleared the tables. Then, the cameraman take pictures of my cousins' relatives and friends. When they are about to go to the park, my cousin went with them. Currently, I am at home. At 6pm, we will head to the ballroom.

Part II tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 Election="The Purge" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 01:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that there are three movies of The Purge, I can speculate that the result of the election can result in the scenes of the movie in the real life.

Based on the recent news reports, if Hillary wins, "The Purge" will be enacted by the conservatives; if Trump wins, "The Purge" will be enacted by the liberals. It can spill out to a possible civil clash, but no war.

However, Hillary will still win, meaning that conservatives will be butthurt and react violently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 01:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched GradeAUnderA's video and he made the same points. Lately, Hillary is regaining ground. I believe the election isn't rigged; Trump is saying so to seek attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you. If I create a mature-themed Anpanman, the way I would create it is by using the show to simulate real life situations. This can cause butthurt to the fans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who do you support? She is the main reason that I think that vice is acceptable, sexual and violent crimes are not crimes under certain conditions, and decline in moral values. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possible 2020 Olympics Boycotts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 02:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that the 2016 Olympics has ended, I will be talking about the possible 2020 Olympics boycotts.

Tokyo had hosted the Olympics in 1964. This event became a turning point for Japan since the events of WWII.

There are three reasons some would consider boycotting the Olympics: anti-Japanese sentiments, radiation from the Fukushima fallout, and whaling.

Japan became modernized after the fall of the Tokugawa Shogunate in 1868. In 1896, there was the first Sino-Japanese War. In 1910, Japan colonized Korea. In 1934, there was the Second Sino-Japanese War and the Rape of Nanjing. After the wars and atrocities, Japan did not owe up to the crimes.

The China-Japan relations are volatile to this day. The volatility increased from the Senkaku Disputes. Some view nationalism on the rise.

On March 11, 2011, the Tohoku Earthquake and Tsunami happened. This has led to the Fukushima nuclear plant fallout. A radius of 50 kilometers is still affected.

Several railway lines in Tohoku got affected. The Iwaizumi Line became defunct due to the high costs to repair it and low demand for the line. Parts of the Ofunato and Kesennuma lines got converted to BRT lines. The Joban Line is partly closed and will be fully opened before 2020. The southern part of the Yamada Line will get transferred to the Sanriku Railway Rias South Line upon reopening. 

Japan is notorious for whaling. It is often documented or reported in political news magazines. Currently, there is a petition to boycott the Olympics until whaling becomes history.

However, some think that the Olympics is a chance for reconciliation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Felling Butthurt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 02:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An hour ago, my aunt came over for dinner. We had a conversation about the 2016 elections. After hearing what she said, I felt butthurt.

She said that Hillary is much more dangerous than previously through. She even said that if she becomes president, America would be worst than before. It's because she was a lesbian.

Trump, on the other hand, would make the US better. He would make the economy and the political system better. I myself would not support him due to his insults at minorities and the disabled.

During the dinner, I told her that Hillary is a liberal-leaning-right candidate while Trump is a conservative-leaning-left candidate. She said that doesn't care, only the person who can be a good leader can be the president.

I have been supporting Hillary since the election campaign, and will never become a political traitor. Ever since the emailgate 2.0, I started making donations to the Hillary Fund and to the liberal non-for-profit organizations.

Now that it's just a few days before Election Day, I see that conservatives will revolt if Hillary wins. A few weeks ago, I saw a conspiracy theory video about a possible civil war. From the video, I heard that younger generations support the left while the older generations support the right. Not only political divisions exist regionally, but rather generationally. Even the military has made theories  on how the war would happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is she crazy? No wonder it became a cult following. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Hillary Is Very Unlikely To Be Indicted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 17:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pyrobooby's Opinion of the Chopstick 1000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 16:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emailgate 2.0 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 05:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Assless Benson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 04:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Election Isn't Rigger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 02:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Land of Ooo is Parallel to Mr. Peabody and Sherman's New York City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 05:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seeing fanarts of Mr. Peabody and Sherman cosplaying Finn and Jake in the Land of Ooo, I speculate that these two universes are parallel to each other.

Finn and Sherman were orphans and were adopted by Jake and Mr. Peabody respectively. As we see from these two settings, they travel from place to place. They become inseparable.

Sherman and Penny where initial rivals, but later became friends, similar to Finn and Princess Bubblegum. Finn and Sherman have archrivals, i.e. Ice King and Ms. Grunion respectively.

Jake is a shape-changing dog, who can manipulate his body structure to suit any situation, while Mr. Peabody is a highly intelligent. They have living relatives.

Finn uses various swords throughout his adventures while Sherman uses different articles of clothing through their adventures. Finn wears a munsell blue t-shirt, denim shorts, a two-colored lime green circular backpack, rolled-down white socks, a pair of black shoes, and a hat that resembles a bear, while Sherman wears a white t-shirt, black shorts, white shoes that resembles Converse high-tops, white socks, and round glasses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [fanart] Dipper Wearing the Baseball Cap With Hillary's Presidential Campaign Logo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [fanart] Mabel Wearing On the Sweater With Hillary's Presidential Campaign Logo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 17:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 00:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mordecai As a Womanizer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grade's Rant To Doraemon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 02:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8 Years Since the Closing of Black Pearl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 23:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black Pearl was a seafood shack in Alphabet City before moving to Nomad. The restaurant was a few blocks from Baruch College that was owned by David, Brian and Greg.

During the episode, we see that David's ego gets in the way of a good atmosphere. Through the episode, we see how his ego cause the restaurant to fail.

4 days after the episode aired, the restaurant closed due to their sales getting halved. David made a rant about Gordon. One thing that surprised me in the rant was that he wrote "While I hope Gordo meets an untimely death so that I can dance on his grave, it is time to move on."

After the restaurant closed, he went back to his previous career in the music industry, releasing the record "The Quickening" in 2010.

Currently, Hog Pit USA replaced Black Pearl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Year Since the Closing of Amy's Baking Company </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 23:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A year ago, Amy's Baking Company's closed due to the conflicts between the owners and the new landlords of the mall, who built new plumbing, causing the kitchen to have problems. A month later, the new owners opened a new restaurant called B R Wine-Food.

After the restaurant closed, Amy's Baking Company became a wholesale franchise, selling cakes to other companies, and an online school. Since the restaurant has closed, the nightmare has also ended.

Currently, the online storm has died down. We don't see much attacks between Amy's Baking Company and Yelp and Reddit. When I search B R Wine-Food on Yelp, one Yelper said that "The ghost of Amy's Baking Company has finally been exorcised..." Another Yelper said "They don't even have Amy's deserts anymore.  But she didn't make them any way." A third Yelper said "You need to give them a try.  They are fighting the bad wrap from Amy's Bakery..."

Update: Since posting this information, turns out Amy and Samy are living in Westwood, CA in a "posh, five-unit condominium building that features primarily 2-bedroom, 2.75-bath homes for rent, ranging from about 2,100 to 2,300 square feet", while owning a home in Arizona, according to azcentral. She is still baking, updating her Instagram account from time to time and still selling T-shirts from the episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Events After the Election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 03:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vanoss and Mordecai </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 01:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grade and Nobita </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 01:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nick As a Doshin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 00:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that you metioned it, these two universes do not coexists with each other, but rather parallel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zootopia Coexists With Soul Society </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 03:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seeing fanarts of Nick and Judy cosplaying Ichiruki and vice versa and people saying how their stories are related, I speculate that they coexist with each other.

Ichigo and Nick were shunned by others, while Rukia and Judy are viewed as amateurs. They meet each other while confronting a wanted creature, where they then work with each other until the peers find out.

They then cover more clues and evidence, eventually confronting the perpetrator. Nick and Ichigo became accepted by their established institutions.

Comparing Zootopia with Soul Society. The districts of Zootopia are similar to the districts of Rukongai, which each district are distinct from each other. The Soul Society is similar to the government of the Zootopia, where each company is similar to the departments of Zootopia or any big city, i.e. Tokyo or New York. Genryusai is similar to the mayor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 23:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand your concern. For the past year, there was enough evidence that go hand-in-hand. I also have made this speculation on DeviantArt, gaining 44 views. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gravity Falls: A Metaphor of the 2016 Presidential Election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 05:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I speculate that the show Gravity Falls is a metaphor of the 2016 election.

From what I know, Li'l Gideon represents Trump, where he had white hair and seen in a suit. He is a fraud, a metaphor of Trump who uses lies to manipulate people, especially whites to support him.

The Pines represents the Democratic party. Mabel herself represents Clinton. At the beginning of the series, we see Mabel and Li'l Gideon dating, eventually breaking up. The dating part is a metaphor of Trump saying that Clinton is good and inviting her to his 2005 wedding. The break-up is a metaphor to Trump and Clinton announcing their presidential run.

Dipper represents Tim Kaine, Grunkle Pines represents Sanders, and Ford Pines represents Former Mayor Mike Bloomberg. Bill Cipher himself represents Mike Paine early in the series and later Wikileaks founder Jullian Assange.

Assange is attacking both Trump and Hillary. Wikileaks represents the Weirdmaggedon. With the Pines defeating Bill, everything becomes routine, which is a metaphor that Wikileaks will stop bothering them anymore. Bill trapping Mabel is a metaphor of the email dump. When Dipper and Mabel pat each other's back, everything gets destroyed, a metaphor that Clinton and Sanders are working together to get rid of the indictment or keep the party united. Dippy Fresh represents the FBI. In the court, we see his true form, which is a metaphor for the FBI going against Hillary.

The Weirdmageddon represents the time from the conventions to the election day. The first and second part describe the meetings and the third part describes election day. In episode 20, Li'l Gideon faces defeat and inceration, which is a metaphor that Trump is already losing and is bolstering his ego as trying to win.

Mabel, however, has friends who support him. Her friends are women, a metaphor that women like Hillary. One of her friends is Korean, a metaphor that minorities, especially Asians, blacks, and Muslims support Hillary. Soos and Wendy working for the Pines is a metaphor that Hispanics (important) and young adults, importantly women, also support Hillary.

In the last episode of the show, Li'l Gideon has to help the Pines and become reformed, a metaphor that the Republican party will lose and Trump becomes what he was before the presidential run.

Preston Northwest in the last few episodes pledges allegiance to Bill Cipher, who would make lots of money if Bill becomes ruler, a metaphor of a British Scientologist making $100,000 if Trump wins.

Update: The Oct 21 DDos is part of the Weirdmageddon metaphor. I might be wrong about Grunkle Stan, he represents Bill Clinton. Bill and Hillary not receiving donations is a metaphor of Grunkle retiring. Ford represents Bernie Sanders. Bill Cipher becoming a statue is a symbol that Trump will haunt Hillary. Dippy Fresh's true from has been reviewed in real life.

Update: Dippy Fresh's true form has been revealed in real life.

Update: Emailgate 2.0 got dropped. Bill Cipher is destroyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
