<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 15:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> m'pissbottles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 21:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's weird as hell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 20:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 19:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its awesome and im not even huge yet. If i ever sit and lean over people think im huge. Also accentuates v taper so all around amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 18:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be a great upgrade to my first PC! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I mean, the Book of Mormon is written in King's Old English.  It is as KJV as it comes.

It's written in *bad* KJV English. It makes basic grammatical mistakes for what it's trying to emulate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 18:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy cake day!

^only ^consume ^if ^on ^a ^cut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 16:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHY ARE WE YELLING? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classic *No True Scotsman* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I don't think about you at all.](http://cdn.niketalk.com/0/06/200x200px-ZC-06271b82_jlaw-okay.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 00:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, keep slinging your broscience, I'll stick with the literally world renowned Mayo Clinic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. 

"Total transit time, from eating to elimination in stool, averaged 53 hours (although that figure is a little overstated, because the markers used by the researchers passed more slowly through the stomach than actual food). The average transit time through just the large intestine (colon) was 40 hours, with significant difference between men and women: 33 hours for men, 47 hours for women."

http://www.mayoclinic.org/digestive-system/expert-answers/faq-20058340 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 21:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I eat a McSandwich I see a poop come out that is only slightly smaller than the original product.

That's not really how it works, at all. Your feces are a few meals worth of indigestible food, plus other waste products. 

Furthermore, I'd be surprised if McDonalds has gotten their calorie content wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 16:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could leave a copy at your work, or your fiances work, as well. But, I'm a little paranoid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 16:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's a few decades ago, and you've abandoned the fridge outside. Maybe you took the shelves out to move it easier. Maybe someone else took them out to use in their own fridge. 

Fridge deaths were a thing. Just because you think that the shelves are eternally linked to the fridge doesn't mean anything. 

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Refrigerator_death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 16:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you kidding? Nearly every full size fridge available at Sears or whatever could fit a normal 6 year old child. You just need to take the shelves out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 15:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just so you are aware, reddit doesn't take HTML tags like p /p.

Paragraphs are made by hitting enter twice. While you're typing in the box, click on "formatting help" for more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 15:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely understandable. I thought your wording was a little ambiguous, thanks for the clarification. Good luck with your LL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 14:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This friend has agreed to say that she lived with him and paid rent.

*Did* she pay rent to him? Or has this friend agreed to lie in court? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 01:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've given up being nice

You were making an effort in the first place?


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weren't you just complaining about downvote delays? Comments like this may be illustrative about why you get such delays.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 03:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given your obvious intellectual prowess, I'm surprised you appear to think that I believe you insult people for debate value.

Again, you were banned because you broke the subreddit's most basic, simple rule. 

No Personal Attacks. Keep things civil. Avoid simple ad hominem attacks. Avoid hurtful language. No trolling.

However, given your previous reading comprehension, I'd like to point it out again:

**No Personal Attacks.** Keep things civil. *Avoid* **simple** *ad hominem attacks.* Avoid hurtful language. No trolling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 14:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, hey, I found out why you were banned! It's because you "debate" emotionally rather than logically.

https://www.reddit.com/r/DebateAnAtheist/comments/3adbnj/who_knew_atheists_were_such_poor_debaters/csbpdgv

some excerpts:

You are actually the complete idiot i'm afriad

Your'e a fuckwit

Again, you're just being retarded.

Again, fuckwit

[sic] for all the spelling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 14:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was banned from the exmormon subreddit just because I posted a question about why they left the Church. They think emotionally rather than logically. 

Bullshit. 

If you were banned, its because you broke the only real rule /r/exmormon has, **No personal attacks.**

You know, like calling people idiots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get hung up on the profanity, then. 

You should respect people's *right to think what they want.* You shouldn't (and can't!) respect all of their beliefs. 

Don't be a hypocrite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 15:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Decent people respect others beliefs, even if they don't subscribe to them personally.

Bullshit!

I can respect your right to believe whatever the hell you want, but I sure don't have to respect your belief. Let's say you were a proponent of child abuse. You may be dead wrong, but I still support your right to freedom of conscience.

Stop abusing the word "respect." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mirin at the grocery store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 00:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fascinating. What do you think of chemtrails? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 18:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  LGBT movement just happens to be on the agenda.

Whose agenda? The reptilians? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 16:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the sin was Lot offering to let his two virgin daughters get gang-raped?

I don't know why Sodom and Gomorrah are held as this grave warning. They damn Christianity much more than they ever do homosexuals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 16:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The only mention of homosexual marriage occurs just prior to the flood of Noah and is a direct cause of that flood.

I don't know, modern Christians/the LDS church/conservatives/the GOP seem to fill the following:

Now this was the sin of your sister Sodom: She and her daughters were arrogant, overfed and unconcerned; they did not help the poor and needy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 23:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love my Chromebook. Used it to get drivers for my new tower (didn't have an Ethernet driver, so I couldn't download anything). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 16:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, according to Packer,

It is not unusual to have a missionary say, How can I bear testimony until I get one? How can I testify that God lives, that Jesus is the Christ, and that the gospel is true? If I do not have such a testimony, would that not be dishonest?

Oh, if I could teach you this one principle: a testimony is to be found in the bearing of it!

So, maybe she should continue being counterfeit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 15:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, you need to have two "enters" to break up paragraphs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, sure. But 

Also 90% of our planet is undiscovered so I don't think **archaeological proof** is necessary.

implies land, so the oceans are *de facto* removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 17:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, you're including fucking **oceans** in your bullshit "90%"?

Maybe you should research logical fallacies next.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 17:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I mean is that missionaries often have no idea about basic history of doctrine of the church. They're 19, have no life experience, and are really not the best resource to actually learn about the church.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 16:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are the best people to go to with questions.

Hahahahahahahahahahaha
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 23:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or hell, physical legs. Books turn me on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 17:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant: 

http://i.imgur.com/mG22AKY.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 15:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Living the teachings of the church is supposed to make you happy

It sure has failed for a vast number of people, then. Maybe the teachings don't work because they're wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 15:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh hey, disadvantaged third-world kid with eye-worms and malaria. God has given them to you for a *reason*! Isn't the Gospel wonderful?"

"Your husband beats you? You're so lucky that God is challenging you this way! Doesn't it help your testimony?"

"You were raped repeatedly as a child? What a *tender mercy*! Look at you, blessed of God."

This is absolutely disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Piss-shit, actually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/AcademicBiblical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Church has no more need of the easily manipulated.

So they at one time had need of the easily manipulated? And by extension, the church church manipulated them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  She did this because of JS III's claims to authority. It was political.

I don't think it matters *why* she did, only that she did lie about something so fucking huge. All her other testimony is now suspect.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks again, your expertise is much better than mine (clearly). That card got recommended via the PCPartPicker, and I submitted a build [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/buildapc/comments/39ulqe/build_ready_first_basic_gaming_pc_600_tv_as/). Which one would you do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 02:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That build seems pretty okay, but I'm not sure if I need/want overclocking (I'm not sure how to do it).

One of my big problems is that I have a general idea of what each part *does*, I just don't know how they'll act together. For example, would your build play better (FPS or whatever) compared to an xbox one?

For the video card, am I right in assuming that more GB is better than less? Would this card (http://pcpartpicker.com/part/sapphire-video-card-100363vx3l?ref=mrob) be better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your input!

The primary way I'll play games is with the xbox controller, the wireless kb/mouse is for lazy internet browsing. Everything will be done from my couch, as I don't have room for a desk, but already have a couch/TV/etc.

How does your current build handle recent game titles? Is your current build roughly equivalent to mine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Ready] - First basic gaming PC, $600, TV as monitor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can purchase these parts as soon as Wednesday, unless there is compelling reason to wait.

###Build Help/Ready:

**Have you read the sidebar and [rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/buildapc/wiki/rules)? (Please do)**

Yes

**What is your intended use for this build? The more details the better.**

Skyrim, Witcher 3, GTA V, etc, as well as netflix/browsing/whatever

**If gaming, what kind of performance are you looking for? (Screen resolution, FPS, game settings)**

At least comparable to a console.

**What is your budget (ballpark is okay)?**

$550-600

**In what country are you purchasing your parts?**

United States. I live near a Microcenter.

**Post a draft of your potential build here (specific parts please). [Consider formatting your parts list.](http://www.reddit.com/r/buildapc/wiki/pcpp)**

[PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/msgtYJ) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/msgtYJ/by_merchant/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [Intel Core i5-4440 3.1GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80646i54440?ref=mrob) | $163.95 @ SuperBiiz 
**Motherboard** | [Gigabyte GA-H81M-S2H Micro ATX LGA1150 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gigabyte-motherboard-gah81ms2h?ref=mrob) | $43.99 @ SuperBiiz 
**Memory** | [G.Skill Ripjaws X Series 8GB (1 x 8GB) DDR3-1600 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gskill-memory-f31600c9s8gxm?ref=mrob) | $45.99 @ Newegg 
**Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 1TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st1000dm003?ref=mrob) | $48.75 @ OutletPC 
**Video Card** | [Sapphire Radeon R9 280X 3GB Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/sapphire-video-card-100363vx3l?ref=mrob) | $192.98 @ Newegg 
**Case** | [Cooler Master N200 MicroATX Mid Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/cooler-master-case-nse200kkn1?ref=mrob) | $43.99 @ SuperBiiz 
**Power Supply** | [EVGA 500W 80+ Bronze Certified ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/evga-power-supply-100b10500kr?ref=mrob) | $35.00 @ Newegg 
 | *Prices include shipping, taxes, rebates, and discounts* |
 | Total (before mail-in rebates) | $604.65
 | Mail-in rebates | -$30.00
 | **Total** | **$574.65**
 | Build automatically generated by [ChooseMyPC.net](http://choosemypc.net)|

**Provide any additional details you wish below.**

I'm planning on using a 42" HDTV LED Vizio, 120 hz, as a monitor, in conjunction with a wireless mouse, keyboard, and wired xbox 360 controller.

This build was automatically pushed out by the choosemyPC build generator. Building computers is new, and completely foreign. Does anything seem *not right*? Anything obvious that could be easily upgraded?

Thanks for your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 23:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll do that! Odd in what way?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 23:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so it might not be a true 1080

I'm not sure that I have a discerning enough eye to notice, but thank you for the warning.

You will want to connect a controller

I'm planning on using a corded xbox 360 controller, it's familiar, and I've heard that it pairs very well with PC gaming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 23:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Most graphics cards have HDMI ports.

Excellent, I had no idea. This whole world is new to me, and I'll probably just go with a computer from Logical Increments or the ChooseMyPC builder, after input from this subreddit.

Thanks for your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help] How do I use a HDTV as a monitor for a computer? Would a build generally automatically include an HDMI output? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 23:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###Build Help/Ready:

*Have you read the sidebar and [rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/buildapc/wiki/rules)? (Please do)*

I have.


*What is your intended use for this build? The more details the better.*

Primarily video gaming, Witcher 3, GTA V, etc., although probably not on the highest graphics settings.

*If gaming, what kind of performance are you looking for? (Screen resolution, FPS, game settings)*

**I'd like to use my 42" Vizio LED HDTV (3 HDMI, 1 Ethernet) as my monitor**

*What is your budget (ballpark is okay)?*

$550-650, tower only.

*In what country are you purchasing your parts?*

USA

*Provide any additional details you wish below.*

Do most cases/builds automatically have an HDMI output? Is HDMI best for this? What kind of play-ability can I expect on a large TV compared to a smaller monitor? I'm planning on using a wireless keyboard and mouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 15:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We understand that demand for The Book of Mormon: The Game, at game stores will initially be in very high demand right when the game first gets into the hands of our supporters.

Hahahahahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 00:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Small claims court? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 23:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His physique is so good, his muscles can metabolize burgers that make you fart into fuel, aka a jet pack. This is my favorite web comic ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 20:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  jetpack made of muscle

http://drmcninja.com/archives/comic/3p38/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 15:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For one, she said it would invalidate his priesthood holder status in the church, and therefore our eternal vows.

Mormon? Yeah, my parents have told me very similar things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 20:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any suggestions if I find that soda water has an almost bitter aftertaste? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
