<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5556</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Stone offers his view of the 3rd debate (Links skips to 3:54, goes up to 17:00; then at 20:30 is a 5-minute interview from the other day with Nigel Farage) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Federalist: No, Hillary Clinton, The Supreme Court's Heller Decision Wasn't About Toddlers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Federalist: No, Hillary Clinton, The Supreme Court's Heller Decision Wasn't About Toddlers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From the 2nd debate: Its obvious that Hillary has trained herself to grin really big whenever she gets angry on-camera, but when Trump said he was going to get a special prosecutor to investigate her, she not only grinned, but stood up and walked around. Her real reaction had to be unspeakable rage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 15:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 15:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Election maps with percentages in a pie chart:

https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/U.S._election_maps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the way that MSM propagandists and their shills write about Trump, you'd think he's been polling at like 30%, which, if that sounds impossible, is actually more than the losing candidate in 1964, '72, '80, '84, and '88. But the new Rasmussen poll (Oct. 20) has him beating Hillary by 3%! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 15:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 08:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it really is true that no one is telling him what to say or what to do. There are so many examples of it. But there are still 3 weeks for his campaign, AND his supporters, and himself, to get the *Vote Trump* message out! I'm doing whatever I can in terms of sharing on social media (and my posting here on Reddit is the LEAST of it), and in donating. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 08:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And for some weird reason, the two main guys in video lost their jobs right after the video was released! Weird! They were just doing ordinary political stuff! Nothing wrong, as you said! 

http://www.snopes.com/2016/10/19/scott-foval-reportedly-fired-from-political-organization-over-sting-videos/

http://www.cnn.com/2016/10/18/politics/project-veritas-action-robert-creamer-donald-trump-rallies/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BEST copy of the 3rd debate (HD pic, clear audio) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 07:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> # POLLS! CAST YOUR VOTE NOW! 

# https://theconservativetreehouse.com/2016/10/19/your-turn-who-won-the-third-presidential-debate-polls-polls-polls/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same shit after the 2nd debate, but the tide already turned against her on 2 of those local Fox ones. EVERYBODY VOTE!!!!!! WE HAVE MORE PEOPLE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just cast your vote, as should everyone else reading this. The tide turned in several polls after the past 2 debates, thanks to voters caring enough to vote. Consider it practice for Nov 8 -

# https://theconservativetreehouse.com/2016/10/19/your-turn-who-won-the-third-presidential-debate-polls-polls-polls/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> # MORE! 

# https://theconservativetreehouse.com/2016/10/19/your-turn-who-won-the-third-presidential-debate-polls-polls-polls/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> POST-DEBATE POLLS! CAST YOUR VOTE NOW!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> POST-DEBATE POLLS! CAST YOUR VOTE NOW!!!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> # POLLS! CAST YOUR VOTE NOW! 

# https://theconservativetreehouse.com/2016/10/19/your-turn-who-won-the-third-presidential-debate-polls-polls-polls/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. At the moment, only 4.5M people have watched the first video, and .3M have seen the second, and I'd bet that virtually all of them are already supporters--and of course there are those who saw the videos on Hannity's show and website, and on the Alex Jones channel. **Those videos (and the next ones) EACH need to have AT LEAST over 80 MILLION views!!!!!!**

https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCEE8w-v6Gg4j3ze3oX-urEw/videos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But his plane is like a really narrow mini-mansion; it has an executive office, a gourmet kitchen, and a shower: 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OygETK3-oN4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought about that, but to accuse the whole party, even though it's accurate and fully warranted, would provoke too many people to start picking out Democrats they like, and going 'Well what about Senator so-and-so? Or Governor so-and-so?'" Just the same, to say Obama used the same system will then expand and therefore complicate the argument and leave too much room for tangents. There are just too many people. The discussion has to be centralized on and around HER specifically, not "the Democrats." That's my view.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This may be a dumb question, but was Jimmy Chamberlain the drummer with her on the "When The Pawn" tour (like in this video)? It kinda look like him, but I can't find the name of whoever it was, if not. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CONTINUING CORRUPTION: NYC Elections Official (Alan Schulkin, from the Veritas video) Scoffs at Mayor's Call for Him to Resign Over Voter Fraud Claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In tonight's debate, Trump NEEDS to say "The videos posted by James O'Keefe on the Project Veritas YouTube channel show just how corrupt Hillary's campaign really is." He talked about the agitators yesterday in Colorado Springs, but didn't name anything! Tens of millions of people will be watching! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 15:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those videos should have 100M views! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  young bloods

It doesn't surprise me that actual gang members are the kind of people who want to give her positive coverage. They aspire to her level of heinous criminality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We know Hannity is not MSM, but that's all I can say for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who missed the splatter:

http://www.9news.com/news/hillary-clinton-campaign-bus-dumps-sewage-on-lawrenceville-street/337744489 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was like a "breakthrough" moment right there--in addition to the #Veritas sign and the chanting at the end!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since this sub doesn't allow linking to posts in other subs, just search the title and read the post and the top answer in /r/AskHistorians - very interesting! -

President LBJ: "Ill have those n*****s voting Democratic for the next 200 years" - Is this a real quote? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very shrewd analysis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Is it too late now to say sor-ry?*

http://www.11alive.com/news/local/dnc-apologizes-after-campaign-bus-dumps-sewage-on-georgia-street/337641655

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, better dump that shit somewhere in Atlanta, since the DNC can't afford enough busloads of fake voters (i.e. shittily bribed PEOPLE) there. 

http://www.9news.com/news/hillary-clinton-campaign-bus-dumps-sewage-on-lawrenceville-street/337744489

http://www.11alive.com/news/local/dnc-apologizes-after-campaign-bus-dumps-sewage-on-georgia-street/337641655 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's up with the word "Democratic"? East Germany was the "German Democratic Republic," North Korea is the "Democratic People's Republic of Korea," then there's the hellishly dangerous "Democratic Republic of the Congo," while we have the "Democratic Party," and "Democratic" Nominee Hillary Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why Trump only ever says "Democrat" as the adjectival form. It denotes the political party, not the moral ideal. 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_sovereign_states </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at what the Democrat Party nominated. It's a piece of shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, we know FOR SURE that it's not any of these 38 pro-Hill pro shills: 

http://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2016/10/wikileaks-outs-corrupt-media-list-reporters-taking-marching-orders-hillary/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but the mainstream media has an iron grip on a lot of people's minds, young and old. That's why we gotta share those Veritas videos as much as possible!!! I posted the first one in /r/CringeAnarchy and it got dozens of angry comments--but it also got 456 points (80% upvoted)! :) I just figured I'd let the voters have their say, and there it is. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put a sign in your window that lets 'em know they MAY be recorded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding the timing of all these releases, I think that both of the leaking organizations understand very well that the American memory span is now just about 2 full days. That's due to the 24/7 news cycle, the internet, and the sheer way that smartphones have totally fried the average person's attention span AND memory. Look at the DOZENS of media-created and exaggerated "scandals" from all throughout Trump's campaign. There are so many that were the center of tornado of stupid coverage, but have long, LONG been forgotten, and there's just the consistent ongoing accusation that he's "racist!" and "sexist!"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Van Jones was clearly cheering at his TV set when he saw the footage of that chaos, which the networks had on a nonstop loop for the whole night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait for all the next videos that just keep undoing the damage control they keep attempting. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who says "Infowars" at 6:25?!

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lz7GaQYJ3zA#t=6m25s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 13:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at her plane. That thing is a piece of shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 13:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> # He's won the penis-measuring contest. Elect this man NOW!!!!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 12:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even Ted Cruz, who talks like an uptight televangelist, had Rubio flustered and shaking with fear in the debates. Rubio would start repeating himself and laughing nervously, it was so pathetic. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 12:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **#FakeOctoberSurprise https://i.sli.mg/2VRcPj.jpg** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #FakeTrumpVictims: Wikipedia lists the various fictional claims that have suddenly emerged in past 2 weeks. The article includes his campaign's responses and there's a whole section titled "Trump campaign reactions." (See the image I linked below, regarding the timing of this stuff) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 12:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For months, I've been seeing comments on YouTube, Reddit, and Twitter that say Trump is "whining" when he points out corruption. Now look who's using the re-defined word. It's a lot like people who say "Yeah, there's corruption, get over it." Vote out defeatism and apathy on Nov. 8!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 12:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The worst political fan-fiction ever: The Tampa Bay Times does an alternate-reality exercise, imagining Marco Rubio as the nominee, and then proceeds to cast him as a brilliantly talented and accomplished political powerhouse. Well, he had 12 debates to showcase ANY of that, yet only won MN and D.C. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 10:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 10:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Creamer rose to public attention in 2009, when Breitbart News [revealed](http://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2009/12/07/was-democrats-health-care-strategy-written-in-federal-prison/) that he had written the political blueprint for passing Obamacare **while serving time in federal prison.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 07:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, stop being logical!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hollywood's political agenda, ever sneaky and strategically placed: In Emma Stone's otherwise goofy and lighthearted Vogue video interview, she's asked "What's one cause that's dear to your heart?" and she makes a serious face and goes "Gun control" (Watch the first minute; or click to 0:56) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 07:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 07:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LNC = Late Night Crew </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And with Facebook:

https://www.google.com/trends/explore?date=all geo=US q=Facebook,Twitter,Reddit,Snapchat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cultural relevance and power: The U.S. Google Trends graph showing the trajectories of Twitter, Reddit, and Snapchat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given Twitter's future, in terms of cultural relevance, Google Trends shows that the service is definitely NOT on the way up:

https://www.google.com/trends/explore?date=all q=Twitter
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> # DEPLORABLE DILBERT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> # GUILT BY ASSOCIATION? THAT'S JUST A BUNCHA OKIE DOKE :P :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 03:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think that many, perhaps most, of his new followers are not actually people who think his corruption-orchestrating ways were cool, but who are just curious to what, if anything, he may post following the release of this footage. At least that's why I've been revisiting the page. Clearly he has no qualms whatsoever; I know I'm not the only one who wouldn't be surprised if he's already being moved to another Super PAC, just like how DWS was immediately rehired after her firing. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Scott Foval said: "We've been bussing people in for fifty years...and we're just gonna find a find a different way to do it" - Yeah, by getting millions of votes from illegals (7.9M people in Texas voted in 2012; *15M* people are now registered there) AND from supposed Americans living abroad!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 03:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the part of the video:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hDc8PVCvfKs#t=2m35s

Case in point: 7,993,851 people in Texas voted in 2012...

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_presidential_election_in_Texas,_2012#Results

...and now: *Record 15 million Texans registered to vote* - Oct. 13, 2016

https://www.texastribune.org/2016/10/13/over-15-million-texans-are-registered-vote/

Soros-Linked 'October Surprise That Will End Trump': The Campaign To Register 8 Million 'Global Citizens' To Vote - Soros Launches Phony Ex-Pat Voter Registration Scam - They know who's living abroad and who's already voted absentee. Easy then to fill out the remaining ballots for Hillary. No investigation will follow this election theft.

http://www.breitbart.com/london/2016/09/21/surprise-that-will-end-trump-globalists-registering-8-million/

Even Politico report that the official UN Twitter account called for Americans abroad to "end Trump"--and then the tweet was deleted.

http://archive.is/8v5gf
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 01:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People throw around the words like "psychopath" and "sociopath" a lot these days. I'm not a professional psychologist, but that guy has DEFINITELY gotta be something like that. The only thing I'm sure he WAS upset about was losing his job and the surely massive paycheck he got from it, but other than that, someone who has been making a LIVING acting as unconscionably as he has, does not think that what he does is wrong at all. There's no way. Also, from a moral or religious angle: when is the word "EVIL" seriously used? I'd say this is one case where it can (JUST my opinion...). Anyway, share the video with everyone everywhere and let them form their own conclusions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 01:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next part: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1GeIo79zhwY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN's Anderson Cooper interviews Melania Trump 10/18/2016 - She actually says that women have constantly approached Trump and offered him their phone number even when she is standing right next to him! (Her answer to the Q @7:43) #FakeTrumpVictimsBTFO (Next part linked below) [Unofficial upload] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 01:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next part: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1GeIo79zhwY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First Archive.is copy saved yesterday - he had 2,862 Twitter followers (so he's gotten 661 news ones as of right now) -

http://archive.is/uC9i4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DEFIANT! Scott Foval on Twitter retweets from @YouAnonNews: "Someday, @JamesOKeefeIII is going to fall so far down a rabbit hole, he's going to pull a sting on himself then blame "liberal media" for it" (Foval now has 3,523 followers, up several 100 from yesterday) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SECOND JAMES O'KEEFE VIDEO: Rigging the Election - Video II: Mass Voter Fraud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 12:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next part: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1GeIo79zhwY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 07:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See my other comment - Axelrod is a top strategist, and he publicly introduced the idea of skipping the debate, 2 days ago. Then consider that Hillary is spending the whole week out of the public eye until the debate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 07:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has 502,000 Twitter followers and this got 1,860 retweets. Just considering what people would bother to follow that guy on Twitter, and then would retweet that to THEIR audience of followers--it would be very active and vocal Democrats both who work for the party and who don't: 

https://twitter.com/davidaxelrod/status/787369040750776320

The MSM echo-chamber (defined here: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Echo_chamber_(media)) picked up the idea and AMPLIFIED it out to their readership, getting the politics-following public thinking about it: 

THE WALL STREET JOURNAL, the 2nd most-read paper in the country, and America's main "serious" newspaper (http://www.infoplease.com/ipea/A0004420.html) -

 "Drug testing?!?" tweeted former Obama aide David Axelrod. "You have to wonder if @HillaryClinton will/should reconsider next debate, given the depths to which this has sunk." (Axelrod was referring to a Trump quip from a Saturday speech.) Boston Globe columnist Michael Cohen also floated the idea to scrap next weeks third and final presidential debate, though he admitted "I offer this proposal with a rather large grain of salt."

http://www.wsj.com/articles/divide-and-conquer-1476727240

http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/301196-axelrod-maybe-clinton-should-reconsider-final-debate

http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-3841532/Top-Obama-adviser-suggests-Hillary-Clinton-SKIP-final-debate-Trump-s-suggestion-drug-tested.html


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Stone: Axelrod wants Hillary to step down so Michelle Obama can take her place. Stone most recently revealed that Hillary wasn't going to shake Trump's hand at the start of the 2nd debate, and she didn't. Two days ago, MSM reported Axelrod suggested Hillary skip the next debate (See below) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 07:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 07:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, it's an imposter account. You have convinced me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ALL of those sites must be have their biggest traffic EVER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Who's Who of NON-establishment-controlled journalism: So far, there are 14 outlets covering that Veritas "DNC Incites Violence" video, and here they are. (Yes, evidently RealClearPolitics is partially uncucked!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird thing as of 4:30 PM ET: The view-count of the Veritas video has been stuck at 17,975 for at least 2 hours now, even as the numbers of Likes keeps increasing! Just keep refreshing the page and see! (21,314 Likes vs. 395 Dislikes at this moment) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hidden Camera Footage from James O'Keefe shows how the Clinton Campaign and DNC Incite Violence at Trump Rallies: "We're starting anarchy here" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NEW JAMES O'KEEFE VIDEO: Rigging the Election - Video I: Clinton Campaign and DNC Incite Violence at Trump Rallies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NEW JAMES O'KEEFE VIDEO: Rigging the Election - Video I: Clinton Campaign and DNC Incite Violence at Trump Rallies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Podesta's most recent TV interview, on Fox News Sunday 10/9/2016 - I hope Chris Wallace will be asking HILLARY these things on Wednesday! Note how Podesta says the leaked emails are "purported" to be real, but then he (like her) unwittingly admitted it, in explaining the "public/private" statement! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 13 comedians who endorse Trump, and then 11 others who endorse Hillary [x-post from /r/OpieAndAnthony by /u/AsunaKirito4Ever - 10/14/2016] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having listened to the show and read the key players' twitters for most of the year I think I have a pretty good list of who is voting for who. Now a lot of comedians deliberately sit on the fence and try not to say a definitive answer but they will also more readily damage control a particular candidate and/or attack one without talking about the other which makes them definitely lean one way. If someone calls Trump Hitler but says Hillary isn't that good either, obviously they're more likely to vote for Hillary. It's more accurate to say this is about which candidate they would rather vote for if they were forced too but that's not as interesting a title. Anybody I didn't list hasn't made a strong lean toward a candidate or I just forgot about. 

**Pro-Trump**

*Anthony Cumia

*Jim Norton

*Greg "Opie" Hughes (Last year he said he never would vote for a dynasty politician meaning both Jeb Bush or Hillary Clinton. In addition he always seems to take Trumps side in political talks since he hates "the media" and "PC culture" as well.)

*Brother Joe

*Bobo

*Stalker Patti

*Bill Burr (Said while he doesn't like Trump he absolutely can't stand Hillary)

*Club Soda Kenny

*Keith the Cop

*Dennis Falcone (Said Trump would be good for small businesses which he is part of one)

*Vic Henley

*Theo Von

*Jim Florentine

**Pro-Clinton**

*Amy Schumer [who is actually related to NY Senator Chuck Schumer]

*Louis CK

*Judy Gold

*Ron Bennington (He asked on one of his recent shows why anyone would bother voting for Trump as he couldn't understand it)

*Jim Jefferies

*Colin Quinn (Said when asked his opinions on Trump or Hillary that Hillary was the more qualified candidate)

*Sherrod Small

*Kurt Metzger

*Pete Davidson

*Travis Tefft

*Rich Vos (November 17th the Comedy Club in Webster NY)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 13 comedians who endorse Trump, and then 11 others who endorse Hillary [x-post from /r/OpieAndAnthony by /u/AsunaKirito4Ever 10/14/2016] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having listened to the show and read the key players' Twitters for most of the year I think I have a pretty good list of who is voting for who. Now a lot of comedians deliberately sit on the fence and try not to say a definitive answer but they will also more readily damage control a particular candidate and/or attack one without talking about the other which makes them definitely lean one way. If someone calls Trump Hitler but says Hillary isn't that good either, obviously they're more likely to vote for Hillary. It's more accurate to say this is about which candidate they would rather vote for if they were forced too but that's not as interesting a title. Anybody I didn't list hasn't made a strong lean toward a candidate or I just forgot about. 

**Pro-Trump**

*Anthony Cumia

*Jim Norton

*Greg "Opie" Hughes (Last year he said he never would vote for a dynasty politician meaning both Jeb Bush or Hillary Clinton. In addition he always seems to take Trumps side in political talks since he hates "the media" and "PC culture" as well.)

*Brother Joe

*Bobo

*Stalker Patti

*Bill Burr (Said while he doesn't like Trump he absolutely can't stand Hillary)

*Club Soda Kenny

*Keith the Cop

*Dennis Falcone (Said Trump would be good for small businesses which he is part of one)

*Vic Henley

*Theo Von

*Jim Florentine

**Pro-Clinton**

*Amy Schumer [who is actually related to NY Senator Chuck Schumer]

*Louis CK

*Judy Gold

*Ron Bennington (He asked on one of his recent shows why anyone would bother voting for Trump as he couldn't understand it)

*Jim Jefferies

*Colin Quinn (Said when asked his opinions on Trump or Hillary that Hillary was the more qualified candidate)

*Sherrod Small

*Kurt Metzger

*Pete Davidson

*Travis Tefft

*Rich Vos (November 17th the Comedy Club in Webster NY)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the border patrol will continue to operate if Hillary is president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 14:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Economic trouble in Hillary's favorite country: "Saudi Bank Stocks Tumble As Bailout Fails To Stem Liquidity Stress" (Damn, they might wanna to ask her to return those tens of millions they gave her! - See the article below about that, which was even shared on Twitter by Trump Jr.!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silver, Debt, and Deficits  From an Election Year Perspective (5 graphs and some analysis) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For any Glassbugs here: A 1942 experimental yellow-amber GLASS cent has been discovered (Oct. 14, 2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 1942 experimental yellow-amber GLASS cent has been discovered (Oct. 14, 2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 3rd debate will be in Las Vegas, where Trump has one of his most famous hotels. Maybe he can get one of his lighting technicians to do the marquee of the debate hall for the event, like this - </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 20:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lapel pins as symbol of what someone is loyal to  Consider that Tim Kaine wears a "H(illary)" lapel pin (as does Bill Clinton, but forget loyalty in THAT case XD), while Mike Pence wears an American flag lapel pin, just like Donald Trump. See the start of this video from today (10/16/2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 19:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In case your level of suspense wasn't already high enough- Roger Stone on The Jimmy Mathis Show (10/16/2016) - He says that everything leaked thus far is "CHICKENFEED" compared to what's on the way, and that "We have yet to have a SUBSTANTIAL October surprise Stay tuned!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 19:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Desperate times call for CROOKED measures: NBC   WSJ claim Hillary is leading by "11" points in their latest poll. The controlled media is just LYING to discourage Trump voters from showing up! Consider the rally sizes, frequency, and social-media followings and activity levels (Fb, Twtr, Reddit)! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 18:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As of right now, Sunday, 10/16/2016, there have been 9 #FakeTrumpVictims, and 9 sets of leaked #PodestaEmails - COINCIDENCE?? (BTW, I just noticed that The Hill is actually reporting about the emails, as seen in these results!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 18:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Maher vs. Ann Coulter FULL Interview 10/14/2016 - First, he tries to interrogate her about media-hyped garbage, and then she successfully turns it to a discussion of the ISSUES and the policies that Trump is fighting for! This is what we call effective messaging! When they go low, WE go high!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 18:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NBC's entertainment propaganda - the most insidious weapon in an information war: In the Saturday Night Live parody of the 2nd debate, the 4 rape victims are collectively referred to as Bill's "mistresses," and Hillary says "This is nothing. Hi girls!" (@3:00) - (copy of the original upload) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 14:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Stone - Stone Cold Truth Radio (Oct. 15th, 2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 08:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just BuzzFeed doing its part to make the election not a contest between Trump and Hillary, but a referendum on whether or not a 16-month avalanche of anti-Trump propaganda from the MSM can discourage enough of his supporters from showing up on Election Day. DON'T BE FOOLED. GO AND VOTE ON NOV. 8TH. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 07:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flashback: Arnold Schwarzenegger on the Howard Stern Show, 6/24/2015 (a week after Trump's announcement), said he liked Jeb Bush and John Kasich, but what he pointedly says about the need to fix the country's infrastructure suggests he had probably spoken with Trump. (@4:25, listen to up 7:00) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 04:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic vandalism at a Texas church: 'No to wall, Islam or die' spray-painted on San Antonio church entrance (Oct 10, 2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 03:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Front page of the NYPost (which is *not* part of the MSM machine): "COLD WAR 2.0" - and then see the front page of the NYTimes (Trump article in the upper right corner, Putin article the lower left corner) and the Washington Post (2 Trump stories right at the top) - 10/15/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 03:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Schiff talks about the media-created Trump "scandals" vs. the Establishment corruption revealed by Wikileaks. "When Trump is able to talk about the ISSUES, he can WIN, because things are horrible! There's no way you can DEFEND the last 8 years, other than to the 1%!" (@ 11:00; listen to 27:00) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 03:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McClatchy describes the ultimate Leftist/Feminist hypocrisy: Why do womens groups treat Bill Clinton and Donald Trump differently? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 03:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today's mainstream-media propaganda round-up (10/15/2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 03:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You just have to laugh: CNN's President Says It Was A Mistake To Air So Many Trump Rallies And "Let Them Run" (Ironically, they were still doing constant anti-Trump coverage the rest of the time for all those months; and of course now it's just solid wall-to-wall anti-Trump coverage) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 03:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Front page of the NYPost (which is *not* part of the mainstream-media machine): "COLD WAR 2.0" - and then see the front page of the NYTimes (Trump article in the upper right corner, Putin article the lower left corner) and the Washington Post (2 Trump stories right at the top) - Oct. 15, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 17:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1990s MadTV skit about the Clintons and Paula Jones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 07:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Proof that RealClearPolitics is another Clinton-controlled propaganda machine: They are IGNORING the new Rasmussen poll that has Trump at 43 and Hillary at 41. They actually haven't included a Rasmussen poll since July 27  word-find Rasmussen to see the results of their polls and you'll see why! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 03:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The public is getting smarter: In the 7 days from 9/30 to 10/6, the Wikipedia article about John Podesta got over 7,500 visits; then, from 10/7 to 10/13, it got over *74,000* visits--and it's not the mainstream media that was mentioning him! (Precise numbers: it went from 7,595 to 74,187) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 03:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Y'know how Trump says that our roads, bridges, and schools are like a 3rd World country? That may seem like an exaggeration, but waitlook at our MEDIA, which is DEFINITELY like a 3rd World country: The news media AND entertainment media are BOTH in the information-warfare "tank" for Hillary  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 02:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And schools are 3rd World-level not only in the physical buildings themselves (see Detroit in the video below, from January of this year, in the Washington Shitpost), but also in the curriculum of total indoctrination.  

https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/answer-sheet/wp/2016/01/20/how-appalling-are-conditions-in-detroit-public-schools-this-appalling/

March 2011: Hillary says "We are losing an information war" (but who's the "we" in that statement? I don't think it's "We the People"...)

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m1p-E2xmpjA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To recap: The media predicted that Trump will never: run for president, file his financial disclosure, do well in the polls or the debates, make it to the Iowa caucus, make it past Super Tuesday, reach 1237 delegates, be nominated at the Convention, and they STILL predict that he may just drop out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 02:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because they claim that he's "not serious." They've also tried to sink him with, what, at least 75 different media-created fake "scandals" that totally filled the airwaves, newspapers, and internet for 2-3 days each?

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Republican_Party_presidential_primaries,_2016

# KEEP THE FAITH AND *VOTE!!!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Record 15 MILLION Texans registered to vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Record 15 million Texans registered to vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Trends US traffic graph: Comparing the NYTimes, WashingtonPost, WSJ, and Reddit. This is why CTR's army of downvote-arrow-clicking nerd virgins are spend so much time here! (I added Twitter in a graph linked below) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 07:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consider how Hillary's largest Super PAC is called "Priorities USA" and then look at this: While Media Obsesses Over Fake Trump "Scandals," US Debt Soars To $19.7 Trillion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 07:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldman Warns "Much More Downside" To Come For Pound Sterling (8-point presentation) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 07:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldman Warns "Much More Downside" To Come For Pound Sterling (8-point presentation) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 07:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Campaign Warns Bill Clinton: "We're Going To Turn You Into Bill Cosby" - Bannon told Bloomberg Businessweek: "There's a whole generation of people who love the news but were 7 or 8 years old when this happened and have no earthly idea about the Clinton sex stuff" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 07:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FAILING: NYTimes.com U.S. traffic, from 2004-Present, as recorded by Google (As Trump said today, "The Times is fighting desperately for its relevance and its financial survival" - see below) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 06:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's foreign policy is the Reaganite stance of "PEACE THROUGH STRENGTH," while Hillary's is BERSERK OVERCOMPENSATION: She'd INSTANTLY wage full-scale war in Syria to prove she's a "tough" woman. Notice the MSM never talks about HER and "the nuclear button"! She is NOT the peace candidate! -- </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 05:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And after overthrowing Bashar al-Assad and leaving the 17 million people of Syria defenseless and at the mercy of ISIS, al-Nusra, and other terror gangs, she will try to "counterbalance" that massively destructive overseas aggression by inviting endless refugees into the U.S., which, OF COURSE, would also boost up the Democrat voter base. Yes, nothing but evil! That's why Trump called her the Devil right to her face! Think of the old proverb - to "tell the truth and shame the devil!" She SHOULD be ashamed of herself, as he repeatedly said! That's LONG overdue!

Just remember what former General Wesley Clark, who was also a Supreme Allied Commander of NATO, famously said about "7 countries in 5 years" - Iraq and Libya have now been destroyed, so there are still 5 others for "strongwoman" Hillary to "regime-change." (Here's the 2-minute video where he talks about it - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9RC1Mepk_Sw) It's so SICKENING to consider, and FURTHERMORE, it's practically guaranteed that Bill would be Secretary of State, to keep the whole Foundation of favors going and growing bigger and bigger, as every industry and geographic area of the U.S. is sold to the highest bidder, just like all those embassy positions! (In case anyone forgot about or MISSED the news about that whole now-public series of "auctions" - http://archive.is/diiuK) 

**We really need to vote for Trump in droves and droves and NOT take November 8th for granted!!!!**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ABC News and AP picking up material from the WikiLeaks' Podesta Emails: "Email: Clinton Campaign Tried to Move Back Illinois Primary" (The article doesn't mention the result: Hillary 50.5%, Bernie 48.7%. And even with all of the DNC's cheating, bribery, and corruption, she 'won' by only 1.8%!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 05:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Clinton media machine goes LOWER and LOWER: Here's today's propaganda round-up (10/13/2016). They can't defend her proposals OR her political record, so their ONLY hope is just endless ad-hominem lies and gossip about Trump. It's not working enough, so they keep making up new ones! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 04:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Clinton media machine goes LOWER and LOWER: Here's today's propaganda round-up (10/13/2016). They can't defend her proposals OR her political record, so their ONLY hope is just endless ad-hominem lies and gossip about Trump. It's not working enough, so they keep making up new ones! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 04:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look how much the MSM wishes that Trump will QUIT! NBC's Chuck Todd interviewed Rudy Giuliani right before the 2nd debate - First 3 Qs: "Might Donald Trump NOT SHOW UP to the debate? Are YOU the only person willing to defend him? Is there ANY chance he'll withdraw?" (Feel free to watch at 1.5 speed) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "This Is War" - Trump Drafting Lawsuit Against New York Times For Story He Groped And Kissed Women (Note the embedded tweet at the end: "Remember when NYT smeared McCain too and then got sued and had to retract?" - and indeed, the retraction is right there) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 16:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington Times: Top 10 Hillary Clinton scandals exposed by WikiLeaks (as of 10/12/2016) - SHARE THIS! WashTimes is practically the ONLY print newspaper NOT doing a blackout on all these revelations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 12:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AWESOME unscripted speech   audience: Don Trump Jr. at the Outdoor Sportsmen and Sportswomen Rally in Grand Junction, CO 10/5/2016 (Link skips to @5:25) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 02:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From way back in MARCH: Trump tells Hannity: "Wait till you see what I do when they set up a Third Party, 'cause I have a counter-move that'll blow them away. [...] I think you'd have a REVOLUTION if they pick some guy like a Kasich." (@6:30; listen to the end) [ignore the stupid image] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TRUMPing the "experts": Last November, Fortune magazine gave their predictions for who'd be in the General Election: Hillary Clinton   Tim Kaine vs. Marco Rubio   Nikki Haley. Consider that Trump won the FL primary by 18.8 points, and the SC primary by 10 points - </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 16:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When a tarot card becomes...THE TRUMP CARD. Time for us to outsmart the evil before us! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 13:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the only good pages on the entire Buzzfeed website: The survey results about the 2nd presidential debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 12:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great 1-minute vid: Donald Trump Jr. speaking in Brookfield, Wisconsin on 10/5/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 11:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Supporters vs. Protesters at PA Post Debate Rally 10/11/2016 (MANY reactions!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 10:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How cucked-up is the rest of Reddit? One user tried to share an article in /r/Trees (the marijuana subreddit) about Hillary's opposition to marijuana, and he got banned! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 03:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ACLU: Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter Provided Data Access for a Surveillance Product Marketed to Target Activists of Color </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 03:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter Provided Data Access for a Surveillance Product Marketed to Target Activists of Color </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 03:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ACLU: Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter Provided Data Access for a Surveillance Product Marketed to Target Activists of Color </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 03:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voters are getting more informed and educated EVERY DAY!  In the past 4 days, Wikipedia traffic to the articles about Bill Clinton, Juanita Broaddrick, Paula Jones, Kathleen Willey, and Monica Lewinsky each spiked way up: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 17:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the stuff that people really want--and NEED--to know about. I had also checked the traffic for other names, including Sidney Blumenthal, Warren Buffett, George Soros, Deborah Wasserman Schultz, and Jonathan Gruber (economist), but the increase was not nearly as significant. The 4 numbers next to each name here represent the traffic for each article over the past 4 days (10/7 - 10/10). If the numbers increase yet again or remain as high, I'll update this and post it again tomorrow! *(Uncheck "Logarithmic scale") -*

**Bill Clinton (22K- 49K- 71K- 202K)**

https://tools.wmflabs.org/pageviews/?project=en.wikipedia.org platform=all-access agent=user range=latest-20 pages=Bill_Clinton

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bill_Clinton

**Bill Clinton sexual misconduct allegations (8K- 88K- 131K- 174K)**

https://tools.wmflabs.org/pageviews/?project=en.wikipedia.org platform=all-access agent=user range=latest-20 pages=Bill_Clinton_sexual_misconduct_allegations

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bill_Clinton_sexual_misconduct_allegations

**Juanita Broaddrick (4K- 50K- 179K- 110K)**

https://tools.wmflabs.org/pageviews/?project=en.wikipedia.org platform=all-access agent=user range=latest-20 pages=Juanita_Broaddrick

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Juanita_Broaddrick

**Paula Jones (2K- 17K- 45K- 121K)**

https://tools.wmflabs.org/pageviews/?project=en.wikipedia.org platform=all-access agent=user range=latest-20 pages=Paula_Jones

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Paula_Jones

**Kathleen Willey (1K- 9K- 24K- 49K)**

https://tools.wmflabs.org/pageviews/?project=en.wikipedia.org platform=all-access agent=user range=latest-20 pages=Kathleen_Willey

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kathleen_Willey

**Monica Lewinsky (19K- 40K- 64K- 113K)**

https://tools.wmflabs.org/pageviews/?project=en.wikipedia.org platform=all-access agent=user range=latest-20 pages=Monica_Lewinsky

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Monica_Lewinsky

An article was created about **Kathy Shelton** yesterday, and contains many statements that don't link back to a source; hence, there are various disclaimers at the top of the page, since Wikipedia requires that every detail of an article be cited: 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kathy_Shelton

It has gotten 5 visits thus far:

https://tools.wmflabs.org/pageviews/?project=en.wikipedia.org platform=all-access agent=user range=latest-20 pages=Kathy_Shelton

You can see those graphs by going to any Wikipedia article and clicking "View history" at the top, and then "View page statistics."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honest Abe vs. Crooked Hillary (1st minute of this video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 16:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump rightly describes the illusion of Hillary's popularity: "The ONLY thing she's got going is the media. Without the media, she wouldn't have a chance." (@30:15; watch for 30 seconds) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 15:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guardian, in ad tech experiment, buys its own ad inventory, finds in some cases, it only gets 30% of the revenue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Schiff talks about the Access Hollywood video controversy and the 2nd debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guardian, in ad tech experiment, buys its own ad inventory, finds in some cases, it only gets 30% of the revenue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The news website The Guardian, in an advertising tech experiment, buys its own ad inventory and finds in some cases, it only gets 30% of the revenue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump 2nd Debate Thug Life - *10* different versions of his epic line  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TV2AUoY5JI8

2 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=en2IR6XxOt4 

3 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zUBqI8Ngt-g 

4 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7mv-7EVWF3Y

5 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X5wwGzPaox0

6 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HIab03wTq_A

7 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uezUBW2VUp4

8 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i5QdVcavXc0

9 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iYPdHVkxI0A

10 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qLOR792oojs

Share those w/ ur non-political friends too :):):):) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary on video, when she was a senator: "After I had just been investigated and all that, why would I wanna do EMAIL? Can you imagine?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nonstop Propaganda Machine: The Washington Post is currently publishing 5 anti-Trump articles every hour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 05:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Washington Post is currently publishing 5 anti-Trump articles every hour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 05:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Washington Post is currently publishing 5 anti-Trump articles EVERY HOUR - The people working there must be foaming at mouth with so much hatred, that their hate-foam is just DRIPPING onto their keyboards as they type </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 05:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hannity talks with Laura Ingraham, Monica Crowley, and Nigel Farage about the 2nd debate [9:27] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 04:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump 2nd Debate Thug Life - *10* different versions of his epic line  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 03:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TV2AUoY5JI8

2 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=en2IR6XxOt4 

3 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zUBqI8Ngt-g 

4 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7mv-7EVWF3Y

5 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X5wwGzPaox0

6 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HIab03wTq_A

7 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uezUBW2VUp4

8 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i5QdVcavXc0

9 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iYPdHVkxI0A

10 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qLOR792oojs

Share those w/ ur non-political friends too :):):):) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Hillary can't even enforce a no-fly zone on her face, how does she plan to enforce one in Syria? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 02:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BASED Wall Street Journal put Trump's legendary comeback right on the front page! (Comedian pro-tip: Spontaneous zingers work better than pre-scripted ones! You just have to be nimble and natural...unlike Hillary ;) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 02:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over 600 newspaper front pages on the 2nd Presidential Debate (Arranged in alphabetical order by state) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 02:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millennials Uncucked: 15 excellent reactions to the 2nd debate from the "Whisper" app </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 02:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another "news" outlet has totally given up: Forbes.com just hit a new low, descending further into trash-blog territory: "Donald Trump's Sniffling Continues, Here Now Are The Possible Causes" - Cause #5: "Trump may be pregnant" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 13:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While the MSM continues to think that Trump supporters will be influenced by a bunch of disloyal congressmen, consider that the only particular influencers are TV   radio hosts like Limbaugh, Hannity, Ingraham, Savage, and Pragerand of course, Trump and the "Independent" Bill O'Reilly are friends! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 13:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The explanation for why silver and gold prices both plummeted last week, and why they'll climb back up this week: China's markets were closed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 13:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The explanation for why silver and gold prices both plummeted last week, and why they'll climb back up this week: China's markets were closed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 13:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cubs Confront the Curse: Is This the Year? - Anxiety and excitement are in the air in Chicago with the Cubs still seeking their first World Series title since 1908. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 13:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Pennington] The Cubs Confront the Curse: Is This the Year? - Anxiety and excitement are in the air in Chicago with the Cubs still seeking their first World Series title since 1908. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 12:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cubs Confront the Curse: Is This the Year? - Anxiety and excitement are in the air in Chicago with the Cubs still seeking their first World Series title since 1908. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 12:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political argument pro-tip: When someone insults you for liking Trump (IRL or online), just ask "You voting for Hillary?" There are 3 usual responses: "I hate both of them," "I don't vote," or silence, because they know that defending Hillary as a responsible, honest, competent leader is impossible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 12:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started doing this recently, now that I'm telling acquaintances or meet I meet that I support him (since I like to talk about politics). The funny thing is that the people I've told it to in-person have actually then said "Yeah, I know [one or more people they work with, or work for, or are related to] who like him, too." 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Corruption of Kashrut: Israel in food fight over kosher licensing - Some restaurateurs are saying the religious authorities are exerting too much power over business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 12:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's a fairly obvious fact, but just keep it in mind as you watch the past 2 debates: Whenever Hillary gets ANGRY, she forces herself to smile a big toothy grin. Anyway, you'd THINK that she'd do something about the hideous yellowness and coffee stains that they have. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 10:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Stone's post-debate analysis - He had said early yesterday that he heard from a Clinton campaign source that Hillary wasn't going to shake Trump's hand, and now he's saying that this week, the next coordinated media onslaught will be a new fake sex scandal [@3:41:09; watch to 4:12:00] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 09:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How raw does this man fight? - Washington Post top story: Trump wanted to put Bill Clintons accusers in his family box. Debate officials said no. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 09:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bipartisan Cuckery: Former Obama Attorney General Eric Holder and former GWBush press secretary Ari Fleischer are both outraged by Trump's "You'd be in jail" statement (They are the only 2 people quoted as condemning it here) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 08:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Make America Great Again: Build the wall  Bring back jobs  Renegotiate trade deals  Obliterate ISIS  Strengthen our military  Repeal and replace Obamacare  Protect the 2nd Amendment  End Common Core  Incarcerate Hillary Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 08:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> # WIN WIN WIN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BEST copy of the 2nd debate (Excellent pic   audio quality and the most split-screen!) [Link skips to 33:00] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 06:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2ND DEBATE POLLS - VOTE NOW!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 05:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2ND DEBATE POLLS - VOTE NOW!!!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 05:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Stone says that he was told that Hillary will refuse to shake Trump's hand and will start off right away with ad-hominem garbage [@1:48:40] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 01:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Stone tweeted on May 3, 2016: "Mark my words- Juanita Broadderick's name ID will be higher than @HillaryClinton's by November #Trump2016" (Let's hope tonight is when that happens!! Tens of millions of people watching NEED TO KNOW!!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 01:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump starts the day nice n' early with 8 tweets showing that he's ready for battle against that demonic entity he'll be facing later tonight at 9PM Eastern, 6PM Pacific! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 16:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Failing NYTimes trots out the first accuser of what they call the "Groper in Chief" (I know I'm not the only person who thinks they are being very foolhardy in resorting to this. And see how the article desperately zigzags into all sorts of off-topic slander, just like Hillarys debate answers!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 13:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The element of timing: I believe that the Establishment was holding on to the Billy Bush video until a few days before the debate, but ALSO could have stirred up this same media-hyped "backlash" if he had recently made ANY of the 30 or so spoken statements that caused a "FiReStOrM oF CoNtROVeRSy!!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 12:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, all the things he has said that the media has WRENCHED out of context and then created a tornado of fake outrage and hysteria over, by sending the deliberate misinterpration through the media echo chamber for the public to mindlessly swallow--or at least the media hopes the public will...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Signs Bill Guaranteeing New Rights For Rape Victims (When Hillary boasts about this at the debate, Trump needs to immediately point out her gross hypocrisy) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 11:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were even THINKING of not voting on November 8th, just consider this comment I just saw on Facebook: "I can't wait till Madame President appoints Obama to the Supreme Court!" Trump supporters better start showing up at the polling places at 6:00AM like they do for his rallies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 11:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skip work that day and get carpool everyone pro-Trump that you possibly can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Stone talks about Hillary's history of bullying Bill's victims (first 9 mins of this video) - Hopefully Trump will be saying some of these things in the debate as soon as Hillary starts with her insinuations and prepared soundbites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 07:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USEFUL piece of history: Arnold Schwarzenegger, who just pathetically refused to endorse Trump, was accused of sexual harassment by 6 women in a scandal called "Gropergate," right before the 2003 CA recall election, and then he won in a 17-point landslide (and that was in CA!)  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 06:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **See here:**

**https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arnold_Schwarzenegger#Allegations_of_sexual_misconduct**

2003 election results: **Percentage     48.6%**     31.5%     13.4%

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/California_gubernatorial_recall_election

2006 election results: **Percentage     55.9%**     38.9%

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/California_gubernatorial_election,_2006

As for all the politicians retracting their endorsements, who the hell bases their vote on what their senator or congressman says? Sorry, the American people are not that stupid. And as Trump has revealed to the public over and over again, **typical politicians are completely OWNED by the lobbyists, donors, and special interests** who they depend on to fund their re-election campaigns and their lavish lifestyles. This is just a list of typical run-of-the-mill politicians who don't want to lose that funding; this isn't about principle. As Trump said in one speech earlier this year, a politician can't even go to the bathroom without first asking their lobbyists. 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Donald_Trump_presidential_campaign_endorsements,_2016#Retracted_endorsements

**As for the Clinton campaign, we'll see what they have to say about these FAR more criminal allegations, which Trump has only HINTED at, as he is a COUNTER-PUNCHER, and now he's been brought to have this fight about who personally treats women better:**

**https://i.redd.it/o58rmxvfeknx.jpg**

**https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/564x/00/43/1b/00431b41a4d84473f58393d19f466fc3.jpg**

**https://twitter.com/atensnut/status/684822324227379200?lang=en**

# THE MEDIA AND THE ESTABLISHMENT ARE COLLABORATING AND CONSPIRING ONCE AGAIN TO END TRUMP. WE THE PEOPLE, NOT POLITICIANS, WILL STAND RIGHT BY HIM ALL THE WAY TO ELECTION DAY!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another great Trump coin (Just posted!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 04:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some cuck who works for TechCrunch tries to compare Trump and Anthony Weiner - Read the subsequent exchange that causes him to give up AND admit that he doesn't even like Hillary! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 03:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump vs. Hillary - We are seeing the media try make what you see on his side seem as bad, or even WORSE, than what you see on her side. Trump needs to go all in with each of these at tomorrow's debate! Time to educate the public! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 02:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tomorrow night, when Hillary says how "horrified" she was by the "lewd" remarks, Trump should say: "Bill Clinton is a rapist, and Hillary is his enabler. Just so you understand. There are MANY women who've been victimized by them, and you'll be hearing the stories over the next two weeks." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 02:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Washington Post screengrab says it all. The entire news-media industry depends on Donald Trump now. What did they even write about before he ran for President? And he's such a job-creator that hundreds of journalists have been earning a living by following him and writing about him every day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 02:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Compilation of the 6 people who went on TV to say "Bill Clinton is a rapist" in the past week (posted Oct. 7, 2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 02:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REQUEST: Can anyone here take this Wikipedia list of endorsements for Bernie and then the list for Hillary, and compile a new list of all the people who endorsed him but NOT her? (I want to assume that SOME of them are supporting Trump, but also to see who actually has INTEGRITY)  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 15:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering who DIDN'T sell their soul to the devil, so to speak. Is there an easy to combine the lists and then separate who's only on the Bernie list vs. who's on BOTH? The only method I know would be to spend a few hours copying and pasting the names all into a color-coded list (a different color for who endorsed which of the two) and then alphabetizing them to see who's who. I'm sure there's a more efficient way to do it, though.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Bernie_Sanders_presidential_campaign_endorsements,_2016

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Hillary_Clinton_presidential_campaign_endorsements,_2016



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While 2 Utah politicians and John Huntsman (who quit the 2012 primary BEFORE the Iowa caucus) have withdrawn their support, here's a list of the people who HAVEN'T. Maybe some lobbyist puppetmasters will force others to do the same, but so far, those are the only 3 of the 800+ listed here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 14:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DEVASTATING Wikileaks Document Drop: Hillary says "My dream is a hemispheric common market, with open trade and open borders" [x-post from /r/The_Donald, where many more leaks are being highlighted] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 14:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reality Check: Here are the 10 highest voted comments on the most watched YOUTUBE upload of Trump's video statement about the Washington Post video: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 12:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Nancy Jewell** 5 hours ago

after seeing this low down trick of the never trump crowd  makes me want to vote for Trump even more !!!! every real man talks like that about women  even women talk trash  about men we are human hillary and her rapist husband have done far more disturbing things need i say benghazi?

# 364 THUMBS UP

**Ace** 5 hours ago 

He's absolutely right! Hell, the leaked audio is just locker room banter or everyday guys talk, it's no big deal!

# 342 THUMBS UP   

**Sheyandaar** 5 hours ago

Like I said in another video - He talked shit with a buddy a decade ago like a typical man has... I'm sure I've said some shameful stuff in private with the guys before.  Anyway, Hillary is the one grabbing cunts in this race. 

He apologized and admitted he's said some wrong things. Hillary just places blame on everyone else.

# 283 THUMBS UP   

**Cassandra Myth** 5 hours ago

Such a double standard in the media and country- Hillary is an enabler and protector of predators. Bill acted- Trump was talking locker room talk casually-

# 259 THUMBS UP  
 
**The Imp Lannister** 5 hours ago 

this is NOTHING in comparaison to the wikileaks that just have been released about the Clinton`s Campaign .

# 104 THUMBS UP   
 
**Mr.Sauceman** X 4 hours ago

THE LEAKED AUDIO WAS NOTHING, ITS A CONVERSATION THAT ALL MEN HAVE, YET IDIOTS THINK HE'S SEXIST BECAUSE OF IT. BLACKS FOR TRUMP!!!! WATCH MY GREAT VIDEOS TO GET TRUMP ELECTED. EVERY VIEW COUNTS.

47 THUMBS UP   

**Maggie May** 2 hours ago

What you said 11 years ago wasn't pretty but let's be real...I couldn't count the number of guys in my lifetime that I've heard utter similar, or much worse, comments. And frankly women do it about men, too. Admit it ladies. Hillary is trying to inflame the people who don't realize what's important for the country and distract us from her downright illegal and immoral actions of the past 40 years. A bit of locker room type braggadocio is meaningless in the grand scheme of things. I'm way more concerned about just how Hill and Bill made $40 million last year!!!!

43 THUMBS UP    

**Richard B** 2 hours ago

Trump we are still with you ever man talks like this around his friends and co workers.  Its nothing compared to what Hilliary and Bill has done.

28 THUMBS UP  

**Jess J** 2 hours ago

We still LOVE you MrTrump... please keep fighting got America. We need YOU!

25 THUMBS UP   

**Jerald Smith** 2 hours ago

He is a chess master. He released his own tax records so he could expose a tax loophole signed into law by Bill Clinton for his rich buddies. Now, he releases a tape of his "locker room banter" so he can expose Bill and Hillary Clinton about Bills rapes. Check and Mate!!

18 THUMBS UP   

See here! - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=47B8LsVOzAU

http://www.theonion.com/article/will-be-end-trumps-campaign-says-increasingly-nerv-52002 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Team Trump Canceling Ads in FL, OH, NCand REDIRECTING ad funds to OTHER states where there's a wider gap! So disregard the stupid "Uh oh" and and read what Trump's own people are quoted as saying. Acc. to RealCuckPolitics, he's ahead by 1.6 in OH, within 2.4 in FL, and 2.6 in NC. (See below!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 07:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inevitable Washington Post headline: "Russian hackers tricked Bill Clinton into raping at least 20 women in the 1980s  Sources speculate about the forms of time-traveling technology they used" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 04:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The rationale behind Correct The Record, Media Matters, /r/Politics, and the 24/7 Hillary-shilling in the mainstream media can be found in this Crooked Hillary statement from March 2011: "We are in an information war, and WE ARE LOSING THAT WAR!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 01:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who exactly is David Brock, the founder of Media Matters and manager of several SuperPACs? See this handy visual timeline, and this Reddit post that calls him "Lord of the Shills" (from /r/media_criticism)  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 01:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.sli.mg/0F6XER.jpg

https://np.reddit.com/r/media_criticism/comments/4p1hcp/david_brock_lord_of_the_shills/

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/David_Brock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From the first debate: Hillary blinks 36 times in 35 seconds as she listens to Trump make what was probably his hard-hitting condemnation of her abysmal record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 14:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yeah, this is how I'd picture the wife of the Most Powerful Man on the Planet... (Feel free to email and share this, free of comment, with everyone you know. Many girls may question their sexuality as a result) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 04:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snapchat retweeted one user's Rosh Hashanah greeting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 15:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the Democrats don't get their way in the national election, Hillary could always just run for President of this high school's PTA! (I am assuming these are local people and not just campaign workers who were brought in.) [Real pic from a rally earlier today, 10/5/2016] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 08:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting bit of history: Roger Stone: "I would just remind some folks that it was Paul Manafort who strongly urged the selection of Mike Pence and who arranged for Trump to meet Pence." (@19:07; listen for 2 minutes) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 08:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uncucked Millennials: 30 excellent reactions to the VP debate from the "Whisper" app </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 00:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rare Pence - Broad-Shouldered Leadership Edition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 09:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rare Pence lookin' suave in front of the Capitol (yes, that's his autograph) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 09:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VP DEBATE POLLS - VOTE NOW!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 06:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FULL: Mike Pence vs Tim Kaine VP Debate (Good audio and picture quality) [starts at 54:50; pictures appears after a minute) (Pro-Tip: Switch speed to 1.25 to watch faster ;) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 05:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
