<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6196</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh, gotcha.

I've seen people claiming that the CNN analyst was doing the walk-backing, so I wanted to make sure that was clear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're also misrepresenting the entire thing. The CNN analyst was speculating and explained they were speculating, and everyone took it as fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If they cared about teen births and sexually transmitted diseases, birth control would be freely available and abstenance-only sex education would be to stuff of dystopian science fiction.

It's truly nuts. There's *literally a magic pill* that reduces:

* The number of abortions
* The number of pregnant teens
* The number of children on welfare 

The GOP should be falling over themselves to provide this to as many people as possible. It's the best investment they could possibly make to further their conservative goals, yet they oppose it.

Bonkers. Pants-on-head bonkers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bay of Pigs is about 1000x worse because in addition to all the unnecessary deaths and chaos and political capitol wasted, we lost 4 American bombers and two supply ships, several of which were friendly fire due to confusing camouflage. 

It's insane how much of an all-around failure the Bay of Pigs was. 

**EDIT**: forgot to mention the two CIA agents captured and executed in Cuba as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those wondering, this was when Bin Laden was killed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh, I thought it was "House Finance Committee."

Too many damn acronyms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump fans, and even boatloads of hardcore conservative celebrities, are all spinning this against Paul Ryan. Wow.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 tinfoil; would use to reheat leftover pizza in the oven.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get fucked Cheeto Benito </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but it does give them the PR excuse of: "Look, he already testified! Why are they bringing him back? This is all a Democrat dog-and-pony show." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That's the only option that offers an explanation for Nunes pulling those weird incriminating stunts this week

Unless the news he learned is that Flynn has decided to flip on everyone. So he panics and goes screaming to the others to let them know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that they're rushing forward a mere hour after Manafort makes me think it's the latter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is why, less than an hour later, suddenly Roger Stone and Carter Page are running forward to testify too:

https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/61arwr/roger_stone_carter_page_volunteer_to_talk_to/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If so, he's got Carter Page and Roger Stone rushing forward to try to get a better deal before Manafort does.

https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/61arwr/roger_stone_carter_page_volunteer_to_talk_to/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might be because Manafort, Stone, and Page have all suddenly agreed to come forward and speak:

https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/61arwr/roger_stone_carter_page_volunteer_to_talk_to/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now Roger Stone and Carter Page rush forward to testify too:

https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/61arwr/roger_stone_carter_page_volunteer_to_talk_to/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Stone, Carter Page volunteer to talk to House committee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Masse - Hotel California [Folk Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finished Ready Player One. Was disappointed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **SPOILERS BELOW**. 

I really hate criticizing fellow authors, but I just don't have much good to say about this book. There are a lot of fun 1980s reference, but beyond that the book has very little going for it. I struggled to finish, and only did so out of an obligation of completeness. 

The plot is bland and predictable: an unexpected boy is the one to find the first "key" to The OASIS puzzle. The characters are one-dimensional and have no real development. The protagonist eases his way through the book without any real strife, succeeding in a never-ending series of deus-ex-machina style skills:

* "To get the first key you had to beat the Skeleton King at the game Joust. Fortunately, I'm the best in the world at it and win on the first try!"
* "To complete the first gate I had to reenact the entire War Games movie. Fortunately, I've watched it a billion times and know all the lines by heart!"
* "To get the one-up coin I had to play a perfect game of Pac-Man, something only 5 people have ever done in history! Even though I'm rusty at my Pac-Man skills, I become the 6th person after just a few hours."
* "To get the second key I had to beat the game Zork. Fortunately, I know the game by heart!"
* "To pass through the second gate I had to reenact the movie Blade Runner. Fortunately, I know the movie by heart!"

It's that sort of thing, repeated over and over. There's never any struggle, strife, or hardship, beyond the first ten pages of the book where the protagonist's living quarters are described (which stops being an issue a few pages later when he's suddenly famous and rich). 

Plot issues aside, the writing disappointed me. It's extremely "telly" (as opposed to showy). The pacing is strange and frustrating: Cline will spend pages and pages describing something unimportant, like the posters on the wall of their chat room. Then, when we reach an important part of the story (such as reaching the Dungeon where the first key resides) he'll skip past all of the action with a single "I completed the dungeon and reached the final room," type sentence. It's maddening. 

Overall, the simplicity of the story and the quality of the writing make this book feel like a Middle Grade book masquerading as adult fiction. I think it will do much better as a movie (which is due out in 2018), but as for the book, you can get the same experience merely by reading a list of 1980s movies and videogames from wikipedia. 

I don't know what I expected with this book, but it's certainly not what I got.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Texans Deal With Snow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those looking for science fiction stories: there's a great pay-whatever-you-want bundle available from Immerse or Die. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Armistice' literally means 'to remove one's arms' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 05:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why was Brian Daubach released by the Florida Marlins in 1998? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 1998, 26 year old 1B/OF prospect Brian Daubach slashed .316/.421/.634 at AAA Charlotte with 35 HR and 124 RBI. He was called up to the Marlins for just 10 games in September, before being released that off-season.

He had a few pretty good seasons in Boston before petering out, but he looked like an elite prospect in 1998. So what gives? Why did the Marlins release him?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite trivia question of all time: in the 1979 draft, the Kansas City Royals drafted two future Hall of Famers. Who were they? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Crichton, Westworld, and his motivations behind writing Jurassic Park (from a speech I saw him give in 2003) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw [this thread](http://i.imgur.com/RanqxE1.jpg) about how Westworld is just a reboot of Jurassic Park, and it made me realize that not everyone has probably heard Crichton's comments on the work. Here's what I can most accurately remember from seeing Crichton speak on it back when he was alive.

Back in the early 2000s, when he was close to releasing *State of Fear*, Michael Crichton came to my high school in Virginia. He was promoting his book, and gave a big speech in our auditorium about the present lackings of scientific peer review and stuff like that (for those that don't know, sadly, *State of Fear* is essentially a climate change denial book). 

Afterwards, he did Q/A. One of the questions was about Jurassic Park. "Were you always a big amateur paleontologist?" someone asked. "Was that your motivation for writing Jurassic Park?" 

He laughed and said that no, it wasn't. He told a story about how back in the 1980s he got together with an old college friend who was in town for drinks. After catching up with him, when they were several drinks in, the friend started talking about his movie debut, Westworld. How it was a great film, etc etc. "I told him I considered it my masterpiece," Crichton said. He explained that it crushed him to see it get such terrible reviews from critics that didn't 'get it' (even though it later got a sequel). He lamented that it was way ahead of its time. 

So the friend jokes, "You should rewrite it, but replace the robots with something people can appreciate. Like dinosaurs." Crichton spread his arms to us, the auditorium full of kids, and said, "I started writing the book the next day." 

I don't know if what he said was true, or if he came up with a funny embellishment to cover up the fact that he essentially rewrote one of his previous works and changed the protagonists (from hosts to dinosaurs), but that's what he told my high school back in ~2003. 

Has anyone heard the same from an interview at some point? I would imagine it's something he's said more than once, but I can't find anything on the internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stadium Golf at the Ballpark in Arlington. Fun way to spend my dad's birthday! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 14:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Line from Episode 7 Nobody Is Talking About </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sylvester is laughing incredulously at Maeve's desire to leave the park. He says something along the lines of:

 "Everything about you--**even your skin!**--is designed to keep you here."

What did he mean by that? What about the hosts' skin is designed to keep them in the park? 

I feel like this was a very specific technical reference to something we the audience doesn't know yet. What could it be?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I Think Episode 8 Will Start </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 14:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theresa smiling, addressing the Board of Directors (in person or via video conference), telling them that Ford is fine and they don't need to worry about him. That she has everything under control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adrian Gonzalez Refuses to stay in Trump Tower in Chicago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 21:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Golf noob here. Etiquette question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DISCLAIMER: I'm a golf noob: just started playing this summer.

So I was out playing yesterday, me and another guy. We play the first hole, and are putting on the green when a foursome comes riding up the golf cart path behind us. I'm wondering what the hell they're doing, and they go right past us and straight to Hole #2. They skipped the first hole entirely.

We then spent the entire day stuck behind these guys. They were *really* slow players, taking a lot of mulligans and farting around on the green. And skipping us didn't affect much: there was another group ahead of them, which they were constantly bumping up against too.

It wasn't a big deal because it was a gorgeous day yesterday, and I shrugged it off and enjoyed my game, but it did make me wonder. Is there a reason they skipped us on the first hole? Is that a thing that happens sometimes? Were they dicks for doing that as a foursome?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J-Walking: The Fantasy Baseball Experiment is Over :-( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll spare you the drama and get right to the sad point: [we lost.](http://i.imgur.com/lRRwlTo.png) And not by much! 

My opponent had *five Red Sox on his team*: Ortiz, Betts, Hanley, JBJ, and Sandy Leon. For the beginning of the week, they destroyed me. I was immediately down in all hitting categories.

But my pitchers played [like Greek heroes](http://i.imgur.com/JqAbJWZ.png). A 2.77 ERA from a roster that was going for quantity, not quality? Well okay then. By Thursday I had all the pitching categories locked up except Saves, so I ended up benching my starters. Slowly, I began catching up in the hitting categories. Going into Saturday, I was leading 7-5! 

So what killed me? A few things.

* On the final day, my team batted .241, causing me to lose AVG. Swell.
* We were tied in SB going into Sunday, so I [benched Justin Turner for Jason Kipnis](http://i.imgur.com/s7wrbZ0.png). See that Run Turner scored on Sunday? That would have broken the tie in that category and single-handedly won me the week.
* Jeanmar Gomez blew two saves and lost the closer's role. If he makes either of those saves, I win. 
* After consistently getting me 1-2 steals per week, Jean Segura didn't get any this week. He also batted .182, and only got me 1 Run and 1 RBI. Way to suck at the worst time, buddy. 

The heartbreaking part? I owned the tiebreaker against my opponent (regular season H2H record), so if we finished tied 6-6 then I would have still won. Any of those things go my way and we're having a different conversation right now. 

Ahh, well. So it goes.

It was a *really* fun year. This kind of team forces a lot of creativity, and kept me interested in the fantasy season much longer than I otherwise would have been. 

Hopefully you guys enjoyed the updates. I'll probably do something similar next year, so look for me come Spring. 

#AWW YEAH SHAMELESS PROMOTION TIME

And hey: if any of you are looking for a good book to read, I happen to be a [science-fiction and fantasy writer.](http://www.davidkristoph.com/) My sci-fi series [TALES OF A DYING STAR](https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B01AWNJHQ2) has won some awards, and if you like Choose Your Own Adventure style books then be sure to check out [ULTIMATE ENDING.](https://www.amazon.com/gp/bookseries/B01EJRZ1E4)

Thanks for cheering on the J-Walkers this year! Feel free to point out in the comments how I totally blew my chance and should have made X move instead of Y.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flags at my local course (Iron Horse) yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 13:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J-Walking, A Fantasy Baseball Experiment: SPECIAL PLAYOFF EDITION - ROUND ONE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 21:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've come a long way since I drafted a team entirely made up of guys with names beginning in J. That seemed like so long ago. A more lighthearted time, filled with laughter and joy. Things weren't so serious back then. Because make no mistake: things are serious now. This isn't a game. 

We've reached the fantasy baseball playoffs. The cream has risen to the top, my friends. And the J-Walkers are [*creamy as fuck*](http://i.imgur.com/xE4QCcY.png).

I missed out on the Regular Season Championship by half a game, but that's okay. I still get a bye week to sit on my hands and think about how best to not screw things up.

I'd like to take a moment and savor the team stats over the course of the season because, gosh darnit, the J-Walkers deserve it.

[**HITTING**](http://i.imgur.com/UhaaCPG.png)

* R: 801 (2nd)
* HR: 237 (2nd)
* RBI: 796 (2nd)
* SB: 87 (6th)
* TB: 2,602 (1st)
* AVG: .286 (1st)

[**PITCHING**](http://i.imgur.com/vT8fg3L.png)

* W: 82 (4th)
* SV: 97 (2nd)
* K: 1,228 (4th) 
* ERA: 3.86 (6th)
* WHIP: 1.26 (6th) 
* QS: 114 (3rd)

Look at those offensive stats. *Look at them*.  It's just so goddamn beautiful. 

Alright. [Here's what the team looks like](http://i.imgur.com/2eMjlSv.png) going into the playoffs next week. A few notes:

* Yeah, Josh Donaldson is injured. Yeah, it sucks. Yeah, it's keeping me up at night right now.
* Quantity over Quality is the name of the pitching game. I'm hoping to take W, K, and QS by sheer numbers, and then win most of the offensive stats. As such, I'll probably be streaming some really shitty pitchers: Jon Gray, Jimmy Nelson, Jose Urena, Jake Peavy. I've got 5 transactions I can make per week, and you bet your ass I'm gunna make them. It's gunna get ugly, but you know what? War ain't supposed to be pretty.
* With that in mind, I'm *considering* punting on Saves and dropping my two closers in favor of more SPs. All of my future playoff opponents have 3 or 4 closers, so it's not a stat I'm likely to win. What do you guys think? 
* I'm lucky that I have very few aces on my team, because it means nobody will have their starts cancelled in order to set a favorable playoff schedule. Jon Lester's the only one I'm concerned with at all, and that won't come into play for another two weeks. 

This is it, folks. Who should I be keeping an eye on for the playoffs? Who's super hot right now? How can we pull this off?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J-Walking, a Fantasy Baseball Experiment: Week 20 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 14:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Background [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/fantasybaseball/comments/4c3fl3/jwalking_a_fantasy_baseball_experiment/), [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/fantasybaseball/comments/4ehu0d/jwalking_a_fantasy_baseball_experiment_week_1/), [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/fantasybaseball/comments/4hwu39/jwalking_a_fantasy_baseball_experiment_week_3/), [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/fantasybaseball/comments/4qaxxh/jwalking_a_fantasy_baseball_experiment_week/), and [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/fantasybaseball/comments/4vrwl9/jwalking_a_fantasy_baseball_experiment_week_16/). 

We're getting down to the last few weeks of the season. It's crunch time. Last week I had a critical head-to-head matchup against the #2 team in the league, over whom I had a 1.5 game lead. The good news? I whooped him 9-3. (Woo!) The bad news? The other guy tied with him for 2nd place won his matchup 11-1, so he [passed me for 1st place](http://i.imgur.com/s99ThuA.png). (Boo!)

But hey, I'm still up there. Sticking to the front of the standings like a squirrel holding onto the back of a velociraptor. 

Last week was the trade deadline for the league. Desperate for pitching, I targeted three players for acquisition: Jose Fernandez, Jake Arrieta, and Jacob deGrom. I have a surplus of offensive players, so I made trade offers to each of the owners. Usually a mix of Joey Votto, Jose Abreu, Jean Segura, Jay Bruce, and Jake Lamb. 

The result? The three owners never respond to my offers, even when I direct-messaged them. All three are active owners, and all three had offensive needs. I never even got so much as a trade decline. Just silence. I can only assume that my fantasy team is the super hot cheerleader of the league, who would love to be invited out by a nice, shy guy to go see *You've Got Mail* (the Joey Votto of romantic comedies) and maybe get to second base with, but they're too intimidated by her good looks to ask. 

Oh well. Looks like this is the J-Walkers team we're going to have to ride into the playoffs (except for adds/drops):

[**Hitting**](http://i.imgur.com/4U2gnuW.png)

[**Pitching**](http://i.imgur.com/zXmKTWf.png)

My strategy is to hopefully blow teams away on offensive categories, and win the pitching categories by sheer numbers alone (W, K, and QS). Hence all the pitchers. 

**THE GOOD**

* JD Martinez finally came back from the DL and hit the ground running: hitting .441, with 6 HR and 55 TB in just 68 AB. Boy do I need that down the stretch.
* The two tiny SS that I acquired just to survive until Kang got off the DL? Jean Segura and Jose Ramirez? *They're both leading the team in TB over the last month*. A combined 41 R, 9 HR, 27 RBI, 21 SB over that stretch. 
* My pitching is holding its own. Lester, Taillon, Verlander, Odorizzi, and Hellickson all have ERAs in the 2.XX range over the past month, and have a combined 15 wins and 22 QS over that stretch. 

**THE BAD**

* Jay Bruce has sucked since moving to New York. Lots of dingers, and not much else. 
* Jon Gray. Yikes. 
* Jake Barrett has decided to suck: 10 runs over his last 7.1 innings. I swear to Jesus/Allah/FSM/Tom Cruise, if he loses the closer's role in Arizona I'm going to buy a table just so I can flip it.

**THE UGLY**

* Jim Johnson is losing his closer spot to Vizcaino, so I'm back down to two closers (one of whom is the above-mentioned Barrett). Here's hoping Jeffress earns the closer's spot in Texas. 
* Jake Lamb is a bad baseball player. I should drop him, but I'm holding on out of sheer stubbornness. 
* In non-fantasy news: I moved to Texas two months ago. Since coming here, I've been to 8 Rangers games. They've lost every one. What the shit? 

Another notable move: I picked up Josh Bell last week, even though he was still sitting in AAA. He was called up a few days later. Hooray for me!

**COMING UP**: in the final three weeks of the regular season I play the #7, #12, and #8 players in the league. So I have a favorable schedule. Six teams make the playoffs, so the #1 and #2 seeds get a buy in the first round. That would be super terrific.

What'd I miss? Are there any awesome J-name September call-ups I should grab now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Gift of the Rizzo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 13:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J-Walking, A Fantasy Baseball Experiment: Week 16 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 13:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Background info here**](https://www.reddit.com/r/fantasybaseball/comments/4c3fl3/jwalking_a_fantasy_baseball_experiment/)

I was out of town last week (at RAGBRAI), so I set my lineup and left it, even though I was playing the first place team in our league. The result? [Whooped him 9-1](http://i.imgur.com/ArekHo2.png), which propels me into 2nd place and only 0.5 games back of 1st. 

The J-Walkers are alive and well, friends.

It's been a busy trade deadline for the team. Jonathan Lucroy, Jay Bruce, Josh Reddick, and Jeremy Jeffress were all traded to new teams. Hopefully playing on contenders will up their value! 

[Here](http://i.imgur.com/OaPjqAY.png) are the other moves I've made. Lots of adding/dropping of potential closers, like Joakim Soria, Jim Johnson, and Jake Barrett. How's the team done aside from that?

**THE GOOD**

* Joey titty-fucking Votto. Hitting a Williamsesque .406 over the past month. Trading Familia for him is looking like a good move for me right now.
* Justin Turner. Leading my team in HR, RBI, and TB over the past 30 days.
* My pitching staff was great in July. James Paxton with an ERA of  3.55. Justin Verlander at 1.77. Jameson Taillon at 3.00. 

**THE BAD**

* Jake Lamb is taking his ASG snub poorly, hitting .229 over the past 30 days. I guess the ride couldn't last forever.
* What happened to Jon Lester? 7.36 ERA over the past month. Oof.
* JD Martinez is still out, but he's beginning a rehab assignment today. I could use that power back in my lineup.

**THE UGLY**

* Julio Urias. Wasted a lot of transactions just for a few of his crappy spot starts. Meh.
* RIP Jake McGee, who sucked as a closer, occupied a DL slot for a month, and then came back and lost his closer's role.
* Jung Ho Kang is another guy. I drafted him early and held him in a DL slot *all season long* because I knew he'd be a big part of my team, and then he goes and rapes someone. What a dick. (We can all agree I'm the real victim here, right?) All jokes aside, I dropped him when the news broke earlier this month, and he's done terrible since then. Good move for me. Eat a buffet of dicks, Kang. 

What'd I miss? Any good fall call-ups with J-names getting ready to hit the show?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J-Walking, A Fantasy Baseball Experiment: Week What-The-Hell-How-Is-This-Still-A-Thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 20:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Previous posts [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/fantasybaseball/comments/4c3fl3/jwalking_a_fantasy_baseball_experiment/), [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/fantasybaseball/comments/4hwu39/jwalking_a_fantasy_baseball_experiment_week_3/), and [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/fantasybaseball/comments/4murfn/jwalking_a_fantasy_baseball_experiment_week_9/).

It's not funny anymore. It's not a game anymore. Shit has gotten real, much in the same way that World War One marked when wars stopped being a gentlemanly sport for monarchs and started to be an *oh god why is his face melting off like that you didn't tell me chemical warfare was the stuff of nightmares* kind of real. 

I'm still doing well, and it's terrifying.

The J-Walkers are [holding strong in 2nd place](http://i.imgur.com/6r7LQzZ.png). Over the past 5 weeks I've gone 7-4, 6-5, 9-3, 9-2, and 9-2. I keep waiting for the wheels to fall off, and somehow, with duct tape and determination and guys like Jake Lamb, they're refusing to. 

**Current team (2016 stats): [Hitting](http://i.imgur.com/ZX8bOrd.png) - [Pitching](http://i.imgur.com/ic930On.png)**

**The Good**

* Joey Votto. That guy I traded Jeurys Familia for? He's finally kicking ass, hitting .312 with 6 HR (and 5 SB!) over the past month. 
* Josh Donaldson is no longer sucking bags of maple flavored shit. Batting .347 over the last month with the second most TB on the team.
* The most TB on the team over that span? Jay Bruce. 9 HR, 29 RBI over the past month. Get it, dude. 
* Jon Lester has a 1.46 ERA in his last 5 starts. So, I've got that going for me. Unlike...

**The Bad**

* ...the rest of the pitching staff. [Look at these assholes over the past 30 days](http://i.imgur.com/GmqqSus.png). *Look at them*. It's a parade of mediocrity, with Julio Urias carrying the baton like he earned the damn thing.
* Jake McGee is on the DL, limiting me to two closers. And he might not even keep the closer role when he returns. Positional J-scarcity sucks. I tried acquiring Jonathan Papelbon (who is also on the DL) but the owner wasn't biting. 
* Remember when Jackie Bradley Jr was good at the baseball? Pepperidge Farm remembers. 
* Josh Reddick and JD Martinez have been on the DL, forcing me to use Jose Ramirez in an OF slot. Thankfully, Reddick returns from the DL today. 

**The Ugly**

* Farewell Jimmy Nelson and your 4.93 FIP. 
* I dropped Jeremy Hellickson. Since then he's pitched two quality starts. Whelp.

I've tried to acquire Jose Bautista, but the owner is AFK in the league. Also made runs at Jose Fernandez and Jake Arrieta, but the prices are (justifiably) too high. 

My strategy from here on out is balls-to-the-wall offense. I've accepted my shitty pitching staff. If I can win 5-6 of the Hitting categories, and snipe one or two accumulation Pitching stats (like K or SV) then I think I can stand a chance for the remainder of the season.

Alright. Anything I'm missing? Are there any J-diamonds in the rough I should be snagging while I can? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers Everything) How Jon will discover... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 12:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...his true parentage.

There are a lot of ways Jon could find out about his parentage. The most common theories:

* Howland Reed (last living survivor from Tower of Joy)
* Rhaegar's Harp on Lyanna's crypt
* Someone else tells him (Littlefinger?)
* Bran Weirwood.net discovery, then tells Jon

So, this last episode made it clear he's going down into the crypts to bury Rickon. At first, I assumed this meant Littlefinger would find a way to tell him, or he finds the harp. 

However, something occurred to me: **what if Jon has his own crypt hidden down there?**

They find a previously unexplored area, or a rarely used section. Jon finds a crypt with a headless statue, since the stonemasons would need to wait until later to do the face. Or hell, maybe it's a small baby statue hidden behind Lyanna's crypt. Anyways, they'll find *something*. Jon's confused, until he reads the words carved into the base:

"Jon, first of his name, trueborn son of Rhaegar Targaryen and Lyanna Stark."

This would neatly resolve several questions:

1. Who are Jon's parents?
2. Did Rhaegar and Lyanna marry prior to his birth?
3. And the most important part: how can the characters discover, *beyond a reasonable doubt*, the above two?

A crypt that Ned Stark had carved does all three. It would remove all doubt, unlike any of the other methods Jon could discover his parentage. Littlefinger can even be there to fill in some extra details. "Your *uncle*, Ned Stark, had this made. He intended to show you when you were old enough." Shit, Davos can even give some Stannis perspective. "Stannis was shocked the Kingsguard weren't at Dragonstone..."

The entire thing makes far more sense than a vague harp on a crypt, or Jon finding out second-hand from someone else, and the scene would mirror one of the first scenes of the show: Ned and Robert going to the crypts to pay respects to Lyanna. 

**TL;DR**: Jon has a crypt beneath Winterfell that specifically names his parents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York style pizza? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 21:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I are moving to downtown Ft Worth later this month. First thing to find on our list: a place with good New York style pizza.

Google maps hasn't been much help. Anyone have any recommendations? Pichi Pachi seems to be the closest pizza place within walking distance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York style pizza in Ft Worth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 19:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I are moving to downtown Ft Worth later this month. First thing to find on our list: a place with good New York style pizza. 

Google maps hasn't been much help. Anyone have any recommendations? Pichi Pachi seems to be the closest pizza place within walking distance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J-Walking, A Fantasy Baseball Experiment: Week 9 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 21:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**BACKGROUND HERE**](https://www.reddit.com/r/fantasybaseball/comments/4c3fl3/jwalking_a_fantasy_baseball_experiment/)

It's been a while since I gave an update, so you're probably wondering how my J-name master race team is doing. Well wonder no more! In the past 6 weeks, I've had 2 *awful* weeks, 2 average weeks, and 2 great weeks, and am still holding strong in 2nd place. The guy in 1st is just crushing it right now, so I'm happy to be holding on. [Here's what the standings look like.](http://i.imgur.com/L1AGdr5.png)

So what do the J-Walkers look like right now? 

* [**HITTING**](http://i.imgur.com/Qq6MY0E.png)
* [**PITCHING**](http://i.imgur.com/aOK6nGK.png)

**The Good**

* Jackie Fucking Bradley Jr. I picked him up just before his streak, and boy did that pay off. He's leading the entire team in TB, despite missing about a week for the birth of his daughter. Me gusta.
* Jung Ho Kang came off the DL and has wasted no time kicking ass. Just in time for Jean Segura's inevitable decline, too. 
* Jonathan Lucroy is hitting .417 in the last 30 days. What the shit? I don't even care if his BABIP says it's not sustainable. His .316/.372/.539 slash for the year gives me a big 'ol fantasy erection.

**The Bad**

* What the fuck is wrong with Josh Donaldson? Hitting .216 over the last month, dead-last in TB over that stretch and with the second fewest RBI. Get your shit together.
* Same goes for you, Jose Abreu. I'm not paying you to hit fewer homeruns than Kang in 3x as many at-bats. 
* Oh, and I bought low on Joey Votto about a month ago, trading Jeurys Familia for the slugger while his value was at his lowest. It hasn't worked out so far, but he's finally showing signs of turning it around over the past week. 

**The Ugly** (players dropped in the past month)

* Julio Urias. Ugh. Even his name sounds like urine.
* Jesse Hahn
* Junior Guerra
* Jose Berrios

Going forward, I've got a really solid team. I'm holding strong in the standings despite hugely disappointing seasons from three of my biggest sluggers (Abreu/Votto/Donaldson), so as soon as they get back to normal I'm going to be locked and loaded. 

J the force be with you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey /r/books! We're Danny McAleese and David Kristoph, authors of the Ultimate Ending series, doing an [Author Spotlight] on the intricacies, difficulties, and processes involved in creating a Choose Your Own Adventure style book. Ask us anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 16:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ultimate Ending](http://www.ultimateendingbooks.com/) books are like Choose Your Own Adventure (CYOA) books, but on steroids! They feature:

* Exciting plots
* Rich, detailed stories
* Clever riddles
* Challenging puzzles
* Satisfying endings
* And of course, in each book, one **ULTIMATE ENDING!** 

Creating a CYOA-style book is a much different experience than a normal novel. The planning, writing, editing, and even normally straightforward steps like hiring cover artists and interior illustrators become incredibly complex. There's a lot to juggle! We'd love to share with you the processes and hurdles we've discovered along the way. 

So far we've released seven books, with two more on the way:

1. Treasures of the Forgotten City
2. The House on Hollow Hill
3. The Ship at the Edge of Time
4. Enigma at the Greensboro Zoo
5. The Secret of the Aurora Hotel
6. The Strange Physics of the Heidelberg Laboratory
7. The Tower of Never There
8. Sabotage in the Sundered Sky (JUNE 2016)
9. Rescue from the Valley of Chaos (AUGUST 2016) 

We'll be doing the spotlight from 11:00am to 6:00pm today. Feel free to ask us anything! Our individual accounts are:

**DANNY MCALEESE:** /u/shakakka99

**DAVID KRISTOPH:** /u/subject6196

Verification here: [Twitter](https://twitter.com/UltimateEnding/status/728957699115880448) / [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/397859980382923/posts/434483216720599)

**EDIT**: Thanks guys, but we're done for now! If you have any questions feel free to contact us at Dan@ultimateendingbooks.com or David@ultimateendingbooks.com. Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Manfred's comments on Mexico City, I decided to run the data on flight times from each franchise's city. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 20:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the biggest complaints I've seen mentioned about a Mexico City expansion team is the horrendous travel required. So for funsies I did the math. Here's the flight time from each city to Mexico City, compared with flight time to Seattle (in parenthesis). I've bolded all cities where a flight to Mexico City is faster, or equal to, a flight to Seattle. 

* **Houston: 2:10 (4:40)**
* **Dallas: 2:30 (4:00)**
* Phoenix: 3:00 (2:50)
* **Miami: 3:25 (6:40)**
* **Tampa: 3:25 (6:20)**
* San Diego: 3:30 (2:45)
* Los Angeles: 3:35 (2:30)
* Denver: 3:35 (2:40)
* **Atlanta: 3:35 (5:10)**
* **Kansas City: 3:40 (3:40)**
* **St Louis: 3:45 (4:10)**
* San Francisco: 4:15 (1:55)
* **Chicago: 4:15 (4:20)**
* **Detroit: 4:40 (4:45)**
* **Toronto: 4:40 (5:15)**
* **New York: 4:45 (6:00)**
* **Philadelphia: 4:45 (5:50)**
* **Baltimore: 4:55 (5:35)**
* **Washington, DC: 4:55 (5:35)**
* **Boston: 6:10 (6:05)**

(I excluded Minneapolis, Cleveland, Pittsburgh, Cincinnati, and Milwaukee because they didn't have direct flight info. But comparing to other nearby cities, they should all be equal or better flight times to Mexico City than Seattle). 

Conclusion: if you're in the NL West then your trip to Mexico City is worse than Seattle, but for *literally every other team in the country* it's an equal or easier flight. North/south traveling is much easier than east/west. 

Carry on.

**DISCLAIMER**: I'm not saying a Mexico City expansion team is a great idea. Merely commenting on the travel times involved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J-Walking, a Fantasy Baseball Experiment: Week 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 23:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two weeks ago I [created a post](https://www.reddit.com/r/fantasybaseball/comments/4c3fl3/jwalking_a_fantasy_baseball_experiment/) about drafting a team comprised entirely of players whose named begin with the letter 'J'. A lot of people expressed interest in getting some regular updates throughout the season, so I figured I'd fill you guys in on how things are going. 

Well, it was a fun gimmick while it lasted. Obviously, fielding a team entirely of J-named players isn't something that can have long term success in a--

.

.

.

JUST KIDDING MOTHERFUCKERS

THERE'S NO STOPPING THE [FIRST PLACE J-TRAIN.](http://imgur.com/tZ7AxAY)

CHOO CHOO

.

.

.

Whew. Okay. Calm down.

So now that's out of my system, what do the J-Walkers look like now? 

[**HITTING**](http://imgur.com/1ilkNWs)

First round pick Josh Donaldson is obviously carrying the team in R/HR/RBI, but beyond that much of my success is due to Jean Segura. Yeah, *that guy*, the one I drafted solely because he was one of my few J-name options at shortstop, who I only hoped could keep the spot warm until Kang got off the DL. The glory will surely fade, but for now I'll smugly smile and pretend it was all part of the plan.

Beyond that, I really need JD Martinez and Jose Abreu to start producing. These were my 2nd and 3rd round picks, and I'm lucky to be leading the league with their sub-par performances. 

[**PITCHING**](http://imgur.com/r4evL8C)

Right now, I'm running four closers. Mostly because I need the depth in case there are any injuries or demotions. And also because the promotions of Jeanmar Gomez and Jeremy Jeffress were gifts bestowed upon me by the baseball gods. These guys are killin' it. If I had known they'd be closers I wouldn't have reached for Familia. 

Starter-wise, I'm getting by. Zimmerman, Lester, and Ross are a fantastic core group. Odorizzi is great. Beyond that though... lots of question marks. I hope Berrios can improve (his last start looked promising). Verlander, Nelson, and Happ... I'm expecting them to regress (or continue doing poorly, in Verlander's case). So I'll ride them a bit longer and see how it goes. Since half the pitching stats are counting stats favoring lots of starters (W, K, QS) I want to be rolling as many guys out there as possible. 

[**TRANSACTIONS**](http://imgur.com/VzremXa)

Ahh, look at all those J-names coming and going. Joey Rickard was solid for a while, until deciding to suck. Jake Lamb's been a great pick-up. I expected big things from Schoop this season, so it was tough to part with him, but with Kipnis already manning 2B he was redundant. 

Things are rocking. Things are rolling.

So that's where we're at. What'd I miss? What J-sleepers are out there I should take a chance at? 

We've reach the point where this is no longer a game, guys. I can't just laugh this off anymore when I end up at the bottom of the standings. Shit's serious, now. *I need to win this*. 

**UPDATE**: just traded Jeurys Familia for Joey Votto. That'll help bolster my offense a bunch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J-Walking, a Fantasy Baseball Experiment: Week 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 21:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two weeks ago I [created a post](https://www.reddit.com/r/fantasybaseball/comments/4c3fl3/jwalking_a_fantasy_baseball_experiment/) about drafting a team comprised entirely of players whose named begin with the letter 'J'. A lot of people expressed interest in getting some regular updates throughout the season, so I figured I'd write up a post. Mods, let me know if this isn't allowed. 

So. Where do The J-Walkers stand after the first week of the season?

[In 2nd goddamn place.](http://imgur.com/hZ2JmU6)

At 8-4, The J-Walkers [did better than I expected](http://imgur.com/T3j9O1n). They won 4 of the 6 batting categories (all but SB and AVG), and 4 of the 6 pitching categories (all but ERA and WHIP). But they did pretty darn good in ERA and WHIP, going 3.16 and 1.09, respectively. The offense also batted .316, but my opponent averaged .335. Ahh, well.

An ERA of 3.16, and a batting average of .316. Yeah. You know who else had a J-name? Jesus. 

Some notes:

* Josh Donaldson is looking like a great first-round pick, anchoring the offense with 4 HR, 8 R, and 9 RBI.
* Jean Segura was the hero this week. A late-draft pick solely because of his J-power, who I was hoping could squeak by until Jung Ho Kang returns, Segura batted .407 with 3 dingers, 5 RBI, and 2 SB. **He led the entire team with 24 touched bases.** Goddamn.
* Jay Bruce was another late-draft surprise, hitting a pair of HR and knocking in 9 RBI.
* On the pitching side, the rotation was anchored by great performances from Jon Lester, Jake Odorizzi, Joe Ross, and Jimmy Nelson. Joe Kelly is the only Starting Pitcher in my rotation that shit the bed, currently holding a 21.00 ERA and a 3.33 WHIP.
* My 3-headed closing trio of Jeurys Familia, Jeremy Jeffress, and Jake McGee combined for 6 saves and an ERA of 1.50. 
* I'm [leading all teams](http://imgur.com/MlURlv8) in R, HR, RBI, TB, and QS, and I'm 2nd in AVG and SV. Glorious J-name Master Race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Oliver's "Last Week Tonight" is giving away 6 front-row Yankees tickets to the fans who dress the most ridiculous. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 18:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hamburger Helper released a mixed tape. And it's amazing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 22:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J-Walking: A Fantasy Baseball Experiment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 00:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually just play one fantasy baseball league, but this year I decided to play in a second for funsies. 12 teams, H2H. We had the draft on Friday. Here's how the first few rounds went:

**Round One**: I had the 5th pick, so I took Josh Donaldson. Nothing fancy.

**Round Two**: 20th pick. I felt good about grabbing Jose Abreu here, as the 1B depth drops off pretty quickly.

**Round Three**: I think the Tigers are going to be a big offensive team in 2016, so I snagged JD Martinez. 

At this point I was sitting there, admiring my dinger-hitting lineup, when I noticed something on the Yahoo Draft board. 

* C: 
* 1B: J Abreu
* 2B: 
* 3B: J Donaldson
* SS: 
* OF: J Martinez
* OF: 
* OF: 
* UTIL: 
* UTIL: 

Wait. What?

J. J. J.

That's funny. All the guys on my team have names starting with J.

For a moment, I considered laughing it off. Just a funny coincidence. But... what if?

There were three more players before my next pick. I frantically searched the remaining players with J names. Justin Upton. Jason Kipnis. You know what pitchers have J names? *All the best pitchers have J names*. Arrieta, deGrom, Fernandez. There was a lot of talent there. It could work. It could totally fucking work.

I started to sweat. My pick was coming up. Jason Kipnis was at the top of the J-list, and he was one of the few viable J second basemen (the next was Jonathan Schoop, averaging pick 275), so I nabbed him.

That raised the question of positional J-scarcity. Who did I need to target to make this work? The biggest problem immediately became apparent: Catcher. Catchers have really shitty names (Buster? Seriously?), and only one within the Top 20 had a J-name: [Jonathan Lucroy](http://imgur.com/qgX8mSI). At this point in the draft, Posey and Schwarber had both been drafted, so Jonathan Lucroy was sitting there at the top of the available catcher list. His Average Draft Position was in the 100s, but shit, I needed to grab him soon. The whole thing would fall apart without him.

My computer dinged. It was my pick in the 5th round. This marked the point of no return.

I grabbed Jonathan Lucroy with pick #53, about 60 picks ahead of where he was averaging. Someone made a surprised comment in the chat. If only they knew. 

I sorted the list of players by name and began filling up my roster. Jon Lester? Easy pick. Jeurys Familia? Get the fuck in here. I started thinking of J-related puns for a team name. It was happening.

[Behold, the J-Walkers.](http://imgur.com/a/ERtQW) SS is my weakest position (Jean Segura was the first J-name, way down around pick 200) but aside from that it's a surprisingly solid team. 

We'll see how the season goes. A few key injuries will destroy the team's viability, but hey, fuck it. If there's any interest in seeing the progress of the experiment throughout the season, I'll post it. 

Glorious J-name Master Race. 

(PS: if anyone has a good J-pun for a team name, I'd love to hear it. "J The Force Be With You" was too long for Yahoo.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When will players move to the DL in Yahoo Leagues? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Science Fiction] Siege of Praetar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 18:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Siege of Praetar

###by David Kristoph

Paperback **|** Science Fiction **|** 169 pages **|** December 2014 **|** $9.99

##Blurb

The red giant Saria is dying. 

Praetar, a sand-blown planet, lies occupied. Its people are buried and beaten, forced to toil for the Melisao Empire that prepares to flee their star. Hyken, a Sentinel pilot in orbit around the planet, is faced with a moral dilemma that forces him to choose between his co-pilot and their mission. Mira, a factory worker on Praetar, struggles to make a better life for her daughters--using what little resources at her command. A slumlord named Bruno makes his own arrangements, gathering what meager power he can in the Empire's scramble to flee. 

Caught up in the exodus, these people struggle to survive. Are they strangers, or do their decisions affect one-another in unexpected ways? 


##A note from the author

This was my debut novel, published in December 2014. The novel won Honorable Mention in the Writers of the Future Context, and has been reviewed by [Publisher's Weekly](http://www.publishersweekly.com/978-1-5031-2808-8):

 "Kristoph skillfully connects three independent perspectives to demonstrate how an individual choice, whether self-serving or for the greater good, can create a ripple of consequences in unexpected ways." **-Publisher's Weekly**

##Review copies

Print copies: 5 available - PM for details

[DOWNLOAD MOBI HERE](https://www.dropbox.com/s/1hqct5fan71nckk/Tales%20of%20a%20Dying%20Star_Book%20I.mobi?dl=0)

##Review links

Please post reviews to the following sites:

[Amazon](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00QXQR7UG/)

[Goodreads](http://www.goodreads.com/book/show/24171340-siege-of-praetar) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The internet is turning against Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 12:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wife and I are moving. How safe is this area of Ft Worth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 22:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wife and I are moving to DFW, and looking at certain areas. The [Race Street Lofts](http://www.racestreetlofts.com/) caught our eye, but we're skeptical about the area. Rent is cheap, and close to several food places and the river. Seems too good to be true. 

I've checked http://www.crimemapping.com/ but it doesn't seem any better/worse than other parts of DFW. Does anyone have anything to add about the area? 

The address is: 2901 Race Street.

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The current Jonas blizzard looks like the Nazi/Soviet battle lines from the Eastern Front of WW2. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 13:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The current Jonas blizzard looks like the Nazi/Soviet battle lines from the Eastern Front of WW2. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 12:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The current Jonas snowstorm line looks like the Nazi/Soviet battle lines from the Eastern Front of WW2. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 12:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to buy tickets to UFC 197. Confused about pricing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 15:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to be in Vegas while UFC 197 is occurring, so I'm looking to buy tickets. I signed up for the premium club, which allowed me to buy tickets yesterday. When registering, it says tickets will be as low as $200. 

However, when I go to buy the tickets, the cheapest ones (up in the worst seats) are $454.

General sale happens tomorrow at noon. My question: should I go ahead and buy these tickets for $454, or should I wait until tomorrow? Will the price go down? Should I wait until closer to the event to buy tickets secondhand? I've never purchased UFC tickets before, so I'm not aware of how the general ticket price trends are.

Thanks for the help!

**UPDATE**: after refreshing the page every hour, a bunch of cheaper tickets suddenly became available. Bought 'em for $300 after tax. Thanks guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2013 report shows that the average life expectancy of an NFL player is 20 years lower than the US male average of 76. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 15:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the average life expectancy for an NFL player is roughly 20 years lower than the US national average. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 15:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iowa governor wants Ted Cruz defeated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 20:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At a charity auction. Here's a snarky Pete Rose signed baseball for $400 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 03:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chad Halbach, Teresa's older brother (not shown in the documentary) was convinced of 2nd Degree Sexual Assault of a Child in 2003. He was released on probation: September, 2005. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 13:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something people aren't getting about Mike Halbach. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 12:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed a lot of people making comments like: "Why is Teresa's brother making statements every single day? He sure likes to hear himself talk! Seems suspicious."

Typically with a high-profile case like this, the family will make a deal with the media. They'll say, "We are making X the representative for the family, and he will give 10 minutes of interviews every single day. In exchange, the media will not bother the rest of the family, will not attempt to talk to them or ask them any questions about the trial."

This is why nobody else in the Halbach family is interviewed at all, why he was constantly being shown, and why the media was calm with him. Compare this to the Dassey family, where the media was chasing Barb out of the courtroom to question/film her.

This is pretty normal for a case like this. Now, you can theorize about the *content* of what he said, but him speaking to the media shouldn't be considered suspicious. 

**DISCLAIMER**: I am in no way defending Mike Halbach or making comments regarding the innocence/guilt of Steve Avery, just providing some clarification as to why Mike was constantly speaking to the media.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone here read American Gods, by Neil Gaiman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 01:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 100% convinced that Mr. Fischoeder from Bob's Burgers was modeled after "Wednesday" from *American Gods*. Same appearance (white suit, one eye), same eccentric way of speaking (referring to people as "M'boy"). 

I tried searching around on the internet but I can't find any info. Has anyone else gotten this impression?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writing about a real business entity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hypothetical scenario that I've always been hazy on.

Let's say I wanted to write a fiction novel about a character's interaction with the NFL (National Football League). The league itself, and their dealings, is the major plot of the book. It probably would not paint the NFL in a positive light.

Would I legally be allowed to write this? Could the NFL sue me? Or would I need to create some fake entity like the National Football Association (NFA) and have them as a stand-in instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Page 5 from The Martian. Oh man, nobody tell him! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 22:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lance Armstrong would have been an awesome name for a medieval jouster. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 13:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Racist airplane banner over Richmond, Virginia during the World Cycling Championships has spelling error (OC) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 20:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Puppygate and the drama surrounding the Hugo Awards this year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 14:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers All) A new theory on LSH. Stay with me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 14:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Stannis has his throat cut by Brienne
* Brothers without Banners appear and resurrect him
* Stannis wanders the north, looking for Boltons to kill out of grief for his dead child
* LSH = LORD STANNISHEART, CONFIRMED

We've got 10 months. A man can dream.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers All) Guys, I think we're missing some clues from this past episode... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shireen reading Dance of Dragons last episode isn't just a neat little reference thrown in for fun. I think it's hinting at what will come. The part about Swann attempting to sneak up/capture the dragon is obviously a reference to Quentyn; since he's cut from the show this will probably happen to Jorah or Daario. 

But I'd like to focus on the second part of her reading, the part she explains to her father Stannis. 

 Shireen: "It's about a Targaryan civil war, when Rhaenyra and Aegon II fought over the throne."

This sounds strangely similar to a book plot: the Dornish plot to crown Myrcella over her brother Tommen in AFFC. This has been cut in the show, however... or has it?

The show has merged plotlines whenever possible. I still believe Doran Martell has something up his sleeve; so far we haven't found out what it is, other than that he's simply sending Myrcella back to King's Landing. There has to be more. I believe the show is merging two plots from AFFC/ADWD:

* Doran's Fire and Blood plan (sending Quentyn to marry Dany)
* Arianna's plan to crown Myrcella as Queen

Doran Martell is going to declare Myrcella as Queen and send her back to King's Landing (or, alternatively, Trysane will do it once they arrive). 

I refuse to believe show!Doran has no secret plan; it's crucial to his character, crucial to the entire Dorne storyline. Crowning Myrcella combines these two plotlines reasonably well, and explains all of Doran's motivations up to this point. We've seen that Myrcella is completely taken with her fiancee; it's plausible that she would go along with this, especially if they convinced her Tommen could be removed peacefully.

**TLDR; Doran is the grass, and Myrcella is the snake.**

**BONUS TINFOIL TIME**: Doran's insistence on sending Trystane back to King's Landing with Myrcella is more than it seems. From the Dance of the Dragons wiki:

 [The war] saw the deaths of both rival monarchs, and the crowning of  Aegon III.

What if show!Trystane is actually Aegon/fAegon? It would explain Doran's insistence on showing peace, so he could set Aegon up. It would insert what is an otherwise important (we think) book character back into the show. It would add a level of depth to Oberyn's death: he died getting revenge for one murder which never actually occurred.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else win Honorable Mention in the Writers of the Future Award? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 13:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found out yesterday that the first book in my series won Honorable Mention at the 2015 Q1 Writers of the Future award. I'm not sure how excited I should be about it. Has this ever happened to anyone before?

Apologies if this sounds like a shitty stealth-brag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confession: I really like the Blue Jays. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 13:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last year I had Jose Bautista and Edwin Encarnacion on my fantasy baseball team, so whenever the Sox weren't playing I would turn on the Jays. Now I really like the Jays, and especially Joey Bats and EE. 

Guys, am I broken? How do I fix this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possible fatty acid detected on Mars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 19:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Looking to HIRE someone to draw a sketch of a spaceship, for inclusion in my book. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 18:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, my name is David Kristoph, a sci-fi/fantasy author. 

For my next [sci-fi book](http://www.amazon.com/s/ref=series_rw_dp_labf?_encoding=UTF8 field-collection=Tales%20of%20a%20Dying%20Star url=search-alias%3Ddigital-text) I'm looking for someone to draw/sketch a spaceship, to be included halfway through the book.

I don't want/need it to be too fancy; I'm looking for [something in this style](http://www.igorstshirts.com/blog/FirePunch.jpg). Sort of a rough sketch, blueprint look. All black and white. I will give you details of the ship once I've selected someone to work with.

You would be hired for this one job, with the possibility of more work in future books. You will also be credited in the front of the book. $20 for the work, paid upon completion. Let me know if you're interested, hopefully with some examples of your work.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Hiring] Need someone to design a spaceship for my next book. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 14:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is David Kristoph and I'm an author. 

For my next [sci-fi book](http://www.amazon.com/s/ref=series_rw_dp_labf?_encoding=UTF8 field-collection=Tales%20of%20a%20Dying%20Star url=search-alias%3Ddigital-text) I'm looking for someone to draw/sketch a spaceship, to be included halfway through the book.

I don't want/need it to be too fancy; I'm looking for [something in this style](http://www.igorstshirts.com/blog/FirePunch.jpg). Sort of a rough sketch, blueprint look. 

You would be hired for this one job, with the possibility of more work in future books. Pay is negotiable. If this isn't the right subreddit for this please let me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book cover being painted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 11:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Timelapse of the cover of my book being designed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 11:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two months ago I shared a timelapse video of my book cover being designed. Here's another for a different book! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 11:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Kindle] "The Ancillary", book 2 of the Tales of a Dying Star series, now available! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 14:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PROMO] "The Ancillary", book 2 of the Tales of a Dying Star series, now available! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 14:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to see how a book cover is made? My designer made a timelapse video of the process. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 15:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Timelapse] Video of my book cover being painted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 19:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Timelapse of my book cover being painted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 19:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Looking to hire someone to illustrate a map of a spacestation for my next book. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 11:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Novel] Siege of Praetar (science fiction) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 16:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for Beta Readers for my next book. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 21:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for beta readers for the sequel to [Siege of Praetar](http://www.amazon.com/Siege-Praetar-Tales-Dying-Star-ebook/dp/B00QXQR7UG/). It's a pretty simply process: I send you a pre-released copy of the book, and you tell me:

* What you liked
* What you didn't like
* What confused you

Once you receive the book I'd need a response with the above info within 2 weeks.

As a thank-you, I'll also be mailing beta readers a personalized copy of the book once it's printed. 

Shoot me an email at David.Kristoph@gmail.com if you're interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Kindle] Siege of Praetar (Tales of a Dying Star: Book I) is free this weekend! Gritty, character-driven sci-fi series. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 19:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Promo] Siege of Praetar is FREE today. Looking for some honest Amazon reviews. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 12:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Siege of Praetar is free to download today! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 12:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Novel] Siege of Praetar (Science Fiction) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 21:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL only two players have ever had a season with more HR than singles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 16:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Barry Bonds (in 2001)
* Mark McGwire (in 1995, 1998, 1999, and 2001)

(minimum 15 HR) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Promo] Tales of a Dying Star: Siege of Praetar is now available for pre-order! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 00:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Promo] Tales of a Dying Star: Siege of Praetar is now available for pre-order! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 23:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asking for Amazon Reviews at the end of your book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 16:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone on here mentioned that they put a page at the end of their story, requesting Amazon reviews from people if they enjoyed the book. What do you guys think about that? And how would you phrase that on the back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PROMO] One person who retweets this will receive an autographed/personalized copy of Tales of a Dying Star Book I, released on Dec 25! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 13:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need some Beta readers for my novella. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 20:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says it all: I've finished the second draft on my novella, and am looking for Beta readers. It's 30,000 words, and I would hope to get your feedback within a week or so.

Anyone interested? I'd be happy to return the favor in the future, too.

**EDIT**: thanks the replies, looks like I've got enough now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any of you use BookTweeters for advertising/promotion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 20:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://booktweeters.com/

Not sure if they're legit or shady. I don't have high expectations, but am wondering if anyone else has any first-hand experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Hiring] Looking for someone to design the cover of a Sci-Fi eBook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 17:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm almost done writing a sci-fi novella, and I'm looking for someone to design a sweet eBook cover. This is a one-time request, but there are several more novellas to follow, so there may be an opportunity to do several more.
The story is about a civilization leaving their star system (because the star is dying), so the cover would need to spacey. Something like two ships in orbit over a planet, one firing missiles at another. Obviously more details will come later, but wanted to give a general idea here in the OP.
Price negotiable, but keep in mind it's a first-time eBook. If you have a portfolio that's a huge plus, or any other way to confirm that you're legitimate.

PM me or reply in the thread if you're interested.

**EDIT**: I'm looking for something like [this](http://fc01.deviantart.net/fs45/f/2009/153/9/a/07_EG1___Spaceship_by_ehaft.jpg) style. The grittier, the better.

**UPDATE:** I've chosen someone for the job. Thanks to everyone to PM'd me! There's tons of great talent here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Hiring] Looking for someone to design the cover of my Sci-Fi eBook. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 17:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm almost done writing a sci-fi novella, and I'm looking for someone to design a sweet eBook cover. This is a one-time request, but there are several more novellas to follow, so there may be an opportunity to do several more.

The story is about a civilization leaving their star system (because the star is dying), so the cover would need to spacey. Something like two ships in orbit over a planet, one firing missiles at another. Obviously more details will come later, but wanted to give a general idea here in the OP.

Price negotiable, but keep in mind it's a first-time eBook. If you have a portfolio that's a huge plus, or any other way to confirm that you're legitimate. 

**EDIT**: I'm looking for something like [this](http://fc01.deviantart.net/fs45/f/2009/153/9/a/07_EG1___Spaceship_by_ehaft.jpg) style. The grittier, the better.

**UPDATE:** I've chosen someone for the job. Thanks to everyone to PM'd me! There's tons of great talent here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd settled on the perfect name for my current WIP, but it's almost identical to something that already exists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 21:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My title: "Tales of a Dying Star", sci-fi short-stories about a civilization leaving their solar system.

Existing title: ["Tales of the Dying Earth"](http://www.amazon.com/Tales-Dying-Earth-Jack-Vance/dp/0312874561), came out decades ago.

Friendly reminder to you guys to do a google search before settling on a title. I'm only 25% done with my WIP, so it's not a huge deal, but it feels bad, man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone heard of the Aeon Award contest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 15:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.albedo1.com/aeon-award/

It's a writing contest for short-stories, but they have a registration fee, so I'm wondering how legitimate it is. Has anyone heard of it? 

I mean, their submission email addresses are yahoo and hotmail. That doesn't inspire confidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [3200] The Sentinel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 15:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here you go](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Hs7IAApum8f71nROlBI25VA5idO7Ak6adFLeFE-adRE/edit?usp=sharing). Gimme dat brutal feedback. What I'm looking for:

* General flow: is the writing crisp? Are there any specific sentences where you fumbled in reading it (if that makes sense)?
* Are there any parts that didn't make sense, or need more clarity?
* Did it keep your interest the whole way through? Were there any parts that bored you?
* Any other general impressions.

I've disabled comments because the last submission I made I asked for no line edits, and got nothing but line edits anyways. My editor will be doing line-edits later this week, so really I'm just looking for general feedback. Thanks guys!

*Puts on Kevlar vest and helmet* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a list of writing contests/submission requests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 03:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A while ago someone posted a comprehensive list of all writing publications that were accepting submissions. For the life of me I can't find it. Does anyone know what I'm talking about, or know of a list for such a thing?

Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Feedback] The Sentinel (3320 words) Sci-Fi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 22:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Title**: The Sentinel

**Genre**: Sci-Fi

**Word Count**: 3320

**Type of Feedback**:

* General flow. Is the writing crisp, does it flow well to the reader's eye?
* Are there any parts that confused or tripped you up?
* Are there parts that could use more information, either because it's interesting or because it needs clarity?
* Did it *interest* you all the way through?
* Any other general impressions

Thanks guys! 

https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Hs7IAApum8f71nROlBI25VA5idO7Ak6adFLeFE-adRE/edit?usp=sharing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Critique] The Sentinel (3320 words) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 19:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I've got a short sci-fi story here that I'd like some feedback on. It's supposed to stand on its own, and I'll be submitting it to a magazine. The kind of feedback I'm hoping to get:

* General flow. Is the writing crisp, does it flow well to the reader's eye?
* Are there any parts that confused or tripped you up?
* Are there parts that could use more information, either because it's interesting or because it needs clarity?
* Did it *interest* you all the way through?
* Any other general impressions

I'm *not* looking for line edits. Let me know what you guys think. Thank you!

https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Hs7IAApum8f71nROlBI25VA5idO7Ak6adFLeFE-adRE/edit?usp=sharing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Okay writers, let's talk about money. What works of yours have been published (type, length, method of publishing), and how much money have you made from them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 20:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We see statistics all the time about how much certain ranges of authors make for their work, but let's get some specific examples. What have you had published, and how much have you made from it to date?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Fantasy Baseball Miracle has occurred. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 13:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to bed last night a loser. My opponent and I were tied 7-7 in the semifinals, and he controlled the tiebreaker (head-to-head record). Every player was done, it was over.

But then I woke up this morning and saw the score:

http://imgur.com/O3BvGM5

What's this? How could this have happened? And then I saw the "stat correction" page:

http://imgur.com/lkavpah

Carlos Santana was awarded a SB in the game on September 18. This broke the tie in the SB category and gave me an 8-7 lead.

It's a fantasy baseball miracle. I'm playing in the Championship this week!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My team on base 19 times today. No runs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 00:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I needed one run to tie the category, and 2 to take it. I'm losing 8-7 right now, and it's all up to Trout, Beltre, and Pence. 

PLEASE. PLEASE BASEBALL GODS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Feedback] First chapter for this character (~7000 words). Fantasy genre. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 21:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it any good? Should I keep going? It's unedited, so I'm just looking for general feedback on flow/exposition/dialogue

[Link here](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1g4h-MYcgOWy-MEatBvavym29rP1P5GfYR2tOZapMK7k/edit?usp=sharing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [7128] The Fisherman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 21:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI I created a new account for this subreddit so people could more easily look at my critique history.

I've already submitted a portion of this to /r/writing, and want some more "honest" feedback, whether good or bad. It's a fantasy series, the first chapter for this character but the fourth in the book. First draft, no real editing yet. What I'm looking for:

* Does the story 'hook' you? Do you want to learn more about this world?
* Does the writing flow/read well? 
* Are the characters interesting and believable? 
* What specific paragraphs do you like and dislike, and for what reasons?
* The hard truth: is it good? Do I have potential as a writer? It's tough to gauge your own writing, and I legitimately want to know if I have talent. Feel free to just give me a 'yes' or 'no', or a scale of 1-to-10, or however. 

I **don't** want line-by-line editing, please. That can come later. But feel free to make other comments in the document for general thoughts/remarks.

[Link here.](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1bfOvK2120QjaIaA0_PnU-gxFGyfJ3pujKyXs_bLYVqI/edit?usp=sharing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
