<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5181</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd go with Tokyo in Lit and Film, Arthurian Lit, or American Playwrights.

A literature class helps you understand books in a way that you'd never understand just reading them on your own. Especially the Japanese stuff. I've read (or tried to read) Japanese classics and I usually feel completely out of my depth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 01:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enid Blyton wrote 762 books (children's) and Barbara Cartland wrote 723 (romance).

ETA: Dean Koontz has written 118 books and 76 short stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 01:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a little hard to believe that your school doesn't require everyone to take a lit class.

What are the course options? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 04:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the same answer for women. It's more important for women than men to be thin, but they don't have to be in shape. It's part of why anorexia is a growing problem in the community.

However, some do exercise. Walking is popular and some go to women's only gyms such as Lucille Roberts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 03:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on the planet that reads the articles before commenting on them. Not the planet you're on that makes ignorant assumptions and accusations.

The survey, of 702 respondents who identify as Jewish and do not live in Israel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 03:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most young people who are working out aren't doing it for their health, they're doing it because they want to look good. Orthodox guys don't need to do that - they'll get a girl without being in good shape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 03:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I have been there.

No, it doesn't suck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course I can get lots of dates

Of course? Most fat girls say they can't get dates at all. So if you have a lot of dates, you're way ahead of the game. Men tend not to go out on dates for the free meal. Not even for the free sex. So it's more likely that they like you but you're doing something to push them away. Maybe you're coming across as desperate and lonely. Maybe you're opening up about your issues too quickly. Maybe you're too put together and they end up feeling not good enough for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fresh transplants sound just like their tourist brethren. Some people take quicker than others to pick up the New York way of talking, and some people never do. My friend's mother who's from Minnesota and has been living in New York for over 40 years still says or-ange instead of ah-range. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at it the opposite way - if your drapes are closed, you can't see him either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did that too today, without even thinking about it. Truly, I judge my clothes by the content of their character.

But seriously, I only have white socks. And I don't care if they come out a little dingy because I don't bleach them. If you're inspecting my socks for whiteness, you're the loser, not me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excluding people who live in Israel. So it's much lower than 85% of all Jews - closer to 50% of all Jews. Even that sounds high, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arkansas, Mississippi and Alabama are worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 21:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barrios is either a misspelling of Barrois or it's Spanish. Or a little of both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can spot a tourist behind me from the way they talk. New Yorkers definitely talk differently from people in the Midwest and other parts of the country.

That said, the classic "toity-toid and toid" New York accent is definitely on the decline. But even if it's been replaced by the "newscaster's accent" it's still an accent. And New Yorkers tend to talk a lot faster than people in other parts of the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah.... and then Redditors wonder why they have trouble "adulting."

Nitpicking my referring to "things that cover one's windows" as curtains as opposed to blinds or shutters means you've run out of substantive arguments. 

Where I live people don't have shutters. They have curtains and/or Venetian blinds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess nobody's ever taught you how windows work. When they're open, anybody can look in. Which is why curtains were invented - to prevent people from looking in.

And the purpose of opening curtains during the day is to let natural light in. There's no natural light at night, which means there is no purpose to leaving them open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These days planes are mostly flown by autopilot so what was happening was technically possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grow up and learn the concept of responsibility for your actions. If you want privacy, you create it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Close your drapes at night or any other time you feel like walking around undressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless it's opening night or some other special performance, you can wear whatever you want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. Judaism doesn't have a whole lot of advice on how to treat people who are treating you poorly aside from saying you're not allowed to treat them poorly in return (revenge is forbidden). What that amounts to is "be the bigger person." So if a person is trolling: ignore them, block them, report them to the mods. 

The only people you're required to engage with who are treating you poorly are your parents. And even that requirement has limits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I converting this right? Height: 5'2, goal weight, 160 pounds? If that's the case, then you are obviously right to be dieting and should ignore your mother's hysterics. Plus, not to worry - no hospital would admit you.

At the same time, the important thing is to find a healthy, balanced diet that you can stick to for the rest of your life. Dieting is easy. Maintaining is hard.

I don't know if your mother is a narcissist or just feeling threatened by your losing weight and her not. Why not make an appointment for both of you together with a dietitian and personal trainer? Make it a mother-daughter project? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Height/weight?

There's no way of knowing if what you're describing is really what's going on, or if you're borderline anorexic and in denial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  at the very least put herself in harm's way

As a police officer or solider you *are* putting yourself in harm's way - but you're doing it consciously, as a choice. And dying in the line of duty is not being a failure unless you actually did something negligent or stupid that lead to your death. 

I just read a war memoir where an armored vehicle was hit by a missile and the only reason why the author survived was because by coincidence he was standing on his seat instead of sitting in it. If he'd have been sitting, he would have died. And that's not being a failure, that's just the vagary of war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 05:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try /r/writing.

Technically each individual case is not anti-feminist, but in the aggregate they are.

Have her be a soldier or police officer and have her die in the line of duty? In other words, try to make it not the typical cliche of the innocent white woman getting murdered by the vicious but cunning psychopath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 05:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For.

Why not, let's see how it goes. The mods can always rescind the rule if it's not working out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harry Potter is bland. As far as I can tell, he has no personality.

Hermione is one-dimensional. I think of her as "the smart one."

Snape is compelling. He's complicated; his motives are murky; you feel compassion for him even while you're hating him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Left Wing Modern Orthodox: 52%

Right Wing Modern Orthodox: 81%

Left Wing Yeshivish/Chareidi: 50%

Right Wing Yeshivish/Chareidi: 15%

The Orthodoxy Test says that I'm Modern Orthodox.

That's accurate, but the percentages are kind of astonishing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To repeat OP's question: What do you consider a sin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you're fun at parties.

I welcome people throwing chocolate at me wherever I might be. 

According to this article, it's traditional to throw nuts and raisins: http://www.chabad.org/library/article_cdo/aid/465165/jewish/The-Aufruf.htm

But in this land of ~~milk and honey~~ fat and sugar, candy is better than nuts and raisins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is from the Reform page about Yom Kippur. It sounds like they want to have their cake and eat it too, no pun intended. They describe some actions as sins but then quickly back away and turn teshuva into a general "spiritual" concept.

The Days of Awe are about more than confessing our sins. They are an opportunity to envision our lives and our communities if we each become a little more caring with each passing year.  On Yom Kippur morning, we read from the Torah portion entitled Nitzavim, in which we learn that meaningful Jewish lives are not too hard for us and not too far awayif we are willing to choose a life of caring for each other. We also recite the Al Cheit, a prayer that recounts our sins:  gossip, arrogance, exploiting the weak, and all the other missteps we took during the year just ended. The High Holidays are a time for tshuvah, which is usually understood to mean repentance.  But tshuvah is much more than repentance.  Its literal meaning is return and, indeed, tshuvah is a return forward to something holy inside us that hasnt yet reached fruition, a return to the goodness and the caring that could have been and still can be. Tshuvah is our search to find the potential for good and for holiness that has been within us all along but somehow became hidden in the hustle and bustle of everyday life.

http://www.reformjudaism.org/yom-kippur-customs-and-rituals-0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Americans tend to get two weeks vacation and two weeks sick leave. People will just call in "sick." Or if their company allows it, take time off unpaid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally 3 is my baseline rating too, but what I forgot to mention was that at times I just wanted the book to be over already. It was really short so I got through it, but if it had been longer, it's possible I wouldn't have even finished it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I look at ratings when deciding whether to read a book or not, and I want people's honest opinion. Three stars is certainly better than 2, but I'd never consider giving the book 4 or 5. I didn't feel *that* bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever rated a book higher than it deserved because you felt bad about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished reading a book that I'd rather not name. It was a memoir about a very difficult period in the author's life. Parts of it moved me, but overall I thought it was weak. I wanted to give it 2 stars but felt bad so I rated it 3 stars instead. I particularly felt bad because my library purchased at my request. 

This is the first time I can remember not feeling comfortable giving an honest rating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the most expensive gift you've ever gotten? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a map of those Green Carts mentioned in the link above. I doubt you're asking about those areas: http://www1.nyc.gov/assets/doh/downloads/pdf/cdp/green_carts_areas.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 03:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI there is no Numbers 16:46-50. Chapter 16 only goes up to verse 35. You're talking about Numbers 17:14. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 03:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which ones?

There aren't that many blessings on food and they're short. 

The blessings after food are longer, but you don't have to memorize them - that's what siddurs and bentchers are for. I always carry a pocket-sized siddur. 

After saying the blessings after food a bunch of times you will find that you'll have naturally memorized them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not worth the money, but if you have money to spare it makes your life easier because you don't have to worry about how much money is on your card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In order from left to right: Ben Ish Chai. Rabbi Moshe David Cassuto. Rabbi Joseph Ber Soloveitchik. Jacob Joseph Oettinger, chief rabbi of Berlin in 1825. Rav Aharon Lichtenstein. Rav Yitzchak Elchanan Spektor, Kovno Rav. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google says the fourth one is Rabbi 20th Century. EDIT: Then it says it's Rabbi Person. 

Found it, it's Jacob Joseph Oettinger, chief rabbi of Berlin in 1825.

Next is Rav Aharon Lichtenstein and then Rav Yitzchak Elchanan Spektor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nat Hentoff, Journalist and Social Commentator, Dies at 91 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 23:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 23:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, first person shooter games make me nauseous. It's a form of motion sickness.

I like Candy Crush, The Sims, Bookworm, and CSI: Hidden Objects. Just because they're not shoot-em-ups or about stealing cars doesn't mean they're not video games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 22:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a lawyer on that floor. There could be 10 or even 20 tenants on the floor, there's no way to know.

https://www.avvo.com/attorneys/10017-ny-thomas-carlson-811535.html

ETA: Another lawyer: http://www.manta.com/c/mmznm9j/the-law-firm-of-lansing-r-palmer-pc

ETA2: No idea what this is: http://leisearch.com/lou.php?id=EVK05KS7XY1DEII3R011 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 22:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes there's a list of offices on a board right in the lobby. No need to even ask.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 05:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked a Visit from the Goon Squad. I think you have to be a certain age or at a certain point in your life to appreciate it, and the average Redditor isn't there yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 05:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UWS too. They installed FIOS in my building within the last couple of months. Talk to the manager of your building to see if there's any plans to come to your area soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not surprised. Traditional Jewish foods aren't that good. The only reason why people like it is because they ate it when they were kids. It's comfort food at best. I'd say the most popular types of kosher restaurants are pizza and steakhouses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But seriously none of them are serving traditional Eastern European/Jewish traditional fare?

Not really. What did you have in mind?

Mr. Broadway is a fairly well-known kosher restaurant in midtown. The only "traditional" foods I see on the menu are brisket and chicken soup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
