<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8902</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen it yet. I think it's pretty cool. I normally play solo, so I don't see people attempting these kinds of kick offs most of the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, ok. Cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably a stupid question, but what actually came of that? I think it was a cool idea and would have been great to not have Andrew Jackson on the bill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His statements may have been inappropriate, but so was Trump's reply. I don't see how the initial statement by Lewis could be construed as racist.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 06:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really think the sword would matter much. I think this is just one shell of many.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to see he had a good game. He has not had a great season at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 04:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The panel with all the doors really makes me think of Interstellar. The final scene with Matthew Mcconaughey in space with the infinite bookshelves. Not sure if it's what he was going for, just what I thought of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lawnmower Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 04:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 23:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually got to meet John Lewis and the author at DragonCon in 2016 when they were there hosting a panel on March. It was really cool and something I will always remember.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 22:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We did this last MLK day too. I think it may be becoming an annual tradition, which is super cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 18:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Melancholia. It's a beautiful film with a fantastic performance by Kirsten Dunst, but it's so hopeless. I watched it once, just never again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 18:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, it's unfortunate we don't all get our news from Brietbart and Alex Jones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 17:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lewis was chairman of the Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee during the Civil Rights Movement and he's actually considering one of the leaders of the Movement. Say what you will about him now, but he helped accomplish some great things in his youth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 16:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He really is. As soon as anyone saw John Lewis's statement, they could guess he was going to be attacked by Trump on Twitter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 15:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with term limits, but that's not a problem I have with Lewis. That's a problem I have with the current system.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 15:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't even know Joe was in Utah, hope he does well though. I really liked him when he was in Atlanta.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 15:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
It's not a perfect district, but there are definitely worse districts in the city. 


"He has since 1987 represented Georgias 5th District, which is predominantly black and includes much of Atlanta and some surrounding suburbs.More than 87 percent of adults in the district are high school graduates, and more than 40 percent are college graduates, according to Census data. The median household income is just over $48,000."



http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/314325-trump-rips-john-lewis-worry-about-your-crime-infested-district </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm okay with this. One of my favorite movies and Jim Carrey's best performances.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. I am dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the Robocop reboot and Total Recall reboots were terrible. The Dredd reboot was fantastic though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 23:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you start losing, it's easy to get frustrated and make more mistakes, which cause you to lose even more. When I get on a losing streak, a lot of times I will take a temporary break to help avoid that phenomenon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why even? Is there actually any nostalgia for that bad television show? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite pool bar is way out the area you're looking, but if you're ever in the Marietta area for any reason, check our Cues. Nice tables and decent bar food and beer selection  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 13:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to see it end because it would make no sense. With Marten and Dora, we always knew they weren't a good fit, there were so many petty arguments, but Marten and Claire seem great together from what we've seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 13:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know what universe you occupy, but in this one, waffles are better than pancakes. Not as good as French toast though I  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we going to get see those memories she's so distraught about? I'm preparing for all of the emotions, but excited to see what's in store after all the buildup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marten is in a happy, healthy relationship. Happy characters are boring. Conflict keeps the story interesting, even if it means new elements need to introduced.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seem to be in the minority. I'm 32 and so far my 30s and late twenties were the best years of my life so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [movies] C C Geekcast | Episode 10: Guardians of the Galaxy (SFW)

On this episode we're going to be discussing one of our favorite films within the Marvel Cinematic Universe, Guardians of the Galaxy, which also happens to be one of the best space operas of recent memory. We're going to be discussing our thoughts on Marvel expanding into the intergalactic realm. We're also going to be discussing our thoughts on all the characters introduced, as well as the villain and of course Thanos. We're also going to be discussing how we think it compares to other great science fiction films.

[Podbean Link](http://candcgeekcast.podbean.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 13:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No offer comes without a cost. If this guy is that powerful, and seemingly evil, I wonder what his cost would be to help Bubbles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 16:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simultaneously exists as clickbait and non clickbait news until you click the link?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize Buzzfeed News has won some awards? They may be known for clickbait, but they've done some good work. The clickbait just helps keep the lights on, so to speak.

https://www.buzzfeed.com/shani/buzzfeed-news-reporting-recognized-with-major-award 

http://www.nlgja.org/blog/2016/08/nlgja-announces-2016-excellence-journalism-award-winners-honorees/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 02:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was pretty funny actually, but I love dad jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I miss that team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 15:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't completely understand what the Hawks are trying to do. If we're trying to blow it up and tank we're not doing a very good job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 03:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just went to the craft beer store and got a few 6 packs. No chance of a beer shortage at my house this weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 03:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the greatest player, but he was my favorite player. This is a loss to me as a fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 04:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not beyond the realm of possibility I think, but who would she fight? She would break Corpse Witch in half no problem,at least from what we've seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 04:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to read it multiple times to not see that title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 04:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there something wrong with always joking around and smiling? Makes it look like he's having a good time. I understand there's a lot of reasons to not like Dwight, but that's not a good one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you like Pistol Pete? He was a fantastic player.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you like Vue as a whole? I think it's a cool idea but don't know much about it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how overtly sci fi Questionable Content has become since introducing bubbles and all the other robot ai characters. I mean it's always been obvious it's a futuristic world, but now with the focus on artificial intelligence and encryption and everything else, it's just awesome to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 04:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Faye does decide to compete with Corpse Witch and poach some of the talent, I wonder how Corpse Witch will respond. Based on what we know of the character, it's not something she would take lying down, and it's very obvious she will go to great lengths to protect herself and get what she wants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 15:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The good part about people that do that is the fact that you instantly learn they're a douche, as opposed to finding out over time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does the amount of money you make matter in regards to meeting people?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 01:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe was great when he was in Atlanta. Ended us getting that ridiculous contract, but he is played well for us when he was here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 19:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on your interests, if you're a geek, there's a big group on Facebook called Metro Atlanta Geeks that's always planning different events.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 19:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 Chainz must be a pretty big dude. He isn't completely dwarfed by Dominique.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I choose to believe they waited so long to make sure their case was airtight, but at the same time, I know you're right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to see him finally getting charged. This has always been a fishy story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're assuming people haven't used official channels. Reddit is a great community in that it allows a wide range of opinions and provides a place to rant and bitch, so just because someone is a member of this community, doesn't mean they're not trying other avenues to express their displeasure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I think this has to be one of the darkest plots ever in this comic. It really seems like we're getting someone that's just evil, as opposed to misunderstood.

 It also seems inspired by Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind, one of my favorite movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 02:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://lnfy.org/thrift-store/

A thrift store where 100% of the profits from donations goes to help LBGT youth who are homeless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 00:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [movies] C C Geekcast | Episode 10: Guardians of the Galaxy (SFW)

On this episode we're going to be discussing one of our favorite films within the Marvel Cinematic Universe, Guardians of the Galaxy, which also happens to be one of the best space operas of recent memory. We're going to be discussing our thoughts on Marvel expanding into the intergalactic realm. We're also going to be discussing our thoughts on all the characters introduced, as well as the villain and of course Thanos. We're also going to be discussing how we think it compares to other great science fiction films.

[Podbean Link](http://candcgeekcast.podbean.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 02:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A broadcasting legend with even more legendary suits. RIP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the idea of a week of cereal is funny, but I really can't wait to see where this is going. There are so many possibilities regarding the relationship of Corpse Witch and Bubbles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 03:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [movies] C C Geekcast | Episode 10: Guardians of the Galaxy (SFW)

On this episode we're going to be discussing one of our favorite films within the Marvel Cinematic Universe, Guardians of the Galaxy, which also happens to be one of the best space operas of recent memory. We're going to be discussing our thoughts on Marvel expanding into the intergalactic realm. We're also going to be discussing our thoughts on all the characters introduced, as well as the villain and of course Thanos. We're also going to be discussing how we think it compares to other great science fiction films.

[Podbean Link](http://candcgeekcast.podbean.com/)
[Stitcher Link](http://www.stitcher.com/podcast/cc-geekcast)


[Facebook](http://facebook.com/candcgeekcast)
[Twitter](http://twitter.com/candcgeekcast]
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 03:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if the Hawks had drafted Deron Williams or Chris Paul in 2005 instead of Marvin Williams? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 02:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, yeah. You're right. For some reason I was thinking he played earlier than that. My bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 18:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who was the last player to do it? Going to assume John Stockton.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 04:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. I think Paul Millsap who wears #4 is better than Isaiah Thomas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That look on Baze's face. It's like "yeah, I know what the camera is really looking at" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was too. Those are my go to drink at any coffee shop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 02:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure about the others, but Dominique deserves a spot on any team. Loved the power with which he dunked. Check out this fantastic dunk on Larry Bird.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CqE9SdpCZv4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Hawks fan I will always hate that Bird and the Celtics consistently eliminated Dominique and the Hawks in the playoffs. 

Definitely a legend though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely one of the GOATs, and he's alone in the #1 spot at trash talking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I guess robotic life would, uh, find a way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, you can reseal caps with a lighter? TIL  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mad Max: Fury Road Black   Chrome Edition review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suicide Squad: Extended Cut review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 22:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 19:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too have a 2012 Focus. I like the car, just the transmission is so temper mental. Some days it's just fine, others it shifts so that hard. 

I really wish I would have got the 6 speed manual ST version that I really wanted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 18:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buzzfeed may be known for clickbait, but they've actually won awards for their journalism. 

https://www.buzzfeed.com/shani/buzzfeed-news-reporting-recognized-with-major-award?utm_term=.mp9kXXgl1#.fnEvMMOlV

They do some good work sometimes. The clickbait just helps keep the light on. Same with the ajc and many other institutions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 18:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude should have been kicked off the flight. Others have been kicked off for a less.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawsuit: Decatur man spends 53 days in jail for crime he didn't commit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hits of 2016 just keep coming. Didn't use what.cd much since I got my Google Play Music subscription, but there was nothing like it anywhere. There was nothing that couldn't be found there. It's the end of an era. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 14:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a beautiful poster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 14:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is nothing new to report in regards to the status of the investigation and as we have maintained from the beginning, we have no reason to suspect the note is a hoax or was fabricated, school district spokesman Bernard Watson said.

There is no evidence that it's fake. Or do you think you know better than those actually investigating the issue?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bill is being potentially introduced to restrict the wearing of Muslim burqa and veil in Georgia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 18:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 15:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a person is a refugee they are here legally anyway. There was a former Somalian refugee just elected to public office in Minnesota.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 14:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because American citizens aren't Muslim?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you see Muslim and you automatically assume she may be illegal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty interesting. Especially when considering voter turnout was actually down nationwide.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gwinnett principal: 'Let's rally around' Muslim teacher told to hang self </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 22:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's one tonight. At the Historic Fourth Ward Park.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great work man. I like some of those. Is it possible to order prints from you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume this picture was inspired by Doctor Strange this weekend. Lol 

Beautifully done though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captain America 3 was Civil War which came out months ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 04:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Momocon is one of my favorites. Become much more fond of smaller cons these past couple of years. Love DragonCon, but it's so damn big.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 23:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really like some of your stickers. Good work man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 23:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sent a message, not sure if I'm big enough for you to care about, but I'm definitely a quintessential super nerd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 16:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intersection of ga-92 and Trickum road in Woodstock. Always a bottleneck there in the morning and traffic always backs up all the way past the church.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 05:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already have one C C Geekcast at candcgeekcast.com but I would love to guest on yours at some point if you get it off the ground. I'm always up for talking about film of all genres.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 23:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going to Geek Media Expo in Nashville that weekend. Not sure what I'm actually doing Halloween day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 21:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wal Mart. Our batteries are a lot of times less expensive than the other chains, and our Everstart Maxx batteries come with a 5 year warranty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 18:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screw the stats that say crime is down, it's all about how I feel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really hope the whole team kneels after hearing about this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 18:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually go to that location on a regular basis. Why was it so awful?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 04:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That coded phrase would work for me as well. There's no way any reasonable person could get tired of burritos for lunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 22:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish I could have purchased some. Offer is no longer available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 04:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comic definitely confirms the speculation I've seen in regards to the dynamic of their relationship. It definitely seems like Corpse Witch is manipulating and controlling Bubbles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparent no longer around. Found a deactivated Facebook page.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit. Give me a minute. May have got name wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 19:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've used Peace of Junk and they were great and more inexpensive than a lot of others  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Morally Dubious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 04:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I empathize with Clinton so much in this comic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 23:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honest question. Why do certain people like armed protests so much? As opposed to completely peaceful protests with no weapons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 06:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in a couple of your pictures from the Fallout shoot. Nice pics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 06:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CW coverage was atrocious. There were so many groups that were left out due to the over abundance of Six Flags and Moe's ads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 14:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Movies] C C GeekCast | Episode 3: Suicide Squad/Warner Brothers

SFW

[podbean](http://candcgeekcast.podbean.com)
[Google Play](https://play.google.com/music/m/Dobvy64p25lfzovolqjydnj3hfa?t=Episode_3_Suicide_Squad-CC_Geekcast)

On this episode we're going to be discussing our thoughts on Suicide Squad. We're going to be discussing our thoughts on all the new Joker, Harley Quinn, and all the other new characters and iterations of characters in this film. We're also going to be discussing our thoughts on Warner Bros and what we think about the future of the DC Cinematic Universe.

C C Geekcast is a podcast where two friends talk about movies and general geekery. Join us biweekly as we discuss our thoughts on movies and geek culture.

[Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/candcgeekcast/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a great taco truck on Bells Ferry next to the Wal Mart. There's also a boiled peanut stand with decent boiled peanuts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that actually make people feel better though? Personally I don't care how it's structured, if I want to see an artist I'm pretty much willing to pay the price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What games?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 02:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually server wage is still $2.13 as far as I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 02:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Film)C C Geekcast | Episode 3: Suicide Squad (Or how Warner Bros is mishandling the DC Cinematic Universe

SFW

[Podbean Episode Link](https://www.podbean.com/media/share/pb-g3a7n-6235bf#.V8SlhSvhAjw.facebook)

On this episode we're going to be discussing our thoughts on Suicide Squad. We're going to be discussing our thoughts on all the new Joker, Harley Quinn, and all the other new characters and iterations of characters in this film. We're also going to be discussing our thoughts on Warner Bros and what we think about the future of the DC Cinematic Universe.



C C Geekcast is a podcast where two friends talk about and dissect geek movies. You should give us a listen if you enjoy discussing geek movies with your friends because that is the experience we try to capture

[Facebook Page](www.facebook.com/candcgeekcast) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 17:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome. I thought I was doing okay with 50 downloads in my first month, lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
