<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7340</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knows....... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why thank you, mjmick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Motel DeMille : Chapter 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Chapter 2](http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/64y3i8/motel_demille_chapter_2/) 

[Chapter 3](http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/66islm/motel_demille_chapter_3) 


Motel DeMille. 1983. Sedona, Arizona. A red '79 Beatle pulled into the near vacant lot in front of the minuscule motel that sat, still and quiet on the side of the otherwise lonely highway. A woman, clad in a red, cashmere blazer with bright red, silk bell bottoms to match, climbed out of the car with her son by her side. She strode coolly towards the glass paned door, her thick, black, curly hair waving behind her. Even as she strolled into such a modest business, she exuded confidence, head up, sunglasses perched firmly in her voluminous frizzy hair. 


The same could not be said for her son however, he limped in the direction of the entrance, weighed down by his mother's luggage. He wore a loose, long t-shirt with baggy, worn shorts and a tight cap over his short, fuzzy hair. He had a slight hunch and a worryingly skinny physique and was several strides behind his mother the whole way across the car park.


They both arrived in the cosy motel and walked up to the front desk. The receptionist was a large woman, with round jam jar glasses and was dressed in several layers of cardigans. She had grey, curly hair and looked to be in her sixties.


"I'd like a two bed room for the week, please and thanks, sweetie", said the woman, smiling.

"Reservation ?", asked the receptionist.

"Uh no, I was kinda counting on you having a vacancy."

"Names ?"

"Linda...... Rhodes", she said, deciding not to give her real name.

"And the boy ?"

"Peter. Peter Rhodes", said Linda.

"Okay. Fine. Room 17. Here's the key."


The white door to the stairs opened as the receptionist hands over the key and the most beautiful woman Linda had ever seen stridesld out and across the lobby. She has had flowing white hair and snow white skin and small, fragile, dainty features. She sauntered over to Linda. The contrasts were striking. Linda was wearing stylish, expensive flashy attire, whereas the woman wore only a toga type shawl. Linda's dark skin was noticeable against the woman's almost spooky paleness. The woman had long, white hair, and Linda had a dark afro. The woman held out her arms and smiled.


"Welcome to Motel DeMille. I'm the owner. My name is Elanora DeMille", she held out her hand.



Linda took it.



"Linda Rhodes."

"An absolute pleasure", beamed Elanora. "This is Constance Utile. She is the receptionist and she likes to be referred to as Ms. Utile." 

Next she gestured toward the young woman sweeping in the back of the lobby. "That is Kitty, the maid. She will be cleaning your room between the hours of twelve and one each day and you are expected to vacate the room during this time. Over there, at the bar by the entrance to the dining area, is my brother, Dennis DeMille. He is the barman. His infant son is also staying with us. Breakfast will be served between nine and eleven. Lunch from two to three, and dinner from six to eight."


"Wow", said Linda. "Well that certainly was a warm welcome."


A particularly sullen looking teenage girl strutted into the lobby from the stairs. She was wearing a walkman and didn't seem to notice Elanora or the new guests.


"Eve !", exclaimed Elanora. "Come greet the new guests. This is my niece, Eve. She's the only daughter of my sister, Cordelia."


Elanora's smile faded slightly when she uttered her sister's name.


"They both live here also", continued Elanora. "All the DeMilles under one roof."


Eve wandered over to the Rhodes, her chestnut hair flowing behind her.


"Welcome to Bates Motel", she said before turning around and laying down on the couches in the lobby.


"Ah, she has an...... alternative sense of humour", chuckled Elanora. "Would you care to have a drink with me in the dining area, alone, just for a few minutes, Ms. Rhodes ? I have some..... rules to discuss with you before you get comfortable."


"Sure thing", said Linda. "Peter, why don't you go sit in lobby while you wait."


The pair of women started toward the dining room, while Peter decided whether or not to sit down next to an attractive, albeit grumpy girl his age. He tentatively sat down opposite her in an armchair.


The two women sat down at a table in the empty dining room and Dennis served them two glasses of whiskey. Linda was slightly unnerved by Dennis. He was in his fifties, yet still had a pointed strand of hair dyed bright red on his forehead. He looked as though he couldn't speak, as if he'd been sworn to secrecy and didn't trust himself to even produce a syllable.


"So", began Elanora. "I trust you know the nature of this motel, considering you actually found us."

"I know what I heard", said Linda.

"And what might that be ?"

"That this is a motel that accepts...... violaters of the law, and allows them to lay low until the suspicion of law enforcement wears off."

"Exactly. We allow criminals to stay here exclusively, in exchange for a handsome fee."

"Which I have paid in full."

"Yes, you have. But, due to the nature of this place, we sometimes get into some trouble regarding the guests, which is why I don't think this is any place for a child."

"But, you're niece and infant nephew live here."

"Yes and we don't allow them to interact with guests that have a certain...... unsavoury aura about them. I just wouldn't want anything to happen to your son."

"Peter can handle himself just fine."

"You're sure ? I must stress that we will not accept any responsibility for the fate of you or your son whilst you are staying here."

"I understand."

"Now, to business. There a very few, but very extremely strict rules that guests must abide by whilst here at the Motel DeMille."

"Okay, go on."

"Rule number one : never, ever, under any circumstances go into the basement. If you or your son does, you will be punished severley. Rule number two : Do not under any circumstances go into room 29. Punishment will be equally severe for this violation. Rule number three : Do not go into rooms 4, 9, 13, 19, or 21. These are the rooms that Eve, Cordelia, Dennis, his son Alastair, Kitty, Constance and myself live in. There isn't any punishment for this rule, but I won't be liable for anything we do if you do in fact trespass on us. And that's it. Those are the three rules. Follow those and we should get along just fine."

"Great, we can do that."

"Oh, and also don't try to use the elevator, it's broken."

"Sure thing. Um...... Given the purpose of this place, I don't have to tell you the reason why I am here, do I ?"

"Oh goodness no", chirped Elanora. "We have a strict 'don't ask don't tell' policy around here."


Peter sat down opposite Eve awkwardly, nervously looking around the lobby. Eve sat up and looked at him.


"So what're you here for ?", she asked him.

"Who, me ?", he said, immediately regretting he'd opened his mouth.

"Well, there isn't anybody else here, is there ?"

"My mother says I'm not allowed to talk about it."

"You don't know, do you ?"

"No", he relented.

"Hmmm. We don't usually get kids around here."


Eve got up and took off her headphones.


"You coming out for a smoke ?", she asked nonchalantly.

"Oh, yeah, sure. Of course", he blurted.


The two of them walked out and sat on the porch. She took out a packet of cigarettes and placed one between her lips. She took out a matchbox, struck a match and tenderly lit the end of the cigarette. She inhaled and slowly released a cloud of smoke, watching it dissipate into the air.


"So where's your dad ?", asked Eve.

"He left my mom and I. Only last week, actually."

"Jesus. I'm sorry."

"No, it's fine. He was kind of an asshole. He was completely an asshole, actually."

"Huh. Well at least he's still around."

"Yours isn't ?"

"Nope. He was murdered five years ago."

"Fuck. I'm sorry."

"Yeah, he was pretty great. They never caught the killer. After he died, my mom and I moved here, with the rest of our fucked up family."

"You don't like it here ?"

"Course not. It's in the middle of nowhere, there's never anything to do, the only people I ever see are my creepy relatives and the criminals that pass through here. It gets lonely."

"What about your mom ? She doesn't take you out to places ?"

"My mother ? Are you kidding ? I can't even remember the last time my mom even spoke to me ?"

"You guys don't speak ? I thought you lived in the same room ?"

"We do. But that doesn't stop her. Every day since we moved here she goes out in a taxi at about eight every night and doesn't come back until two the next day, smelling of booze, with her underwear in her pockets. Then she eats something, sleeps until eight and does it all over again. Every single day since dad died. She doesn't work, or drive either. She hasn't been sober in five years."

"Five years, huh ?", said Peter. "That's rough."

"I wouldn't even be in school if it wasn't for Elanora. And now it's the summer and I have to just wander around all day, every day. Sorry about all this, you must think I'm some kind of weirdo, spilling my guts to you like this, but, no ever talks to me around here. I can't tell anybody how frustrating it is."

"No, it's fine. I haven't really spoken to anyone in a real long time, either. Whatever my mom did, it must've been bad. We had to go from hotel to hotel for ages before we heard about this place."

"Well, it whatever it was, she's not nearly as bad as my mother."


Eve put out her cigarette and walked back inside just as a taxi pulled into the parking lot. A dishevelled looking woman stumbled out of the car. She threw a few dollar bills in the window of the cab. She had wild, frizzy, dyed blonde hair with noticeable dark roots. 

She had heavy mascara around her eyes and black mascara stains streaming down her cheeks. She had bright red lipstick smeared all over her lips and chin. She was wearing a tight, blue mini-dress that left far too little up to the imagination and heels so large Peter wondered how she stayed upright. She stumbled along the pathway up to the porch with a bottle of whiskey in one hand, the other shielding the sun from her eyes. She didn't even notice Peter sitting there as she stumbled through the door. A smell of alcohol and sweat wafted onto Peter as she went by him.


Peter walked back inside just in time to see his mother come out of the dining area holding her drink. She came over to him and ushered him along towards the stairs.


"Come on", she said, hurrying him along.

"What ?", he asked. "What's wrong ?"

"I don't know but we're getting out of here just about as soon as we possibly can."


The mother and son reached their room and scurried inside. They laid their luggage down on one of the beds. 


"What did she say ?", asked Peter.

"She said that we're not allowed to go into the basement or room 29 under any circumstances. She said we'd be punished or something."

"Punished ?", chuckled Peter.

"Yes, I have a bad feeling about this place. That woman is hiding something, and I don't intend on sticking around to find out what that is."


Evening came and Eve was still as frustratingly bored as she was all day. Her mother was gone again. She found herself back in the lobby. Elanora glided in, graceful as ever. 


"Why Eve, why don't you go set the tables for dinner ?", she asked.


Eve would be grateful for the distraction, if it wasn't doing menial tasks for no pay, only for no one to even show up to dinner. She rolled her eyes and trudged into the dining room.


Linda came into the lobby and sat down at the bar as Elanora sauntered back into one of the hallways. She sat down at the bar and looked at Dennis. He avoided catching her eye and continued to clean glasses.


"I'll take a martini please, barman", she said.

"Coming up", muttered Dennis.

"So", said Linda after he served her the drink. "How long have you been here ?"

"Two years", he mumbled, still not looking at her.

"So you've been living here with your son, huh ?"

"Yes", he said.

"What age ?"

"Five."

"So this is all the DeMilles then ? Under one roof ?"

"Yep."

"What's it like working for your sister ? She can be pretty intense, huh ?"

"You're telling me", he said dryly.

"She always like that ?"

"For as long as I can remember, at least. No wonder I chose to work at a bar", he said quietly.


Linda laughed and Dennis smiled. It wasn't often he got to chat  to the guests.


Eve was reluctantly setting the twenty or so tables in the dining room for what felt like hours. She didn't see why she even needed to do this, they only actually had one guest staying with them. She stopped. She decided she was fed up doing this. She decided she was fed up living in one room in the middle of the desert with a bunch of weirdos. She decided to go to the basement. For the five years she'd been there, Elanora had told her the same thing every single day : don't go into the basement. Eve had never once dared to go there. What could she be hiding that was so bad, anyway ?


Eve grabbed the torch from the front desk and quickly went down the stairs in the lobby. She slowed down as she neared the door. Something about it made her feel uneasy. It would probably be locked anyway, right ? No, she wouldn't lose her nerve now. She touched the white door. She jumped as she heard a click. She pushed open the door and stepped inside.


It was pitch dark and the door closed behind her. She tripped and fell knee deep into something thick and sludgy. It smelled rancid. She turned on her flashlight. It was dead bodies. She was laying in a sea of dead bodies. Eve screamed.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life of Po </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lord of the Beans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 11:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>                                                  Shift Part 3

The next week, Tony woke up in his new apartment and had breakfast with his new friend. So there they were, just a couple of attractive, platonic friends living in a stylish yet impossibly cheap apartment in New York.

"Howdy Tony !" smiled Lizzie.

"Hey, guess what ?", said Tony.

"What ?"

"I got two of the resident artists from that posh gallery down at NYU to come look at one of my pieces."

"Oh my god, that's great, Tony. Wait, they're coming here ?"

"Yep. 12 o'clock sharp tomorrow. And they're real serious, sophisticated types so make sure to wear something nice."

"Wear something nice ?", she said, offended.

"Well you know, just not in pyjamas."

"And what makes you think I'll be in my pyjamas at 12 o'clock ?"

"I... I don't. Just in case."

"Hmm. Anyway did I tell you I met someone ?"

"You did ? That's great !"

"Yep. His name's Chip and he owns a bar downtown."

"Wow, that's great."

"Well look at us", said Lizzie. "Just two friends having a grand old time in New York."

"Anyways I gotta go out, I've got to go buy a suit for tomorrow."

"Okay", she chirped.

Tony sauntered out into the hallway, finally feeling something positive again since Lily died. The door opposite their apartment opened and an ld woman in a red, flowery night dress and curlers in her hair peered out. She didn't look happy. She had one of those faces that always looked angry.

"Good morning", greeted Tony as he shut the door behind him.

"What are you so grinning about ?", she inquired with a deep, raspy voice.

This struck Tony as an odd way to introduce ones self to a perfect stranger.

"Actually, things are finally going my way, miss."

The old woman rolled her eyes and lit up a cigarette.

"Uh, I don't think you're allowed to do that inside anymore", said Tony politely.

"You know what's wrong with kids like you nowadays ?", she continued. "You all think your entitled to a rich and stress free life like those idiots on tv, and you think your working but you don't know what real work is like. Like that poor Lizzie you moved in with. She thinks she was come here and everything was gonna turn up rosy, but that was never gonna happen. And look at her now. Throwing raves and getting drunk with you and disturbing my sleep while your at it."

"We've literally never done that."

"You do it alright, you goddamn kids, always intruding on an old lady like that, you oughtta be ashamed...."

With that, she closed the door in his face. Tony went back inside to Lizzie.
"Um.... why did an old lady just criticize my whole generation before she even said hello to me ?"

"Oh, that's just Mrs. Crooks. She just like to complain, she doesn't mean half the things she says", she assured him.

"Okaaay. Still in the pjs, huh ?", he said and left, leaving Lizzie on her own in the apartment. Lizzie decided to invite her gentleman caller over. After a while he showed up and subsequently broke her heart by telling her that she shouldn't have quit her job to become a writer and that her couldn't be in a relationship with someone who wore pyjamas until 1 o'clock. Lizzie wandered out, crying into the hall after he left. Mrs.Crooks came out.

"Why so blue, sweetie ?", she asked, puffing another cigarette.

"My guy just broke it off with me because he thinks I should've kept working for a pig."

"Sounds like a real asshole."

"No, maybe he's right. Even Tony told me I shouldn't wear pyjamas at 1 in the day."

"You're new roommate ?"

"Yeah, he said it wasn't sophisticated. Just because he got a fancy art job now he looks down on me. It's not like I'm not working I've been writing all day every day."

"Sophisticated ? Fuck sophisticated, honey. Your doing what you love, and there ain't nobody can shit on that, not your asshole boyfriend or some art stiff."

"Thanks, Mrs.Crooks. But, could you do me a favour ?"

"Sure."

"Just don't tell Tony that I broke up with Chip. Just tell him that we, you know...."

"Fucked ?"

"Well, yeah, if you wouldn't mind. I just don't want him to think I'm a complete fuck up."

"Sure thing, sweetie."

Lizzie went back, angry that all the men in her life think she's lazy. Tony came home just as she was about to change. He was carrying bags. She couldn't even remember what he bought, as she was still angry about earlier.

"How was your day ?", he asked happily.

"Fantastic. Chip came over."

"So it's still going strong huh ? Looks like it's cause for a celebration. How about some of Poland's finest tonic ?"

Lizzie could've sworn she heard a laugh track.

"What ?"

"Well I couldn't afford Champagne, so I went to the Polish shop and this was in the 10 cent bin, so there you go."

"Yummy."

Morning came and Lizzie got up feeling even worse after that Polish tonic shit. She rose up and didn't even bother putting on real clothes, as she was still angry about the day before. She sauntered into the kitchen, grabbing the tonic on her way. She took a swig and burped loudly on the way into the kitchen. She turned and saw the two artists and Tony in a suit. The artists. Holy shit, she forgot about the artists. Suddenly, Mrs.Crooks burst in.

"Hey, sweetie, I heard you banged your man real good last night, huh ?", she recited before leaving.

The artist, seemingly horrified scurried out, leaving an apologetic Lizzie in front of Tony, who was in disbelief. 

"Oh my God. I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm so, so, so sorry", pleaded Lizzie. "I completely forgot."

Tony sighed.

"It's fine, Lizzie."

"No, it's not I-"

"No really, I've been a dick to you all week and I'm sorry I deserved it. I was nervous about getting accepted into that pretentious place anyway."

"Well, since we're being honest, Chip dumped me."

"I'm sorry, Liz."

The pair sat down on the floor, after learning a painfully obvious, yet nevertheless important life lesson; friendship is more important in life than material goods. They poured some Polish tonic and clinked their glasses together, glad that they'd found each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>                                                    Shift Part 2                                                     

Tony walked along the streets of New York with his head down, still in despair about Lily. As he trudged ahead he crashed into someone and the world was temporarily turned upside down. He scrambled back up, regaining his composure and noticing the woman he had crashed into had dropped her bags, spilling papers and personal effects all over the street.

"Oh god, I'm sorry. I wasn't looking where I was going. Oh, jeese. I'm sorry", sighed Tony as he rushed to help her pick her things back up.

Tony and the woman locked eyes and he felt something he hadn't felt since Lily died. Hope. She had icy blue eyes and flowing chestnut hair. She looked into his eyes, smiling kindly.

"Don't worry about it. I was rushing too much as usual anyways", she laughed.
 
Tony helped her pick up her things and stood up.

"Well thanks a bunch for that. Not everyone in this city would be so nice", said the woman.

 Tony looked at her. She had piles of folders in her arms and there were several bags hanging out of each arm. She was being weighed down with each stumble.

"You want me to carry some of those for you ?", asked Tony.

"Oh no, that's okay. It's giving me a great workout", she said her voice strained from the pressure.

"You sure ?"

"Well, if you really want to....", she said as the folders began to topple again. Tony thrust out his arms and caught them.

"Whew ! Thanks, pal", she beamed.

The pair walked down the street.

"So what's your name ?", she asked him.

"Tony", he responded.

"Well, Tony, you might just be the last gentleman left in New York."

"What about you ?"

"Am I a gentleman ?"

"No", chuckled Tony. "What's your name ?"

"Oh, it's Lizzie. Ah.... are you alright ?"

"Me ? Yeah I'm fine, why ?"

"It's just that you look significantly more gloomy than everyone else in this city, which is pretty difficult."

"Oh it's a long story."

"We've got time, the parking lot is another few blocks away."

"No.....I'd rather not talk about it."

"Okey dokey. How about I bore you with the details of my awful day then ?"

"Great", he smiled.

"Well first off I wake up and the first thing my roommate tells me is that she's moving out because she can't stand the sight of my fingernails."

"Fingernails ?"

"Yeah, she works for some fancy ass fashion company and believes everyone should have "poppin'" nails. Then I go out to my shitty car and realise a squirrel just died on the bonnet and had to whack it off with a crow bar I found on my balcony a few weeks ago. Next I arrive at my dead end receptionist job and my pig boss asks me to bring these big ass folders full porno magazines to the dump before his wife catches him and then makes me do his grocery shopping."

"Sounds pretty awful."

"Yep. It was. Was your day as bad as that ?"

"Somewhere around that level, yeah."

"Well here we are."

They arrived at the old, rusted car and Lizzie popped open the trunk and heaved all the porn folders into the car.

"Well, I thank for your service, good sir", she said.

"Anytime", smiled Tony.

"Hey" called Lizzie as he walked away."Do you.... wanna get some ice cream by any chance ?"

"Ice cream ?"

"Yeah, I really don't wanna go back to work and it's a nice day and...... you know what, never mind, it was stupid."

"No, no. I'd love some ice cream."

The two friends hopped in the decomposing car and arrived at the ice cream shop in minutes. They sat on the bonnet of the car eating ice cream.

"So what do you do for a living ?", asked Lizzie.

"Well I was trying to get my art business off the ground in Paris but- things got in the way and....... here I am."

"Huh. Well you can always try and start it up here. It is the concrete jungle where dreams are made of, you know. There's nothing you can't do."

"Yeah, I guess. So what about you ? How did you end up disposing of porn folders ?"

"Well I moved to New York to start a new Sex and the City super cool lifestyle where my biggest problems would be picking the right pair of super sexy shoes to go to some super sexy party with my super sexy friends, but that obviously didn't happen and five years later, here I am. Sitting on a car full of my boss's porn eating ice cream with a stranger."

"And what would you like to do ?"

"I mean..... I guess I want to be a writer. Well, I know I want to be a writer, but I guess I wanna pursue it."

"I think you should."

"You do ?", she looked at him hopefully.

"Of course. Life is relatively short. There's literally no point in ending up doing something you don't like doing for the majority of it."

"You know what ?", she smiled. "That's exactly what I'm gonna do. You're a real wise man, you know that Tony ?"

"Well, I try. Have you written anything yet ?"

"I tried to write a random opening paragraph and let things kind've flow from there, but I haven't having a whole lot of flow recently."

"Well go on. Let's hear it."

"Well it's about this dude and he wakes up and his wife is laying next to him and there's a half a pack of playing cards, a coffee jar filled with blood, the drivers seat of their car and their neighbours toupee spread out in front of her and she says there is a reasonable explanation for all of it."

"Sounds........ great."

"It's stupid I know."

"No, no, really. You should do it."

She smiled and looked at her watch.

"Oh, nuts. It's nearly five. I gotta get back to work."

"Oh shit", exclaimed Tony. "I don't have anywhere to stay."

"Hey ! Why don't you stay with me ?", she said enthusaistically. "My roomate just left and I won't be able to pay the rent. It's perfect."

"Really ? You'd be okay with that ? I mean..... I'm a complete stranger. I could be a killer."

"Are you ?"

"No."

"Well then ! I know it's sudden. I didn't mean to sound too eager, but it's  perfect. I need a roommate and you need somewhere to sleep ! How about it ?"

"Why not."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>                                                 Shift Part 1
Tony strolled down the Pont des Arts with his girlfriend, Lily. In Tony's eyes, Lily was the most perfect human being in existence. He was in complete, unbridled ecstasy whenever he so much as saw Lily. She was intelligent, but not so intelligent that it became unmanageable. She was witty, but didn't boast her sense of humour. She was calm, collected, kind-hearted and friendly. And she was the most beautiful woman Tony had ever come across. The two strolled merrily down the bridge and Tony stopped. He knelt down on one knee and produced a shiny ring in a red velvet box. Her brown eyes twinkled with joy. She stood there speechless, her mouth agape.


                                                               -------------------------  


Things took a turn for the grim, however when an erratic, out of control French cyclist veered off course and crashed into Tony, causing him to lunge forward, the ring soaring from his grip. The ring took flight and shot straight into Lily's gaping mouth. The ring became lodged in her throat and she lost the ability to breath. Before Tony could gather himself and perform the Heimlich, Lily fell back from the shock and toppled over the bridge. The particularly vicious Seine swallowed her up. The cyclist remounted his bicycle and sped off into the distance. Tony stood there, in utter disbelief of the tragedy that had befallen him.


                                                              ----------------------------



Tony had wandered home, filled with fury. He had just been on top of the world and suddenly, because of one uneasy cyclist, had that all taken from him in mere seconds. Tony had gone to the police station and provided a detailed description of the perpetrator of this heinous act. It turns out, this particular bike enthusiast had a history of hit and run incidents. His name was Pierre Velo. Tony had also paid a visit to the local firearms shop and bought himself some weapons. Tony had one thing to do and that was to avenge the death of his wife to be no matter what. He would take down Pierre the Sadistic Cyclist if it killed him. Tony meaningfully threw a knife at a hand drawn picture of Pierre's likeness that Tony had sketched himself.


                                                                 -------------------------

 

Tony's mission for vengeance took him to New York where he was currently tailing Pierre through a dark alleyway. Tony followed him at a safe distance. Pierre ducked into the side door of a large, plain warehouse. Tony ran up to the small, metal door. He braced himself. Whatever secrets Pierre the Sadistic Cyclist had, whatever had driven him to committing all those hit and runs was behind this door. Tony pushed open the door and stepped inside. His knees turned to jelly at the sight of what was inside the warehouse. Pierre cycled across the warehouse and joined a group of identical Pierres cycling in perfect formation across the empty warehouse. Standing on a stage above the hundreds of Sadistic Cyclist Clones was another identical Pierre, except he was taller and broader and was straddling a larger bicycle. Tony sneaked up to the stage and confronted the seven foot cyclist.

"Who are you, human ?", boomed the biker.

"What is all this ? Who are you ?", gasped Tony.

"I am Pierre, King of the Sadistic Cyclists", proclaimed Pierre.

"You. You killed my fiancee."

"Actually Pierre number 217 did, but that's the general idea, yes. Pierre is one, Pierre is all."

"What are you doing ? How is this possible ? Why did you kill Lily ?"

"We are cleansing the earth. Removing the disease that is man, and replacing them with a flawless species: Pierres. One hit and run at a time."

Before Tony could respond, the ground beneath his feet opened into a dark, metal chasm. Tony fell down the metal pipe until he landed in a dusty old chamber filled with rusty old road signs and several, thin, sickly looking people in shackles. They didn't seem to notice Tony until he spoke.

"Hey !", whispered Tony.

They all looked at him blankly.

"How is all this even possible ? Why are you down here ?"

"We're like you", said one of them in a raspy voice.

"Like me ?"

"We've all lost loved ones to a Pierre, followed them here and gotten imprisoned here forever."

"Why didn't they just kill us like they did with my fiancee ?"

"Apparently we have to be killed in a hit and run incident or not at all."

A Pierre came down the steps into the chamber carrying shackles for Tony. As the Pierre cycled toward him, Tony picked up a twisted, old stop sign and and held it out in front of him. The Sadistic Cyclist stopped dead in it's tracks. It looked as though it were trying to move, but couldn't. The prisoners gasped, wide eyed, at Tony.

"What ?", asked Tony.

"It's the chosen one", whispered one of the prisoners.

"The chosen one ?", chortled Tony.

"It was fabled that a prophet would come in the form of a prisoner and rid the world of the Pierres and free the prisoners. I never believed it would actually happen."

"And how exactly would the chosen go about doing this ?"

"It was rumoured that they would would have the power to take advantage of their biggest weakness. Road signs."

Tony planted the stop sign in the ground and the Pierre stayed put, vibrating from constraint. Tony found a burnt out motorbike have covered in dirt. Tony touched the handlebars and it roared to life. He straddled the motorbike and picked up the stop sign and swung it at the Pierre. It's head rolled onto the ground and the body exploded and sparks and smoke plumed from the charred robotic body. Tony then slashed the prisoners chains open, setting them free. Tony rode up the stairs to the rest of the Pierres. The prisoners escaped out the metal door. All the Pierres immediately started towards him. He planted the stop sign and they all ceased. Another group of them crept up behind him and Tony waved a red traffic light at them. A third group came at him and Tony picked up the stop sign and traffic lights so the whole legion of Pierres were chasing him. He put a 'cycle track this way' sign beside the pit he had fell through on the stage and continued back down. All the Pierres toppled into the pit, one by one, causing a cacophony of electrical explosions emanating from the hole.

"NO. It can't be !", exclaimed Pierre, King of the Sadistic Cyclists.
Tony threw the stop sign at the King. It pierced his chest, causing him to malfunction and spark. Tony then produced his rifle and shot several rounds into the King. He too toppled into the pit. Tony turned, relieved it was over and walked out of the warehouse.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ATM abortions ..... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That bit is there....... at the bottom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feminism at it's finest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh dear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Short and sweet. Nice job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's okay...... this was taken three years ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's a picture of my dog sleeping sitting upright </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When will Indiana Jones 5 be out ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They'll never be the same again...... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 12:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
