<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1614</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RadioBio Podcast sits down with Chris Amemiya from from the Benaroya Research Institute and discusses comparative genomics and its uses for both medical and bio technical fields. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RadioBio Podcast sits down with Chris Amemiya from from the Benaroya Research Institute and discusses comparative genomics and its uses for both medical and bio technical fields </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RadioBio Podcast sits down with Chris Amemiya from from the Benaroya Research Institute and discusses comparative genomics and its uses for both medical and bio technical fields. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RadioBio Podcast sits down with Chris Amemiya from from the Benaroya Research Institute and discusses comparative genomics and its uses for both medical and bio technical fields. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RadioBio Podcast sits down with Chris Amemiya from from the Benaroya Research Institute and discusses comparative genomics and its uses for both medical and bio technical fields. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in my mind that applying for graduate school is not the same thing as applying for undergraduate: you aren't applying for a position at the university but for a position within a lab. 

The bare minimum a PIs look for a good student with good GRE, GPA, and a great personal statement. What is the real clincher is what you have on your CV: what experience do you have and how can you help out the lab. 

Did you make any meaningful progress in the research you accomplished? What does being active in college mean? What skills did you pick up in industry? 

Applying to graduate school is similar to marketing: know how to sell yourself and who you are selling yourself to. Know the field you want to work in, know if your potential PI is interested in picking up students, and know how soon you can start working potentially for your potential PI. Think about what you'd want to do with your degree, and what the program you are applying to is like. 

Let me know if there are any other questions you want answers to maybe i can help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of big bang vs. creationism there is a documentary done by PBS called Nova- "Intelligent Design on trial" which describes a supreme court trial where the two sides debated if intelligent design is a science and if it should be taught in school. They also discuss how intelligent design stems from creationism. The documentary is two hours long, but does a good job of explaining the arguments presented for a general audience. It breaks things down point by point and refutes the best points that creationists/intelligent designers had during this trial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its going to sound annoying but a lot of earning the undergrad degree is dealing with stuff for the sake of stuff. The optimistic way to look at it is figuring out how its relevant to what you're doing. From what I've seen from this post just focus on making it through calc so you can get past physics for the bio degree requirement. Statistics and Pre-calcu with the problem solving is way more important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glucose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who likes to homebrew beer, and has a good understanding of the molecular basis of alcoholic fermentation articles like this is fun to read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people are familiar with genetics as having to do with DNA or with genes. Make sure they understand what DNA is and what gene regions within DNA are. The easiest form of epigenetics for people to understand in my opinion is how DNA is packaged around histones and how histone remodeling fits in with gene expression so the rest of my post will be about that.
 
I'd start out by stating saying that epigenetics is a form of regulating gene expression, but not at the DNA level. Tell them to imagine DNA being millions of nucleotides long, and that in order for them to be stored in space as small a cell requires them to be packaged in a special way by proteins called histones. Tell them to think of histones and DNA like a yoyo: The DNA is the string and it wraps itself around the histone. Much like the yoyo the String can be completely wrapped around the yoyo or it can be completely unwrapped around the yoyo. When the DNA is unwrapped around the histone the gene regions can be read and expressed and when the DNA is wrapped around the histone the genes cannot be read. 

There are proteins that wrap/unwrap the DNA around the histones and they know which histones to work on due to chemical modifications done to the histone. These chemical markers are part of a histone code and understanding where and why they are added to specific histones is an active part of investigation in epigenetics at the moment.

Sorry for the lengthy response, but its complicated to explain to people. Let me know if there are more areas that I can clarify. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of math you require depends on the field of biology you are thinking about entering. While Math may be problematic the lessons from it are very useful when applied to biology: think about how you want to solve the problem, plan out your steps, apply methods you know to find an answer, show your work, and check your answer to make sure you don't find a mistake. You'd be surprised how much stuff outside of your intended field serve as powerful lessons. 

If you intend to to become a molecular biologist you may be working with bioinformatic or molecular dynamic programs to find the answers you are looking for in your research. These tools may utilize pre-calc, calculus, and statistics.

Don't be intimidated by math. I also had some problems in high school and during undergrad, but I got some help and did a lot of practice problems. I was surprised when matrices from pre-calc  became relevant in my research.

TLDR; If this is what you are passionate about think about how you can apply what you have learned to solving the problem , ask for help whenever you can get it, and expect things to reappear at some point in your career.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me try and answer some of your questions point by point....

cells are able to detect overpopulation, but its not necessarily through telomere length. Imagine you are at the movie theatre and all the seats are filled. You wouldn't sit on a  stranger's lap if the movie is sold out: you would effectively remove your self from the theatre so the intended audience size can watch the movie undisturbed. Now in a situation of cancer cells imagine a drunk person were to walk into this same scenario: their inhibitions are now gone and they don't care if they have to watch this movie sitting on some stranger's lap. They will just sit down even thought its bothering the people around them. 

Your cells treat the telomere length much like you would treat the expiration date of food at the supermarket. Some cells are meant to have a limited shelf life over others.  

In some cancer cells they prolong their life by inducing the expression of telomerase. Similar to the Mr. Meeseeks from rick and morty show cells can start acting weird if they dont eventually die. They can accumulate mutations which may alter how the cells behave and may eventually become cancerous. So in terms of fighting cancer we would want to stop or prevent cells from using telomerase.

Slowing down the aging process is complicated because the cell needs not only to keep its telomeres a certain length, but conserve the gene coding regions (make sure mutations don't occur). 

Telomere research is useful for gathering information regarding chromosomal disorders, shelf life of differentiated cells, and how they function in stem cells. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
