<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9647</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I was living out of it for two months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it! Take baby steps. Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize I worded the title weirdly. This stuff was from Walmart and Target. I went to Ulta about an hour or so ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Magic of Purses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purses make lifting so much fucking easier than you can imagine. Sometimes I feel like I have a bag like Mary Poppins.  No one suspects a thing when a woman goes into a store with a huge, slouchy purse slung over her shoulder. My purse has a crossbody strap that frees up both my hands and makes things even easier. As long as you're confident, you can slip small items into your bag without even being in a blind spot. Just keep walking and looking forward, not down at your hands or up at the ceiling trying to find cameras. I have grown a lot in my lifting skills and one of the best things to do in your blind spot is just take the items and fucking drop them in your purse. You can't even hesitate for a second, and it should be one quick, smooth movement. That's the key to success.

Fuck, I love my purse... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear god, no. My asshole isn't that big.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take that as a compliment...most of the larger items I took from Target. I just did a simple push-out with them hidden under my purse. My purse is fucking huge. Then, I got some other items from Walmart...I dropped them in my gigantic purse in a blind spot and then strolled happily to the register and bought a coke. Made friends with the cashier too. Her name was Estrella. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nooo, this was all from Walmart and Target. I went to Ulta at like 8:00. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I went to Ulta a little while ago. The brushes are AMAZING. And no RFID. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I was very lucky today. I lifted over $500 total, from Walmart, rue21, Old Navy, Ulta, Barnes and Noble, and Target. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
