<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5136</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 22:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In another thread, I responded to:

Oil is traded on the dollar. A weaker dollar will mean oil is more "expensive"

With

It's the opposite...

Because global buyers have to convert local currency to dollars.  Stronger dollar means oil is more expensive for global buyers, demand decreases, price of oil decreases.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 21:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/energy_trading/comments/4cvclg/0401clk6/d1ls1w3

Rode that until a few days back, now I'm short, and a little down on it but have a stop in place.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 21:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't trade equities.  And I have an answer.  But from the responses there are clearly many in here who don't know the effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 21:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What effect on S/D?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 21:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What effect does that have when the dollar strengthens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 21:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a Bernie Sanders supporter?  I had no idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relationship of Dollar and Oil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 21:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was having a debate with a basement dweller a little bit ago who wouldn't listen to reason.

The dollar and the price of oil are strongly negatively correlated.  What is the reason for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 20:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oil is traded on the dollar. A weaker dollar will mean oil is more "expensive"

[Using recent advances in panel data estimation techniques, we find that an appreciation of the US dollar exchange rate leads to a significant decline in oil demand for a sample of 65 oil-importing countries.](https://www.ecb.europa.eu/events/pdf/conferences/mopo_commodity/peersman.pdf?4f6b917a3a688b180d589de9ac1f6170)

Empirical data shows that you are 100% wrong.  We have established that the price of oil and ~~demand~~ the dollar are inversely related. The price of oil, fundamentally, is affected either by supply or demand.  When the price of the dollar goes up, which side of the equation does that affect?

You should probably get out of your mom's basement and take Econ 101 before talking about big boy stuff.

Edit dollar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 20:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not going to try to understand one of the most basic fundamentals of the oil market and the petro-dollar?

[Using recent advances in panel data estimation techniques, we find that an appreciation of the US dollar exchange rate leads to a significant decline in oil demand for a sample of 65 oil-importing countries.](https://www.ecb.europa.eu/events/pdf/conferences/mopo_commodity/peersman.pdf?4f6b917a3a688b180d589de9ac1f6170)



Oil is priced in dollars on the world market. When the dollar is weaker, foreign currencies are stronger, by definition. That means people in other countries can buy more oil for the same amount of money. So let's assume oil is $100 per barrel, and $100 is equal to 70 euros. If the euro appreciates against the dollar by 10 percent, then instead of 70 euros it will take only 63 euros to buy one barrel of oil. So that oil becomes cheaper to foreigners, and they can buy more. And do they buy more?

Usually, yes. There are other factors obviously, like in many countries taxes are such a big portion of the cost of oil that the savings aren't that dramatic. But it would still make sense to buy more if the price in your own currency goes down. So for those of us stuck with the dollar, why does that make the price of oil or gasoline go up?

http://money.usnews.com/money/blogs/flowchart/2008/03/10/why-gas-prices-rise-as-the-dollar-falls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 19:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't tell if you are serious...

If you are, my comment from elsewhere:

Oil is traded on the world market in dollars, which means that countries have to convert local currency to dollars to buy in the global markets. When the dollar is strengthening it makes oil more expensive, thus decreasing demand.

For example, for simple purposes let's say the exchange rate for a country is 100 currencies to $1. The means the can buy one barrel of WTI for $40 * 100/$1 = 4000 currencies.

Tomorrow, the dollar strengthens to to 101 to $1. You now buy one barrel of WTI for $40 * 101/$1 = 4040 currencies.

[Chart](http://i.imgur.com/KlBt4eN.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 18:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the opposite... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 17:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The market seems to be reacting very negatively to the EIA numbers, which were not that bad and better than the forecast. Only thing worse was the gasoline inventories. Sadly for you, UWTI just hit 28.10 and it could be a start of a down-trend. Although the EIA and other data have not been that negative and it could stay between $43 and $45 this week.

+1.6 gasoline build vs. -0.4 API on a 88.1 refinery run rate I don't view as better than forecast, [but buyers area massively abundant.](http://i.imgur.com/DjUNILP.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 17:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting time to buy... 15 minutes before the report.

I'm going to give you a few charts, interpret as you will.

[MM](http://i.imgur.com/DjUNILP.jpg)

[Crude Stocks](http://i.imgur.com/wAcjCVW.png)

[Distillates (this is what your fam does)](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/ChDoTplXEAACAUC.jpg)

[Imports](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/ChDqD7iWUAAloOW.jpg:large) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 04:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Know a guy that used to work there. I think the regulations aren't there in Canada nor the US for commercial livestock feed, but these guys are getting there. Brad and Glen from enviroflight are good friends. Glen just did a Tedx talk.

I also don't think they are quite at cost competitiveness with what they aim to compete with - fish meal, soybean meal. 

By expensive they are trying to fully automated the facility. From what I've heard their VC backers pushed them to scale before they were ready.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gartman Nailing It Again! Long Manziel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 21:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you checked ZH?  They probably have 20-30 reasons they are gloating about calling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 19:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the Voldemort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 23:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried PP?  They provide very low cost visits for people who can't afford to see a GP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 23:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Rand a lot as far as conservatives go, and I think this could be a solid plan, but what really worries me is the "Obama's war on coal" bullshit followed shortly by "regulation cuts" from these zones.

NG and general market forces have taken the market from coal, MATS regulations did very little to shut down the coal plants which have been decommissioned in the past few years.  MATS regulations were a conservative scapegoat.  I've yet to see a model for deregulated nuclear plants, and nuclear should be baseload electricity for the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 00:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are long 10 lots?  Is that what this is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 23:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $SUNE has strong support at$0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 20:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Actually, none of those links are broken, and the statistics you've cited have no basis in reality.

*According to some guy's totally unbiased blogs based on his opinions from footnotes of a World Bank Report.  

He has no problem quoting the Economist, who admits that the 10.9% is high, but:

Yet, despite these self-imposed brakes, Ethiopias economic progress has been spectacular. Its growth rate, if the latest official figure of 11% is true, is the fastest in Africa; and even the lower figure of around 8%, which the IMF and many Western analysts prefer, is still very perky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 00:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half his links are broken, and most of his arguments simply point to the margin of error in the statistics.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 22:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite a few years.

Brutalization in Africa is hardly rare, and has been significantly less in Ethiopia, especially recently, than neighboring, non-Communist countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 22:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every day there's a handful of articles about how Venezuela's economy is failing.

Ethiopia is a communist government who has the strongest growth rate in the world.  They are also handling one of the worst droughts in their history remarkably well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 21:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a country without direct federal ballot initiatives, wouldn't 

when you vote for a candidate, you may or may not be voting for that candidate for that one particular issue.

directly dispute

There's no way to convince people who don't pay income tax to vote to reduce income tax </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 21:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hate to break up the circle jerk, but maybe let's look at Ethiopia.  I'm not condoning communism by any means, but:

In 2013/14, Ethiopias economy grew by 10.3%, making the country one of Africas top performing economies and this strong growth is expected to continue in 2015 and 2016.

Owing to a co-ordinated prudent fiscal and monetary policy stance, inflation has been contained to single digits since 2013.

Federalism and devolution of power to the regions are paving the way to overcoming geographic and socio-economic barriers to inclusive growth and structural transformation.

A communist country has one of the strongest growth rates and industrialization in Africa.  And who's next door?  (Somalia = libertarian paradise is about as legitimate as Venezuela = socialist paradise) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 21:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good info, thx.  Any specific plays with those numbers, or somewhat standard across?

 Again, that doesn't factor in the dry holes we drill that are complete losses

Have you seen that % come down recently?  I ask because I know at least 5 startups locally (CO) that are working on that specifically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 20:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, [they very well may have nailed this one,](http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2016-04-16/big-move-coming) although I don't think the result will be of consul for OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 18:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the marginal cost of a bbl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 17:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was actually the opposite.   And there was a response from someone else who copy and pasted the question to the AMA.

https://www.reddit.com/r/Anarcho_Capitalism/comments/4f7i7k/rscience_bans_and_silences_scientific_dissent_in/d275qpo

 Thanks for this (lengthy) comment. It neatly encapsulates the key flaw of criticisms of Cook et al. (2013) - the unwillingness of critics to consider the self-rating survey that replicated the 97% consensus. To my knowledge, every criticism of our research has studiously avoided the self-rating replication.
To give a quick overview of Cook et al. (2013) (freely available at http://sks.to/tcppaper), we first estimated the scientific consensus by categorising the abstracts of scientific papers about global warming. We identified ~4000 abstracts stating a position on human-caused global warming - amongst those abstracts, 97.1% endorsed the consensus.
Next, and here is the crucial part that every critic of our paper has conveniently ignored or avoided, we replicated our result by inviting the authors of the scientific papers to rate their own research. If we had mis-characterised a significant number of papers (e.g., rated them as endorsing AGW when they didn't), then there would've been a significant discrepancy between our abstract rating and the self-rating. 1200 scientists responded to our invitation, resulting in over 2000 papers receiving a self-rating. Amongst papers that were self-rated as stating a position on human-caused global warming, 97.2% endorsed the consensus.
However, when you dug deeper into the data, there was one significant discrepancy between self-ratings and our abstract ratings. More than half of the abstracts that we rated as "no position" were subsequently rated as "endorsing AGW" by the paper's own authors. So in contrast to this commenter's characterisation that we characterised papers as endorsing when they were not, quantitative analysis reveals we were actually much more likely to go the other way - characterising papers that did endorse AGW as expressing "no position" on AGW. However, the reason for this was relatively straightforward. Abstract ratings were based solely on the abstract text while self-ratings were based on the full paper, which were more likely to include an endorsement of AGW simply for space reasons.
The self-ratings also present another key statistic that I don't recall ever being mentioned by a critic of our study. Amongst papers that were self-rated as stating a position on whether humans were causing most of global warming, around 96% endorsed the consensus. So Cook et al. (2013) found that regardless of the definition used, there was overwhelming scientific agreement with the consensus position.
It's significant that critics of our study refuse to take a step back and look at the full study, with independent methods replicating the finding of an overwhelming consensus on climate change. Further, they refuse to take that extra step back and see how our finding of overwhelming consensus is replicated by a range of independent studies. That is the key result of the new "consensus on consensus" study - that the scientific consensus is robust and replicated across many studies. This new study is freely available at http://sks.to/coc
-- John Cook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 22:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like glaciers between Stella's and Uhuru?  [Here's mine from August.](http://i.imgur.com/VmsQHJE.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 18:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YUMA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 04:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However, Verizon is a large company and its revenues were $659 billion for these years, as told by the annual reports. Verizon, therefore, paid an effective tax rate of 1/2 of 1%. (We didnt even bother to check whether Verizon paid $3.4 billion for those six years.)

Effective tax rate is not % of revenue. They didn't even look at EBITDA. Some facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 23:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did your mom make you for lunch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 23:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crazy day.  I expected a little algo drop on 10+ build.  

Cash prices strong. 

I have the y/y surplus coming in by 250 by end of April.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 03:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you doing is this sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 22:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the libertarian debate, Johnson said he took the quiz on his site.  His first match was himself, second was Sanders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 21:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not disagreeing with Panama Papers and wealthy, private citizens hiding from taxes, but would laundering money from child and other sex slavery be legal in a libertarian world?  Also, a bunch of this money was stolen by government officials, from private citizens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 21:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only do they have articles, [but they will soon be *only* articles.](http://www.npr.org/sections/thetwo-way/2015/10/13/448182158/playboy-magazine-to-stop-publishing-nude-images) (Actually just not nude photos). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 19:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Slaughtering takes place in front of the animals, usually with a club to induce the pain and fear that restaurant owners claim makes their adrenaline-rich meat tastier." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 15:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You argue that there is some kind of "abnormal" warming. For something to be "abnormal", there must, by definition, be a "normal".

Abnormal being the the excess warming which would not have happened without the CO2 emissions... 

The empirical data is the empirical data. There was no warming for almost two decades. Some scientists played around with deep ocean temperature data and claim that they found the missing warming.

[Flat out wrong](http://data.giss.nasa.gov/gistemp/graphs_v3/), and you only get this if you cherry pick the data through 2014.  But 2015 changed all that, not sure how you are still using this talking point.

It's insane. If any other hard science field such as physics, chemistry, or biology was able to cling to a theory that has time and time again led to predictions that were false, it would be a laughingstock of a field.

Because even if some scientists still want to cling to AGW as a legitimate scientific theory, the theory must be amended to account for new information.

Please link to scientific papers showing the models as a whole have been massively wrong.  Of course they will reassess factors when new information becomes available.  That in no way means AGW is wrong.

 The fact that you think that microbial evolution is not going to be a significant factor in how the Earth's climate will handle increased amounts of carbon dioxide tells me how little you understand about ecology.

More of this vague wanna-be science, with the "you totally don't understand ecology like me, man."

Ultimately, this is coming down to a matter of faith.

It's hilariously ironic that you mention faith.  In the US at least, the majority of the folks who don't understand AGW are religious people. The believe in supernatural forces told by preachers who also deny evolution and believe the Earth is a few thousand years old, yet not scientists who dedicate their lives to empirical evidence.

But keep parroting the "science". I'll enjoy cheap, abundant energy and so will my fellow countrymen in one of the most impoverished parts of the world as we grow our economies and increase our standard of living.

And there it is.  You come to the conclusion that coal is good, then go back to the science and try (poorly) to find holes.  But that's fine, I do believe that developed nations should be taking the lead towards cleaner energy, and can lead by model by vastly expanding incredibly clean, incredibly cheap energy - nuclear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 19:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You keep on talking about science, but when I ask for specific scientific literature, you mention Popper's fasifiability, which completely misunderstands the models and the previous attempts to disprove the science.

"human activity causes global warming" is also not disprovable.

Absolutely disprovable.  Find the factor that's responsible for the abnormal warming.  

There has been no warming for a decade and a half (arguably two decades).

Debunked.  Next you are going to talk about how scientists were talking about global cooling in the 60's

The IPCC models were wrong.

Plenty of peer reviewed scientific literature saying that the IPCC models underestimate the potential warming.

a disproof of a claim that is not disprovable.

You don't understand the science, so you continually come back to the claim that the theory isn't disprovable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 23:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, point me to the peer reviewed literature which disproves anthropogenic global warming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 22:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All those stupid scientists can keep their mathematics and statistics.  Us smarties looks at things like horizontal gene transfer for climate science. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 21:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but smart people 

Hilarious.  Are you a parody account? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 16:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree, meant more rightist initiatives/solutions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 16:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long UWTI from 19.00 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will it be a Make or Break Summer for Appalachia Production? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 14:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will it be a Make or Break Summer for Appalachia Production? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 14:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 00:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gotten stopped out being short a few times in the past few weeks trading NG, not the greatest month of trading, but made some really nice trades in CL which made up.  Some updated things I'm looking at for shoulder season:

Weather correlation to shoulder is fairly low, I haven't been looking too much at the 1-15 days models, but demand a decent amount above normal.  

Production has been flat, and I think a little will drop off going forward due to capex cuts the past year, and some possible bankruptcies.  y/y: .7 b/d to LNG exports, 1 b/d Mexports, probably .5-1.5 b/d from Canada less puts pretty tight supply wise.

Good consensus on a hot La Nina summer.  Same ideas as before about hydro, wind, solar.

The market will price us for EOS from 3800-4000 tcf.  I think there will be a little more push down, but bullish mid-summer to next winter. 

But look at last shoulder season last year - Late April, NG was 50 cents higher, producers had much higher hedges, with a looser S/D and the looming notion of an El Nino cool summer, warm winter. It then proceeded to rally 70 cents.  So I'm on the sidelines for now, looking to buy dips at technical points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 00:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to hear some rightist policy initiatives.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 00:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... what court will the Maldives sue in?  And who will they sue?

Who has dominion over the Great Barrier Reef and the fisheries which will be crashing from the bleached corals habitat being destroyed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 19:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would be your proposed solution to the global markets mispricing energy production? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 19:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Capitalism and free markets are not the problem that need to be regulated to quell AGW.

I think capitalism and markets are absolutely the solution, if energy production is properly priced.  

The problem that needs to be regulated is the human population itself...

While I don't necessarily disagree with population being out of control and a culling would help the problem, poor countries have tiny emissions per capita, and much of the development work, at least where I've been involved, is focused on non-fossil fuel energy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 18:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe from libertarians who don't deny AGW, and believe that a solution would have to be pricing carbon into the markets on a global scale? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 18:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read what you posted before you edited. 

Plenty of people looking into externalities, I've yet to see a meta analysis where the positives outweigh the negatives.  

Edit: Man, you are the king of ghost editing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 18:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well, that's sort of the whole fight though isn't it?

100% is not the whole fight, not even part of it.  The fight is whether climate change is real.  Once we get past that, we can start talking about solutions.  Unfortunately one side of the debate brings snowballs onto the Senate floor to disprove AGW.  Until that ridiculous mentality stops being at the forefront, there will be no logical debate on solutions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 17:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Global warming is a global issue.  One of the most common arguments I hear is *if we cut emissions that doesn't mean China will.* Wouldn't a global trading scheme be the only way to solve that problem?

If CO2 emissions do have a negative monetary effect, how is this not a failure of the free market by mis-pricing?  Wouldn't a properly institued trading scheme properly price energy production? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 14:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I received a multi-cooker from extended family member for Christmas, and already having a slow cooker, rice cooker, stove top pressure cooker, and yogurt maker, wasn't overly excited. But then I started using it, and was very happy.  If you wash basmati rice really well, it makes perfect sticky rice - better than my rice cooker.  I haven't tried the paella style, but will soon.  The pressure cooking setting works great, and you can brown before slow cooking.  I'm not an expert with yogurt making but seemed to do a good job.  My only complaints are it's a little small for slowcooking, and it's very noisy when cooking rice.  I think mine is Presto brand?  I'll check later.

OP - When moving into your own place, I highly suggest as many multi-items as possible.  It gives you extra room in your kitchen, and much easier when you are packing up the kitchen and moving.  I made that mistake, and now I'm trying to get rid of things I never use that are filling up my kitchen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 17:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "I'm actually in the oil industry/representing the oil industry and using futures contracts as intended."

Published every Tuesday from the previous Friday.  Do you really not know what the CoT is? Edit: And please explain the intended purpose of futures contracts.

If I'm reading you correctly, you're factoring in that "trading just to trade" crowd as part of S/D by default

What I'm saying with deliverability is: If there futures contract price is that out of whack with the physical markets, physical players will make or take delivery.  And this does happen, more often in softs and metals than energy.  That hints at something.

Here's the way see it and why I don't think my "no reason to have fallen 80%" comment isn't really out of line.

There's too much oil being produced, not enough being used; simple as that.  It has to be priced out of the market.  80% decline appears to have had some effect, and there was, without a question, a reason why prices fell 80%.

You keep on using the word sheep.  I think you need to learn a little more about energy markets before you continue throwing that word around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 16:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's better for both parties.  Let the Libertarian promote libertarian candidates, and have someone in the Republican party who can hopefully bring them back closer to what they have traditionally stood for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 13:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boudreaux would definitely earn an A if this is how we are judging.  He uses vague analogies, misleading statistics, and undefended assumptions.

This article is really poorly written and defended.  I try not to read the NYT, but can't imagine it being that much worse than this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 19:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Could you PM me your channel as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 23:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your view is that the current price is "correct"....which is impossible, because the fundamentals in both time frames were virtually the same.

I guess we disagree with what fundamentals are.  But, I would wholeheartedly disagree with every word in this statement:

There's also no good reason it should have lost 80% of it's value in nine months either. It's all trading desk driven speculation and sheep following sheep. Trying to retroactively apply actual energy market fundamentals to it or rationalize the movement will just leave you dazed and confused.

There were plenty of reasons for it to lose 80% of it's value, massive amounts of reasons.  It's "trading desk driven" not only from HFT and other trading desks, but from physical cash transactions driven by direct S/D, with speculation in there of course. Applying actual energy market fundamentals to it absolutely sheds light to the crazy S/D imbalance.  There are certainly sheep, but there were plenty of people that saw the imbalance and made ungodly amounts of money in both oil and NG.

My one and only point is that prices are a function of trading pressure moving them for trading gains, not a result of fundamentals.

You don't think that trading pressure comes from fundamentals?  You do know that every major futures contract has deliverability, right?  You do know that physical oil trades flat price elsewhere, and against non-futures benchmarks other places, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 21:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, I'm not sure what you're not looking at that you believe there wasn't something in the fundamentals that justified an 80% price drop.  I would actually argue that the s/d imbalance *not* changing in the past 1.5 years is exactly what justified that kind of price swing.  Do you really believe there isn't an imbalance that led to almost every storage medium close to filling?

[S/D balance over time period](http://i.imgur.com/O3Ri3EE.png)

[Crude stocks.](http://i.imgur.com/9bXsEdx.png)

I'm seriously baffled.  What do you consider fundamentals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 16:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a silly position.  Just because you don't understand the market fundamentals doesn't mean there aren't any.  The world is awash in not only crude oil, but also gasoline, distillates, NGLs.

You seriously believe there isn't any good reason to lose 80% of it's value?  Disclosure: I'm short CL now, from ~40 on K6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 00:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where was Inglis mentioned?

While there are a few outsiders, the overwhelming majority of the GOP hasn't made it anywhere where close to the nuance levels of climate sensitivity the person I responded to suggested, and the conversation is dominated by Inhofe's bullshit, and Cruz's ridiculous Senate hearings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 23:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So which of those questions is Inhofe asking when he brings a snowball to the Senate floor?  Or when Republicans say AGW isn't real because God controls the climate?  While you may understand the nuance, conservatives are straight black and white. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 22:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do appreciate the response, but you are suggesting the libertarian solution is deregulate and get the government out, and maybe it might improve?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 21:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When one side can't get past the "natural patterns" and "well have you looked at the sun? It's hot!" or "what about volcanoes?" then we can't possess any of that knowledge.  We can't get to a debate about how to deal with it, because one side's "science experts" are politicians who bring snowballs out in winter.

Seriously, look at this thread.  Would you consider some of the folks climate deniers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 21:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I agree with you on two of the points - racism, private funding - in your original comment, I think it was absolutely ridiculous to include AGW in that list.  On the one side, there are scientists who devote their lives to studying climate, spend every day looking at every factor in the climate warming.  Then there's the other side, bringing a fucking snowball onto the Senate floor in winter. Just look at the comments in this thread.  

Was just pointing out the ridiculousness of the list your created in your original comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 21:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet you care enough to complain about liburls yelling at people calling them "climate deniers" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 20:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discourse is impossible because politicians are denying the science, not because "the left is just shouting out anyone who disagrees with the positions."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 20:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If we subsidize the wind/solar company to bridge that cost per hour gap, we have given no incentive to that company to innovate and we could ultimately end up with less efficient technologies overall.

Or, like recent years have shown, after subsidizing you end up with technologies that are incredibly cost efficient (nuclear), and technologies that are very close to be cost efficient and dispatachable (intermittent renewables with battery backup).  The alternative could be that these technologies simply go bankrupt and nowhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 20:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Don't support free money for alternative energy? You are a climate change denier.

Or, you know, claim AGW doesn't exit, you are a climate change denier.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 20:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea how I missed one paragraph out of the total 4 in the article. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 19:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So would this boat supply power to a grid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 19:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [James Lawrence Powell found a much higher acceptance, 99%+. Here's his methodology. Pick some holes in it.](http://www.jamespowell.org/methodology/newmethodology.html)

Now it's likely that had those papers that had mentioned no position either way would have had a majority of authors saying that humans have a large role in climate change, but it does no service to anyone to obscure these details when trying to look at things in an objective light.

[Endorsement in scientific literature](http://www.jamespowell.org/methodology/Endorsement/endorsement.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 18:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Remove all regulations that make it harder to start a business.

I always hear "remove regulations," what specific regulations do you suggest getting rid of that will help alternative energy, efficiency companies, etc. 

2. Remove unnecessary regulations on nuclear power. 

I do think nuclear is absolutely key if we want to do anything about climate change, but what specific regulations are unnecessary?

3. Get rid of all subsidies... even for clean energy companies. 

Unfortunately fossil fuels have had decades of subsidies to help them get way ahead.  And without externalities priced into the system, there's no free market to take care of the problem.

The reduction of greenhouse gases can only be accomplished through free enterprise. The left thinks government can stop climate change, but all government will do is destroy individual freedom while doing very little to actually prevent climate change.

Agree with the first, but without the externalities priced into the market, markets won't take care of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 18:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, let's silence dissenting opinion and turn this place into more of a circlejerk than it already is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 23:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would an alternative be structured?  More state focused?  Or what would private sector look like?  Serious question, as I believe environmental concern is a big thing for a lot of prospective here.  I've heard the private organizations are better at conservation because of one or two examples on a few acres, or people would take care of private property because why wouldn't they, which I think are very shaky arguments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 12:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I lived in Chengdu, there was one guy on one bridge who had a machine like this, but the final product was crunchy and tasted exactly like golden grahams.  One day he was gone, and I never found him or anything like it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 20:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The funniest is when people talk about gaps to be filled the levered ETNs.  Why the fuck would a product twice removed from the underlying then levered need to fill a fucking gap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is why biofuels are theoretically a renewable energy source, even if there hasn't been much success of that in practice.

What do you mean by this?

Sugarcane ethanol is vastly more efficient than corn ethanol, and can definitely be considered a renewable energy source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 13:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /NG is in a tough place now.  Ending the season with 2400+ ( in storage, a record and should keep a cap on any significant strength - ICE swap EOD 2440/2490 (2470 settle) as of yesterday. There could be a one last shot of cold the last week of March, but the difference between 2500 and 2450 in storage won't make a huge difference.  The next few days have record low GWDD for same days, next week's report could see an injection.  

Looking at summer, early analogs for some heat M-Q. But hydro will be much higher yoy - 1998 CA hydro 49.5TWh, 2015 was in the low teens. More coal retirements and build out of NG PB, but also much more wind and solar coming online.

The big decider going forward is production.  I'm of the opinion that there was a lot of hedged and contracted gas for the winter strip, and April should finally see production roll over some.  But it has been incredibly resilient, so dangerous bet.

I was, and still am, starting to get bullish for later in the curve, but I think short front months, build length late summer through winter. But any significant strength will be met with production coming back online, there are plenty of companies ready.  I'm short J at the moment, and probably put on a spread this week or next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 18:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [New Mexico has a similar system.](http://www.hed.state.nm.us/students/lotteryscholarship.aspx) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 17:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The new tax blow is all the more frustrating for the  British government after data emerged recently to show that the Treasury pays more to Facebook for advertising placement than it receives in taxes from the Silicon Valley giant."

Hilarious.  Perfect example of broken window. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 22:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Southern saying she believes it was urine is the reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 22:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to go into it two much because I'm not expert, but my understanding is that biological sex is determined by chromosomes, gender is cultural identity and norms, much of which comes from biological sex.

But besides that, why does she care that much about saying there are just two genders?  This seems way more antagonistic than anything.  It seems that the libertarian movement has gone much more anti-trans/gender/whatever, rather than anti-free speech infringement.  Why do you care what others and a lot of new researchers are defining as genders?

The urine or whatever it was is clearly disgusting and that protester should be ashamed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 22:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Additional references in the Breitbart article too

Only reference I found in the article:

"which Southern later said she believed was urine, over the libertarian commentator." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 21:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I read your comment wrong.  I thought you were implying that "it has been proven that reddit is manipulated by the *liberal media* to push Sanders as a candidate," rather than "social media is manipulated."

Not questioning the second one, I was simply asking for a link if you claimed the first to be true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 21:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We are small gov't, pro-business and anti-establishment. 

You think this is what libertarianism is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 21:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a crosspost from /r/TrumpForPresident or one of those subs about auditing the Feb, since then this sub has been overrun with Trump supporters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 21:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Its been proven many times.

Where? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 16:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure it wasn't urine, the only place that came up was when she said "I hope it's not urine." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 13:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dumping water Lauren was really childish and the two (females) she was talking with probably weren't pleased about it either, but the *attack helicopter* and *science and technology* arguments were pretty ridiculous and didn't really make reasonable debate, and I didn't see many libertarian arguments.

The dragon-kin and other silly 12 year old attention grabbing Tumblr posts get the most attention, but there are legitimate people who don't identify as male or female, and there's plenty of scientific research going into gender identity whether or not folks here agree with it. It's still a very new field of psychology.

Forcing your ideals onto another through the government or attacks on free speech clearly aren't, but why would direct mocking of someone's identity be libertarian?  In the gender part specifically, she kept on calling herself libertarian, but I didn't see many arguments to believe she was a libertarian, all I saw was anti-SJW.  Being anti-SJW in the context of defending free speech is one thing, but just by this video I don't see the libertarian arguments showing up strongly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 16:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Prinskipper Skipple! Uh, Primnickle Skipsker! I found something! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 09:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if I would classify this as luckily. Small percentage increases in unemployment means millions of working aged men unemployed. Millions of unemployed working aged men in large cities has been a hotbed for revolution, especially in repressive regimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 07:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 Rig added, and still near record production.

The 12z GFS runs were brutal.  Perfectly mild everywhere and pattern not great for demand at the end.  There's no atmospheric cold left - patterns similar to last years' high HDD Feb.

Looking at summer, early analogs for some nice heat M-Q.  Hydro much much higher yoy - 1998 CA hydro 49.5TWh, 2015 was in the low teens.  More coal retirements and build out of NG PB, but also much more wind coming online.  

I was, and still am, starting to get bullish for later in the curve, but I think short front months, build length late summer through winter.   If weather and production hold, $1.50 prompt coming soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 18:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in Chengdu 2011.  I wonder how many packs of cigarettes equivalent I smoked, as I saw the sun maybe twice that year. Scary stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
