<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7521</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, how are animals NOT better than children? Animals are sweet and friendly and usually quiet so fuck this bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This person can choke to death. What the actual fuck? Children are some of the dumbest and most annoying things in this earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this is the age of attention seekers. People love praise from random strangers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it really is. So disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! You tell em. This whole kidstagram bullshit should be against the rules honestly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god that is beyond pathetic!! Fucking ridiculous what people will do for money these days. It really goes to the kids' heads too I've noticed 

Edit: fucking not ducking. I meant what I said autocorrect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I agree. It is very dangerous to be plastering their kids' faces all over the web and then sometimes they even check-in at locations! The whole thing is really just sabotage for the kids safety and future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People making ig for their kids? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are people making Instagrams for their kids? It's seems pathetic. Using children to get likes/followers on social media is ridiculous...and then they advertise for prams and bibs or whatever and they have "fans" and people sending them shit. People just eat it right up.

It's honestly just ridiculous and makes the parents look stupid. They are using their child just to take pictures of and as a source of income. Isn't that exploitation? Maybe just let your damn child have a childhood??? Maybe they should get off their damn phone and actually play w the damn child THAT THEY BIRTHED.

Idk how to explain it there's just something so wrong with having a child and using them like that. And it infuriates me that the comments on those pictures are like "baby goals" or just people generally not seeing anything wrong with what those parents are doing. 

Am I making any sense? Anyone agree?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I'm going through the same thing, I don't really have advice but I just want to let you know you're not alone here and I can kind of understand what you're going through.

 I finished 70 straight weeks of chemo in January and have been suffering from terrible depression ever since. Can't work for all the same reasons. I feel exactly the same, I don't enjoy anything anymore and I'm too tired to do anything. 

Hope things will get better for you though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 29 1/2 gift. I loved it so much and was dying for the box so I paid over $300 (bc of tax) for it. I use it to store a lot of my lush and I still have a lot of the products that came in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's possible but I just want to offer my condolences because this has happened to me and it's terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure, I think it's probably the same size as the large ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it so much! It's so pretty I don't even want to open it lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to use the whole bubble bar for most baths, the more bubbles the better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Does this make my butt look big?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep it is quite small. I think it's just for a single use unless you cocktail it. Smells lovely though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 06:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for your kindness. I'm trying to stay positive but I still have little mental breakdowns here and there. But you're right, we have to keep moving along (it's hard for me too ). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
