<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6932</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's making a joke about Ted Cruz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laser fading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of laws are written with gendered language but it's understood that unless specified it's gender-neutral. This bill forces the opposite of that assumption. So, for example, a law that references a "husband and wife" cannot be taken to mean "husband and wife or husband and husband or wife and wife", which means only straight marriage would be accepted as valid for a lot of things, even if gay marriage is is legal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you've described isn't a gay person. They're attracted to people of the opposite sex.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When that denies people their rights to due process or equal treatment under the law, yes, it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like saying that I set the world record for fastest 100m in New York. That's a New York record, not a world record. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And not to be indelicate, but there's a very plausible explanation for that.

More seriously though, the whole point of hormone therapy is that it changes your body, and part of that is changing your muscles. Without testosterone, muscle mass tumbles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that what they call it these days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. It's not just chromosomes. Sex is determined based on chromosomes, internal and external genitals, and a couple of secondary characteristics that don't really hit until puberty. In actual practice the determination is made based on external genitalia; very rarely are chromosomes actually tested.

2. "Unless there is a rare mutation." Such as, perhaps, having a brain physically not what would be expected based on externally visible indicators of sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're just repeating things without explaining them. That's not an argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DSM is a nearly thousand pages long and it's not particularly light reading. And it did make some news at the time but people didn't really care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ACLU-TN Statement on Passage of "LGBT Erasure" Legislation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The APA is a medical association, not a political one. There's plenty of evidence that being trans is not a mental disorder, though you could argue that the research wouldn't happen without some amount of political pressure; the same sort of thing happened before when being gay was considered a mental illness until research showed that it isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing I said would make being gay a choice. You realize gay people can be attracted to straight people, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The World Will Be Watching as Muslim Ban 2.0 Goes to Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So every time you have sex it's to get someone pregnant and never because you enjoy it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It kind of is if you're choosing not to be attracted to someone based on something you can't tell about them without asking. Not saying that's the case here, because this guy specifically sought out a trans woman, but if you find yourself attracted to [someone](https://imgur.com/a/dMpqb) because of something you can't actually tell about them, then that's kind of a choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is about a woman though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's got Kevin Spacey and an amazing soundtrack. I am worried that the rather prominent Subaru doesn't sound very Subaruy in the trailer and that's going to take me out of it. Though if the rest of it is as good as it looks I don't think I'll mind if it isn't super realistic; I love a good heist movie and that seems like it's going to be a big part of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the idea that they did so without even trying to put up a fight is ridiculous. France just wasn't ready for war and their tactics were completely unable to keep up with the German forces at the start of the war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on my limited understanding of /r/kappa, I think they'd love this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solid snek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize that this is a woman, right? And also she did get the help she needed, but by the time they found her laid out on the sidewalk and actually got her to a hospital it wasn't enough. She'd been in ICU for some time, apparently in a coma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Obama_irl](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V4MF2s6MLxY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's worse if you have the reddit comments displayed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [MFW](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nj12LaDvwKA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, adrenaline makes everyone a little gay. Trust me, I'm an adrenologist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For every boop is equal and opposite boop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> futuresnek </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transgender Woman Found Beaten on Sidewalk Dies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nigerian singer helps others with transgender surgery fund </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I tell a fib </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he's sick. People do the same thing to gay people too; they'll have sex and then regret it and attack the person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It used to be classified as such; the APA's newer DSM does not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true. Chromosomes are only one of several things used to determine sex. And they don't always indicate the same thing as other indicators. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be measured with calipers, not a scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sought her out because she's trans. He knew full well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just checked and as it turns out none of my posts say that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's a transvestite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but since chromosomes aren't the sole defining feature of sex that doesn't really matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For someone who doesn't care, you sure spewed a lot of garbage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy knew beforehand. He sought her out because she's trans. If you're going to defend an attempted murderer at least get the facts right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's a physical one. The brain is one sex but for whatever reason the body is a different one (to grossly oversimplify). That disconnect can cause depression/anxiety etc, but not all trans people suffer from that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dysphoria is a mental illness, but not all trans people have the associated depression/anxiety that makes it a mental illness. Many do, in fact I'd say most, but it's not a prerequisite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did seek her out because she's trans though. That doesn't mean nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He knew beforehand. He sought her out because she's trans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I see what you mean. I haven't seen pumps use nautilus gears, but I have seen them use very elliptical oval gears that have a similar effect but without the jolt. 

I forget the name of it, but nautilus gears can be used as a quick and dirty escapement. You know those machines on assembly lines that take the workpiece around a carousel and stops at each tool so it can do it's thing? You could make a version of that with this sort of gear, slowing almost to a stop and then speeding up again, but at a larger scale you couldn't have exactly this shape because that jolt would shatter the gear eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He actually sought her out because she's trans, it seems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically it's a physical condition, it seems, which causes a mental condition if not treated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, sometimes it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that there are physical differences means that it's not a purely mental condition though.

[Zhou et al 1995](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/7477289)

[Kruijver et al 2000](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/10843193)

[Gooren 2006](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/16870186)

[Rametti et al 2011](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/20562024) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the scenario you described, the person would go mental from lack of stimuli long before any sort of personality could develop. But assuming they maintained their sanity, it's quite possible that they, on some level expecting to be in a more feminine body, would eventually have a feeling of dissatisfaction, confusion, or distress, etc, especially around when puberty starts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were highly voted within those threads. Looking quickly through some other threads with similar numbers of comments, the top comments have similar scores. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Identity is just how you feel, your self-image. It's like in the Matrix when Neo has hair in the simulation because that's part of his self-image, how he sees himself (though this is more than just hair, obviously).

As for how you know, well, per the APA:

 The Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders (DSM-5) provides for one overarching diagnosis of gender dysphoria with separate specific criteria for children and for adolescents and adults.
 
 In adolescents and adults gender dysphoria diagnosis involves a difference between ones experienced/expressed gender and assigned gender, and significant distress or problems functioning. It lasts at least six months and is shown by at least two of the following:
 
 1. A marked incongruence between ones experienced/expressed gender and primary and/or secondary sex characteristics
 
 2. A strong desire to be rid of ones primary and/or secondary sex characteristics
 
 3. A strong desire for the primary and/or secondary sex characteristics of the other gender
 
 4. A strong desire to be of the other gender
 
 5. A strong desire to be treated as the other gender
 
 6. A strong conviction that one has the typical feelings and reactions of the other gender
 
 In children, gender dysphoria diagnosis involves at least six of the following and an associated significant distress or impairment in function, lasting at least six months.
 
 1. A strong desire to be of the other gender or an insistence that one is the other gender
 
 2. A strong preference for wearing clothes typical of the opposite gender
 
 3. A strong preference for cross-gender roles in make-believe play or fantasy play
 
 4. A strong preference for the toys, games or activities stereotypically used or engaged in by the other gender
 
 5. A strong preference for playmates of the other gender
 
 6. A strong rejection of toys, games and activities typical of ones assigned gender
 
 7. A strong dislike of ones sexual anatomy
 
 8. A strong desire for the physical sex characteristics that match ones experienced gender
 
 For children, cross-gender behaviors may start between ages 2 and 4, the same age at which most typically developing children begin showing gendered behaviors and interests. Gender atypical behavior is common among young children and may be part of normal development. Children who meet the criteria for gender dysphoria may or may not continue to experience it into adolescence and adulthood. Some research shows that children who had more intense symptoms and distress, who were more persistent, insistent and consistent in their cross-gender statements and behaviors, and who used more declarative statements (I am a boy (or girl) rather than I want to be a boy (or girl)) were more likely to become transgender adults. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Physical difference in the brain. 

[Zhou et al 1995](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/7477289)

[Kruijver et al 2000](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/10843193)

[Gooren 2006](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/16870186)

[Rametti et al 2011](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/20562024) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because stereotypical things are usually stereotypical because they're common. Tomboys are a minority, trans people are a minority, so trans people that realized they were trans because they felt like a girl but a tomboyish girl are a super tiny minority. The odds of someone like that existing, never mind that they want to talk about it, are tiny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Identity and behavior aren't the same thing. Plenty of women watch NASCAR and fish, and plenty of men decorate and sew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You said that thinking that gender is a social construct and that brains can be male/female is doublethink, which means that those things contradict.

But they don't. If something is different between societies, it's socially constructed. And the brain is sexually dimorphic; that's well established.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multiples of 200. Regardless, a group having a higher suicide rate than the general population does not mean the same thing as a treatment not preventing suicide. That's a pretty important distinction, not some subtle statistical thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not at all like whats being pushed in the west. 

I never claimed it was. I claimed the opposite; it's a different society that has a different perception and attitude about gender. But thank you for so eloquently proving my point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 500 isn't a valid amount in Jeopardy.

Now *that's* condescending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enlighten me then. And you've still ignored the whole Asia thing.

Also, you're the one getting hostile here, not me. You're dodging questions and then getting upset somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what you claimed.

Ah, yes, I can see now how aggressive that was. Certainly fighting words that warrant such a response as yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, tiny tribes like the Greeks. Tiny tribes like much of Southeast Asia today. Only about a billion people or so, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those aren't mutually exclusive things. The brain is a sexually dimorphic organ. And different societies have different perceptions of gender.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what you claimed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they know better than you. Obviously you're the one trans person out, literally everyone else robs people. Gosh, this is what you get for not attending the meetings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sought her out because she's trans.

[In an interview with The News, Nessel said it was very clear that Hogan solicited (the victims) services because she was a transgender woman. She continued: They discussed specific sex acts that could only be performed on a man or a transgender woman.](http://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/local/detroit-city/2017/05/04/man-pleads-guilty-shooting-transgender-prostitute/101278766/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy knew the whole time too:

[In an interview with The News, Nessel said it was very clear that Hogan solicited (the victims) services because she was a transgender woman. She continued: They discussed specific sex acts that could only be performed on a man or a transgender woman.](http://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/local/detroit-city/2017/05/04/man-pleads-guilty-shooting-transgender-prostitute/101278766/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not mental though; the brain is physically like that of the sex of the gender one identifies as, generally speaking. 

[Zhou et al 1995](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/7477289)

[Kruijver et al 2000](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/10843193)

[Gooren 2006](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/16870186)

[Rametti et al 2011](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/20562024)

When that is left untreated, that's when dysphoria happens. That disconnect between body and brain is not fun. Fortunately, the body can be altered to better match the brain, which really helps alleviate that tension. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't trust Graham. Same with McCain. I don't trust them to do anything but vote party line no matter what they say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I say "smooth", I mean more that the fluid comes through at a more consistent rate, not so much that it creates a laminar flow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aware of that. However that's not born of a physiological condition; that's purely mental. And they're not getting treatment to have the body of a child. So all in all it's completely irrelevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't even understand the first thing about this article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize that's the attacker in that picture, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's something with a physical cause, which means you can't really treat it psychologically. No amount of therapy is going to change the fact that your brain is physically the way it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not so much of a gender role thing though; it's about expecting a body fundamentally different from the one you have, and socializing as the person you know you are but that you don't look like and aren't treated as.

If everybody just started calling you Ms. co99950, and every time you spoke it was someone else's voice, and when you looked down you don't see yourself, that would screw with you. And even if they called you Mr the fact that your body was still fundamentally *wrong* would still sting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't say that putting off transition doesn't aggravate dysphoria, just that transition doesn't always cure dysphoria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus it's easier to make an expressive character when they have a better-defined personality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't jinx it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But not something that all trans people experience. It's certainly possible that she does or did, but given the quality of care she can afford I wouldn't be surprised if it was effectively dealt with. 

Though that does bring up the question of if you can ever "cure" a mental illness; presumably if she went off hormones that would cause her some level of distress, but would that mean she doesn't have dysphoria now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't blame them for not understanding, but I do blame them for not even trying and enacting harmful policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Believing you're a different age than you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's a terrible human being, but so far as I know she's not mentally ill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL. I could have sworn it was one of those things they don't bother with unless someone is making a problem out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it's legal to discriminate against you, you may not have any better options. It wouldn't be the first time. Even if it's not legal to discriminate against you, addiction and poverty are a vicious cycle and if you're born into it you can get sucked in without even doing anything wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [In an interview with The News, Nessel said it was very clear that Hogan solicited (the victims) services because she was a transgender woman. She continued: They discussed specific sex acts that could only be performed on a man or a transgender woman.](http://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/local/detroit-city/2017/05/04/man-pleads-guilty-shooting-transgender-prostitute/101278766/)

If you're going to make excuses for someone trying to murder a woman, at least get your facts straight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but in the same way jaywalking is illegal. They don't exactly hunt it down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is not typical though. It seems like reddit draws the line somewhere around attempted murder.

Plus, the implication of your comment (not sure if it's the intended meaning but it's the one that comes across), is that trans people don't face discrimination and aren't victims of violence at much higher rates than the general population, which isn't true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to [another article](http://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/local/detroit-city/2017/05/04/man-pleads-guilty-shooting-transgender-prostitute/101278766/) (thanks /u/Kettrickan!), the guy knew and specifically sought her out because she's trans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, several people have made that joke and it gets removed by the mods.

Thanks for that by the way, mods! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much of a stretch in places where you can be denied employment just for being trans. Michigan is one such place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trans people are the worst. They account for such a small % but they want everyone else to change for them. So bizarre. [23]

---

Si why am I not shocked that the ACLU would side with the retarded position that a confused teenager should be able to shower shop in junior high and high school on a whim and regardless of biological sex? Moreover title 9 has fuck all to do with this as the authors obviously never intended for protection of the fair sex to mean the dude that wants to go shower with chicks. [5]

---

Well I mean yeah... She's a man. [Yes I'm aware that's a Jake from State Farm reference. Doesn't make it appropriate.] [18]

---

Maybe there is a difference between physical gender, of which there are two, and individualized mental perception of gender. And maybe all of society is being extorted into pretending this difference doesn't exist by a bunch of mentally unstable people that will become triggered and riot if anyone says anything about the Emperor's New Clothes. [17]

---

Ugh, ridiculous. Why should I pay for someone's cosmetic surgery? [30]

Hey depressed people who are suicidal also want to change thier body. From alive to dead. Should insurance pay for that too? [13]

---

Who gives a fuck. Quit trying to normalize this mental illness. [6]

A lot of the worst that were just cheap jokes were removed, but they had not usually been buried by downvotes before then, to say the least.

Edit: added a few, plus scores </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F A M I L Y V A L U E S  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So was Jeff Dunham. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I](https://np.reddit.com/r/news/comments/64gutk/aclu_files_suit_in_wisconsin_over_denial_of/)
[can](https://np.reddit.com/r/news/comments/68dkcp/catholic_hospital_that_refused_transgender_man/)
[assure](https://np.reddit.com/r/news/comments/639z4h/aclu_takes_legal_action_to_defend_rights_of/)
[you,](https://np.reddit.com/r/news/comments/6846iq/japans_first_transgender_male_politician_vows_to/)
[trans](https://np.reddit.com/r/news/comments/68460x/college_roundup_transgender_athlete_makes/)
[hate](https://np.reddit.com/r/news/comments/67j756/lawsuit_against_uil_over_transgender_wrestler_to/)
[gets](https://np.reddit.com/r/news/comments/65n5ly/transgender_uw_employees_sue_over_insurance/)
[upvoted](https://np.reddit.com/r/news/comments/67rkfo/judge_dismisses_suit_against_uil_to_ban/)
[quite](https://np.reddit.com/r/news/comments/65xzit/survivor_contestant_who_outed_transgender_player/)
[often.](https://np.reddit.com/r/news/comments/67rmez/transgender_bill_shot_down_in_ny_state_senate/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Dysphoria](https://www.psychiatry.org/patients-families/gender-dysphoria/what-is-gender-dysphoria) is a severe discomfort caused by having a body that doesn't match one's gender identity. Not transitioning can aggravate it, but not all trans people experience dysphoria. Some simply have their identity but aren't distressed if their body doesn't match (although under the current definition that counts as dysphoria too (there's some controversy over the exact definition at the moment)). Either way, transition is typically recommended, though the extend to which it's required is far different.

There are some slight physical differences between male and female brains. Trans people seem to have brains that are physically like those of the sex of the gender they identify as. Why exactly this happens is still a mystery.

[Zhou et al 1995](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/7477289)

[Kruijver et al 2000](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/10843193)

[Gooren 2006](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/16870186)

[Rametti et al 2011](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/20562024)

To oversimplify, some people have bodies that don't match the sex of their brain and for many that causes serious strain, but we can alter the body to match the brain and that works pretty well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In most subs it's okay but that's not the norm in /r/news.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is not the norm, I can assure you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Monsters? Nope, just people. Just [men](https://imgur.com/a/75JZb) and [women](https://imgur.com/a/dMpqb) like anyone else.

2. Mentally ill? Nope. According to the APA, ["identifying as transgender does not constitute a mental disorder."](http://www.apa.org/topics/lgbt/transgender.aspx)

3. Gays? Possibly. Your gender identity doesn't necessarily dictate your sexuality. There are both straight and gay trans people.

4. Deviants? Possibly. Your gender doesn't necessarily dictate your kinkiness. There are both kinky and vanilla trans people.

5. They need to get help with their mental illness? Again, while I'd like to stress that being transgender is not itself a mental illness, failing to get treatment to affirm one's gender can cause it it. Again per the [APA](https://www.psychiatry.org/patients-families/gender-dysphoria/what-is-gender-dysphoria), transition is part of recommended treatment.

6. Not get butchered by a plastic surgeon? I should hope not; it's far better to get competent surgeon if surgery is required, though that usually goes without saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What culture? Poverty, addiction? That's not exclusive to any race either, and its impacts are pretty much universal. The only difference is if one race is somehow artificially held down by the culture around them... but oh... we can't possibly acknowledge that, can we? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily. Sometimes people know and still freak out. The same sort of thing happens to gay people too sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say that it's transphobic just to mention trans people, it's transphobic hate to someone just for being trans. I don't really like Caitlyn Jenner, but that's because of her politics and shitty reality TV show, not because she's trans. That's not transphobic. Just like how not liking David Clarke for his politics isn't racist, but not liking him because he's black is.

Edit: i accidentally a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I never said that transphobia was a whites-only thing. I said the opposite in fact:

transphobia has little if anything to do with race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That guy's a quack. He's been disavowed (not sure if that's the right term) by John Hopkins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure I never claimed one did. Pretty sure that nobody claimed the attacker here is white, actually. Certainly nobody in this comment section at any rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you mentioned white men, which the attacker here isn't. The closest association I could think of is the Michigan state legislature, a body largely made up of white men that has so far allowed discrimination against trans people that often leaves them with no further choice but illegitimate work like prostitution. If you want to say that there's some group of transphobic white males to blame here, that seems like a good candidate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If all I wanted was to be shit on by reddit, I'd post my own stupid face to /r/RoastMe. And I wouldn't bother posting similar articles to /r/politics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan, for instance. You can be denied employment just for being trans there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And...? This happened in Detroit, which is in America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is that doesn't change that what /u/katzgoboom said is true. Yes, trans people are only a small subset of the population, but that doesn't mean it isn't significant that homicide is one of the leading causes of death of that subset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vote them out, I suppose. I assume you're talking about the ones in the Michigan [state legislature](https://i.imgur.com/aNlvmVT.jpg) that are yet to make it illegal to deny someone employment simply for being trans, something that seriously affects the ability to find legitimate work. To be honest, I'm not sure exactly why race is important; transphobia has little if anything to do with race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, if you could go ahead and tell me what page it says that, that would be really helpful. [PDF](https://psicovalero.files.wordpress.com/2014/06/dsm-v-manual-diagnc3b3stico-y-estadc3adstico-de-los-trastornos-mentales.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people who complain about others "virtue signalling" usually seem to just be incapable of understanding that you can genuinely care about other people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's that the story gets posted, it's the response it gets. /r/news is not a place that seems to like trans people by and large; just sort this thread by controversial. It's a bit more positive than usual because someone was nearly killed, but generally there's a lot of hatred whenever an article about a trans person is posted, and usually that gets voted up pretty rapidly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking offense to people's comments on an anonymous website is pretty much the definition of being insecure.

Sensitive, perhaps, but that's not the same thing as insecure. Insecure would be lashing out at people because of an innocuous comment, attacking them for asking genuine questions, that sort of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can guarantee that's not true. You can be turned down for any legal reason. The Civil Rights Act (among other acts) prohibits discrimination on account of color, race, religion, sex, or national origin. If you're fired or turned down because of one of those reasons (which is usually quite hard to prove), that's illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you hate trans people? [X](https://archive.fo/x89fv)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the one that said if there's no reason for evolution to make something, that thing is a disorder. There's no reason for evolution to make some people have red hair, ergo it's a disorder according to you. 

The DSM is not being politically correct, it's just being correct. The APA is a medical organization, not a political one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not so much that someone else got it, it's more of the fact that it's legal to turn someone down for a job in Michigan just because they're trans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can legally be turned down for a job in Michigan for no other reason than because you're trans. When it is legal to discriminate against you, you may be forced into unsavory work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you hate trans people so much that you feel the need to defend someone who tried to kill a trans person, yeah, that shows some insecurity on your part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's legal to deny her employment in Michigan just for being trans. That's not her fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not fair because they forced a trans boy to play against the girls. Of course he was going to win. The appropriate action would have been to let him compete with the rest of the boys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that hard to find a copy. 

[PDF](https://psicovalero.files.wordpress.com/2014/06/dsm-v-manual-diagnc3b3stico-y-estadc3adstico-de-los-trastornos-mentales.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no reason for evolution to give people red hair either, but it's not a disorder. Plus, the [APA](https://www.psychiatry.org/patients-families/gender-dysphoria/what-is-gender-dysphoria), which writes the DSM, [disagrees](http://www.apa.org/topics/lgbt/transgender.aspx)

Identifying as transgender does not constitute a mental disorder.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can flatten out that peak though. You're still drawing the same amount of water, but you can do so in a way that the return stroke happens faster and the draw stroke is slowed in the middle. You get a more consistent flow that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? From the [APA](https://www.psychiatry.org/patients-families/gender-dysphoria/what-is-gender-dysphoria), the people who write the DSM. Nowhere in there does it say that all trans people have dysphoria, and in fact it recommends transition with hormones and (sometimes) surgery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not entirely sure what you're asking. Could you rephrase the question? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's safe harbor. You're allowed to take "banned" substances so long as they're for a valid medical reason and you disclose and monitor it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The IOC rules say get within spec and stay there for two years. It's not instant but it is very quick, especially for someone who was on puberty blockers and doesn't have anything to undo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not a thing that happens. And if it is, it's born of pure psychology, not a physiological difference. And that 17-year-old isn't getting treatment to turn their body into one of a 12-year-old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt anyone here can name a single trans Olympic medalist.

To my knowledge, there has never been one, at least not one that was openly trans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Articles about women who cheat in sporting events do not garner nearly the same amount of hate and vitriol as those about trans women simply participating, never mind if they win or lose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> due to higher levels of testosterone and lower levels of estrogen

So it shouldn't be an issue if someone is on hormones that change those levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IOC asks for two years of hormones within spec, and that's at the Olympic level with people who have trained their whole lives and with a big margin of error to boot. Without the hormones supporting  muscle mass, lung capacity, etc, they fall to the same level as a cis woman training just as hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not entirely sure if it was the motive. Seems likely he knew because he finished whatever he was doing with her before shooting her. 

Either way it's a super shitty thing to do, shooting someone in the face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When one of those groups is protected from discrimination and is less likely to be the victim of violent crime, it's not an agenda so much as it is a statement of fact. 

You cannot legally be turned down for a job in Michigan just because you're a woman. You can if you're trans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She lived. I don't know much about her condition beyond that, but he was charged with *attempted* homicide.

Edit: Not exactly "attempted homicide", but similar. I was on my phone when I first replied, didn't look up the exact charge. /u/NEEK0 has the actual charge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nevermind that the DSM disagrees. It doesn't say that being trans is characterized by having dysphoria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I'll concede. The pelvis is really the main one, but since the skeleton regenerates over time like any other organ it too can change drastically with hormones. Especially if someone is on blockers and doesn't have to undo puberty in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since *Michigan law permits employment discrimination against LGBTQ residents*, trans people sometimes must resort to sex work in order to survive, which puts them at extreme risk of criminal violence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just as a quick clarification: being trans is not itself a mental disease. Failing to get treatment matching body to brain, however, can and often does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they don't change bone structure, general muscle mass or flexibility.

Not true. Bone density, muscle mass, and flexibility are all incredibly sensitive to hormone levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  id kill anyone

Not really on the whole "mental stability" train then, are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too late.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It should be noted that cis men who have been diagnosed with low T are also prescribed the same testosterone injections as trans men.

It's called safe harbor. You can absolutely take a controlled substance so long as it's disclosed and monitored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hormones are a hell of a drug. They play a massive role in your physique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By that logic the number of people killed in school shootings is insignificant. It also doesn't change the fact that what they said is true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you think it's okay to kill a person if they're trans. That's pretty fucked up of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas school officials dont understand transgender athletes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. I doubt he didn't know beforehand.

2. Even if he didn't know that doesn't make it okay somehow to try to kill this woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas school officials dont understand transgender athletes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detroit man shoots transgender woman in face after paying for sexual act in back seat of car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Farm and Fleet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well duh, just don't get raped and you won't have any problem getting healthcare. Or get elected to Congress so you can keep the same protections. God, I don't understand why you women insist on making things so complicated.

/s because I'm sure someone actually thinks this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have the right to a sandwich either but you do have the right not to be denied a sandwich for reasons like race, religion, sex, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Protection from discrimination, however, is a right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Civil Rights Act 1964 if it's a private institution. 14th Amendment if it's public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's HHS Spokesperson Had a Blog Full of Transphobic Slurs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll never be perfect but you can smooth it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who can understand her,  that annoyance is not unfounded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8:03 in London and nothing on the BBC homepage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? I thought Paul Ryan's tweet was a complete analysis! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, Ben Garrison. What a twat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, because absolutely everyone has exactly the same opportunities as you had. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you entitled to the labor of the people that teach your kids, or build your roads, or inspect your water, or protect your country? Healthcare can be and is much of the world is treated as a public service like those, and a particularly important one, which is payed for with public money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the average Dutchie is more of a healthy happy degree holder than the average American.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Capitalist Communist: no, those are antithetical.

Democratic Communist: yes, on paper. In reality not so much because full-on capital C Communists usually are the only party on the ballot if they can make that happen.

Democratic Socialist: absolutely. It's a subtle distinction but basically Communists believe in a command economy (five year plans etc) and Socialists believe in a demand economy, but with lots of state ownership (ideally both believe in direct ownership but it's tricky in practice).

Of course this is kind of oversimplified; any political movement will have different ideals depending on who you ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh damn my dad totally used this on me when I was little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Works well with "your mom" too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he's aware of the Lamb Sauce meme so that's pretty great. It's nice to know he's in on the joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Badly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm not contradicting anything I've said. In fact I've said the same thing a couple times already. You however, have avoided any questions.

1. Can people be trusted to figure out where to pee, as they've done pretty much since pluming was invented?

2. Do you want to force [these women](https://imgur.com/a/dMpqb) to use the men's room? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I can see, it takes some serious smush for it to work on a macroscopic scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been on this ship since [the slinky full of ball-bearings remark](https://www.questionablecontent.net/view.php?comic=3279). But then again so has [Claire](https://www.questionablecontent.net/view.php?comic=3341). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The good ship that launched with slinky full of ball-bearings is still steaming ahead. Looks like a Friday cliffhanger, folks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's literally built like a tank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some pumps use a mechanism like this, but the shaft is stationary and the piston/cylinder rotate around it. And usually they use a solid disk and multiple cylinders. 

Like [this](http://www.hydraulicspneumatics.com/sites/hydraulicspneumatics.com/files/uploads/2014/04/Fig8.png). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I looked up the numbers. And America is not so unique that no other country has dealt with similar situations effectively. You can condescend all you want, but it doesn't change the fact that America has dramatically higher rates of gun violence than parts of the world with effective gun control, so obviously gun control is possible. I didn't say that it was right, I didn't say it was wrong, I said it was possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, in my head "flappy-paddle" = dual clutch because of Clarkson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The gear on the left is the one being driven at a constant speed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do follow a Golden Spiral, but they don't have to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's also /r/mechanical_gifs, which has both useful and useless mechanisms that look cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're just normal slushbox autos with paddle shifters instead of a slapstick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking more of an old-school piston pump, like the hand operated ones. Those were often retrofitted with small motors, connected by oval gears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That wasn't what I had in mind but I suppose you could if you wanted (I think those are pretty smooth anyway). I was thinking more of an old-school piston pump, like the hand operated ones. Those were often retrofitted with small motors, connected by oval gears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you turn a crankshaft at a constant rate, the piston will move in a sine-wave(ish) manner, going fastest during the middle of the stroke and very slowly at the end. But if you use a set of oddly-shaped gears you can smooth that motion out some by speeding up the gears at the ends of the stroke and slowing it down in the middle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brings up an interesting question in the QC universe then. When is it okay to have sex with a robot?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are compared to in the US. Otherwise they'd just use guns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gun violence in the UK is roughly 1/100th the rate it is in the US. That's two orders of magnitude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying that gun control is some magic bullet, the the fact is the UK and other countries with gun control generally have dramatically lower rates of gun violence than the US means that the notion that gun control is impossible is silly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the argument falls back to "people are capable of deciding where to pee". Only recently have people felt the need to legislate to trans people by saying that treating them like any other human is opening the door to pedophiles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure about that?

You're taking an increase in crime over one year and acting like it's a huge increase. If two people are shot and then next year three people are shot, that's a 50% increase in the rate of gun crime year on year. The actual number (per capita) is orders of magnitude lower than in the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the UK doesn't have a gun violence rate (not even counting suicides) orders of magnitudes lower than the US?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh these memes are gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is like two months stale by now, surely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's their right as a state so I doubt that any small-government, states rights Republicans will have any problem with this at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
