<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8145</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flowers in the Attic (aka The Dollanger series) by VC Andrews. The paperback looks so innocent at the thrift store, a little sad girls face inside a flower petal. It's only a quarter. Yeah my mom bought that for me and yeah I liked it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have emailed Erik Larson, asking him a question, then complimenting his work. I got a response! Would do again  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this book? I have it on my to-read list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read In a Glass Darkly? It looks good! 

I found this link with 10 Victorian Ghost stories so maybe that will help you find something new. [Link](https://interestingliterature.com/2015/10/28/10-classic-victorian-ghost-stories-everyone-should-read/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently listening to Still Foolin Em on audiobook and Billy Crystal seems like a super nice, sentimental guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vick brought a lot of Falcons fans back to the flock. We were so angry because we were hurt. I loved this article, def brought a tear to my eye  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Vick got me watching the Falcons again. I was SO mad at him when we found out about the dog fighting. He ruined the team and he ruined the hopes I had for my team. But, with time, I forgave Mike Vick and I learned to be thankful for him making the Falcons a legit team again. I think most of Atlanta forgave Mike Vick before he even got released from prison. There was so much hate (because it hurt!) when we found out. But the city forgave him and you see Vick jerseys around.  I have even rooted for the Eagles  when Vick played for them. He's definitely a birdbro. He can fly with us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I totally think of this cat!](http://media.bigshinyrobot.com/uploads/2015/12/eek.jpg.400x0_q100_upscale.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got swept up into series like Hunger Games, Divergent, Twilight, etc. . . . and after getting book 2 into 50 Shades of Gray, I was like ... why am I doing this to myself? 

I have a hard time picking up a new series now. I am not a huge fantasy or sci-fi person, so I mainly stick with memoirs, nonfiction, and fiction that are confined to one book. Most of the series seem to be urban fantasy, paranormal, detective, and those other genres I'm finding that Im just not interested in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I listened to this on audiobook and the author narrated it. Wonderful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's the guy you want to do it though. Huge sci-fi nerd. 

He stated in interviews that he wanted to take time off bc his creative side was running dry. But he had like 2 or 3 concepts that he'd like to direct ... and a lot of people assume (me included) that Dune was one of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

I really liked Sex Drugs and Cocoa Puffs by Klosterman. But I wasnt a huge fan of What if we're wrong. I did listen to it on audiobook and I dont think that really helped consuming the book that way ....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's a book section on amazon that translates best-sellers from foreign language into english 

one of the books i'm trying out is Pathological, by Jinkang Wang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thus begins chasing that * feeling *  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they looked through your post history, ha!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first yoga asana book was Light on Yoga by BKS Iyengar. 

I also bought [Mark Stephens](https://www.amazon.com/Mark-Stephens/e/B002TCS1GW/ref=sr_ntt_srch_lnk_1?qid=1485880856 sr=1-1) (amazon link), Yoga Sequencing for myself ... but his Teaching Yoga book might be more up your alley.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, I spend all my practice doing hot yoga on the towel. So I would definitely go for a YogiToes. You can get them for like $40 on eBay. 

I bought a Jade yoga mat, and they're nice. But I found the oils from my hands and feet stained the mat and the mat started "cracking". So I have a Manduka ... but the mat is really heavy and kind of a pain to lug around. 

As long as I bring my YogiToes, I find the mat underneath doesnt really matter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried browsing amazon crossing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive read the book, it was hilarious! 

The only thing really similar I can think of would be chuck klosterman, sex drugs and cocoa puffs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Still Foolin Em, by Billy Crystal, narrated by Billy Crystal**

he's talking about baby boomers and turning 65, but I'm honestly cracking up laughing. He's hilarious. I was never really a huge fan of Billy Crystal growing up ... I've never seen When Harry Met Sally. But I did watch Throw Momma From the Train. I never found him particularly interesting as an Oscars host (but I was fairly young when he hosted). 

He does his impersonations on the audiobook and I just can not imagine going through the same experience reading the actual book. It definitely wouldnt be as funny. But perhaps Im missing out on pictures.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have you completed this book? i mean, is there ANY redemptive qualities to it or more of the same?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Fates and Furies, by Lauren Groff**

I started this book last year. I stopped reading after I was about 75% of the way through. And then I found it at the library, so I'm just reading it to finish it. It's so pretentious and over-written, ugh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to make a post this week. Thanks for everyone's input!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, sometimes I find that extra money when I don't blow it on $20-60 worth of alcohol every weekend ....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I havent read it, but I want to read Red Notice by Bill Browder. It's got a lot of great reviews and it's been on my to-read list for awhile. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter user adds a little something to his Falcons tattoo (too soon?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dogs are the other little creatures that seem to interrupt workouts.l but dogs seem to do fine around lifting ... but practice yoga and they're all up in your business.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RPO is one of those books that will make a really fun movie. But, I agree, it's just a terrible literary thing .... Wade is 100% good, the corporation is 100% bad. He doesnt struggle through any of the challenges he faces (except when he doesnt defeat Pacman on the first try but it's okay because he gets it with no real problem on the 2nd try). And he is playing for one mill- ... one BILLION dollars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to stick with current fiction releases and fun nonfiction books bc that's what I enjoy. I havent read a classic in years. I didnt like reading them in high school and I havent really liked anything since.

Some people don't even READ ... so you're ahead of the game by just picking up a book in the first place. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read books, on my ereader, and I listen to audiobooks. 

I'm currently reading a Norm Macdonald book on an ereader, and I *know* id probably consume it better as an audiobook. I feel that way with most comedian memoirs (like Mindy Kaling, Bossypants, Yes Please). 

But I listened to The Magic Art of Tidying Up, and I'd think I'd prefer to have read that one. 

I count all the experiences as having read the book though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Based on a True Story: A Memoir, by Norm Macdonald**

This is one where I REALLY REALLY REALLY should have got the audiobook. It's an okay read, but I feel like it would be a GREAT listen, especially because it's narrated by Norm Macdonald. It's hard to tell what's true and what is Norm just being silly. Which is part of the charm, I guess. 

**A Wild Swan: And Other Tales, by Michael Cunningham**

This is a short modern retelling of fairy tales. The artwork is fun and great; the stories? they're okay. This was a good novelty read but I wasnt swept up in a whole new world or anything.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Falcons vs Browns rn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bird bros stick together 

Edit: fly together  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C2zjuqEUQAEda-t?format=jpg name=large </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't see the first half going like that, but I'll take it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C2zkizHUcAE3W6j?format=jpg name=large </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Packers will have to be Mighty Ducks good to win this game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know you're a true Atlanta sports fan when your ass cheeks are still clenched at 24-0  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that's a cutting edge reference  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> depends on what side you're on  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 07:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jack is the hero we need.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely try Big LIttle Lies by Lianne Moriarty. 

It's going to be a show on HBO too so I feel like you'll hear more about it later! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished this! It was okay. I definitely needed to hear some things and I'm glad I grabbed it. But man that narrator makes the author seem kind of like an uptight beeyotch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She reminds me of Natalie Portman from The Professional.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> church basketball - the brawl that begins with a prayer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked Versaspa ... I have done some cross-training a few hours after and have been okay, but I don't think I would try a hot yoga class until after at least one shower (wearing dark clothes and on a dark towel) and just see what happens. Maybe use a white hand towel and see what wipes off? 

They only last about 5 days from my experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved this book. I had no desire to see the movie after reading it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 21:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never heard about this from yoga ... I will say the most I hear about are queefs. And when you're upside down, sometimes things can open up a bit, air gets in .... and then when you turn back rightside up, gravity works (like it always does) and things (as in the air that fell in) fall out again.

Keep your hips high as you come out of the handstand (like drop one leg slowly to the ground) so you're not slamming to the ground as you come out of the handstand. And maybe a smoother transition will help your body keep a little firmer in that area!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 21:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's fair for a gym to ask it's clients to show up in clean workout gear and shoes without mud on the bottom of it, etc, I think the odor can be distracting to your other clients. 



We had a similar problem, but the guy in question was one of the coaches. He was also a cancer survivor so no one would expect him to put on deoderant bc he was militant about not wearing it. But I think he started baby wiping and bringing an extra shirt sometimes. 

I think you're completely reasonable with setting boundaries with your client. But be direct. And be kind. 

If you want, you could make a blog post above your workout (when you know she's supposed to be there) commenting on your expectations for the members. "We expect you guys to show up clean and realize you're not exercising in a bubble  ... " I'm sure Google could help you a lot more than me! 

Either way, I do think it's the owner's responsibility ...  the members might make it worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's on audiobook so I don't have the pleasure of holding it in my hand and seeing if it sparks joy or not  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> young adult angst

our generation's Catcher in the Rye 

kidding kidding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am of the opinion that Bret Easton Ellis is a gifted writer. And I've only read American Psycho from Ellis, but I do think it's more complicated than trash or pornography. 

Patrick Bateman accurately portrays a true psycopath. What's the difference in how Bateman murders versus Hannibal Lecter? I wonder if AP is more troubling because the book follows Bateman's perspective. 

Because Bateman is truly psychotic and because he states his murders with about as much affectation as the next guy's Versace suit, I do see the book following a logic of "true" storytelling. EVERYTHING in American Psycho is superficial, and I think Ellis intended on doing that. And because there's really no conscience with the murders, I think that makes the book more "horrifying". 




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think some of the SNL writers or other comedians are really awesome to listen to on audiobook - Tina Fey, Norm MacDonald, Amy Poehler, Mindy Kaling, Aziz Ansari and more recently Trevor Noah .... 

I can only listen to audiobooks on my commute .... if I'm cleaning or cooking, I still have a hard time concentrating on the content. And sometimes I think I would absorb more of the material if I actually read the book with my eyes.  

But I've been listening to audiobooks for years now and I know I'm experiencing books I otherwise wouldnt through this medium. NPR and music gets so tiring after awhile. I always have an audiobook going on in addition to my regular reading.  This adds about 10-15 extra books a year to my "read" pile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. I think Larson doesnt do a great job of tying everything up nicely. He didnt do it with Garden of the Beasts nor did he do it with Devil in the White City. I just want a complete story. I feel like i get 85% of a good story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally like Laura Hillenbrand. If you havent seen the movies, I'd definitely pick up the book. I read Unbroken and I have zero desire to see the movie bc the book was just SO good. 

I've also heard really good things about Alfred Lansing's Endurance: Shackleton's Incredible Voyage

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I found this one to be a slog at some parts (i mean he goes on and on about people's outfits and cds he likes) but I do feel like the last 10% is worth a read, especially if you make it about 60-70% of the way through the book. 

It's just unique and I do think it's still shockingly relevant with the materialism and Trump references! I think it's funny how Batemen is always confused with other white yuppies ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read this right after I read Before the Fall by Noah Hawley ... and I just feel like they're great to read around each other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second WritersAlmanac.org and Bukowski. You can go to Writers Almanac daily and just read a short poem. 

I find Billy Collins very accessible and Mary Oliver is WONDERFUL if you love nature.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked listening to Mindy Kaling, Aziz Ansari, Amy Poehler ... those are fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Life-Changing Magic of Tidying Up, by by Marie Kond**

I dont know if it's me just being a messy asshole or what but this woman seems like an uptight bitch tbqh. I'm listening to it on audiobook and maybe the narrator has a nasally voice .... Or maybe it was the fact the author threw away all of her family's clothes while growing up bc she thought they didnt need any of it. I'll definitely take something positive away from this book. But I would NOT want to hang out with the author. 

**Every Body Yoga: Let Go of Fear. Get On the Mat. Love Your Body., by Jessamyn Stanley**

This is a yoga book written by the instagram star Jessamyn Stanley. She's interesting in the yoga world bc she's Black, Overweight (and she can do a lot of the poses). THe first part of her growing up and talking about her first yoga class is GREAT.  The pictures of the poses part is take it or leave it for me. She uses un-traditional models - like normal sized women or ones who don't shave their armpits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just dont insult a novel without reading it first, thats all I ask.

Thank you Faye Weldon! 

This was actually my first book of 2017 I finished. I think the book has stuck around bc it does capture the materialism and selfishness of that whole "yuppie" world. And those are human characteristics that never really diminish ... it just changes over time. 

Also, I think Ron Jonson, in the Psychopath Test, claims that Patrick Bateman is the closest thing to a "true" psycho that he's ever seen in movies or books ... 

And because there's really not another book out there like American Psycho ... I mean, it's hear to stay! I think it's odd how Patrick Bateman idolized Trump and Trump Tower and here we are in 2017 where Trump is our PRESIDENT. Like Bateman IDOLIZED the guy, Trump, and this guy is leading the country. 

American Psycho is here to stay and extremely relevant after a quarter century.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 14:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 5'10" too. I feel like this makes me think I can eat WAY more calories than I need. Did you track your cals at all?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I give so much gratitude to my first few students bc they taught me about as much as I taught them! 

Congratulations :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tripod headstands or forearm headstands?  Start from the ground up. 

I think it's important to know where to put the weight in your head ... you want it on the CROWN of the head and not the FOREHEAD. You shouldnt feel pressure in the neck ... put more weight into your hands and your forearms so little to no weight is on your head ... and as you get more confident, maybe add a little more weight to the head. 

And when you do workouts with HSPU, I would use 1 or 2 ab mats and modify the movement until you get through this hurdle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yoga with Adriene is doing a 30 day yoga thing. 

Esther Ekhart, Sarah Beth Yoga .... also some other youtubers with pretty accessible (ie. beginner), free yoga classes online. 

Romwod will cost you and it is basically yin yoga - where you hold the poses for 1-4minutes. It stretches a lot of the back body and most crossfitters and western people in general, would do some good to stretch out the front of the body. But the pros is that it's 20 minutes and people find that accessible. 

I personally see flexibility improvements with doing some sort of yoga or stretching at least 3 times a week. 

Hope that helps!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pure Drivel / Steve Martin / Comedy / 1998

- See title for content

Thing Explainer / Randall Munroe / Science / 2016 
 
- Randall Munroe explains complicated mechanical things using the most common words. 

Thing Explainer was a great idea that didnt play out well for me in book form. The text was really small and light blue written on a white background. There was no logical flow of where to stop and start reading. And he would say "fire water" which made me have to do some mental gymnastics to understand what the real world thing he was trying to put out there (which was gasoline). And after pages and pages of that, my brain was fried trying to uncomplicate his attempts at uncomplication. Had high expectations bc I really liked What If. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 Year in Review. What is the WORST book you read in 2016, regardless of publication date? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to piggy-back off the u/bobknobber post of Best Books you read in 2016 regardless of publication date, I'm interested in the worst book you've read (regardless of publication date). 


Title / Author / Genre / Year Published followed by a one-to-two sentence summary of the book

Feel free to discuss why you picked it up, why you didn't like it, and any other thoughts you may have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this on audiobook. Ive heard great things. This was published in 2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That should be a personal goal of 2017 ... to read a novel by Sarah Waters. I've had her on my to-read list 4ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I have Endurance in my audiobooks. I have heard great things about both books. 

I really enjoyed Unbroken by Laura Hillenbrand so I feel like these are right up that genre. Thrilling nonfiction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this thread! 

Before the Fall / Noah Hawley / Mystery Thriller / 2016

 - Guy, Rich Guy, (some other people) and Rich Guy's kid are in a plane crash. Guy and Rich Guy's kid are the only two survivors. The book follows the clusterfuck of media attention that follows. 

Another Brooklyn / Jacqueline Woodson / Fiction / 2016

 - 4 African American teens grow up in Brooklyn during the 70's. It was just super well written and read almost like poetry! 

I read about 50 books in 2016. Most of them not published in 2016. My favorites just happened to be published this year! I usually dont get to read recently published items. But I re-upped my library card about 2 years ago and I figured out Overdrive. So both of these books happened to be from the library!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's good on Amazon Prime?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starting **I Am Legend, by Richard Matheson**

The Road by Cormac McCarthy was very good but I find I Am Legend is more tense and has me on edge more .... it's just very scary to read!

and about 70% of the way through with **American Psycho, by Bret Easton Ellis**

American Pscyho is over the top so I find it a little hard to take seriously. But the Trump references are kind of funny seeing how his name is popping up in the news again ... 

probably gonna move onto some lighter fare after getting through these reads!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 04:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he lost weight, he could get a few more inches  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rooting for Westworld and Natalie Portman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evan Rachel Woods looks better in a tux than most men  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's up with sleeves ruining otherwise perfect dresses  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely has a Jack Vettriano vibe to me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have a picture of him from westworld? I can't remember which character he was and google images isn't helping me out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an UNO one and I don't use it bc I'm not sure how to put the lamp together. Does it go at the base of the lightbulb? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm nikirtehsuxlol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any LITSY users here? Litsy is like if instagram + goodreads had a child </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Share your usernames! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I thought it was from Honeymoon!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friends and I have talked about how Castro would make the prettiest girl. He looks like he has no leg hair and his hair seems very thick and shiny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> so glad I found this subreddit! here's book marky mark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 05:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no clue what to expect before I saw this movie and I loved it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there should be the following topics

- New to CrossFit - touching on "is it right for me?" and the other insecurities people go through trying something new

- Some guidance on shoes posts

- list free and paid programming

- home gym essentials

- no equipment, no problem workouts

- a list to the girls

- what to expect in your first class

- signs of a good gym/bad gym

I think that people should be able to post about those topics ... but right now there is NO guidance at all. 
Thanks, no pressure but don't disappoint us! 


edit: and also maybe a link to rediquette bc SOME people in this sub are some downvoting assholes that dont put forth any content. if you disagree, POST WHY instead of lazily clicking a downvote button. I have no clue why my comment is getting downvoted. It happens all the time in this sub. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 16:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he's just bringing them a refreshing can of Coke  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> gorgeous location to boot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 05:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contamination by Lamberto Bava

It's terrible and it desperately tried to be something that it didnt have the budget to become.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldnt want something so weird that it would ruin my life or I'd feel like I *had* to be a superhero. So I'm going to go with night vision. Like an lol look what I can do type power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about pushing the sides of your waist into the mat. And if you're doing that, you're probably using your core muscles. And as you lower your legs, your lower back will probably lift, but keep pushing the sides of the waist into the mat. That's part of the work! And I usually slide my hands under my hips and that makes the movement less strenuous on my back. Or I just don't lower my legs down all the way ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I do hot yoga, I ALWAYS have to use a towel anyways. I'd spend like $40-60 on a towel that covers your whole mat. I personally like the yogitoes manduka towels with the rubber dots! If your main practice is hot yoga, just go with the cheaper mat and splurge on the towel! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, this would be my main concern! Beginners should put most, if not all, of their weight into their forearms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New to Netgalley. What do you do if you didn't like the book you read? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im brand new to netgalley and I have about 5 books in queue that I need to review. 

But one of the books ... I REALLY didnt like. I havent gone through the review process ... Do they expect you to post a negative review? Or can you just click that you didnt like it and would rather not review the book in a negative light on a public forum? 

I dont know I'm new to this halp.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **American Psycho, by Bret Easton Ellis**

It's totally not what I expected. Patrick Batemen will methodically go through people's outfits and that is getting repetitive and tiring. But I think that's the point too? He's starting to throw in how the Chinese launderers are not getting the blood out of his suits. And all his shocking murder talk fits right in with the rest of his meandering thoughts. And then his freakin friends are really no better! They're just not murderers. And even though the book talks about recording on VHS and Sony Walkmans ... it still seems quite relevant to the Wall Street culture ... I'm not quite sure what to make of everything just yet though. 40% of the way through. I'm at Evelyn's Christmas party. 

**Embrace the Suck, by Stephen Madden**

Some book I picked up at the library talking about this 40-something male's introduction to Crossfit, I guess? I have only read the introduction so I actually have no clue what it's about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 20:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the cut of your jib!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know if this REALLY fits what you're looking for, but I've had it on my to-read list for quite awhile. It's Red Notice, by Bill Browder. The book seems very well received by amazon reviewers and the topic seems interesting. But it's more post-Cold War and financial/political leaning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been on my to-read list! It even made [Bill Gates book blog](https://www.gatesnotes.com/Books/Sapiens-A-Brief-History-of-Humankind)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Villeneuve gets it. I heard in an interview he leans towards sci-fi and there's two big projects he'd like to do and everyone is assuming Dune is one of them. If he already has a yearning to do it, THAT would be the guy you'd want to do it. 

Enemy was my favorite movie I've seen in the last few years. I loved Prisoners, I liked Arrival. He's my favorite current director at the moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Han Kang is releasing another book. She authored The Vegetarian. 

And the guy who wrote Wolf in White Van is releasing another book in 2017 as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmmmmm, I don't think so. I got a shirt x 3 (for each day I volunteered) and food/snacks. I know the Games volunteers get more swag. But we did have a party one of the nights where they raffled off gifts from the vendor village every night. I got some free grips one year! But other people have gotten airdynes and things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 15:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rule is with this stuff is if it causes pain, stop. 

I had issues with my back just getting super washed out after kb swings. I had a decent deadlift. But my back squat was BARELY above my front squat numbers. And it seemed like I would always ended up having to take a few days off every month to let my back "rest". 

Long story short, I ended up with a disc herniation. I had sciatica and foot drop. Luckily did not have to have surgery. (And you do NOT want to end up at this point! MRI, doctors visits ... holy crap it adds up $$$)

Back pain can have a multitude of causes. So your best bet would be to see someone who is trained with athletic injuries and see if they have anything to offer. After dealing with neurosurgeons, I did not have the foot drop or sciatica anymore, I go see a chiro once a month about. He doesnt do a lot of bone cracking but a lot of myofascial release/ART techniques, and that has really helped me move forward with the healing process and understanding what I can and what I probably shouldnt do in the gym. Because a 20 year old Crossfit coach doesnt know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 15:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've volunteered at Regionals for about 3 years now. They keep you busy, but it's kind of fun to see how things work! If one is opening up near you, keep an eye out on crossfit games website's announcements for volunteer signup :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend is searching hard for some Hawks Knicks tickets on the 28th in the 100 or 200 section so I sent her your info!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Central Station, By Lavie Tidhar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crosstalk, By Connie Willis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper Girls, by Paper Girls by Brian K Vaughan and Cliff Chiang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Underground Railroad, by Colson Whitehead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't like, don't watch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard she wrote a thriller called "the chemist". Havent heard anything horrible about it like I heard about Twilight!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 14:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Horrorstr, by Grady Hendrix**

it is a horror comedy about a haunted IKEA like store. 

I liked it so much that I ran across **My Best Friend's Exorcism, by Grady Hendrix** from the library and had to check that out too. So I'm reading them both and having a good time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 05:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Franco, when was the last time you interacted with Tommy Wiseau (The Room guy) and do you feel comfortable describing it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For Survival, I'd definitely try out Endurance by Alfred Lansing. This ship got stuck in the ice when they were only a day away from their destination. They ended up being stuck there for 10 months! A lot of great reviews and an incredible story.

edit: I've also read Unbroken by Laura Hillenbrand. It's an awesome book and an awesome story. Probably really easy to find. But there was a movie released over here directed by Angelina Jolie so if they're a casual reader, they might have already read this one ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fates and Furies by Laurie Groff. But boy is it a slog to get through! 

The Vegetarian by Han Kang

Swamplandia by karen Russell


That's what I've read this year that kind of fits that ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Matched by Ally Conde was a big deal trilogy that never made it to the big screen like the other ones did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eleanor and Park is cute (by Rainbow Rowell). It's bascially about this shy asian and a poorer female who find connection on the schoolbus when the asian lets her borrow his sony walkman to listen to some sweet tunes. It's sweet. 

I've heard a lot of buzz around All the Bright Things by Jennifer Niven and The Sun Is Also a Star by Nicola Yoon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to a member's house on Wednesday to watch Love Actually after we take another member's pilates class. Two other ladies that go there are basically my best friends. 

So we're pretty close! But just within our class time. 6am cant sit with us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once you understand what books tend to turn you off, you know not to pick them up in the first place. I was falling victim to those $0.99-$2.99 books on amazon. And they were almost always the start of series and almost always crap. Now I just know not to even pick one up!

I also thought I wanted to read romance ... after a few of those, I know to stay away! Because I generally do not like romance books. Nothing happens in them. 

Everyone likes scifi ... scifi should be great! I pick up scifi books and realize they're not for me. So I stay away from most scifi.

Doesnt mean I wont ever pick up a scifi or romance book again (or even a romantic scifi book) .... if I hear about a good scifi book, I still might pick it up, I'm just not going to force myself to like the genre. 

As a Completionist myself, I find myself having to understand who I am as a reader (and you just gotta take time to figure that out), to select better books in the first place. 

If you find yourself reading a lot of crap, move along to a different genre!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between the LInes definitely reads like a YA ... I'd even say it's aimed towards 11 year olds bc it's so juvenile. 

But I read My Sister's Keeper and another one (where this teacher was accused of sleeping with one of his students and he becomes a dishwasher ... ) and I really liked those books!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Jodi Picoult, then I read that book she wrote with her daughter, Between the LInes, and was immediately turned off. I should re-visit her (adult) books again though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also listening to the Girl with all the Gifts on audiobook. It's a good romp so far! Melanie is extremely likable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Its a trilogy and I'm desperately hoping that the third book won't be a massive letdown (like in most of the other trilogies I've read)

I know! I hardly ever read trilogies anymore because of the time investment vs payoff ratio </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It becomes a bit of a slog to get through but I'm very glad I read it! Mainly the fact that it reads like one huge paragraph ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Tampa, by Alissa Nutting**

Finished this one. It's about a 26-year old teacher who has sexual attraction to teenage boys. Some people hate the book because it's offensive. I thought it was well-written, witty and shocking. It's not a book I'd recommend to friends "hey this book is about a child rapist, check it out!" but I mean, 4/5 stars. 

**A Fierce and Subtle Poison, by Samantha Mabry**

YA book about a mysterious girl who poisons people just by touching them (think plants ... like a poison ivy thing). This rich kid gets caught up with her when his gf is found on a beach, dead. It's the authors first book. I dont love it. I have about 50 pages left so I'm just trying to see what happens at this point. 

**Horrorstor, Grady Hendrix**

Just downloaded this one. I'm only a chapter in. But it's about a haunted Ikea like store.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There can only be one!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the bull is being more of a bro than the human.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only read Ocean at the end of the lane, but I dont really get what the bfd is surrounding Neil Gaiman either. 

I'm not sure if he's catering to a YA crowd or adult crowd. 

Gaiman seems to be great at world building but his characters seemed flat and boring in Ocean at the End of the Lane. And typically if you have all good or all bad characters, I find myself not enjoying those books.

I also suspect if you read a lot, you're going to eventually find there's an author you generally dislike who other people really love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 04:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes me wonder if Maeve is more sentient than Dolores? Dolores seemed to fulfill Fords wish in the finale. Maeve actually made a decision against the program ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 04:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that Dolores was starting to have inner monologue, which implied consciousness. But on the other hand, the piano started playing and it definitely seemed like Ford planned a lot of this too. So I'm trying to understand what was programmed by Ford versus what is a good prediction of what a "conscious" Dolores would do? 

Ford seemed to have planned or intuited Maeve's crew letting out all those guys on the cold room and having all them go after William (? I think)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 04:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doritos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Negan's got BOTH Rick's kids. That's nasty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The older Daryl gets, the more he looks like Kathy Bates  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Negan, Tegan, and Sara  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's Glenn's favorite restaurant? 

Popeyes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daryl, Carol, ... Coral  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh baby, baby, how was i sup-posed to know ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one zombie looks like the witch from Sword and the Stone or Never Ending story (the one that stretches Wesley)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 03:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would sing Gangsta's Paradise fo sho. 

 As I walk thru the valley of the shadow of death ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 03:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Negan looks like a mix bn Clive Owen and Javier Bardem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 03:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is like Hook when they're like Rufio!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 22:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have only read the Hugh Howey series (the first two books) and I really liked The Water Knife by Paolo B. It's set in a similar world where water is on short supply and only the rich can afford it. It really reads like an action movie though. 

I also remember reading a lot of Blake Crouch (Pines). But I didnt want to get into another series so I kind of stopped reading this after the first book. 

A Darker Shade of Magic is on my to-read list and I feel like it might be of a similar vein to what you're looking for. 

Sidenote: I feel like when Silo came out, people were also excited about Ready Player One and Martian. But those have been very much exposed on this subreddit. But, still, if you havent read them, then get on it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 22:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read quite a few Bill Bryson books (Short History of Nearly Everything is amazing too!) and Erik Larson (DitWC and Garden of Beasts). 

I really really liked Laura Hillenbrand's style of writing. I loved Unbroken (this Olympian gets stranded at sea for over a month and then ends up in a Japanese POW camp during WWII). And now I want to read Seabiscuit. 

Now I kinda want to check out Lost City of Z

On my to-read list that's simliar is A Spy Among Friends (about a British spy during the Cold War) and Into Thin Air (about an Mt Everest expedition). I'm also very interested in a book called Into the Abyss (about a plane crash where the only survivors are a cop, a prisoner and a mayor - something like that) but it was written by a granddaughter? and so I'm not sure how factual things are. 

Also, read A Short HIstory of Nearly Eveyrthing by Bryson! It's long but the chapters are very digestible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 22:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I immediately thought of Hyperbole and a Half. I wasnt a huge fan of Furiously Happy personally but I did listen to it on audiobook and Jenny Lawson has a high pitched grating voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or putting on 15 pounds! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll just stop the fall with my vagina  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 15:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in the minority and was not a fan of the book. However, I can understand how other people like it. It's a good book, just not for me. 

I just personally didnt like the arbitrariness of it all. You could take out or add chapters and not really affect the outcome of the book. Nothing built upon itself; it was just a collection of short stories as far as I was concerned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was spending so much money on amazon because I was buying so many ebooks. So after hearing how you can download ebooks from the library, I was like - eh let me check this out  .... 

I was kind of hesitant bc I didnt want to be mandated to read a book in a 3 week window. And I was also kind of wondering about how to get the books to my kindle (software? yikes). 

But I can turn off my wifi to my Kindle if Im REALLY into a book (and it wont turn it in). And you can use amazon to download the books you check out from the library (so it already works for your kindle!). 

What I also noticed as a benefit is that I increased the quality books I was reading. I was buying all the $1-5 amazon books bc I didnt want to spend like $15 on a Harper Collins release .... but now I can just check whatever new release I want out (for the most part, especially nonfiction!). 

I am also reading paper books again.

I check out audiobooks. 

I downloaded Mango and I'm learning spanish too. 

You can also download magazines - Oprah, Yoga Journal, Rolling Stone, etc. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of Fantasia  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 05:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if you didn't want a tribute, you shouldn't be posting all that porn! 

But seriously, your foodporn pics are amazing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Underground Airlines is not very pop culture heavy as far as Ive read. They have general mentions of smartphones but not of a specific type. Its definitely not like Ready Player One specific ... 

I really like Girl with all the Gifts so far. The narrator is good. And I feel like the author really puts us in the head of a "child" that has only grown up in one building. I'm less than 10% in though. But I'm not finding myself struggling with the decision to audiobook or listen to the radio on my commute home; I always want to listen to GwAtG.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think the concept is very interesting. I hope the plot can keep pace with my expectations.  I'm not really getting that deep social commentary that NPR led me to believe .... 

edit: I got this from the library too and I have to average 25 pages a night to get it done in time ....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Ursula's Poor Unfortunate Soul from The Little Mermaid  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 poor 4 h m  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 14:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Girl with All the Gifts, by MR Carey**

This has been on my to-read list for awhile. Listening to it on audiobok. I'm only a chapter in. 

**Underground Airlines, by Ben Winters**

Set in today (so there's cellphones, atms, etc) but the Civl War never happened and so there are 4 states where slavery still exists (called The Hard Four). We're following a free black man as he's tracking an escaped slave? As far as I can tell right now, anyways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 14:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive been reading this off and on for ages! It's taking me forever to get through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did this episode need to be over an hour?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When she assumed that walker with dreads was Heath, my friend yelled, "THATS RACIST."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The theme of the episode has to be Tara's lactating boobs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peter Pan of Walking Dead right now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! Rick has zero guns at the moment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Rick kill all their men when they killed the Saviors hideout? 

I doubt it, but that'd be awesome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I kind of like the episode. Women only community reminds me of Z Nation and Y: The Last Man  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Natania: I hope you like fish! 

Tara:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Natania is a post-apocalypse name. There's no way that's her real name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tara's boobs are off the chain tho  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tara and Heath have zero clue that those are probably the last guns that any Alexandrian owns  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like with Tara being a lesbian, she kind of lucked out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that an all chick place?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wanted a Lost/Walking Dead crossover  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 15:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not a big fan of having a the block of text requirement for text posts when people can post links to articles with really no thought attached. 


But I really do like the sub and I'm sure that rule was enacted for a reason. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stopped reading for pleasure during college. There are times in your life where you have to learn to say "No". And I chose to say no to reading. I was already writing papers and reading chemistry books, etc .... I picked up the habit again later. But I have friends try to fit EVERYTHING in. But you have to say no to some things. It might not be reading ... but there are so many hours in the day. 

I personally like listening to audiobooks during my commutes. And I like to read about 20-30 minutes before I go to bed. And that's usually just stopping my social media browsing earlier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 15:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read this from the library. I think I forget about short story collections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 22:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We started as the Woodstock of Fitness."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 19:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Tampa, by Alissa Nutting**

This 26-year old attractive female has an unnatural attraction to teenage boys. And of course she chooses to be a teacher. She's very manipulative and sexually aggressive. The book is indeed shocking but, I must say, well-written. I've never read American Psycho buttttt I'd be interested if somenoe has read both of these books and can make some comparisons bc this chick is ... I mean, no words.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 04:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Maggie should have saved that watch for her unborn child.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 03:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gregory has those grandpa brown pants on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 03:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is Trevor?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 03:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like some civil war era discussion going on bn shitbag Gregory and Negan's Billy Bob Thornton  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 03:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carl: Get in loser, we're going shopping  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 00:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During college and a year or so after, I did not read any books for enjoyment. 

Writing papers and reading chemistry books for school drained me. When I needed a mental break, reading a book for enjoyment didn't seem to be a good option at all. I'd go to Netflix or some reality tv show to give myself a break.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 20:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever thought of trying out a book club? I think it's nice to get a relevant and fun read for the bulk of your office. And then send out a weekly email to the participants suggested page reads to get through for that week. And then at the end of the month, meet up at a bar or something and drink and talk about books and make friends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does he have The Villa by any chance? Asking for a friend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 21:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read The Road Less Travelled by Peck and it was a life changing book for me when I read it! The first part, he comes across fairly haughty. But the ideas he put forth in the book are solid! 

I have another book by him about Civility. He talked about how America used to have civics lessons ... what it meant to have respect for your country and he started touching on how it's no longer taught in schools (again, this is a dated book). but I didnt really read beyond that. 

he seems like an interesting guy to say the least!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 14:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's very informal and there are better ways to change the topic of your discussion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 03:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot he ran like that   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 03:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh I know, they're going to ruin it if history with sequels tells us anything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont even read King to understand this but the first thing that came to mind was Apt Pupil when I read your comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Books on the Subway or something like it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have some decent books that I own and I dont really feel like selling them for $0.50. I guess I *could* donate them to the library, but I've been hearing about books on the subway with Anna Kendrick and Emma Watson. The problem is ... I dont have a subway around me! I'd like to leave books in a similar manner though ...  

My questions are: 

- Is that considered littering since I'm not a celebrity? 

- If I don't have a subway around me, what places would you recommend to leave a book? 

- Is there a sticker that I could put on the book that's not so specific to subways?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took me 2-3 months to get a chin up. 

After I did my workout, I would go to the pullup bar and do 3-5 negatives. And then I would just go for it and try a chinup. 

I'm 5'10", 200# btw. I am not new to fitness though, so I can do pushups and the like .... 

I had some smaller girls at my same gym getting pullups after a few months. But we were doing it after almost ALL our workouts! Patience, consistency and dont burn yourself out where you cant try it again the next day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed Before the Fall by noah hawley. The author writes for tv shows (I think Fargo). And the writing was accessible and I found myself getting through the book very quickly. 

I added Wolf Road to my to-read list! And Another Brooklyn was already on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 16:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
