<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5968</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 18:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1970's Western Field (Sears) .30-06.

The thing can knock a deer down at 600 yards and absolutely take a coyote to pieces at about 400. I exploded a duck with it once at about 100 feet and reeeeaaalllly felt bad about it afterward; poor thing was just gone in a puff of feather and red spray.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 20:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This scenario happens way more often than one would expect.

When I was 20 I was out hunting on a friend's property when this tall, thin figure stood up from a field of thigh-high grass about 600 yards away from me. 

Through the x3 power scope on my .30-06 I couldn't clearly see what it was, and began to assume that it was a deer standing either facing directly at me or directly away from me, because I wasn't seeing the large, obvious side-on profile of a normal deer.

The shape was the right height and color to be a deer and I was sitting in a blind overlooking a field that deer regularly crossed in between patches of wooded area. So the thing must have been a deer...at least that's what my brain was telling me.

I chambered a round, clicked the safety over to "fire" and was just about to exhale and wait for my sight picture to steady out, when something in my head yelled *STOP*.

I put the rifle back on "safe" and pulled up the binoculars around my neck, and, sure as shit, this fucking moron *man* clearly comes into focus. Asshole had no orange on whatsoever, was in full camo, and was most likely on my friend's property without permission.

God damn idiot came about 1.5 seconds away from being dead as fuck. (I'm an excellent shot with a rifle...can't hit shit with a shotgun) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 19:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like he's from an agressor squad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 19:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there an article or story on this? What exactly happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 19:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rookie Ensign U.S. Navy pilots regularly flew the F-8 and A-7 off the deck of carriers with the wings still folded up. Happened all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 00:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hooray just finished Part 1 and saw this was up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 21:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you ALWAYS deliver. 
I get excited every time your username pops up on a submission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 19:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha cool. I hardly ever watched Eagle Eye because I was either in band or in a class in which the teacher didn't bother attempting to turn the TV on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 01:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My silhouette is painted on the wall in the Fine Arts hallway. The image is of a band Drum Major with his arms out conducting and his face turned to the side. It's me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 01:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I graduated in 2009.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 01:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when did you graduate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 05:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may have my floorplan backwards. B201 would be the classroom furthest West at the end of B hall, right? It sits on the South side of the hallway with the door facing North toward the west stairwell leading down to the first floor of B hall. 

If *you're* right, then yeah the classroom would be B201. 

If *I'm* right, then it's B210. 

Simple clerical error, either way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 17:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More likely that Scarface 1 is in a wheelchair or shambling around with a cane calling all the other flight leads "kids" or "young'n's". 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 21:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 21:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of fucking course it does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 01:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but I stiiiiiiiiilllll haven't found





...what I'm looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 05:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you ever find yourself quoting AC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 19:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My two favorites are the 8492nd "sure thing"

And

"They've all gone insane!" 

What are yours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simply Unsettling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 08:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 07:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just played in the F-5 too. Seems cool but after working almost entirely as air to air, it's so hard for me to get into a ground attacker. 

I need to beef out an A-10... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 05:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't. 

Not sure if they've handed out prizes yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 05:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> np. still finished top-500 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 05:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unsurprising. It costs like $45,000 of ground maintenance *per flight hour* and the ratio of ground maintenance to flight time is somewhere between 11-18 hours for every 1 hour spent in the air. 
EVERY aircraft has to undergo a monthly maintenance package that, alone, costs like $125K. 
The A-10 was supposed to go out of service this year, but, because this production halt for the Raptor was already in the works, the A-10 has been spared the chopping block. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 05:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F-111, F-105 THUD, MiG 15   17, ME 109, P-38, A-4   A-6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 05:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the AC2 soundtrack in its entirety (plus some unreleased content) is available on itunes. I think some of the other games are as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 04:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice job! I'm at 555 right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 03:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gracias. looks like I'm staying up tonight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what time does the event go til tomorrow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 03:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ?? I'm central standard time U.S. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
