<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3967</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, with Sowell back, you think the coaches bench Fant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cut..... Bennet? Or trade him. Pray that the oline holds up?

Is this an option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The configuration on Lenovo's website offer a max of 16GB, but the hardware supports up to 32GB. In my research ([Reddit](https://www.reddit.com/r/thinkpad/comments/4lft2p/would_a_thinkpad_13_support_32gb_or_ram/) and [Crucial](http://www.crucial.com/usa/en/compatible-upgrade-for/Lenovo/thinkpad-13)), I've found that you can, in fact, install 32GB of memory in the 13 (Intel version).

I mean for the bit of development I do, the [i5-6300U](http://ark.intel.com/products/88190/Intel-Core-i5-6300U-Processor-3M-Cache-up-to-3_00-GHz) is more than enough. I run a VM or two for my dev environments with Vagrant, so memory is usually what my laptop is hungry for (and yes, I know 32GB is still overkill haha). The 6300U supports Intel's virtualization tech, so I guess that helps too.

Can you define "kind of suck" a bit more? I'm just curious as to why you'd prefer the previous generation i5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RW3 with the fadeaway... fucking love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 06:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd build a completely stock, brand spanking new, 1998 Jeep Cherokee XJ. Every single part brand new. 0 miles. Original design.

edit: My bad, you said "mod your Jeep".

I'd do a 3.5" RE lift with 33 BFG muds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 01:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ow. Gronk is a monster... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 07:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://media.giphy.com/media/GlSOTpOQHJVKM/giphy.gif

Bad man... that ET3... bad man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 23:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fear of missing out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 23:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad yall... what I was really trying to say was:

"I'm taking shots of Crown Royal and chasing with Rainier." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 10:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm shot of crown and trainer beer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 04:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a bit farther up north, but I really love [Saffron Grill](http://www.saffrongrillseattle.com/saffrongrill/index.html). I like their garlic naan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 02:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. That's where I got mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 20:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if it seems like I'm hijacking... but my Thinkpad 13 will be arriving next Thur. I got the i5 with FHD and plan on installing 32 gigs of memory because, ya know, Vagrant and stuff.

Anyway, is the trackpoint that much more terrible than on the 460(s)? I'm upgrading from the X220. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 08:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simply updating the harness (Putco) got my stock headlights to shine nice and bright. They aren't HID bright, but they are definitely brighter than stock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Ordering mine this weekend. Already have 32 gigs of memory ready to go in... ya know... for programming stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first Thinkpad (and laptop I ever bought for myself) was a T61. Got me through my computer science days at university back in 2007. 

I used it until 2011. I upgraded the CPU, LCD screen, memory, and HD. It was my first foray into Thinkpad tinkering. It was my first foray into Linux (Ubuntu Gutsy Gibbon). And it was the last Thinkpad I owned with the classic IBM logo on it.

Ah, the memories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should offer classes on football somewhere. I'd gladly get a B.S. or B.A. in armchair coaching/quarterbacking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the heads up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 08:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But like, we'd miss out on all the GREATNESS we're about to get back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 00:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean dedicated graphics? Will she be doing any gaming on it? I see no reason for a dedicated GPU at in this case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 00:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tried speaking with a representative for this option for my X220 and, more recently, my Thinkpad 13. Unfortunately, they don't do this. At least, I haven't had any success. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For multi-line blocks, I prefer
    
    .each do
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 21:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For more a bit more insight into the defensive principles described in the article, I found the first chapter of Chris B. Brown's [The Art of Smart Football](https://www.amazon.com/Art-Smart-Football-Chris-Brown/dp/069244825X/ref=pd_sbs_14_img_0/160-2780550-0482554?ie=UTF8 psc=1 refRID=9V6RQVVSYRBWJ5W2DXZB) a great read!

Goes into why Carroll prefers a one-gap defense. Also describes the reasoning behind his 4-3 Under and Cover 3 schemes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Capitol Hill and First Hill. You should be able to find a 1BR within that price range in those neighborhoods. Your wife could probably walk to work. And as for nightlife, it's a pretty lively place.

I've lived in SLU, Lower Queen Anne, Fremont, Northgate, and Capitol Hill. Feel free to PM me if you have any more specific questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work down on Dayton Ave back in 2010. It's definitely got an older crowd, lots of retirees. However, if you're looking to settle down, I think Edmonds is a great place to live.

 Feels up and coming, like it might be a good future investment?

I haven't heard anything about Edmonds being "up and coming" in any way. Not amongst my peers anyway. Nobody is "flocking" to Edmonds... Property, in general, is a good investment though!

It's not the city, so it'll be slow and boring. Yes, there are busses and trains, but getting into downtown via public transit will be no less shittier than it already is to commute from any suburb. In fact, commuting from downtown Edmonds to downtown would probably be worse than other suburbs because it's proximity to I5.

Costco is just a quick hop south on 99. The Harbor Square Athletic Club is still one of the best gyms I've ever been to in the entire region (though it's relatively expensive). Great crabbing and squidding from the Edmonds fishing pier!

My wife and I are also in the hunt for a house to buy, good luck with the house hunt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Checkout [Aloha Ramen](https://www.yelp.com/biz/aloha-ramen-seattle) up north. It's a small place, but really good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 03:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to Seattle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 21:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! I ended up buying some overpriced water from that same stand! It was definitely a bit of a hike. Did you get to see the sunset from up there? We went up earlier in the day, so there was no sunset for us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 23:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did these just bolt (screw?) right into the existing holes from the stock speakers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 21:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, there's tons to do in Florence, it's a very popular destination in all of Europe. Based on many recommendations, I visited popular sites such as Duomo, Ponte Vecchio, Uffizi, Piazzale Michelangelo, etc.

However, one of my favorite places to visit was [Giardino delle Rose](https://www.visitflorence.com/what-to-see-in-florence/gardens-in-florence.html), up in the hills of the Oltrarno district. The view was pretty spectacular and I remember it better than the view from Piazzale Michelangelo.

Don't get me wrong, the panoramic view of the city is awesome from up there, but I quite enjoyed this view as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's been months since my visit to Florence, Italy. One of my favorite memories (unexpectedly) was exploring Giardino delle Rose in the Oltrarno district. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 21:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like Earl Thomas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome! [Teku Tavern](http://www.tekutavern.beer/) also hosts Seahawks games. Might wanna hit that up on Monday night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why dont these Seattleites want the single mom in Renton or the family in Everett coming to the waterfront with their kids?

If only we had more effective ways for suburbanites to get in and out of the city without driving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling most players in the NFL are intelligent and have a deep understanding of the game. It's his ability to express and convey these concepts to fans like us. He's a great story-teller! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you need liquidity? Like, is this for an emergency fund of some kind? If so, I'd go with BECU over an online bank like Ally. If you don't need liquidity, then any online bank with the highest % would be my choice. Well... not *any*, do your research first! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a 3.5" RE lift and ran with stock brake-lines for awhile. However, I extended them because I was afraid they'd rip out during flex. It also makes it easier to drop the axles (for any other work you need to do).

I also drove for awhile without an SYE. The vibes were annoying, so I did a T-case drop in the meantime. A T-case drop is not a permanent solution, but it'll hold over until I have time/money for an SYE.

Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 23:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in the suburbs for a good portion of my life. One major difference I've noticed between my suburban friends and city friends is a huge aversion to walking.

Assuming you are able to (which may not be the case), simply walking to the grocery store would save you the $2.50. Lower Queen Anne is a very walkable area, so it shouldn't be too terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 23:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you try visiting the Orca website?

1. [Get an Orca card](https://orcacard.com/ERG-Seattle/getACard.do?m=2)
2. Add value to a card [online](https://orcacard.com/ERG-Seattle/haveACard.do?m=5) or [at a kiosk](https://orcacard.com/ERG-Seattle/p2_002.do?m=42 i=542)
3. When hopping on the bus or rail, tap the card on [the reader](https://www.orcacard.com/ERG-Seattle/common/images/easyToUse.jpg)

It's really that simple.

edit: On the rail, you tap [the reader](http://www.soundtransit.org/sites/default/files/styles/hero/public/images/fares/orca/hero_ORCA.jpg) before getting on the train AND when you get off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 22:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are tons of places, you might have some luck searching /r/SeattleWA for "Pioneer Square".

A couple of my own favorites in the area:

* [Tat's Deli](http://www.tatsdeli.com/)
* [McCoy's Firehouse](http://mccoysfirehouse.com/)
* [J   M Cafe](https://www.facebook.com/jmcafeseattle.pioneersquare/)
* [Pyramid Alehouse](http://www.pyramidbrew.com/alehouses/seattle/)
* [Quality Athletics](https://www.facebook.com/qualityathletics/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I just stayed at the Hotel 1000 for a "stay-cation" and I'd say it fits your description. It's sleek and modern, has a spa, gym, etc. We were able to walk everywhere (Westlake, Pioneer Square, Waterfront). It's close to the Pioneer Square light rail station, so you can take a quick ride up to explore Capitol Hill (we live on Capitol Hill and we took the rail down to get to the hotel).

We did some quick research on the Fairmont Hotel, Inn at the Market, and Alexis Hotel. You'd be fine with the others, but Hotel 1000 was our choice.

PM me if you have any other questions. Goodluck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 22:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! Lived in the area my whole life and finally got to do this tour. Pretty interesting stuff! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hanging out on Yesler and Occidental this evening </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 08:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 07:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wearing baggy clothing. Boy, was I wrong. Now I'm an /r/malefashionadvice drone: blue OCBD, khakis, and Clarks desert boots... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 07:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A pro, in my opinion, is that it hides any belongings you might have in your car if you park in an exposed area. Not that you should have any valuables in your car at all, but it's definitely better to have tinted windows to prevent a would-be prowler from peeking in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 00:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only place I've gotten green beans were Seattle Coffee Works downtown and Vivace in South Lake Union. Don't know how prices compare anywhere else, but they seem to have good quality raw beans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice photo. I love that our city is growing "up" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a nice location in terms of easy access to all the things a 20-something would want living in the city. 

I take the 12 every day from 19th to 2nd (on Madison) and do notice more homeless folks hopping on and off the bus around that area, but none have ever caused me any trouble. I wouldn't be nervous at all. Just be vigilant when walking around at night (just like you would anywhere else you're unfamiliar with).

Side note: check out [George's Deli](https://www.yelp.com/biz/georges-sausage-and-delicatessen-seattle) and let me know how it is! Always wanted to eat there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! It's a cool hike isn't it? Check out this [absolutely stunning view](http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-TfinVGq6EYo/VLNYwtLLIMI/AAAAAAAADxQ/xBZyQ1eieUA/s1600/IMG_20150110_104830554.jpg) that I was able to witness the last time I was up there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Seattle Coffee Works? I do like me some Ladro though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try [this](http://betterspecs.org/), it comes in handy when I want to know if there's a particular way to assert something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Godspeed. If you come out alive, let us know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The next step for the new medical school is approval for membership by the American Association of Medical Colleges

Wouldn't it be in the best interest of this association to NOT include WSU as a med school? They'd potential lose incoming students, right?

edit: Go Cougs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, I'll plan to run a hose over it when I get the chance. Until then, I'll just keep clearing out puddles. Might be a good time to rip out the carpet and rhino-line the thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wanna find out how huge puddles of water end up on my floor when it rains on my XJ? Because... damn it... that's what I'm dealing with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at that teamwork too. The chip by Ifedi to help Britt (?) get around before going into the second level. The ceiling looks really high on this guy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 05:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the pleasure of driving dune buggies through this. View was breathtaking and the buggies were a really fun way to get around! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So was it a miscommunication between McCray and Sherman on coverage? I can't imagine Sherman would bite so hard on the slant unless he didn't know it was deep cover 3... it almost looked like he was playing man. Or maybe he was trying to do to much and just blew his coverage?

Meh, it was an ugly play altogether. McCray just let Julio blow by him and there was no way ET3 could get there in time to stop it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll occasionally read up on http://www.freshjess.com. She mostly blogs about fashion events in Seattle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The feel of a vehicle is important to me.

It rides rough. You might not like that.

 I am not mechanically inclined. From what I've read, the Cherokee is easy to work on.

You're going to have a bad time.

 I am not good at trouble shooting.

You're going to have a bad time.

Unless you've got someone who will work on your XJ if/when it breaks down or needs maintenance (or you've got enough cash to pay someone to do it), I'd stay clear of one. While you might get lucky on one that needs little-to-no maintenance, chances are you're gonna have to put in some wrench work.

Good luck in your search! Enjoy Hawaii! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't be attending the game, but I'm sorry to hear about your uncle. Go nuts and get loud with fellow 12s in his honor! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 22:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit. Hopefully he's good to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 01:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The link is an article from 2010. Do you have a source that's more recent?

edit: Go Cougs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 01:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wear a JCrew Medium Slim button-down. Would Uniqlo medium fit similarly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 01:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a couple of flannels from JCF and noticed they were really long. However, the "flannels" at Old Navy were a better length. Which ones did you try? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 06:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a different view high above the city, you could check out the Columbia Tower [Sky View Observatory](http://www.skyviewobservatory.com/
). 

However, I wouldn't just un-plan the Space Needle trip. It's really a "do it once and never again" type thing. I'd say the same thing about the [Great Wheel](http://seattlegreatwheel.com/). It's expensive, really nice waterfront city view, but I'd probably never ride it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 06:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome. I wanna do the subwoofer mod. Did you do that yourself? Or buy one of the "kits" from Crutchfield? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 06:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to WA! What's the name of this hike? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else have their prom here? Gorgeous venue, terrible acoustics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought this was what most XJ owners did. Bought stock, built it up from scratch. The "fun" is experiencing the same joy and pain of getting it the way you want it.

I'm not saying one route is better than the other, just genuinely surprised at how many folks bought their XJs built already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  we assumed a 20-percent down payment on a 30-year mortgage

I mean, I don't think there are many who will have problems affording the monthly mortgage payment. I think the true barrier is getting a large enough downpayment.

According to this article, many folks could probably afford to live in these neighborhoods based on the monthly payment, but who has $60k just laying around?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 02:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any advice on the fit of the their slim casual button-down sizing? How does it compare to JCrew's slim fit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 02:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any advice on the fit of the their Regent or Milano sport shirt sizing? How does it compare to JCrew's slim fit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's more trouble than it's worth, I don't see why selling it would be an issue. Yes, you will probably regret it, because XJs are awesome, but if it doesn't make sense for you to own one, why bother? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pretty cool. There's a bus stop right in front of it and it's already on a busy street (California Ave). Seems like a good option for someone who works downtown, but wants to live a bit further from the city. I wonder what the rent will be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 08:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I'll throw up a peace sign to other modded XJs. Rarely do I get anything in response, but I know it's generally a Wrangler thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Capitol Hill, back closer to 15th, has plenty of apartments in that price range. Just know you'll have to pay a bit more for parking in addition to rent. Even then, under 2k a mo is very doable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 01:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 23:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There's also that place that specializes in growler fills, The Growl Store, on Madison just east of 12th Ave.

I roll by this on the 12 every day on the way to work. Going to have to check it out!

EDIT: https://www.facebook.com/growl64 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 22:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wearing my jersey. I don't see anyone else wearing a jersey. Fridays on a bye week is still Blue Friday... right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 22:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same... this is definitely Comcast's way of ensuring some future profit. 1TB isn't a huge deal right now, but with tech like 4k becoming more and more popular, expect to pay for data plan "upgrades" soon. Not to mention, demand to stream things vs watching them on cable (cordcutting).

As per advice from [this thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/cordcutters/comments/567zkb/comcasts_1tb_data_caps_start_to_roll_out/), I recommend contacting the FCC and filing a complaint.

https://consumercomplaints.fcc.gov/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket_form_id=38824 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 21:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Nominated homecoming queen as a joke." Some cruel fuckers out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 21:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to the actual event: http://www.seattlemade.org/sm-events/seattle-made-market/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I play flag football, I always try to park in the garage attached (or nearby) the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation. It costs money, but it's covered. I think there's a security guard that patrols, but I'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manual tranny? Because damn... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 22:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lasser raised some valid concerns about the building, including the traffic caused by loading trucks potentially double-parking on 19th and ADA accessible front entrances.

Either way, I don't think she opposes the building outright, just the design and lack of input the neighbors had in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if we imposed a tax on property owners who don't reside in the property they purchased? It'd be more targeted at those who are using Seattle houses as "a safe harbor" for cash and driving up prices, regardless of where they're from. So, less "an attack on foreigners", since that seems to bother people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wondered about the spare tire on top. Are you ever worried it'll get stolen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love squid jigging. I used to hit up the Seattle Aquarium pier during the week back in the day, but ever since the Wheel went up, it's been busier and busier in the evening. Maybe I'll try heading out again this season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 20:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cool to think that we could potentially colonize Mars in my lifetime. Even cooler that two of the big players (Blue Origin and Boeing) are from the PNW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> West Seattle is definitely on the radar, but I'm a bit wary of the bus options that go out there. Neighborhoods along the light rail seem to be better options (Columbia City, Beacon Hill, etc.).

Do you commute into the city for work? Care to share your experience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, where did you end up buying? I'm currently in the process of hunting for a home as close to downtown as possible.

Feel free to PM me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 00:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unrelated note, I suppose... does anyone here work at Blue Origin? Just curious how it compares to, say, Boeing in terms of workplace "culture". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 17:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, there's a Mariner's game today. Expect delays in the south end. Keep Fighting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 01:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pardon the newbiness, what's "NIR"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 22:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking forward to that Sherman/Marshall matchup! Hoping to see him bait Fitzpatrick into throwing his way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 22:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gives us a chance to see how much Ifedi affects our O-Line cohesion. He's back this week right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 01:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you looked here: https://www.reddit.com/r/Watches/wiki/buyingguide

They break it down by price too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 00:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Carroll says defense was frustrated with last two drives. Reiterates Seahawks were in pass-defense mode while 49ers ran it.

Man, I was getting so frustrated watching the end of that game. You could totally see the frustration on the defenses' faces after those 49er TDs.

I suppose, overall, it was a decent strategy to focus on stopping the deep pass and just let them run the clock down.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 22:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not go to the gym. Do not spread this shit around. Nobody will admire you for working out sick. Stay home, get better, then hit the gym hard when you're healed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In [this Alan Thrall video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BYKScL2sgCs), he mentions his head rising off the bench. I don't know if this will cause long-term injury though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 21:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sent you a PM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I was farming Karp to evolve one down at Ivar's... sure enough when I'm close to 100 candies, one pops up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a special something about breakfast while camping... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 07:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nothing like some New Yorkers while in a cabin in the woods! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 06:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 20:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of Starfox64. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 23:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So, if you look back on all of your career, what, for you, was like the highlight?

 Being able to retire. And then being able to do this with you after retiring.

The most interesting thing I learned about Marshawn was how he viewed himself as more than an NFL player. That he doesn't view himself as "Marshawn: The Beast", but a person. He's someone who is grateful to be alive and healthy, who is seeking happiness, who is trying to live a fulfilling life... just like the rest of us out here.

Blegh, this shit is too deep for me right now... GO SEAHAWKS!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 18:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 18:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anti-seize when you get the old fuckers off and the new bolts in. Since it's a budget boost, I imagine you might go higher later. So, you'll thank your past self if you make the next removal process easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 20:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I caught a ton during the jersey retirement game on Saturday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 19:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought some bluetooth headphones awhile back thinking, "I can make my gym mixes on Spotify and just use my phone for music during my workouts!" Real fuckin' convenient to have one device for music, food tracking, etc.

Now, I'm going back to a dedicated MP3 player for music during my runs/lifts. I'm not as distraction-prone as I thought as was, often checking my texts and ESPN updates between sets. Kind of breaks the concentration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 08:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. I installed the Putcos before a road trip and the stock headlights were much much brighter than before! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
