<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4306</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 08:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you stringing this girl along? You don't want to be with her. Taking a 'break' isn't what needed to happen. You're either together or you're not. Break up with her and let her find somebody that makes her happy. And you do the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're moving in together! Finally got everything worked out and it's happening. I can't wait to have a sleepover every night with my best friend!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 07:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of odd, but when I was feeling really low about a year ago I adopted a cat? It was mostly because I needed something to love me regardless but I also wanted to have something that relied on me; something that needed me to stay alive in order for its life to continue smoothly. My cat really saved my life... Still an asshole though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing I would say is a concern is potentially the Neutrogena sunscreen? A few of their sunscreens have methylisothiazolinone in it, which is a preservative recommended only for rinse-off products. You'd have to check the ingredients of the type you have, though. My go-to sunscreen is either the Biore UV Aqua Rich Watery Essence or Dr. Dennis Gross Sheer Mineral Sun Spray. 

Also, Drunk Elephant's products are the best. Their vitamin c serum is killer and I just got their TLC Framboos serum a few weeks ago and my skin has such a beautiful natural glow to it; I've stopped wearing foundation.

What type of maracuja oil are you using? I haven't done enough research on the Tarte one but I've heard a couple people say they just buy passiflora edulis seed oil from the local health food store since it's a third of the price of Tarte's version for the exact same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you actually expect him to take your advice when the way you phrased it is so incredibly condescending? Maybe you're right about them and their relationship will fizzle out, or they won't meet, etc, but all the kid was asking about was fun things to do with his girlfriend. He's happy doing what he's doing and he's not hurting anyone. He's 14. Give the kid a break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 22:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mahatma Gandhi, as you know, walked barefoot most of the time, which produced an impressive set of calluses on his feet. He also ate very little, which made him rather frail and with his odd diet, he suffered from bad breath. 

He became known as a super-calloused fragile mystic hexed by halitosis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 22:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yoga pants and one of my boyfriend's sweaters. Half my closet consists of stuff I've taken from him. I swear, clothes just feel better when they're not yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 08:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this feeling exactly. My skincare routine used to consist of this scrub and Johnson's baby lotion as moisturizer. How my skin didn't just throw in the towel and disintegrate is a mystery to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 07:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know the marshmallows that come in Lucky Charms? It turns out you can buy a pound of them for only $12 on Amazon. Damn you, 'buy with one click' button. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 07:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realized that every time something good/funny happened I would immediately think "I can't wait to tell him about this".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend is spending Christmas with my family this year (who have all met and love him) and then we're moving in together early next year! It's the first time I've ever lived with someone so it's really scary but I've also never been in love like this so I'm really excited to see how the future goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 03:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not necessarily planning on reporting her because she cut my hours, moreso it was the straw that broke the camel's back. I'm hoping that at the very least they'll have something to say to her about the way she treats her employees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My boss (40s F) cut my (19 F) hours drastically and I don't know what to do next </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been working in a high end women's clothing store for almost a year now. I started as a general sales associate but I was promoted to the head of the lingerie department about 6 months ago. I have had several other jobs and I've always gotten along well with my coworkers and supervisors so I don't think that my personality factors in.

My boss has been there for about 2 years. During the interview process, we talked for about 15 minutes and then she hired me on the spot, which she told me she's never done before. The first shift that I had, though, her demeanor totally changed. She was short with me and rolled her eyes every time I had a question. Her take on 'training' is basically to throw the employee in the middle of the action and they'll have to figure it out themselves.

The turnover rate for my store is absolutely abysmal; the average length that we employ someone is 5 months. Aside from my boss, I've been here the longest.

Onto the pressing issue, I recently got sick but since my boss dislikes when people call in sick, I stuck it out for a couple shifts and just relied on tea and Buckleys. Last Saturday, though, I was puking uncontrollably so I called in sick and went to the doctor. He gave me some medication for the nausea and told me to stay on bed rest. I turned my sick note in the next shift I had.

Since it's December I've been working a LOT of hours despite being part time (I'm a full time student). I was scheduled to work approx 35 hours a week for the rest of December which was going to be really hard to handle on top of school, but I was managing quite well. 

Skip to this morning, I opened the store and went to double check the schedule to see who else I worked with, and almost all of my shifts have been crossed out. I am now working 4 hours a week for the rest of December. My parents pay my rent so I don't have to worry about housing or anything, but I'm still annoyed and confused.

My coworkers are as mad as I am and have said they would back me up if I contact HR, but at this point I kind of just want to quit. I was offered a job a couple of weeks ago that pays almost twice what I make here, but I'm really good at my current job and I get excited to go to work. 

This isn't the first instance of my boss screwing her employees over. She has a long history of slacking and spending her entire shift on her phone in the staff room, as well as leaving 4 hours early and telling me to clock her out when her shift is supposed to end. She also manipulates our sales target program and changes other peoples' names to hers so that she looks good in front of her bosses.

I have my letter of resignation typed up and ready to go but I'm on the fence about turning it in. I do really love my job but our HR department has proven ineffective in the past. My boyfriend thinks that I should just quit and report her and hope that they do something, but I feel like that's just the easy way out. Is it?

TL;DR - My boss cut my hours from 35/week to 4/week after I called in sick, despite having a doctor's note. My coworkers and friends think I should report her to HR and see if anything is done, but at this point I kind of just want to be done. Is quitting just the easy way out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 09:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got out of an abusive relationship in the beginning of this year and I never got to yell at him. I never got to tell him how I really felt. I never got to be angry. I have this weird sense of half closure surrounding him and I think it'll always be that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
