<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7426</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was rushing to finish this up before the update and was finally able to do so today (at the last minute too). If for some reason the update doesn't push today, I'll keep filling in Qasr Graa but I'm happy with where it is at now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ul Uren - 100% Finished...Friggen' Finally! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another tip I have is to browse r/mapmaking. It's a really great community that has excellent resources for beginners. There is a little bit of a stigma against Inkarnate maps on that sub though because some people view them as derivative while forgetting not all of us are as artistically inclined as others or have the resources to buy software like Campaign Cartographer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The darkened "map folds" are the borders of each if the individual maps I created in the program. I just combined each of the maps in Google draw and the end result made the six borders look like map folds. I think some people dump their large maps into photoshop and do color corrections but I'm way too lazy for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start small and take your time. Work from the ground up. Build your landmass first. Start with broad, clunky strokes and refine with gradually small and smaller subtraction brushes until you have a shape you like. Don't worry about realism if that's a concern for you until you've become comfortable with the tools. Make your practice fun for yourself. After you have your landmass, I usually add mountain ranges where I want them. This helps dictate terrain later on. After laying mountains, I add in rivers and lakes. Once that's done, I paint the terrain. Depending on the scale of your project, this could be one or two simple terrain features or it could be large dynamic biomes. Don't bite off more than you can chew right away and don't worry about it looking pretty right away either. Play around with different brush sizes and fade intensities to get the aesthetic you desire. Once you have your world painted, add cities and other landmarks. Remember that less is often more. For my map, my goal was to have it represent terrain and cities. If I were to do a more political map, I would exchange the terrain for a plain background and add in boarders and roads with the cities. Know what you want when you start and you'll be able to achieve that goal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been seeing other people post their large compiled maps and thought I'd share a project I've been racing to finish before Jan 21. The geography is done (save for any last minute nit-picks) and I've been adding in the cities one nation at a time. I didn't expect it to be as time consuming as the actual terrain painting, but it has been very fulfilling watching my world come to life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ul Uren (WIP) - Racing Against the Clock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL that all those random shapes in the Microsoft Office suite have a useful, practical, and historical meaning behind them. My life will never be the same again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 23:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Witness! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me tell you - the genuine leather look and smell are worth the money. I would check out the brand I mentioned above. They have a great return policy as well as a cash back program if you make subsequent purchases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels really comfortable and will only get more so as I break it in. I got it from Gear, who sells Mr. S Leather products. The jock is really high quality and I feel I got some great bang for my buck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 16:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd go with the mid/upper end one just because why not treat yourself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 20:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm I'm trying to remember what I used. I think we used the Kirkland brand vodka from Costco because they generally slap their label on mid-tier quality brands like Svedka or Absolut. I would say if there's a vodka you really enjoy, go ahead and use it to make the gin. Just don't use Smirnoff or Karkov. Unless you are into that sort of thing.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 20:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm bummed about that too but it must mean that they are pushing some pretty significant changes if they can't port over old projects. I have my wallet ready to excitedly throw at them for their premium services as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply! I'm dying for the update and have put a hold on pretty much all of my Inkarnate projects save for the one or two I'm frantically wrapping up before the Jan. 21. I hope there will be some more advanced brushes to make tasks like this easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get ready for some tasty gin! My husband got me one of these kits last year really enjoyed the end product. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet Jesus, I love the way you've blended and shaded on this map. Do you have any tips or insights into your process for creating consistent blending/shading effects? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are doing God's work. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you're definitely in a situation to not have to go through therapy if your parents wanted you too. I didn't have a whole lot of choice in the matter back in 9th grade. If they do suggest therapy (of any kind) though, take a moment to think about where they are coming from. I don't think my parents knew that the church counselor was going to sit me down and tell me in our one-on-ones to either pray it away or live a life where I just don't act on my sexual feelings. Being raised in a Catholic household (granted, we were a very liberal household), the church provided an easy, cost-effective, and familiar outlet for aid for my parents because I was pretty tight-lipped about it and had shut down any communication on the matter after the letter. My parents turned to what they knew and felt comfortable with and over time I've learned not to fault them for this. So, tl;dr - sometimes people do or suggest doing the wrong thing because they don't know what else to do and are seeking the familiar. Keep an open mind and create a dialogue because that's the only way any bridges will be crossed. Best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came out to my parents via letter when I was in high school. The pro of it it is that it allowed me to gather my thoughts and put them into a coherent structure that wouldn't be clouded by the heat of the moment. The mistake I made was not being open to talking to my parents about it in person. Since they couldn't break my wall of silence, they took me to a Catholic family councilor (aka thinly veiled conversion therapy). I don't really think my parents knew the damage this did but it resulted in me keeping my entire sexuality and dating life from them for eight years (not that they couldn't put bits and pieces together here and there). Hell, it took me that long to recognize that the "therapy" had affected me the way it did. They thought they were doing the right thing and I've realized I can't blame them and have forgiven them. But the moral here is that all of this could have been avoided by having a talk in person after sending that letter. Nothing can replace a real human conversation and it will need to happen sooner or later. When I finally had the talk with my folks after I graduated from college, there was a lot of healing between us.  So just be prepared for step two, because a letter can only further the conversation so far. Best of luck to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 05:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hallo from Milwaukee! It took me two and a half hours for my normally twenty minute commute today that is to the snow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahah I feel you - I'm in the same boat. Thank god there's a post office open till 10 otherwise I'd be in full on panic mode right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I start the daily snooze button war around 6:30 and roll out of bed around 7. I'll sit on the john for a while and play mobile games or rub one out before hopping in the shower. After that I force both my dogs to take pills (which isn't terrible MOST mornings) and then make sure my hubby is up before heading out the door to work. I'll hit up Starbucks on my commute and start praying to god that road construction hasn't migrated to my commute path yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The goofy ones are the best. They keep you on your toes! ;p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would talk to someone about what you are going through. While I've found a lot of solace in my online communities, being able to communicate with one or two people irl has helped a lot. And, if you are comfortable with it and it's an option, talk to a PCP. They are there to offer objective, judgement free help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
