<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1963</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YEEEEAAAAAAAHHHHHHHH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suggestion - RCMA no color powder. I'll never go back to LM or MUFE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blegh 

My mom keeps trying to convince me to wear a huge poofy dress with a shiny beaded corset (not me AT ALL) and I keep picking dresses that are farther and farther away from that. And much more comfortable. Moms are weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, I would read the shit out of any blog or book you happened to pen. As a young woman with depression, panic disorder, PTSD, and ADD, I love hearing about other's experiences - not because of any "ooh wow fun" factor but because I like hearing about other "crazy people" who live their lives despite the fact that their own brains are raging against them. People who haven't had to deal with mental illness up close tend to see "crazy" exactly how you've described, which is awful, but the more visibility we get, the better. 

My fianc and I have been together 5 years. I never thought I'd actually find someone to "put up with" my four kinds of "crazy", but, here we are. I am still teaching him things. Even those closest to us struggle to understand what we are going through. I only recently got the RELIEF of a PTSD diagnosis after years of knowing something "else" was wrong with me. I had a rough childhood and grew up in a shithole and I couldn't figure out why I constantly lashed out at people over stupid shit or why I needed absolute silence when I slept or why I have trouble forming and keeping relationships. When my therapist confirmed my diagnosis (and to be honest, I wasn't surprised) I cried. And I cried when I told my fianc. And I haven't told anyone else because there's so much stigma around it. His whole family has no idea that I have any mental health issues. They just know I spend a lot of alone time, even on family trips, and that I sleep a ton. 

It may never objectively get easier, but slowly, we become better at ignoring the bullshit and focusing on getting past our demons so we can shower and eat. 

Thank you for sharing your story. I'd love to hear more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say surprise them in the morning - let them get hyped up for the day ahead. Get a Mickey or something, have the tickets out, hell - get some confetti on the table and blow up balloons, leave them all on the bed for when the kids wake up. Make a sign with simple printer paper to go near the tickets. go big! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha my mom constantly did this when I was younger. She'd take me off the plan and then complain that she couldn't get a hold of me any time she wanted. I just waited. Eventually she'd backpedal and say it was just to teach me a lesson for whatever moronic thing she was mad about, and I'd have phone service again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had something similar happen recently. My usually stoic fianc suffered a tragic loss in the family. This is the man that has cried in front of me maybe twice before - both when my depression had gotten terrible and he was upset hearing how bad I felt about everything. He does not show much emotion - happy, sad, angry, whatever. This loss hit him really hard though and was so unexpected. He kept putting on the blank face and acting like everything was going to be fine, but we got home and he just lost it. He's in a good enough place that he's not suicidal over it but it scared me seeing how upset he was. 

I can't even imagine being in your shoes right now. If you need to vent, I'm free any time. Don't forget to take good care of yourself in the mean time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! And yeah, it's great! I am comfortable in these jeans that used to make me embarrassed about my body. I can't wait to toss these bad boys and get some smaller ones, maybe 10 pounds or so from now. Not looking forward to having to buy new clothes every few months but eh, it's worth it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is awesome! I am proud of you! I suffer from binge eating disorder and it got to the point where my weight was affecting my health. I also suffer from depression, and most anti-depressants can make you hungry/make you gain weight, which I was terrified of. My doc worked with me to find the one that would make me NOT do that. In fact, we found one that helped REDUCE my urge to binge, and I'm proud to say that, even though medication was sort of the "easy" way out, I haven't binged in almost two months. Feels so good to be mindful and to recognize when the bad feelings are coming, and to let that urge pass and not act on it. You've had to work harder than I did, so, major props! Keep it up!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had to pull up my pants all day today. It's the first day I've felt like I've lost "real" weight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an odd shape no matter what weight I am - giant hips/butt, narrow waist, big thighs but small calves, tiny ankles and feet. I'm like a caricature, at least I definitely was at my heaviest weight. I was 206 some time this past summer at 5'7"ish. 

I bought these jeans several months ago. My old jeans were too tight, I was devastated. Couldn't even squeeze into them. Went in, managed to find two pairs - both high waisted, but one was VERY stretchy and one was not. I've been noticing lately that the stretched out pair is loose, but they shrink back up in the dryer and are fine for a wear or two. They're mostly like yoga pants. (They do have weird stretched out bumpy spots though, which I find amusing.) 

These pants, though. These were a little snug even when I bought them. They are only mid-rise, I think, which usually means a giant gap at the waist when I sit down. I rarely wore these jeans in the last few months, mostly because I still couldn't really see or feel my weight loss. I decided to throw them on today as I was running late, and oh, man. 

ALL. DAY. I had to pull these babies up. Not like, fall-off-my-hips loose, but definitely LOOSE. They started to sag a little in the butt. I had to make sure I wasn't flashing crack to innocent bystanders. The kid I nanny for kept laughing at me for my "big jeans". My biggest jeans were actually a 14, these are just a barely stretchy 12, but yeah, they look a little looser now. 

I weighed in this morning and I'm 17.3 pounds down. 188.7 lbs. I haven't been sub-190 in well over a year and a half, maybe two years. I suffer from depression and Binge Eating Disorder, which obviously has made weight loss extremely difficult. I finally sought help and have been slowly working towards getting my mind and body back in shape! It's not some massive success story yet, but I'm getting there, one crappy pair of loose jeans at a time!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I nanny for a 4 year old girl, and she likes visiting the animal rescue and adoption events and hanging out with the cats. We walked up to one last week and I saw on his sheet that it was his birthday! I told her and she immediately started singing to him, haha. So cute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to a bad kid school for a while and EVERYONE hated our math teacher. Dude was not a good teacher, first off, just yelled at everyone to do worksheets and didn't help people that needed help. In retaliation, any time he'd leave the room, the tallest kids in the room would get up and stick every single pencil in the room into the lower-than-average foam tile ceiling. Math teacher was short.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am super shy/anxious in front of other people in general but I am always cheering on people in my head, especially when I see bigger folks busting their asses to improve their health. 

^work ^^it ^^^girl ^^^^!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh nooooooo. I mean, yay also, because I haven't really been satisfied with most vegan ice creams so far, but muh calorie count D:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do anything in Chuck E Cheese if you're sneaky enough. 

That came out sounding awful haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU! They weren't up like a day ago and they're not on the app yet from what I can tell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is EXACTLY what I was hoping for, thank you!! And congrats! It's going to be a great week!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the plan is to do BOG on a day that is NOT a party day. From what I can tell from looking at past years calendars, I should be safe with a Monday or Wednesday as neither of the last two years had parties on Wednesdays only one Monday, mostly Tues/Thurs/Fri/Sun. We'll definitely try to avoid MK on party days. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Booking ADRs around Halloween Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FH and I are going to be there Sep 16-23 for part of our honeymoon. We're coming up on the date to make our ADRs, but how do we plan which park/restaurant to go for if we don't know the dates of the party yet? Like, I want to book Be Our Guest but how do I nab a reservation if I don't know what nights will or won't be party nights? Do I just have to guess and check based on what it will allow me to book on certain days? We'd prefer to not be in MK on party days to avoid crowds, I'm guessing. 

Any tips or info? 


Edit: also, California grill - if I'm trying to book that on a day off from the parks, how do I know if I'm going to be seeing the regular fireworks or the Halloween ones? Also, is there a schedule of any kind for AM and PM magic hours? Certain parks on certain days? Trying to optimize.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have plenty of my own, just also appreciate others, thanks.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw man, why does everyone else write stuff like this that I IMMEDIATELY want to turn into my next book? Whyyyyy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is awesome! I was also a little skeptical after not being able to find much online about them. And good to know about pore strips, too - I used to use them religiously and stopped when I heard they were terrible, but now I might use one on occasion if I really need to clear stuff up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, so, the funny thing is, mine is that and also backwards but I've been wanting to vent so here goes. 

I was a very hyperactive child. Not the run around in circles and fight people kind, the cantstopfidgetingohmygod kind. My mom worked in education and decided to have me observed by the school. They tell her it's because I have ADHD. Okay. So she takes me to therapy but tries to weasel her way into every appt. The therapist realizes this and starts asking me "you're big enough to have this appointment alone, right?" And I would always nod and my mom would always do and say awful things to try to get me to fess up as to what I had told the doc. I think she was taking me for appearances, and to tell the therapist that I was just acting up for her, as she did and does often. She kind of realized that taking me might backfire because the therapist wasn't an idiot. Guess who magically got better and didn't have to go to therapy anymore? Yeah! Me! And then when I was still hyped out of my mind and couldn't write a single sentence without wanting to die, she would say I was just being lazy/whiny and being bad. She would say that I did it at home too, but only when I had to actually focus and do things but that she was sure I was faking it. The other teachers at my school, where she worked, believed her. Son of a bitch. 

Later, when I was 11 and already showing signs of depression, she would scream at me for crying or for not being cheerful about some bullshit that I hated or for not immediately praising her for things. When I really started to retreat into my room more, she would yell that I deserved to be there anyway and I could stay there until I grew up and got a better attitude. I was self harming by 13 and miserable and she didn't give a shit. 

I was in an awful place by the time I was 13, but I kept up appearances alll the way until Junior year. I was in clubs, on teams, I was doing just okay in classes. Then I crashed. I failed all of my classes and they made me go to a special school where I could make it up. I knocked two years of classes out in six months. Without a full class of people, I could focus! I could go outside and do my work and finish a weeks worth in an hour and a half! I went back to regular school with enough credits that I could have already graduated, but I wanted to go to prom and stuff so I went back. My mom had zero interaction with this school. None. But the weird thing is she would tell me how proud she was of me for working hard to make it up. She almost never put me down for being in that school. The ONE thing she should have gotten mad about. Nope. W

So here's where it gets funny - she used to kick me out allllll the time. For various infractions. I think I was 14 the first time this happened. And then she'd call and beg me to come home and say she was sorry, and I was a fucking idiot doormat so I'd walk home with my tail between my legs and she'd cry and hug me and then the next day she'd be yelling again. (Guess who's bipolar? Yes! My mother! But that's actually only a little relevant.) She would tell everyone at school that she didn't know what was going on with me, that I'd just disappear sometimes and not answer the phone and wouldn't tell her where I was going. School counselor called me in. By this time my mom didn't work for the district anymore and had switched careers. This counselor, who had already thought I was lazy and awful for having to go to the other school, mostly ignored me when I told her my mom was actually kicking me out and had hit me several times in the past and committed abuse by taking away "privileges", some as easy as TV and some like "laundry and shower". Didn't care. Thought I was acting up. 

Enter - me, 19. I am flunking my second semester of college after barely scraping by in the first. I hate college. I feel like an idiot and I'm not as put together as these other people. I flunk out and start working. I meet my FH just before I turned 21 and moved into his place 2 weeks later. His roommates all bail. In the interim, we have to find a place to stay. Guess who has the only open room in town? Yep. At least FH got to experience how she treated me. She only did it when she thought he wasn't there, but he's quiet. He saw and heard everything. 

We move out again. At that point, I'm 23 and completely unsure if I was actually ill or if she'd twisted it all up. It takes me two years to get help because A: I am scared and  B: it takes me that long to actually call the abuse what it was. 

Turns out I'm not only ADHD and have full on depression, but I also have a panic disorder and show many signs of PTSD! Yay! I don't obviously tell her any of these. 

In the last two years, she has started pretending we have a great relationship now and she's always talking about how I'm "sooo much better after getting help" and that I was a terrible and difficult child to raise because of my ADHD and mood issues. 

The fuck. You claimed that I both did and did not have these things. Made them worse. Kept me from getting treatment and turned my teachers against me. And now you're saying I was difficult because of the illnesses that you couldn't make up your mind about? 

Ugh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, is your mom my mom? Minus the guests thing because our #1 rule was "we write the guest list, we're not expecting contributions to our wedding so anything you give us is appreciated but doesn't buy you extra seats". So glad I put that one out. FH's family is MASSIVE and my mom has many interesting "friends" that I do not know that I'm sure she'd love to be able to show off to. 

My mom, who wasn't even married to her guy, said his daughter counted as more of a stepsister than my actual stepsisters on my dad's side. Uh. 

My mom is the kind of person who wouldn't make the grievous error of wearing white or doing anything tooo over the top, just grating awful selfish wicked little jabs all the time that wear me down that nobody else sees if they're not paying attention. 

She also does the fake stories thing and then claims I don't remember them correctly or that I was "so young". I was a dumb teenager and got arrested for petty theft when I was 18, it was super embarrassing and I'm not that kind of person and I had a really stupid (but in my head, very valid) reason I did it. Anyway, I have told FH about this, he knows I was a bit of a wild child but that's my only reeeeally real brush with the law. She was having dinner with me and FH and some family one night and like out of fucking nowhere brought up my "law breaking habit" and said I stole stuff and that I used to steal her things all the time. (Partially true, we were a big house of girls and all borrowed each other's shit. But she also stole my shit that I bought with my own money then said "you're under my roof, it's mine.") right after she brings this up, she gave herself whiplash doing so I swear to god, she looks right at FH expecting some horrified reaction. You could see the immediate cat butt face when he had zero reaction. At all. Bless this man.  

My mom also has been telling everyone she's "sooooo surprised" that I didn't turn into "a total bridezilla." First off, bitch. No. I may sound angry in these rants and I use a lot of vulgar words but I am literally the chillest motherfucker in this family. Everyone's all "what should the bridesmaids wear? What color are your tables? What kind of guest book are you getting? Do my kids have to dress up?" And my answers are 1. I literally do not care what anyone else wears, their body not mine. 2. Table colored 3. What? and 4. Your kid can wear a friggin batman costume for all I care, in fact, let them pick out the weirdest outfit they want and flaunt it." I always dreamed of having a big fancy wedding when I was younger but then I turned 22 and was like "lol, you fuckers will be lucky if I don't elope." 

My mom promised us $4k and I haven't seen a dime. She is contributing the LEAST of any other parties. She did buy a small percentage of our decor and she drove me to one of my dress appointments. Ok. Then she demanded the best room on site at the venue for herself because she "just really needs this right now." 

Not much advice for you other than what FH tells me - moms like this make promises, but set your expectations low because she's probably only going to deliver on what she wants to do. Don't leave her in charge of anything you can't live without. And when in doubt, buy more wine. (He's a wise man, my FH.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thiiiiiis. I was chubby all through high school, though admittedly when I was 17 I was mostly curvy in the RIGHT ways, I just had thick ass thighs too. But that was 50 pounds ago. Now I'm just fat. I am getting married in six months and going on a bitchin' honeymoon, and at that and then basically anything where I haven't seen people in a while, I wanna make them say "damn!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask her! Everyone is different. Some people want a partner to hold and comfort them, some people want to be left alone for a while to work things out. Let her know that you will help however she wants you to, and that she only needs to let you know what that is. It might take her some time though. Personally, I normally retreat into the bedroom and hide under the covers, but sometimes I need a little comfort and don't know how to voice it and I'll just grab my FH's arm and put it around me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS is the most important thing, OP. If you don't tell, other people are still going to trust the care of their kids to this guy and he's going to do it to them too. If you don't want to tell for your own reasons, tell to save some other kid from having to suffer through the same thing or worse. 

Also, as someone who had something sort of similar happen to me as a child, pleeeease go to therapy. I was 9, I am now 26, I am just now getting help and I wish I had gone sooner because it does have an impact on how you form and keep relationships.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many recommendations, ah! Thanks for all the lounges and things - I wasn't even thinking about places to grab a drink. We're definitely going California Grill and will look into the luau. No way we're dropping that kind of money for Victoria and Albert's. It's not that we can't, but I'd rather spend the money on drinks and fun stuff than on one meal. 

Disneyland dole whip is 100x better than WDW dole whip. No clue why. I was actually really surprised at how different they were. And Morimoto's sounds good too, that's our kind of food (I could drink a gallon of Thai tea. I would probably be sick afterwards but I'd do it anyway.) 

And I think that's what we're going to do with the split. AK seems like it's got more things that we'll want to be there for later in the day. We'll probably go back for Fantasmic one night though, as it's totally different than the DL one and soooo much easier to see!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooh okay. Eyes out. Haven't seen anything yet. How long does that email usually take to come out? FH is probably fine with gray (he'd probably prefer it!) but i want pretty colors!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, so much great info! I know we'll definitely want to check out the new land, but I don't know that it's something we're going to want to spend a whole day in that park for. We really only went on two or three things in AK when we went, and two in HS, so we'll still probably try to split it. But then, we'll be able to park hop, so we can always go back just for a ride and dinner on one of our "off" days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the week I am going happens to be pretty much one of the least busy weeks out of the year according to everything I can find. Didn't even plan it, just worked out that way. We'll be there Saturday the 16th through the next Saturday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are all awesome recommendations, thank you! Definitely going to look into touring plans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're not interested in using a travel agent. I only work part time and will be able to regularly check for price drops myself. But thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All good advice! Thank you! I have been playing around with the app for a while, it's similar to DLs but much much larger obviously. And lucky us, we'll have the premier passes so we get all of our pictures anyway!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your reply! ADRs make more sense. I know for sure we're going to want to do Be Our Guest, California Grill, and at least one other good sit down meal. I feel like our tastes are pretty varied and we'll eat pretty much anything. Last time we went, we did peel away from the main group enough to drink (and snack) around the world, but we took it easy and split each drink between three people in all but two areas. I do remember grabbing like five pastries in France and just being way too happy about them. 

I definitely want to do all of those, and ToT (DL just lost theirs, I never got to ride it again and it is TRAGIC) and other stuff. Still have some looking around to do I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good, low cal breakfast for someone who doesn't have time to cook in the mornings/good to reheat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will admit, I am very new to being a full time vegan so I am just getting the hang of things. I made a potato okra hash that was DELICIOUS straight out of the oven, but is very very sad now that I've reheated it. I am super lazy in the mornings and sometimes roll out of bed twenty minutes before I have to leave for work, which means I have about enough time to microwave leftovers and put them in a container and eat them in my car. 

I tend to eat bigger lunches and dinners, so I'm hoping to find something around 200 cal that isn't as awful as these friggin potatoes. Ugh. Not a big fan of oatmeal or any of its grainy cousins in the morning. I avoid fake processed "meats" (looking at you, tempeh bacon) and try to keep my wheat and fat consumption down as much as possible. 

Any input is greatly appreciated! Thaaaanks! 


Edit: thanks, everybody! I'm going to try a few of these out this week :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totall agree that he's being gun shy post-divorce, and he has every reason to be. He thought that was going to be it for him, he clearly put a lot of time and effort and love into that relationship, and he was crushed. My ex had an exgf that did something similar to what your guy's ex did. He moved her into a nice apartment, bought all their furniture, helped pay for everything while she wasn't working, did EVERYTHING he could for this woman, and they weren't even married. Three years in she decides she's bored, cheats on him, THEN leaves him. He was messed up about that for years, too messed up for us to ever work out. 

Your guy sounds like he does see a future with you, but is hesitant to make plans. You obviously understand why. And while I don't think it's a good idea to pester him about moving in and talking about the possibilities, it's probably also not a good idea to just wait for him to come to you. If you leave it up to him, he may NEVER come to you about this. It may take MORE effort later if you leave it alone. 

So go about it like this: instead of coming at him with "why won't you move in with me?", let him know that his hesitance to move in with you is a little worrisome, and that you'd like to at least have a frank discussion about what he sees happening in the next five years. Does he want to get married? Probably! He might not be ready for a while, but if you're willing to wait several years, let him know that. Or let him know that you'd maybe want to get married in 20xx and see if he might want to move that. Reassure him that you're in this for the long run, but that his complete avoidance of certain topics is scaring you. You just want to make sure you're both on the same page so that neither of you is left wondering. 

And it's a good conversation to have anyway, especially if he is dodging near-future topics. Do either of you want kids? Is buying a house together something you'd eventually do? Having that knowledge, even if he isn't ready to get married yet, you guys could start putting aside money for a house or a wedding for whenever that may be. It also is a little bit of a reminder for BOTH of you that the other person is still emotionally (and then also, financially) invested in this relationship in the long term.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [insert joke about bearing broken arms, something something...]  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooh dang, this has a lot of the favorite elements of the dresses I've tried on. I would need a medium though and it appears they're out of stock, at least for now. Literally bookmarking this and buying it as soon as they have it. Even if it doesn't work for my wedding dress, I'll figure something out. Maybe rehearsal. 

Edit: never mind, I have no self control, I just ordered it in a size down and I'm losing weight anyway, so, yay!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this sounds bonkers. Everyone else is wearing different designers and styles, but you can't change yours? It's obviously not like she's looking for identical dresses. 

I agree with another poster - let her know what your budget is for the dress, and tell her that if you were to pay for the dress + structural alterations, it could be well over your budget. Maybe come at her with styles that are similar to the ones she suggested. 

And let her know that if she can't tell you what she does or doesn't want, you're not going to be able to buy a dress in time at all. 

I may sound insensitive here, but is the bride being like this with the other bridesmaids? Is there some kind of difference in conventional attractiveness that could be making her say No for one reason or another? I ask because I had a friend get married who was being really weird with two of her bridesmaids because she thought the dresses were unflattering on their fuller figures. And I have seen plenty of stories of brides just being weird about bridesmaid dresses because they want to be the center of attention (as they should be, it's their wedding!) and are worried about anyone else wearing something that might outshine them.) 

This is why I'm letting my bridal party pick their own dresses. But my wedding is fairly casual and up a mountain, so my guidelines were "anything in this color range, I don't care what else, long or short, sleeves or straps or not, whatever, be comfortable."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually would kind of love if Spencer killed Charlotte. Not just because she's my favorite, but because I have this idea that she planned to lure Charlotte up, kill her, all that. She snapped from all the trauma of being in the dollhouse, she's had pleeeenty of issues before. 

But I like it even more if I think she didn't know who her real mother was while all this went down. Like she thought she was being so clever, exacting some harsh revenge, thought she had the perfect plan, and then gets blindsided by the fact that Mary was her real mother.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, TIL my big birthmark on my neck is a cafe au lait spot. Mine is a little blotchier, like a hundred weird spots all in a weird smear down my neck, but it kinda makes sense. 

Makes me always look like I don't know how to blend my foundation though. I cannot count the number of times someone has politely tried to tell me I didn't blend out under my chin, and I tell them it's a big birthmark, and some still don't believe me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so weird. I've seen one consultant I love that does outfits, but if that outfit isn't sold within a day they allow people to purchase separately. That kind of makes sense to me, but for some reason the 2nd required item thing just rubs me the wrong way. 

Thanks for your answer!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just booked the second leg of our Honeymoon - September 16-23 at Port Orleans, Riverside. But I have almost NO IDEA how WDW works. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! We've been talking about this honeymoon for ages and finally booked it. We're from Los Angeles suburbs and have both had Disneyland APs for several years. I could navigate DL blindfolded. We both also worked at DL in some capacity at some point. Point being, we reeeeeally know DL but have no idea about WDW. FH went once as a kid, and a few years ago we went for a few days with family. But that was a nightmare - we got stuck with the toddler group for the entire week and most days the whole group left at 3PM. I also had more serious health issues then so I was in an ECV the whole time except for part of one day. 

Trip goes like this: we get married 9/9, we have a brunch the next morning to say goodbye to our guests. We drive the two hours home, pick up our luggage, relax a few hours, then head to LAX. From there we fly to Miami for a 5 day cruise to Grand Cayman and Ocho Rios. I would have gone all Disney, but FH wanted a liiiiittle bit of beach time. (Can't blame him). We get off the cruise, have an early lunch in Miami, and we'll rent a car and drive up to WDW. Should get us there right around check in time. 

We'll be at POR for those 7 nights. We are probably upgrading our DL APs to the Premier pass instead of buying tickets - both of our passes expire a month or two after our honeymoon, so the upgrade charge is less than the ticket cost. This is what we did last time and it was great because we also got AP discounts. 

Now. Here's where we're stuck. I've read quite a few "first timer" blogs and lists but still have many, many questions. It seems like so much information is old or conflicting and I can't figure this out. WDW is something like 43 square miles, DL is less than 1! I only have a Disneyland's worth of knowledge and need help from the pros. 

1. How do you decide which days to go to which parks? Preference? Or does it have something to do with ADRs? I have seen some impressive spreadsheets on here. Which brings me to... 

2. How do ADRs work? Can I do them through the app? I read somewhere that staying on property gives you 6 months plus ten days - does that mean ten days before six months, or the ability to book the (up to) ten days of your vacation after your first day? 

3. Which restaurants should we book first? Do reservations open at midnight or some time in the morning? I want to be there first thing to make sure we get what we want. We were super unprepared last time and didn't even know which counter service places to go to. 

4. Magic Bands - I see they're complimentary with resort hotels. How does it work for having a premier pass? Is there a way to add it online? 

5. I've seen all the romantic tips and stuff that people post - nice dinners, walk around POFQ or POR, fireworks from California Grill. But we're also people who like to just stop and people watch, or check out a really insanely tasty snack. What are some good places for relaxing a bit, in parks or out? What food item would you say we absolutely HAVE to have while we're there? What other little/less popular things are really cool that many people miss out on? 

6. I vaguely remember using Fastpass+ when we were there and getting lucky enough to snag some good ones. I've read you can get these 60 days ahead while staying onsite. Which rides do we most need these for? We'd like to have a good amount of structure, we're both the kind of person to say "I don't know, what do YOU want to do?" for half an hour. Which inevitably loses us valuable time. 

7. I've seen some people say that you can do both HS and AK in one day. Does that work well? I planned on a day each but if I remember correctly, last of fastpasses and long lines on these days was the only way we were even able to fill a significant portion of time at either of these. I remember thinking AK was kind of cool, but we can see most of that stuff at the big zoos around here. I would like to open up another day for DS or just relaxing or maybe doing another half day at Epcot, if possible. 

I will probably have more questions later, but I think that'll do for now. I'm so freakin' excited. 

Oh one more thing! I saw a picture of a girl with decals on her magic band, searched Etsy, and WOW there are a lot of them on there. How well do the decals stick? I would like to maybe get a cute monogram one with my new last initial, or something wedding related. Does anyone have someone they go through that makes really good ones?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question for consultants... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I joined a group on Facebook that has their inventory up 24/7, but does different hosts and things every few days. I'll be honest, I almost never look at this group. It's just too big and there are too many people. 

Now, I'm not sure what the deal is with the last few days. The pictures have been uploaded by someone other than the consultant whose name is on the page. Not a big deal, I'm guessing. But they are also saying that if you buy a pair of their leggings, you MUST buy a second piece that can't also be leggings. There is no way to buy individual leggings on this group. Is this against the rules? I feel like it should be. Requiring a full other item just to get a cute pair of leggings seems like the consultant is asking too much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me either. I used to have moderate acne that broke out at the slightest irritation and for whatever reason over the last eight months, my skin has stopped being so sensitive and I have almost zero acne.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish we would have thought of this when we had my German Shep/Lab mix. Dumbest dog. She never broke the glass but she tore through several screens, so many that initially, we bought a new screen door. After three doors, my dad bought a massive roll of the material and just cut and installed it himself every time. 

Good old doggo and I miss her but wow was she a dumb little turd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using that shiny spine as a friggin whip. A+. High five him for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god I was just thinking to myself "eh, Ben is good but what's something that I could laugh off like 'ugh _____ is just doing their thing again, whatever" and this is what I'm gonna do. Thank.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She called me immediately after and I legitimately fell over laughing. Precious angel child. He thought they had to plant a penis in a lady like seeds. He was so confused.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humor break, a kid I used to babysit for started going to daycare. One of the kids said something about sex making babies so they decided to broach the subject with him early on. They said something like "puts his penis inside mommy" and the kid listened intently, looking a little weirded out, and then asked if he could see the scar. Confused, mama asked him what scar he meant. The kid was like "when he put it inside you. By your privates. They had to cut you open and put it in your tummy, right? Does daddy still have his penis? Does it hurt? Will mine fall off some day too? How do daddies make more babies after their penis is already gone?" I love children.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old DB drove me and two of the three kids over an hour away to this car dealership (apparently he only really liked this one) where one of their cars was being worked on. He drove home the dependable car with his son and stuck me and his daughter in the car that kept having troubles with overheating and randomly shutting down! And guess what happened? The freaking car got super hot and shut down in the middle of a busy freeway. Luckily it coasted far enough that I was able to get us to the shoulder, and it was double lucky that we were in an area that has a shoulder at all, because there was a bunch of construction. And instead of coming back for us, DB went all the way back to his house, dropped off the son, and THEN called a tow truck and came to get us. 

They were normally pretty nice but they had a lot of weird issues like this where they did something totally strange. This was like three days into working for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, I just spat out my drink, take your updoot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jaden Smith would wear the bird as a hat. And tweet about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With travel days, (even though Sunday, day after wedding, we'll just be leaving our venue and heading straight to the airport, the transfer day in the middle is mostly getting off a boat and getting to the hotel, and the last day is just a flight home) it's 14 days! 2 full weeks! Which is kind of incredible for us because time off is insane to get, and also a two week trip can just be expensive as hell. We are usually super good with money, my FH is a pro budgeting person, our wedding is more than we wanted it to be and so is the honeymoon but what the hell, you only get to do it once and we're getting plenty of help from family. 

I am too damn excited. Weeeeeeeeeee!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some time traveling dickhead in the crowd: "PLAY FREE BIRD" 

Plant: (poofs a dove into his hand, confused. Is this bird real? How high am I? The bird? What's a free bird? Is any bird truly free?) "yeah. Anyway, here's Stairway to Heaven..."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We just booked our dream honeymoon. And we don't have anyone to celebrate with because there's so much family stuff going on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FH's family suffered a loss last week. They're all still reeling so talking to them about this right now is out of the question. 

My own family CONSTANTLY has some sort of drama, usually petty, but this time around both my mother and grandmother had to get a hysterectomy because they each, separately, had uterine growths. My mom's weren't cancerous, thank god, but my grandmothers were. She already beat breast cancer! She's tough, but she doesn't need this shit! Luckily they caught it early enough that the hysterectomy should have removed it all. 

My dad, who previously offered to pay for my wedding dress and whose wife and stepdaughters were super gung-ho about wedding planning a year and a half ago, don't even bother answering a phone call or text from my sister or myself. They're off in their own little bubble, whatever. 

My sister was kinda excited/happy for us and I'll get to talk to her, but still! I wanted to be able to be happy about this. Instead I'm doing it because the booking window is closing and now I can't even talk to people about it. 

We're flying out the day after our wedding, landing in Miami, staying there for a night. Then we're heading on a weekish long cruise to Jamaica and Grand Cayman, and then heading back to Miami for part of a day. Then we're renting a nice car, driving up to Orlando, and going to Disney World for eight days! I have only been once when FH's family all went a few years ago, but we got stuck with the little kids most of the trip and didn't get to explore. We go to Disneyland a ton because we have passes but it's soooooo different. 

I'm just excited, damn it! And to top it off, today marked exactly six months until our wedding! Ah!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unusual ideas for people in the bridal party? or: Lack of Bridesmaids (and two cancellations!) Makes a Bride Feel Lonely. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I originally planned on a big bridal party. Before we got engaged, I was much closer with my dad and stepsisters (we now see each other maybe twice a year, tops?), and wasn't aware that my other stepsister would be in college across the country or that our parents would split so it would make her uncomfortable just to be there. I luckily also asked my bio sister, my guy friend, and my girl friend. My FSIL is going to be on FH's side because they've always been super close and I love that! 

I don't have a ton of friends, period. FH and I are pretty solitary people, the quintessential picture of a couple that burrows so deeply into coupledom that they forget about the outside world for weeks at a time. It's super gross and normally I love that companionship, but in planning my wedding I realized how long it has been since I've made a new friend. The friend group I was with before I met FH, I had a falling out with because one of them was a dirtbag and the others were super immature about it and I didn't want to be friends with them anymore. Crappy situation, but whatever. Early in our relationship I was friends with FH's friend group, but that whole group sort of imploded for unrelated reasons and then later, a handful of them did something pretty hurtful out of nowhere to FH, who is literally the coolest most neutral and helpful person ever. 

It sucks. We used to have pretty big groups of friends but they kind of just all disappeared and we've been okay with that up to now because we're not super social anyway and I get anxious with people. In general. 

Anyway, my initial group was mostly sisters but amounted to the six mentioned above and then another really old friend that I've completely lost touch with in the last year. I'm down from 7 to 3. FH has had 5 from the very beginning, because while it was less than mine, it wasn't too much smaller and he didn't care either way. It didn't bother me for a while, but it's starting to. I literally went through all the contacts in my phone and all the friends I have on Facebook (not many, but enough that I should have been able to figure this out) and couldn't think of any girl friends to ask. I already have my best guy friend, a dude I've known since I was 5 who is basically my brother. 

I'm stumped. At this point, I'm not 100% sure I want to ask more people, but I do feel like I would be upset with having such a small group when the day comes and when all the other events happen. I would like to at least consider other options. 

What "unusual" bridesmaids do you guys have or have you heard of? Other family members? My family is pretty small but his family is huge, but I don't know if I'm close enough with any of them. Mostly Facebook friends. I literally thought about asking my grandma, who I've always been very close with. She'd probably not want to do it though, she's had some health issues lately and usually uses a walker and doesn't much like being the center of attention. 

I. Am. Stumped. And I am feeling lonely. Help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would suggest using that last page as a cover sheet that uses the right formulas to compile info. We use something like this for budgeting right now - each tab has a different section of our budget with transactions and totals, our cover sheet has the latest totals in each account and shows projected and past totals based on date ranges. So, we know that the first week of the month, our monthly spending is dramatically different than the fourth because of rent, but the third is a close second because we pay off a few things that week. 

So for example, you could keep your tabs similar to how they are now, for detailed product reference, but compile the data on those sheets onto the last page as a cover. Add a similar table beneath it for skin concerns. How are your eyes felling? Irritated? Skin feeling oily? It'll all be right there. 

Goes like this: you have your database already here. Awesome. 

Each week, you take note of which products you're using and how your skin feels/looks, in two separate tables.  Easy. So each week you fill a different row across however many columns/categories you have in each tab, like you have. 

Next week, same thing. And again. Oh, you notice your skin has felt irritated all three of the last three weeks. Cover sheet/log says that in the last three weeks, you've used two overlapping products say, a moisturizer and a mask. Note on each product listing in the detailed reference that x and y product could be causing irritation. Next week, take one away and continue to use one. Skin still irritated? Drop the other one. You'll probably be able to figure it out pretty quickly when you have a sheet that's got all the information summarized for you. 

If you want to take it a step further, each week that you use products, take note of which ones have ingredients that others are sensitive to. Certain natural oils, scents, gritty exfoliants, gel type vs lotion type moisturizers, fragrances, etc. 

You will probably realize "hey, this and this primer both made my skin weird. They're both silicone based. Maybe drop the silicone and see if that helps!" but it can take a few months of diligent logging and comparisons. I used the silicone primers as an example because I tried every cult favorite primer on the planet before realizing that silicone primers made me feel super gross halfway through the day. And fragrances in skincare make my skin sad. 

I am admittedly terrible with remembering how to technically design spreadsheets (I can plan it out but as far as remembering formulas, I can barely remember how to do totals some days) but I have been actually working on one with my fianc for a couple of weeks, just never got around to finishing it. Now I need to go figure out how to best grab similar info from ingredient lists. Hmmmm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first "you have such nice skin" compliment got me all giddy and silly. I was like "really? Me? No way. I've had crappy skin always and I'm just starting to work on it..." 
congrats, OP!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it can feel really personal at first and really make it a You vs Me conversation. Just remind him that it really doesn't have to do with what you think of his family so much as it has to do with the details HE has given and the concern for your kids. It's a PRO HAPPY, HEALTHY, SAFE KIDS conversation, not a 1v1 battle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, your mom sounds like my mom. She keeps insisting that she's surprised I'm "not turning into a total bridezilla", which, first of all I HATE that term, and second the only -zilla of anything around here is her, the momzilla. She cries at everything and guilts everyone around her into a bunch of bullshit and has literally blamed me for most of her problems since my birth. Textbook narcissist. Moving out helped our relationship some, but not much. 

Basically, we're tossing tradition too. Both my parents and my FH's parents are divorced and remarried, so we have four sets of parents to contend with. Everyone and their mother wanted to pay for my dress, but if I went with that I'd have $25k in dress and $5 in wedding, so no way. We said "contributions are welcome but not expected, we're not taking directed payments because there are too many people offering to take care of one or two things and nobody wants to pay for the important things like, you know, a venue. We'd be happy to include you in planning and celebrating regardless of if you contribute or not." We expected backlash but that mostly went well (until everyone wanted to go to catering tastings, which got me to the point of saying "FH and I will be the only ones going to tastings so that nobody thinks we're playing favorites!") 

My stepmom is also kind of an abrasive person though, and while my FMIL is organized, she and I do not see eye to eye on ideas for wedding and events. FSMIL is the kind of lady to write a check, tell us to have fun, and ask us to make sure she's got some champagne, so she's my favorite right now. We have gotten to the point where everyone has a specific list of things they can help with. In the nicest of terms, these things are suited to everyone's unique strengths. In the plainest terms, my mom's and MIL's responsibilities amount to "important" busy work like talking to out of town Family about travel, helping pick stuff for the dessert bar, and helping pick centerpieces. Shit I know will happen whether or not they put real effort into it, stuff that can't really possibly get messed up. 

That ended up more of a rant than I was planning on but whatever. 

Make your people a list. When it comes to pre-wedding event, it would be totally acceptable to have them "co-host", have a "planning dinner" with them both, and then tell them you'll email what you need them to do, or find reasons it would be easier for stepmom to do these things instead of mom. For me, a lot of our "reasons" are "I'm actually headed over there for an errand today!" Or "her friend can get us a discount!" If they have tasks, they feel useful. I have taken my mom shopping for decor stuff like ten times. I rattle on about details and pretty things to pacify her for a while, I pick out some lanterns or some shit I was going to get anyway, she cries about being excited and how she wants to be involved more, I tell her she's getting more time than anyone else (sort of true since FH and I are doing everything ourselves lol) and that I will let her know when we've made a decision about something. She's already shown me like fifty MotB dresses she loves and I'm just like "wow! So beautiful!!!!!!1!!!11!" And she is happy again. 

Little white lies won't kill anyone and they'll save you a huge headache. My mom is currently in charge of asking her friend if we can borrow dessert table stuff. She has taken over a month to do this. I am preparing to buy or rent stuff if she doesn't get it done soon, so whatever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couples therapy, man. But I'd suggest looking into a MFT that specifically helps with families and abuse as well as communications issues. Ours wasn't and it was difficult for us to find a plan that really worked. We mainly fixed our communication issues there and then worked on handling our parental issues (my mom is the kind of person who can occasionally be awesome but for most of my childhood was the type of person that should have had CPS called on her, FH used to be a hardcore momma's boy who would always take her advice/choices over anyone else's until he realized that he was being super weird), which was helpful in the long run but maybe not the best way to handle it. 

Sounds like he honestly wants to try, and sounds like he had my kinda younger years. My parents were at times awesome, fun people, and I remember those days fondly while also remembering that they were pretty shitty a lot of the time too. It makes it really hard to have that kind of childhood because you desperately want to defend family members that gave you good memories. Took me a really long time to come to terms with what my relationship with my parents really was - I didn't really admit it was abuse until last year, and I'm 26, even though I was openly able to talk about the worst days of my childhood with people. sounds like your guy is maybe not at that point yet. It's not an easy point to get to. If he wants to work on it, he does. I love my mom, but there's no way in hell im leaving my kids at her house overnight after the emotional abuse she threw at me for so long. 

I'd maybe sit down with him and say "I understand your relationship with your family is complicated, but as someone who wants to be a mother, I cannot in good faith have children with you and then leave them alone in the care of people who YOU have told me did x, y, and z when you were a kid. If you heard that a nanny or daycare worker yelled/threatened your kid, or smacked a kid, you'd say they were not capable of caring for your kid, right? You'd fire them and not leave your kid in their care. Same goes for family. I am not rejecting your good memories of your childhood! There were probably plenty of happy memories. but I am looking out for our future offspring so that they don't have to have the NEGATIVE experiences you did." 

My FH got to a point where he understood that I would not be leaving our kids in the care of any of our four sets of parents. But it took him a while to get there. I wouldn't have agreed to marry him without his agreement on that. It's why so many people say you need to have that real, in depth conversation about child rearing and child care. Sometimes people think "we're both good people! Our kids will be fine!" And then they have totally different ideas. 

I hope everything goes well for you. I don't doubt that you'll stand your ground, which is a badass Step One already! 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I need all of those things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High of 85 and low of 68. Hoping it's actually cooler than that because I'm a baby about warm weather, lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. I, too, was nervous about it somehow taking away my personality or changing me. I didn't want some revolutionary Happy Kate Pill, just to feel less shitty. And that's pretty much what's happening. I'm still me, still weird, just a little less down on myself and less anxious overall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds exactly like my experience with Wellbutrin so far. I'm a little over two months on, and the changes are so subtle they're almost not recognizable, but if I really sit down and think about it, my mood has improved in small ways over the last two months, and I'm not so tired all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Rant] I CAN plan my whole wedding by myself, but I've got a huge family that has all offered to help and then flaked at one point or another. Also my bridal party is half what I thought it would be and I feel friendless. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FH and I have been together six years, we've always known we'd get married and I always knew I'd plan most of it myself. Not because I had to, but because our parents are both divorced and remarried, so we have four sets of parents and a zillion other family members to contend with. It's just easier if we dole out small tasks and handle the bulk of it ourselves. We knew we'd have plenty of help from people when the time came that we needed help, so we didn't want to hire a professional planner or anything. We just figured we'd hammer our the details ourselves first and then welcome help as soon as we needed it. 

But jeez, people, come on! 

My mom has been super gung-ho about wedding planning since before FH popped the question. She's a Pinterest junkie and has literally had a board for her kids weddings since before FH and I got together. She's got so many IDEAS but refuses to believe that anyone else's ideas are worth anything because they're not this pinterest perfect blush and sage wedding she's been obsessing over for years. Not that I really give a crap what she thinks about my wedding, because I'm a grown woman and she and I have had a rocky relationship since my birth, but it takes a toll when every. Single. Thing. Is "well wouldn't it be nicer if you did x, y, or z thing I showed you?" No. It would not. She also has a good friend at work that is an awesome event planner. She does these things for fun and puts together flowers, dessert tables, all kinds of stuff. Early on in planning my mom said the friend offered herself up for planning help, grabbing fresh flowers day of and helping set them up (my wedding is up a mountain, so vendor organization is a bane) which I was super happy to hear, but now my mom is being a pain in the ass and won't give me the girl's contact info. She insists on doing all of the communication herself. But she doesn't have time to hear details, so now I'm six months out from my wedding, all the local florists are booked up, and I am this close to telling my mother that if she doesn't give me this girls contact info, she's going to have to be the one who pays for my flowers since I can't find a friggin florist. 

My dad and stepmom were also super excited about planning and promised to help pay for a bunch of stuff. Then my dad very suddenly got "laid off" (for the third time in three years, which, let's face it, he's getting fired because he's addicted to painkillers and he's an idiot) so they can't help financially. Fine. We have more than enough money at this point. But they still seemed interested in helping until they just stopped answering my phone calls. They're lucky they're even getting invited to the wedding at this point, because I see them maybe once a year even though they live like an hour and a half away. He's moved on with his new family, I get it, but once again I fell for promises that nobody could keep. Also, we used to be closer with them so I had always planned on having my stepsisters as bridesmaids, but I'm pretty sure my dad has been telling them that I have been ignoring HIM, instead of the other way around, so they pretty much don't like me now no matter what I do, so I'm down two bridesmaids. 

My FH's family has been on and off helpful, but they've recently been rocked by a devastating loss in the family so I am not going to take up any more of their time than absolutely necessary. This is something that made us consider postponing our wedding entirely, we're just barely in the midst of it, but I'm not going to bother them with wedding stuff for a while. I know they'll want to help in their own time and their own ways, but I am giving them as much space as I can for now. (I haven't brought up postponing to any family members that are close to it, but some on the fringe have said that we shouldn't, the family will need something happy and six months is enough time to process things and be able to have something happy happen later on.) 

My sister is supposed to be my MOH but she's literally the least helpful person. She's combative and she's got an attitude on her. I've always known this, but she seemed like she really wanted to help at first, so I asked her to be MOH and now she's basically always busy or wants to talk about something else. She's supposed to be planning my bridal shower and bachelorette and not only can I not get her to help me plan, I can't even get time to see her to bring it up. She's super keen on planning what dress she's going to wear and where she's going to stay and what fun stuff is going on, but she can't be bothered to actually be responsible. I made sure to ask her, "are you sure you can handle this?" And she was all promises. She's got a good job but she doesn't work long hours, so she can certainly afford to help with these things and she has plenty of time, but she's holed up with her new boyfriend that she very suddenly moved in with and everyone else is just out on the line. 

My other stepsister, who was supposed to be one of my bridesmaids, found out that she's going to be going to her dream school next September. Across the country. And her dad's relationship with my mom is sort of on the rocks, so I'm definitely not going to make her fly back and miss her first weekend at college for a wedding that might make her uncomfortable. 

I don't have a lot of friends and even fewer of those friends have gotten married, so I'm kind of lost. 

FH has, luckily, been my rock. This just further reaffirms why I'm marrying this man. Even in the face of his own tragedy, he's been supportive and loving and as helpful as he can be. He's always been pretty involved in wedding planning but now he's pretty much the only one giving me motivation to keep going. We'd elope, but we already have so many deposits in and we are really actually excited to have this wedding and get everyone together. I suffer from intense bouts of depression, and this whole loss thing just has me at a really low point. 

We visited our venue last weekend though, and it was so beautiful and really tried to kickstart the rest of our planning. FH says we should just bunker down for a week or two and plan the entire rest of our wedding, and I'm not against the idea, as long as he brings vodka.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, I connected my ipad keyboard so I could type this shit out because it would take too long to peck out manually. Sounds like you're in roughly the same situation as me. I have one bio sister, three step sisters, one sister in law, two best friends, and not enough vodka. Mine sort of weeded themselves out by a combination of location (one step sis going off to college, I am not making her miss her first weekend there) and other crap (my other two stepsisters I see maybe twice a year, we're not close and they're kind of flaky, my FSIL will be FH's best 'man' because they've always been super close) so I'm down to three. FH has 5 because he thought I'd have 7, so now I'm super short on people but whatever, I'll have my most important people with me. 

Yours sounds harder to figure out, but just from what I can see from your comment, I'd suggest this: 

1. Little sister: MOH doesn't have to reeeeally be anything but a title. Like MY little sister, I don't expect her to actually plan the whole thing herself, even though she's technically my MOH. Can you maybe ask a parent or another bridesmaid to help her with planning and organizing? Especially since she'll be out of town for some of it and probably busy. That's what I'm doing with mine. I love her dearly but she's an airhead and she's 22 and can barely remember what day it is sometimes, so she's getting an "assistant" in the form of our mother. She might not be in town every day while you're planning, but she'll probably be eager to help when she IS there. 

2. Baby sister: would be an awesome JB. Take her dress shopping, find her a cute JB dress, have her get ready with you and the girls, maybe take her to lunch with a few of the other bridesmaids and let her help out if you're having a bridal shower. Age-appropriate jobs can make a JB feel helpful and included if they can't do standard stuff like Bachelorette parties or stuff like that. 

3. Big sister: This one's tough. I would say ask her if you want to, but make sure she knows upfront what will be expected of her, financially and otherwise. Get together with her or call her and say you'd love for her to be a bridesmaid if she wants to make that happen, but that you'd totally understand if she can't swing it. Let her know that you're planning on a dress within $x-$y range, that you're hoping to do x, y, or z for a bachelorette party (like, what do you have in mind? a one-night party, or is she going to have to shell out for a weekend away?) and that the wedding will be in x location (will she need a hotel, or is there family she could stay with? Any other wedding weekend events in the mix?). Then, with all of that information presented, let her know that you'd love for her to say yes, but that if she doesn't think she'll be able to swing it, you'd still love it if she could get ready with you and maybe make it to the bridal shower or bachelorette if she wants. You also have to consider this: if you ask her and she says she can commit to those things, but then later down the line she suddenly can't afford the dress, can you afford to help her out? If that's something you're willing to help out with or risk in order to have her with you, then ask her. (I have some money set aside to help my little sister with stuff since I know she committed to being my MOH, but she will inevitably need some assistance with it.)

4. Older sister: I wouldn't ask her. You just listed several reasons I wouldn't want to invite someone to be my own bridesmaid. Sounds like more trouble than it's worth. And it's not really your fault FH is asking your brother. She can still get ready with you without having to be in the bridal party. 

5. College bestie 1: Ask her to be a bridesmaid, with the additional note that while your little sister is your MOH, she's going to need plenty of help in that department and you'd love it if she could help plan and organize, since she's just as important to you! You COULD also ask them both to be co-MOH, which I've seen done successfully! My old friend just got married and had two MOHs, and they split responsibilities and helped each other out a ton. Like your little sister, she might not be in town all the time, but she'll probably be very excited to help out when she can.

6. College bestie 2: I would say have a conversation with her about it. If she really might not be able to be there at all, it might not be worth it. But if there's a chance she'd fly back, or a chance she would be in town at that time, she could do it. Be honest with her about it, that you'd love to ask her but that it would be painful to ask her and then have her not be able to be there at all. 

7. High school bestie: Ask her! With so many others in the bridal party missing for huge chunks of time, it'll be nice to have a good friend who will be in town and physically there for a lot of it. 

8. Study abroad friend: I'd skip. It would be a nightmare organizing dresses and events. NZ is pretty far (obviously) and not like someone who lives a few hours away and can make it down for a weekend. She'd probably only be there for the wedding itself and that's not really the point of a bridal party. She can always get ready with you, etc, but logistically, long-distance bridesmaids are a problem. 

9. Bye, college roommate. Invite her to the wedding, but don't push for someone you aren't as close with anymore. 

tl;dr: Bridal Party: Little sister (MOH), baby sister (JB), big sister (maybe), college bestie 1 (possible co-MOH, definitely helping little sister), college bestie 2 (maybe), high school bestie. With others invited to join in getting ready and pre-wedding events as you and they see fit. If both of your maybes say no, you have 4 but a dedicated 4. If both of them say yes, you've got 6, which is pretty close to even anyway. 

Okay that was a lot of words, but I hope it helps a little haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walking? PT. 
Walking in the dark? PT. 
Falling objects? PT. 
Wild animals? PT. 
Pack too heavy? PT. 
Hungry? PT.
Gushing blood? PT. 
Existential crisis? P motherfucking T. 

You smack that beautiful bitch around you and quit complaining.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So beautiful! I love the whole thing, top to bottom. 

My center stone is my late grandmothers, it was in a necklace my late grandfather gave her for one of their big anniversaries. It's smaller than most people would electively choose, a little discolored, but I love it. And the coloring sometimes makes it look like a fancy yellow diamond, even though it's not suuuper yellow. I went with a very pretty verragio setting that almost wouldn't accommodate the smaller diamond, but my fianc told the jeweler the deal and they somehow made it work and made it very secure. 

She passed when I was 8 or 9, breast cancer. We were all on vacation when it happened. My grandpa passed about ten years later. They were by no means rich, but he found every way he could to spoil the hell out of her. They loved each other so much, and I'm glad I get to carry a bit of that with me every day. 

Having a reminder like that is a blessing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooh I'm going to have to go to target for a bunch of those. We're doing something very similar - mountains, string lights, etc. 

The ones we have so far are black and gold, we're hoping to add larger ones though. We're doing all fake flowers and LED candles, since we can't have open flame at our venue and we'll be up there the whole weekend, so we're doing very minimal real flowers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to say the same thing, lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap. Not much advice to be given because I'm approaching the same situation, almost to a T, and I have been wondering the same. FH and I are getting married in a few months and don't want to wait too long for kids. My mom is bipolar and has explosive, manipulative anger problems that meant some shitty mistreatment for most of my life. When FH and I got together I moved in with him super quickly and my relationship with my mother, which I had hoped would get better with us not living under the same roof, basically just got worse. 

I think the only thing I can suggest it this - you may not even have to broach this topic if you set boundaries very very firmly. Something like "mom, while I would eventually like for us to reach the point where we are more comfortable, I do not want you stopping by unannounced anymore. We have a routine at home and your visits often interrupt and make things difficult. If you'd like to schedule times to see kid with us, we can do that. But right now we can't trust you to respect boundaries." 

If she throws a fit, she's not being respectful and you shouldn't feel bad about telling her that she won't be allowed to spend time with your kid until she can fix it. And if it gets to the point where she honestly is trying to respect boundaries, be frank with her. "Remember all those stories you told me? I am not ready to trust you alone with kid because of these. It will take (time/effort/whatever) to make us think about it in the future but I am very protective of kid and for right now, you watching kid alone is off the table." 

If she STILL throws a fit about your MIL watching kid, fuck it. She can't see your kid because she mistreated you and doesn't give a crap about respecting your boundaries as parents. She is cut off until she can grow up.

Gives her a chance to change without risk of leaving her alone with kid. Idk. I am still struggling with how I'm going to tell my mom this stuff, so if you figure it out, let me know. Ugh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 05:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, thank YOU.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I had problems last week when wedding planning was being a pain in the ass. Hah. Just when I start to get annoyed with petty things in my life, bad things must happen. 

My grandmother beat breast cancer just a few years ago. She's a tough old broad but when she was diagnosed with uterine cancer a few weeks ago, the whole family was worried. Luckily they caught this new stuff fairly early so the hysterectomy should get it all out, but she's 75 and her body is just barely recovering from the breast cancer and the chemo. Lady just can't catch a break. 

My sister-in-law was due to have her baby shower this Saturday. I just bought gifts for her babies, including a beautiful wingback glider chair she wanted and a bunch of clothes. I wrapped the gift at home and within the hour we got a text that she'd gone into early labor, they were trying to stop it. Twenty minutes later we get the text that she's going in for an emergency c-section. She's 24 weeks along, which is JUST on the right side of viable, but neither of the babies seemed to be in any kind of distress, SILs body just didn't want to be pregnant anymore. They both came out crying, which is great news because it means their lungs are working a little on their own. They're both in the NICU and we're just hoping for the best. 

And I can't visit either of them because I'm still fighting off this stupid cold that I've had for like the last fucking MONTH. 

And I'm STILL supposed to just keep planning my wedding like the world isn't crashing down around me. I don't give a shit about tablecloths right now. I just want my family to be okay. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been engaged for a year PLUS two months and have six to go. I think half of my celebrating at our wedding will be me celebrating not having to plan my wedding anymore. (Doesn't help that we both have divorced and remarried parents, aka 4 sets of parents with very different opinions!)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, DB has a potty mouth. 4F used to think it was a good idea to copy his curse words because initially it made people giggle. This lead to, when I had just started with them and she was 2.5, the best line ever. 

I was telling DB - he just got home, then-2.5F was sitting by our feet - that some jerk cut us off on our way to school and we had to brake really hard to avoid him. She looks up at her dad, scrunches up her face, and says "yeah, fuckin' asshole!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad Nanny Diaries: I called one of the kid's friends a turd when she was sitting two feet away. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She didn't hear me, and she deserved it. This kid is spoiled, whiny, and a total BRAT. She apparently said some mean things to 8F today and tried to get her excluded from the friend group. 8F is a little sensitive so she came out almost in tears. 

She wouldn't tell me what it was at first, but when she finally told me I was like "Oh, Sophia? She's a turd, just ignore her. You know who your friends are." And 8F cracked up and told me well, she HAD gotten to hang out with some friends she didn't usually talk to, and yeah, Sophia is kind of a turd but she'll be fine. 

I also curse in front of my kiddos (the parents do it occasionally too, it just makes them giggle) and give them extra screen time when I don't want to deal with the drama. 

But the kids love me, the parents love me, and I love them. Oh well! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nah, I'm gonna walk solo. Grandma is getting pretty old and uses a walker and I am a grown woman who really should be walking alone. But I did think about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My FH is a gem. And he's gonna yell at my mom for me re: wedding shit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean he's also prone to being a total turd sometimes because he can be a bit robotic but he's a genuinely good dude who has committed to better communication and has shown effort. I am so proud of him. 

The icing on this magical cake is this. I, who have always had problems with my mother, am getting married to aforementioned robot man. We've been together over five years, it's time, we're super chill about the whole thing. I actually surprised myself with how I am not being totally neurotic with this process. (My general feeling is "Wear what you want, show up when you want, yes I am wearing keds, no we are not getting a giant cake, yes there will be bugs, we are getting married in the forest, we can't take everyone to every fitting and I'm not giving in to tantrums, hope you can make it, there's gonna be an open bar!" That said, I am fully aware that the hardest part of wedding planning is everyone ELSE that is involved. 

My mother, namely, is the Chief Crazy Person. My mother and I don't have the best relationship, she's bipolar and never sticks to meds long enough to make a difference. She was not the best mother during my younger years, and I continue to slip back into her persuasive clutches even though she continues to treat me like crap. I'm actively working on making myself more resistant to this kind of shit but I still fail sometimes. It completely stresses me out to the point of tears at least once a month. I have had to take communication breaks and go temp NC just for my mental health. It's gotten better but still hard. 

So where we're getting married, there are cabins onsite. Not a ton, but enough for maybe 30 people. When we went for our venue visit it was just me, FH, my mom, and his mom. His mom paid our deposit even though I asked her not to (she's a whole other problem, ugh) and my mom immediately tried to take over, saying she was going to visit and rent a cabin a few weeks later and that she really wanted this one cabin for the wedding weekend. I was like "ok we'll talk about it later" but since we booked in July she will Not. Give. Up. She constantly says "oh just put me wherever!" But then when I suggest something else (we're trying to save certain spots for family with young kids) she gets all whiny and says how she'd reeeeally like this one instead. She also promised to help my sister (my MOH, the GC, also another problem) plan my bachelorette party and bridal shower. So far she: 

A: hasn't given us the money she promised us 

B: has bitched about the cabin thing 

C: is upset I didn't take her to our catering tasting 

D: threw a fit about dress shopping (I told her to invite my sister, she forgot, she blamed me for my sister being upset even though my sister had already gone with me once and this certainly wasn't the last time) 

E: she keeps making comments about how she's soooo surprised that I'm not being a bridezilla (I hate that term, and also I am not the kinda person to be weird about my wedding. I am normally a pretty chill person, it's just HER that annoys me all the time) and that she expected me to be a control freak and make everyone do things just right. That's all her. 

F: She thinks she's entitled to so much. My dad's kind of a jerk so he's not walking me down the aisle. My next thought was my sister but now I don't want that either. When I discussed this with my mom, her response was that she thought she would get to do it. Even though she has verbally, emotionally, and sometimes physically abused me since I was very young. Uh. No. 

G: She has in the past had jobs that have included putting on events. Some of these events have been big and pretty cool, not gonna lie. But she has very different ideas than we do about this wedding. She basically insisted that she would be our coordinator, and when I told her we were thinking about hiring someone, she got all offended and went "well, I DO plan events for a living," (not really anymore but whatever) "so I don't know why you'd waste your money." Uh, because you're crazy and you scream in my face when you are the least bit stressed and I don't want that on my wedding day? Jeez. 

... and I'm just sure there's more to come. I was stressed out for a while about all this. Basically, FH and I both have parents that divorced and remarried, so we have four sets of parents and my grandmother (who is contributing significantly and is my mother figure and a total badass awesome lady) to contend with. Everyone wants a piece of this wedding and I'm in the middle. I basically told FH the minute we started talking budget that we needed to be clear - contributions do not equal decision-making power. Noooo way. Because warring opinions will not get this thing off to a good start. If someone gives us an idea that sucks or tries to control something, I just clam up and ignore it. Sometimes people (like our mothers!) keep bringing stuff up. I told him I was done. This was OUR wedding. I am not going to compromise and lose something we love because so and so doesn't like it. 

So my man, my big goofy robot man, he smirks and he says "let me contact her then. Seriously. I will tell her I'm in charge of x, y, and z things she's bugging you about, and I'll email her and tell her to bring up any comments she has to me, not you. She what she says about THAT." 

At first I thought he was being facetious, but then he wasn't smiling and he started talking about which things he could take charge of. He said he could take care of lodging because it's mostly his family, and he could take care of putting together a music set up and requests, and he would be totally up for "taking blame" for anything I wanted that my mom was against. Like hiring another coordinator. Heh. 

So last weekend he and I went to visit the venue. It's just as perfect as we remembered. We're so excited! And while we were up there, we booked the wife of the venue owner as our coordinator, since she does that sort of thing. Last minute, FH realized I needed an "out" for my mom taking charge and said "hell yeah, let's do this."  

When we came back and my mom flooded my phone with texts, I told her we hired the lady. She knows the place better than anyone and will also help with the rehearsal dinner the night before. She's cheaper than any coordinator we looked up and she's super on top of it. 

My mom's reply was icy, but... civil. She'll be upset about it in time, I'm sure. She was expecting me to offer her the spot after (under pressure) I told her I would think about it. 

But for now, we've removed her from a spot of power, I'll placate her with other jobs, and my FH has agreed to be the point of contact for everything she wants to bitch about. 

Super glad I'm marrying this man. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. A veil and belt would look pretty, but keep them both minimal - how are you thinking of doing your hair? If down, a simple comb veil that could be worn for the ceremony will give you a traditional feel without being too traditionally bridal. As for a belt, with that I would shy away from anything too sparkly. Something beaded in the same color scheme of the dress might look nice. 

I am also considering a fairly non-traditional dress. People are not every good at hiding their... confusion? disappointment? Whatever. It hurt at first and it still kinda stings but at the end of the day, if it makes YOU feel beautiful, and it's going on YOUR body, wear whatever you want! Which leads to my next point: 

2. Next time your MOH says something that negative about your dress/choices that you are obviously excited about, tell her she's being a turd. From me, if you want to pass blame. My sister was purposefully left out of one dress appt because she and my mother team up with their opinions, which are usually the opposite of whatever I say. Turds. The whole lot. Love them, but jeez.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A haz-mat suit and bunny ears  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 07:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, same, I am so looking forward to wedding pictures where I'm harrassing waiters for bites of food and then standing in a corner eating alone. No shame. I also totally put our sweetheart table on a porch above people and a thing sort of in front of us so people can't easily come talk to us. I'm paying like a zillion dollars for catering, I'm gonna eat like a damn queen. 

I also am a nanny by day, so I am used to making weird voices and faces WAY too much, so pictures are gonna be awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ovulating today. Very sensitive to hormonal changes so I feel like crap. Also there is literally no good food in my house and I have a migraine. Fuck. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yikes. Super fun thing about ours is that most of our guests are staying on-site or within walking distance. We have a full four day weekend rental of a place up in the mountains with a dozen or so cabins, and other rentals literally a few hundred feet down the road. The hope is that zero people have to drive!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah fuck that. What does your husband have to say about it? Has he talked to his brother? This kind of behavior is batshit. 

If the brothers haven't talked to each other about this, they need to. If your husband isn't backing you up, he needs to. And if he does back you up, he can politely tell his brother that not only will you not be staying elsewhere, but that you're uncomfortable and a bit offended by the fact that the bride wants to completely separate you from everyone else. 

This is not how healthy family relationships start. Wedding or not she's being super disrespectful and she needs to be told NO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I used to be wedding obsessed but now I'm 6 months out from my wedding date and I'm basically like "lol wear what you want, come when you want, idc, we're not doing a big cake, I'm wearing sparkly keds and idk what dress I'm wearing, but I do know there will be an open bar." I don't even understand how people can be this crazy about weddings. We're shelling out a big ass chunk of change but we're not making demands of people. Wtf. The marriage is more important than the wedding. My mom and sister expected drama (even though I am not a dramatic person in the slightest, that's all them) and are like waiting for me to go through some kind of metamorphosis from level-headed grown ass woman to total narcissistic banshee. Not happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 09:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take #5!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geez OP, warn us when you and DH are going to whip out those shiny steel spines! You could fucking cut someone!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speak for yourself, Dirty Jeff has never been inside me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say just ask her! Either way she'll probably appreciate that you were thinking about her level of comfort with the situation. She may be also wanting to hold hands or kiss but also unsure if you're comfortable with it. Just send her a quick text or call and say "hey, I'm so excited to see you later. But I just wanted to check with you - would it be okay with you if I hold your hand or kiss you in front of the group? I didn't want to just spring it on you but I would like to do those things, as long as you're comfortable with it." 

Just be prepared for her to say she might not be comfortable with it yet. That doesn't mean she doesn't want to do those things, just that she might not be ready for other people to know since it's so new.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, your list sounds like mine. And your categories are basically exactly what we went with. We're having a semi-destination wedding (same county that most of the people we're inviting live in, but up a mountain or two and a bit of a drive for a day visit). 

We split up our list into three initial groups - 

A: those we know for a fact are coming (parents, siblings, wedding party, other very close family)
B: those who we think are probably going to come, at least for the wedding day but probably for the weekend (fringe family, old friends) 
C: those who probably won't be there but at least needed an invitation (far away family we haven't seen in a while, busy family friends, people we haven't seen in a while but used to really care about) 

Each of those is in a column. Would the whole family come? All four in A. Are maybe the parents of this family going to come, but their kids won't be there? Two in B, two in C. That kind of thing. That way we could more accurately guess at a guest count when we had early meetings with vendors. 

From there, we had additional columns. 

- adults versus children under 12, which is a standard sort of age cut offs for vendors like catering who might have a separate charge or menu for kids. 

- What days we expected them to be there. Our parents and close family will come up with us on Thursday. We're having a welcome BBQ combined with our rehearsal on Friday. Saturday is the actual wedding. Sunday we're having a farewell breakfast before everyone heads out. Who do we expect to come for the long weekend and help us set up? Who will make a weekend out of it and come for Friday and Sunday? Who is local and might just come for the day? We did our best to set this up just for our own estimates re: rehearsal BBQ and farewell breakfast, but they won't be accurate until we start getting RSVPs, and they don't need to be anyway since we'll just be making a costco run the day we drive up. 

I can send you a picture of how we did our spreadsheets, if you're interested. FH is a data organization dork who counts Excel and Google Sheets as two of his favorite things on earth, so a well-organized wedding was a no-brainer. 

Edit: Forgot to mention - since your wedding will be far for these people, it would be really difficult to expect them to not come with their kids. If you say "No Kids", expect that a significant portion of your guests with kids won't be able to attend at all because of it. However there's also the option of hiring a babysitter/care of some kind for the duration of the wedding. If there's space at your venue, hire a babysitter. I had a friend have her wedding at a nice hotel. She hired two babysitters to watch the kids under 10 in one of the hotel rooms so that the parents didn't have to stress about finding babysitters in an unfamiliar town. The parents loved it because they weren't far from their kids, the babysitters were good about contacting the parents with updates, etc, but the parents got to relax and there were no toddlers underfoot at the fancy wedding. The kids watched movies, had snacks, and got to stay up a little late and have their own little party with their cousins and stuff, so it was fine by them. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like you're me! I could barely be bothered to wear moisturizer most days before I started thinking about the wedding. I've always had a bit of acne and rough skin so I figured that now, at 25/26, I should do something about it. Changed up my routine first. Awesome. Skin cleared up mostly. Then went to get a facial one day, just to try it out. Now I'm getting them monthly. My skin looks amaaaaazzing, best it has since I was a child basically. I am growing out my natural hair for the first time ever (I used to bleach it, dye it, cut it in weird ways, the whole deal) and now it's like 100% my natural color and long and I found out it's curly! Taking care of myself is weird! 

I'd say if you're interested in the back facial, try one out now and see if you like it. I have been experimenting with different facials and stuff and finding out what works. 

My biggest tip would be to stick with the same person. If you love the person who did your facial last time, stick with them. They'll help you figure out what works best with your skin. I know too many people who bounce around between aestheticians because they think THAT's what's going to help things, but most technicians have the same tools. Sticking with one person allows them to keep notes on your skin, what works and what doesn't, and lets YOU become more comfortable with telling them what didn't work so well. Example: I have been seeing a lovely lady named Holly for my facials for about six months. I LOVED my first two, but my third was a little underwhelming. The extractions weren't as thorough, I didn't like the moisturizer she used afterwards, and my skin didn't have that GLOW. She totally took note of my concerns and my facials since then have been amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I'm going to pass - just saw that the shades I was most interested in have a poor formula. And I have too many neutrals to make up for that. Darn! Sorry!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mega Pro! I would also like to see close ups  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 08:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same! I always had bad skin, but I've gotten it almost perfectly clear lately. Might just use like a tap of concealer where needed for the face, then do eye makeup and stuff like normal. I've done this before (at family occasions to test it out) and loved the feeling!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 08:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Srs I saw the sauce, said "lol I can't wait to see the jerk" and then this was directly under that. A+  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 05:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! And I can! 

Basically the key to using flowers next to lights is LEDs - you MUST use an LED bulb or the lights just get too hot and can be a fire hazard. These are the GE Reveal LED bulbs - a great color temperature for applying makeup, dimmable, the whole deal. I'd suggest using four instead of six. If you do use six like I did, you have to have a dimmer or it's waaaay too bright. Found that out the hard way. My eyes. Ouch. 

The electrical stuff is not my area of expertise, my guy did that and it looks a little patched together and I'm not sure that's the right way to do things... but basically we built a larger frame around an IKEA mirror with some cheap boards from Home Depot, and we drilled holes through the frame to put the flowers through so they'd be straight instead of having to bend or glue them, which would make them crooked since so many fake flowers have big plastic bases. I just bent the leftover stems flat back against the frame. That also means they're replaceable! So I can change it up if I want to. 

As for the vanity, it's basically just an IKEA laptop table with the original small shelf taken out and a big piece of shelving from Home Depot in its place, with brackets to secure. I put the dimmer switch for the mirror on the side of the vanity so I can easily reach it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 05:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got them all from Joann - vanity materials were all Home Depot, flowers and paint from Joann. I had awesome coupons but the flowers were still the most expensive part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazing TJ Maxx find - Valentino cardigan for $60! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [THIS](https://imgur.com/a/8ClQP) is the cardigan in question - excuse my weird dressing room picture. 

I was looking for a black cardigan anyway, have been for ages, and in sifting through the racks I saw the Valentino tag. I mean I've never seen one before in my life until today but I recognized the name immediately. I thought I was seeing things, but the price tag doesn't lie either. It's not something I would ever ever consider buying at full price, but a good quality cardigan in a nice cut is totally worth $60 for me, since I have a short torso and short arms and most of them make me look weird. 

I can't find this exact style online anymore but I saw similar cardigans listed at $600-$1000, TJ Maxx tag says $800! (Those things are sometimes off but this price seems to be right on based on what's currently and recently available!) If it were actually $800, I got it for just 7.5% of it's original retail value! 

Probably the best TJ Maxx deal I'll ever find, ever. I will probably be the only one that knows it's Valentino but oh well, I'll feel fancy. Werk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 07:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he's here trolling Reddit with us now, finally happy that someone realized he was right the whole time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [BEFORE ](https://imgur.com/gallery/NN82K) 

My fianc and I built me a custom glass topped/see through vanity a few years ago. The mirror was always a crappy little warped plastic frame from Walmart (not pictured) so I wanted to upgrade. Grabbed a big square mirror at IKEA with the goal of building custom lighting and possibly putting flowers around it. 

Great success! 

[Here](https://imgur.com/gallery/Et5ay) is a better/softer picture so you can see bulb placement and the flowers better. 

I haven't officially sat down to use it yet, as I don't wear makeup to work, but I'll use it Saturday and Sunday! I am officially considering my vanity setup complete. (Yeah, right.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Built a floral framed vanity mirror to top off my DIY glass top vanity setup! It's the prettiest thing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My FMIL didn't like them when I told her. She said something about "TENNIS SHOES AT A WEDDING?" Then I just sort of zoned out until she was done and never brought them up around her again. Still wearing my damn Keds, I'm getting married in the middle of the forest and I literally haven't worn heels in 5 years so I'm definitely not hobbling around in stilettos in the dirt. Agh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 07:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Palos Verdes, actually. They're fucking everywhere here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother was just diagnosed with several large non-cancerous fibroids. In the same week my grandmother, who JUST beat breast cancer a couple years ago, was diagnosed with early stage uterine cancer. Their matching hysterectomies are scheduled for the same week in different hospitals. Just... ugh. 

But my grandma is a tough old broad and survived her first cancer and will beat the second one. And you will too. Keep ya head up, OP. We're rooting for you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm, I work in an affluent neighborhood in Southern CA that is littered with them. They're assholes and they're drama queens. Yelling at 4AM and crapping on everything and just laying down in the middle of the road and refusing to move.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 08:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having been in her position before because of a mess of depression and body image issues, she reeeeeally needs to get help for this. Specific, separate help with a therapist that has experience with sexual issues. I didn't get help and for several months the thought of having sex with my fianc was bizarre. I'd begrudgingly do it and do whatever I could to make it end soon, even when it felt good, because I was so anxious. He constantly tried to reassure me, is as attracted to me as you are to your girl, but it is hard hearing it from your partner because OF COURSE they love you and want you. 

Individual and/or couple's therapy can be so so helpful. I also started eating healthier and working out a bit (partially to lose weight and partially just to feel better about my body) and my endorphins are through the roof. 

See if you can't be intimate with her in other ways in the mean time. Massage, making out, lots of cuddling. It helps when she can be very comfortable and when you're patient. That's all I got for ya.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
