<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5580</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 20:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what flea market you went to haha. Wagon Wheel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 00:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Florida?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 01:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so glad I got one away from the scalpers. I have had so many problems with them lately with the amiibos and all the limited additions that I stress out more than I should. Still haven't given them one penny yet though so that's a victory! I am glad you feel the same way as I do. 
My friend hates scalpers so much that he buys multiple of things so that he can sell them to friends and others he meets in real life for the price he bought it for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 06:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they're goneeee. I got one because of you. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 05:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the red is a limited edition?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 00:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are 16 do not be thinking of this so soon. You still have a lot of time before you fully 'grow out' my friend went from A to D from 16 to 19. Be strong and don't let other people get you down. This would be a lifetime commitment and could end up backfiring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 20:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, from the pictures I don't want to trade for anything unless you have a double because you have some great stuff there and I would hate to seperate anything! I love gamecube in case you have anything for that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 07:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great collection! Pretty jealous haha. Willing to trade anything you have extra? I have a ton of stuff and I am moving soon so I would like to trade up to stuff I can move with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tying knots is just tangling ropes so that they don't untangle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 16:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 03:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love City Trial for that game it was my first real free-roam game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 00:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper mario the thousand year door for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 03:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not notice that until now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Clockwork Quartet - The Doctor's Wife [Alternative/Steampunk] (2012) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 21:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 23:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oxygen would be spiders.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
