<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3154</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 07:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read it in German and I generally liked it! My favorite story was the one with the Ralf Tanner imposter because it's the most confusing and interesting one. "Rosalie goes to die" was also pretty unique, it kinda reminded me of the game "The Stanley Parable". The worst one is most definetly the one with the internet forum. God the language in that one is so "Fellow Kids". I know that it's supposed to be the joke but it comes of like Daniel Kehlmann has no idea how people in forums really talk and the writing style in that short story is just obnoxious. Apart from that one I found "Ruhm" a pretty interesting short-story collection with unusual narratives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that they think that it is an arbitary phrase, however, why would you wish Muslims f.ex. "Merry Christmas"? Doesn't make much sense imo. Also, why complain about a problem if you can just go on saying "Merry Christmas" as much as you like? It seems like the mere fact that _other_ people choose to use it offends them on a personal level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever witnessed someone being criticized for saying "Merry Christmas"? I have never. For me "Happy Holidays" is just something you _can_ say to be more inclusive. I never understood why that is such a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IJ is great. After a while it feels like you really _know_ some of the characters, like you understand them, even if they're just side characters in Ennet House. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly English words written in Katakana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make America Sterile Again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly the politically themed ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason I laughed out loud at the part where Orin was supposed to be looking after Hal and Mario but instead smoked pot with Marlon Bain and is REALLY BAD at lying to Avril. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first 100 pages are indeed pretty confusing and seemingly pointless but it really gets better in my opinion, when you start to get a feel for the world and most characters have been introduced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the same for me, though I have seen lots of people who find it _really_ scary and I get why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 19:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I'm not sure we're going to get that but I fell in love with the characters so it's alright. I suspect that the tape is like the Pulp Fiction Briefcase and that it will be up to the reader to decide what it shows, I already have a suspicion what it could be though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 14:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I'm a 17 year old high-school student from Germany. I started reading the German, physical edition of IJ on December 20th and right now I'm about 900 pages (out of 1500) deep. So far it has been an amazing experience. The first 200 pages were pretty confusing and all over the place but somewhere around p 300 it really set in and it has already become one of my favorite novels! I only know about David Foster Wallace from /r/books. After listening to This Is Water, I was really impressed and definitely wanted to give IJ a try, especially since the award-winning German translation is supposed to be more than great. Really looking forward to the discussion here and I'm planning on reading through the English version sometime in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't the sin and cos basis just orthogonal and not orthonormal, since their length in function space is not 1 but pi if I'm not mistaken. Is there an additional factor for correction? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Infinite Jest, by David Foster Wallace** I'm 850 out of 1500 pages in and it really grew on me, I'm really digging the little stories, the subplots and all of the weirdness, as well as actual food for thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whilst it is better than the anime

Not that hard to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> German edition, it has a bigger font. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 09:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's worth it in my opinion. I'm on page 702/~1500 right now and it's great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 23:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only like a tesseract in the sense, that it is a 4d object (rotating around the 4th axis) projected into 3d space projected into the 2d gif you're watching. Other than that it's a fractal that zooms in on itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 23:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that Girl On the Train is overrated. It seems like most redditors really disliked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 00:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Anti-racist is anti-white!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naja, es kam, wie man Anhand der Downvotes sehen kann aber so rber. Fr mich brigens auch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mag sein, dass du dem Ersten nicht zustimmst, aber zu sagen dass beide auf einer Ebene stehen ist doch absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 11:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erster Post: Darstellung der eigenen Meinung

Zweiter Post: "Lutsch doch deiner Mama den Schwanz, du Troll!" 

Ja, eigentlich hast du schon Recht. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 11:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it's a 1168 page long justification too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole Eschaton chapter is just hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have finished reading it just two weeks ago and I'm still in high-school too. It's certainly possible though you have to have the willpower. For me it was a challenge, though it may have been easier had I read it in my native language. Totally worth it once you get a clue of what's going on (and completely lose it afterwards). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only through a third and it took me two weeks. I wouldn't say that I read particularly fast. It opens up a lot after the first 100 pages, once you start to understand the setting and the chronology a little better. Just don't get put off at the start and read it at your own pace. I'm loving it so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich wei nur, dass viele die Englische Ausgabe auch schon unlesbar finden, aber ich wollte mich mal ranwagen. Vielleicht sollte man zuerst mit was einfacherem wie Inherent Vice/Natrliche Mngel anfangen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Knnt ihr Thomas Pynchons Romane in der deutschen bersetzung empfehlen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was haltet ihr von den deutschen bersetzungen von Pynchons, ja eigentlich schon berchtigt, schwierigen Werken? Sollte man trotzdem lieber versuchen sie im Original zu lesen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 10:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Skeptoid" is a great one, that uploads very regularly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 10:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you write like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 15:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree, my point is just that the word gets thrown around so casually and I've seen it being used against people who were just being polite to trans people for example. I didn't mean to take stance on OP's post at all.

Edit: typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 11:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treating every human being with basic decency is an extremely SJW thing to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to read a book in its original language if it's in English, or German but when I know that it's going to be nigh impossible for a non-native speaker (Infinite Jest, Gravity's Rainbow), I tend to grab the German version, since German is my first language. My biggest achievement in English reading so far is getting through House of Leaves without much difficulties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I thought that part was pretty good, considering the context which it occurs in in the novel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally liked it as a work of fiction but I have to admit that I wouldn't want to read any other novel written like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here, started it about a week ago and I'm now on page 350 (German format which has 1500 pages) and it starts to get really great when you get used to his writing style and get a slight grip on the world the characters live in. I'm really happy that I didn't get scared off by people who found it "pretentious" or unnecessarily difficult. Thanks /r/books, I would have never heard of it otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 22:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but that's the point of the meme and your original answer was pretty confusing considering that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 11:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just try it: The antiderivative of x^2 - 4 is 1/3 x^3 - 4x [+C]. Plug in the upper and lower bounds and you get 16/3, which is 5.3 repeating. So the image does get simpler while the actual value gets more accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "only for actual stuff like making a doodle of Muhammad" Yeah it's very hard to tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 00:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a non-native speaker in the sub, who thought the word "feucht" means something along the lines of "cool", while it is actually an ironic translation of "dank" and is probably closest to "moist". It got pretty good when he accidentally said "Das ist echt feucht" at work, which translates to "this is really moist". I can't find the thread right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 12:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, my Mom is all over that crap it is so annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 16:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has a raging hard-on for Wikileaks, Trump and /pol/. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 13:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here: https://wikileaks.org/w/images/a/a1/FBI-pedophile-symbols-page1.jpg

Additionally, look at Podesta in one of Garrison's comics: https://twitter.com/GrrrGraphics/status/811056653399257088 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 01:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He does, in his recent cartoons Podesta is often portrayed with a pizza(face) and sometimes even a pedophile symbol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 00:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it told me that I'd read Infinite Jest in just about 20 hours. Good luck doing that when looking up tons of words (not everybody will have to but I do) and trying to keep track of the chronology and the characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, they took it down again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are probably not serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 23:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much, great advice. If I feel like I can't keep track of the characters, I'll probably write them down if feel the need to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should I take notes on when reading "Infinite Jest" for the first time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 23:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have just bought the German edition of Infinite Jest since it is my first language and the award-winning translation is supposed to be great (it took 6 years to make). After all the praise I've heard, I'm determined to make it through or at least give it a good try. I have read that it is useful to use three bookmarks, to take notes and to look up words or phrases but I'm not completely sure what I'm supposed to focus on. Should I try to keep track of the characters, their intentions, specific words or all of those and more? Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 01:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have just finished HoL. It is a very polarising novel but I enjoyed it greatly and couldn't put it away. It is not for everybody. There are some sequences which are very convoluted (Truant's long footnote in the Echo-chapter) and are borderline non-sensical or, at least for me, very difficult to follow to understand which is probably the intended effect but don't give up, it is a rewarding and horrifying read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's funny, in our school it is reading material in English-class (German high-school) in 10th grade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard the audiobook and man, it is so bland and unoriginal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Und das ausgerechnet von der AfD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 00:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a visual novel that can thematically be compared to Saw and Battle Royale or Hunger Games and has the gameplay of something like Phoenix Wright. You gotta be into that but if you are it's a really fun experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 00:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you played the Danganronpa games, I think it's nicely handled there with the whole Mondo/Taka story being relatively ambiguous for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 23:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree, that would be badass. Sadly I can't see how such a game could be made, because of the target demographic being at least 75% straight males (pulled that number out of my ass, don't know what the actual percentage of straight male gamers is). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 23:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say that theoretically it would have to be a tie between straight males and straight females although statistically it should vary to either side. I don't see a reason why there should be more of one group than the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 22:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is not that there is another majority, it's more about that there are more people who aren't straight men (Women and gay/bi men) than straight men. Although that would be discounting lesbians, nevertheless, straight men do not make up 50% of the population. That's what I get from it atleast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are absolutely right. Out of boredom I've someday decided to just learn a language, fuck it, let's learn Japanese. Put all your energy into it. Math is good too because it's probably more useful and can be really rewarding if you decide to learn programming later.
This is good advice, learning an instrument is also something you can do if you're bored. It is difficult to transition from "reading up on how to learn something best" into actually learning but aside from the intrinsic reward of becoming better at something, you may accidentally learn something useful for life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 23:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's one of the main points people bring up but in my opinion the gunplay is well done, better than in HM1 and I personally like it. Melee oriented playstyles in HM1 and 2 felt like too much of trying to bait the enemies behind a corner. I like that the extensive usage of weapons often allows for big combos if you want to min-max. (Through long range and/or off-screen kills) Thoug I totally get why many people don't like that playstyle as much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.redd.it/rkjn72gba81y.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gets a bad rep, but I find the controls to feel much smoother and the mechanics seem more refined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must have gotten it wrong. Voat is the bastion of ~~hate~~ free speech (it's a constitutional right) after reddit took it away from them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might have worded it badly, but that is not my point. Just calling someone an SJW now, does not automatically give a clarification of what the word means to you when other people read it. It's fine that PmYourWittyAnecdote has a concrete definition but people that just read "SJW" have a very vague sense of what it means and will, regardless of what you intended to say, think that it means what they think it means. I'm not a native English speaker, so forgive my crappy wording. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not arguing that, but if most (not some) of the time, edgy kids obviously misuse it, your definition is not what "SJW" means to most people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but the vast majority of people getting called SJW's are not the extremists that you've described. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He asks "Why should I pay for the decision of others to have children?" again and again as if he didn't read all of the extremely detailed and rational answers given by many of the people in the thread. But who cares, he got his opinion and he won't deviate. Also very contradictory, when he writes things like "time will tell" or to wait for the "long-term effects", when statistically, time has already told very clearly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 20:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, also "cat" would probably be written with  instead of the Kana but as the guy above me said, it's not a big deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also really enjoy Nyx Fears, a rather small channel with a focus on horror films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 19:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not so much political as it is spammy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or on a saddle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 13:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> o0o0o "retarded bitch" o00o0 "fucked like a dog" (you mean doggystyle? i knew you flyover country rednecks were a "once a month on a thursday night at 9 PM missionary style stick my dick through the pajama panthole" bunch. any girl I bang gets fucked like a dog). the only thing you're worse at that than piecing together half assed reddit conspiracy theories is trying to shit talk on reddit. how about this: you should be sterilized, you worthless fucking cunt. not only do you have shit for brains, not only should you have been a blowjob, but the world would be better if you were a cumstain on your parents sheets, a mere piece of jizz dribble that dropped out of your whore mom's (ostensibly legally retarded) mouth after she blew your redneck dad before he slipped her a $20 because he couldn't find any woman with a hole to let him have it for free. but yet, your little bitch of a dad couldn't pull out, and now we're stuck with you, using up our oxygen. just do us a favor and kill yourself. now, I want you to know that wasn't directed at you, but more a theoretical lesson of what I'd say to you if you were actually worthy of any actual anger. from time to time, I like to throw people that are less intelligent, less articulate, and all around more inferior than I am a lesson or two. call it charity. you're a t_d poster, i expected better use it wisely, young padawan. maybe one day, you can learn how government actually works, what the role of a president is, and why a free press would inherently flock to covering a democratic party candidates campaign manager's pedo ring (hint: it has to do with capitalism and "$$$$$". even though you haven't worked in NYC finance like me, I figured you right wingers could at least piece that together. apparently not). anyway, while you've been a nice fun little exercise and fun to lash out towards, you've used up/exhausted your usefulness to me. piss the fuck off cuntrag, and don't speak to me again unless I message or address something to you. blocked and inbox replies off. have a nice life faggot, don't forget that i'm your daddy, fuckboy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 13:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: https://www.reddit.com/r/announcements/comments/5frg1n/tifu_by_editing_some_comments_and_creating_an/damvdr4/?context=3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't forget that i'm your daddy, fuckboy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 13:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> o0o0o "retarded bitch" o00o0 "fucked like a dog" (you mean doggystyle? i knew you flyover country rednecks were a "once a month on a thursday night at 9 PM missionary style stick my dick through the pajama panthole" bunch. any girl I bang gets fucked like a dog).
the only thing you're worse at that than piecing together half assed reddit conspiracy theories is trying to shit talk on reddit.
how about this:
you should be sterilized, you worthless fucking cunt. not only do you have shit for brains, not only should you have been a blowjob, but the world would be better if you were a cumstain on your parents sheets, a mere piece of jizz dribble that dropped out of your whore mom's (ostensibly legally retarded) mouth after she blew your redneck dad before he slipped her a $20 because he couldn't find any woman with a hole to let him have it for free. but yet, your little bitch of a dad couldn't pull out, and now we're stuck with you, using up our oxygen. just do us a favor and kill yourself.
now, I want you to know that wasn't directed at you, but more a theoretical lesson of what I'd say to you if you were actually worthy of any actual anger. from time to time, I like to throw people that are less intelligent, less articulate, and all around more inferior than I am a lesson or two. call it charity. you're a t_d poster, i expected better
use it wisely, young padawan. maybe one day, you can learn how government actually works, what the role of a president is, and why a free press would inherently flock to covering a democratic party candidates campaign manager's pedo ring (hint: it has to do with capitalism and "$$$$$". even though you haven't worked in NYC finance like me, I figured you right wingers could at least piece that together. apparently not).
anyway, while you've been a nice fun little exercise and fun to lash out towards, you've used up/exhausted your usefulness to me.
piss the fuck off cuntrag, and don't speak to me again unless I message or address something to you.
blocked and inbox replies off. have a nice life faggot, don't forget that i'm your daddy, fuckboy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 08:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's also different, because if we draw a cube on a 2D sheet of paper, we are looking on said paper from "the third dimension", from outside, where we can see all of the drawing at once. 4D beings could also look at out 3D world from outside and make a model of a tesseract, that will look weird and pointless to us but makes sense to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 08:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends, AFAIK the consensus is that we live in a 4D space-time. What you are implying is something like the super-string-theory where 5+ hidden dimensions exist but they are really small (around Planck length) and curled up. It's pretty hard to prove string-theory with our capabilities though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 21:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's totally what he just said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sobald man einen TheDonald-Post mit vielen Upvotes runterwhlt, wird man gebannt. /s ^^knnte ^^aber ^^sein </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 00:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure it's a placeholder since the sentence was an example for a situation where you can guess the meaning of the counter out of context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Requiem for a Dream is so crushing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 00:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mac Book Pro, baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 14:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't agree with that, people that say Lgenpresse are in my experience very ignorant and easily manipulated by right-wing populists but I wouldn't say that they're supporting Hitler's ideology. Not to defend them but you have to differentiate a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 16:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, that's pretty good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 09:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will never not like a Dark Souls game, though it's hard to replicate your first Dark Souls experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 07:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really looks like the beginning of Bloodborne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 23:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/LearnJapanese is a good place to start </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My soul has been separated from my body. As my material form descends deeper into the underworld, my soul remains on this purgatorial plain. Goodbye flesh-suit, I have worn for the short period of my life. I have ascended, I am a starchild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My soul has been separated from my body. As my material form descends deeper into the underworld, my soul remains on this purgatorial plain. Goodbye flesh-suit, I have worn for the short period of my life. I have ascended, I am a starchild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 23:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reaper main? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 16:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 16:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I thought I've read all of it but it could well be. There are spirals after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 14:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like Junji Ito, what is it from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is actually very good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 17:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ctrl+F'ed just to see if it was on here. Great soundtrack, great characters, great visuals, we need more :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 13:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could almost call /r/TheDonald a safe space </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 15:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Auerdem gibt es berhaupt keine Handlung und manche Szenen sind einfach total lcherlich, warum hat Florentin einen Plschpapagei, warum wirft die Frau eine Ananas gegen eine Wand, warum sitzen Florentin und sie sich total ernst an einer Tischtennisplatte gegenber, in der Garage, wieso hat Florentin eine Uniform an und einen Basketball am Strand dabei. Dazu noch so Szenen wie die Frisbee Scheibe, die auf das Auto fliegt oder wie Florentin gegen eine Steinwand klopft, wieso auch immer. Die ganzen Dinge sind mir beim ersten Mal gar nicht aufgefallen, ist schon eine gute Parodie auf diese typisch deutschen dramatischen Indie-Filmfestival Filme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 14:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't constant hi-speed kind of a cheese strat for BPM varying tracks? I used to use it but I found that it defeats the point of BPM changes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 14:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I got better and played higher level tracks I upped my hi-speed to 700 where it is now but I would recommend starting out at 400-500 at your level, if you have it at x2.5 for example it depends on the song but I would not recommend that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 16:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The White Bear episode freaked me out for good though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
