<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4227</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who else but Quagmire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh we got our own problems over here. Hey we'll trade you. We'll take Caine if you take Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that's where all our tax dollars are going? Into new complicated ways to say bullshit? It all makes sense now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Assad was an American plant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canadians are the worst tippers on the planet.

That's because Canadians working in service industries (Food Service, etc..) are actually paid a living wage and therefore tips are not encouraged as much as they are here in the U.S. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I John McCain, am a stupid idiot."

For him to vote yes he should be required to stand up in front of the senate and say this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unofficial-official-but-vindictively-enforced-policy-non-policy.

That has to be the most complicated way to say "bullshit" that I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously that guy is going to have evil politicians/company owners/dictators world wide begging for his services. His ability to spin a story is uncanny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free souls!? Oh what a deal. I gotta get out to the stores. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See this is a prime example of how "alternative facts" can be Dangerous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much $ do you think he got for selling his soul? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump: "If I close my eyes and scream fake news loud enough all my problems will just disappear." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah Bush wanted to finish what his father had started. There was reasoning to how we ended up engaging fully in the middle east. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh. hes touched regulations in very specific areas such as coal and manufacturing. We would have to wait until he releases his tax plan and if he ever gets around to that whole deal making / tariffs he was talking about. To call a company deciding to take its business elsewhere asinine is really playing down playing how much of an effect trump really has. I would not view the effect he has had with certain foreign relations asinine. I'm not saying that companies would pull out already placed products / factories. I'm talking about plans for new products / factories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. China is just an example. I was trying to say that America is not the only place to do business. If a company decides they do not want to deal with trump shenanigans there are other places to take their business. Hence another countries view of the U.S is very substantial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ?? Everyone knew about this but they were banned..... well until now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $15 a week is pretty exaggerated but yes they do make less than the average U.S family. But you fail to realize that they have almost a billion more people than the U.S  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe the heads of the foreign companies think America leader is dumb and would rather sell to china then deal with Trump... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 55% of our populace decided to vote. Iirc the number of trump supporters pans out to 25-27% of our eligible voters. The problem wasn't that a majority of our country was stupid. A majority of our country just didn't care and that's the scary part. Too many people saw this as an election between a "douche and a turd sandwich" not realizing that this had a demonstrable effect on their every day lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Europe (besides UK) is actually doing pretty well as far as internal strife is concerned. Their two largest problems are the threat of terrorism and inflation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would be surprised how much another countries perception of the U.S can effect your personal life. Remember we import way more supplies then we export. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each case that you stated had a small hierarchy with more money/power therefore were not actual implementations of socialism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President taps Christie to lead commission to ~~fight~~ encourage opioid abuse.  FTFY  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scan brings up check baggage

Does it actually? I'm pretty sure that concerning baggage it only shows if you have pre-check. 

They are suppose to visually look at you to see what you have on you as well.

Really not too sure about this either? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it would change securities view on someone who walks in with a gun holstered. As of now they have to question is this gun legal or not and is this person a threat or not. This would change to: disarm the person with the gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how baggage check works. The question proposed was that this man checked his gun properly but had no carry on luggage.

Maybe the red flag should have been that the only thing he checked was a gun with no carry on and not just that he had a gun.

I was questioning how you would check if someone had no carry on baggage but did check a gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
