<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject721</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That depends entirely on your definition of rich, and the individual's interest.

Both my current and previous landlords, who both own numerous rental properties / apartment complexes, drive 10-20 year old mini vans.

If you met either of them you'd think they're just your run of the mill  $100K income middle class, based on their dress / car / mannerism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like others said, could be a number of things:

* Switch to a Model X
* Decide they wanted a nicer car (I'm an unashamed Musk/Tesla fan boy but in terms of sheer "luxury" and quality control they're far behind the Germans)
* Have had bad experiences and simply don't want it
* Lease

There are dozens of reasons to get rid of a car. I fully acknowledge this was a financially stupid decision but I've sold a car 6 months after buying it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all for NN and I despise Ajit Pai but holy shit I couldn't even finish the first two paragraphs of that article.

I'd consider myself fairly cynical and distrusting, especially so ISPs merging and NN facing a tough battle the next few years, but this reads like the author just read 1984 -- which would make sense, given the name *Thought Crime Media*. Just as much fear mongering as the ultra conservative/religious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assumed what was meant was that, over the course of the discussion, Trump listened for a collective total of 10 minutes and that's what he gathered. Not that he actually listened for 10 minutes straight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the superconductor allows magnetic flux to enter in quantized packets surrounded by a superconducting current vortex

What does that even mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The hobos who live under the overpass just got ~~a new house and a truckload of free stuff. Plus they can probably eat whatever is left of the driver~~ crushed.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if Lady and the Tramp were ~~metal~~ brutal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm impressed he got as far as he did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those gold wheels look sooo good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Pain of Salvation - Handful of Nothing (live)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_6I2-A3ZxOo#). They changed up the outro for their 'Ending Themes' DVD and it is fucking brutal.

[Opeth - Closure](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DJzvWSEBaBs) is another great one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How are you at exorcising demons

lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, that makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So long as being around isn't a hassle, I think I would use it regularly.

I really want a Vive + steering wheel for a cool racing setup. If AAA games start to come with support then cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not just ramming in VR. It's essentially a major port. So if there were problems like that before, it'll be ~~fixed for 90 now (if they don't fuck up).~~ replaced with new ~~bugs~~ features.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, now all I need is $60K.

Why does the TT RS link in this article go to an Amazon page for a car cover...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd guess $15-$20. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope it'll be a nice big NA, but I'm not holding my breath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect it'll come back eventually, but whatever we get will be quite different. Largely, I suspect, due to energy/safety requirements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It actually was a really great video.

I'm not into drag racing or straight line speed at all. With all of the Teasers they were posting, I was just like, "It's a Hellcat but faster. Cool, I guess."

But actually watching it, him explaining how it kind of is in its own market / class, explain things like being the first production vehicle to come equipped with drag radials, or using the AC to cool the air intake I was like, "OK that's hilariously absurd and I love this thing".

I don't care about drag racing, but I can get behind most automotive projects where the justification is, "Because we can" / "Because no one else is". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The bill, which received general approval last December, tackles the main issues head-on by granting copying permission in some circumstances and by flat-out banning the use of DRM when the public should have right of access to a copyrighted work.

 In a boost to educators, citizens will be given the right to circumvent DRM for teaching and scientific research purposes. There will also be an exception for private copying.

 The draft also outlaws the use of DRM on copyright works that have fallen into the public domain, works which support cultural heritage, and works that were created by public entities or funded with public money.

Seems perfectly reasonable.

Between this and Portugal decriminalizing drugs I wonder how we can get the US to take note... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I flew, 5 months ago, I had no issues uploading and sending photos.

It really wasn't a bad connection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 times her annual income

 ... Wang was stopped by security at Austin-Bergstrom International Airport with **$30,000 in cash wrapped up in several duct-taped bundles**, the document said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So long as they're a demand, there will be a supply.

May as well legalize and regulate it.

Prostitution is no different than drugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If 365 used rubbers makes a Goodyear ...

Ew, Goodyear uses condoms to produce tires!?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory Sewer Level.

Fight off the giant gator living there and loot the treasure. 

All the water down there will have washed it clean, good as new, ready for reuse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... Interesting.

Either way, just the whole, "We (the IRS) don't give a shit where it came from so long as we get a slice) mentality kind of rubs me the wrong way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you propose be done with flushable wipes or things like that?

I wouldn't want to keep a "spare trash" in my bathroom exclusively for throwing shit-stained wet naps into to take out to the trash more frequently.

Not only does that sound smelly, inconvenient, and unhygienic, it just also seems wasteful to then be going through trash bags more frequently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spent $70 to fly from New York to Boston, booking my ticket on Friday to fly out Saturday, 5 days before Thanksgiving. Still had free WiFi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I'm oversimplifying it, but if they have WiFi on planes why can't they do cell service?

I have Google Fi which has text and calling over wireless. So theoretically I should be able to make a call 30K ft in the air. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone making jokes about Uber and United and I'm just sitting here thinking about how cool Whetstone is for a last name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. Just like one that one recent episode of Last Week Tonight about marijuana when John Oliver notes how the IRS says you're supposed to declare all income, even if it's earned illegally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For as long as I've had a bank account, credit cards and computers have been a thing. Any time I've written a check, a scan of it is included in my monthly statement from the bank.

What happened in ye olden days, before scanners and such were commonplace? Did you ever get evidence your check was cashed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That adds [so much context](https://www.reddit.com/r/Dogberg/comments/5uvhqk/all_posts_must_have_wwe_commentary_style_titles/). I had no idea why this was a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can a dog be evil? Like, genuinely, maliciously, evil? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I'm misinterpreting it, but in the article for the 2015 attach it says:

 The Dridex Trojan infected computers through a malicious Microsoft Office document, typically disguised as an invoice and emailed to victims.

 The malware **relied on tricking people into installing it** on their machines, **rather than exploiting a security hole in the operating system**.

Compared to today's article:

 When recipients open the document, the exploit  if successful  is used to carry out a series of actions that lead to the installation ofDridexbotnetID 7500 on the user's system.

Sounds like it's an overall different attack vector. 2015 sounds like the user is opening legit_file.doc.exe where as today they're opening an actual .doc which contains links to a dangerous, outside source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I've found that dotnet devs tend to be terrible at javascript and most javascript devs are bad too. linting saves lives.

Heh. So I actually work for a medical company. When they were just getting started in the 80's / 90's they outsourced the development for their Windows desktop application to an Indian firm. Eventually paid them to rewrite it as a web application and purchased the source code so they could hire some devs in house to maintain / improve it over the years. It was recently re-written *again* using more recent technologies / frameworks.

So yeaaa... Definitely lots of *quality* code here.

I'll have to look at one of those JS analyzers. I just spent 2 months using a static analyser for the .NET stuff, didn't even occur to me that there might be a similar tool for JS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example?

If you mean something like this:

    if (x == y)
        Foo();
    else if (x != z)
        Bar();

I'm not sure what you take issue with? Or do you mean

    if (x != y)
        Foo();
    else
        Bar();

Even still, I don't think it's any better or worse than using `==` and "leaving" the `else` block to handle inequalities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the same boat with LINQ. I think it's absolutely wonderful but so many people abuse it to a point where it's so difficult to read.

I especially dislike when you see a question on stack overflow by someone who is obviously a novice and the top answer is a complex LINQ statement with minimal explanation.

I think it's better, from a teaching perspective, to give them a 5-10 line solution *then* show how it can be reduced through LINQ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would assume it ultimately comes down to budget.

It's probably not worth the cost to cover much more than the main WRC teams. They can only afford so many cameras, air time on TV, and editors for producing their "Daily Highlight" videos.

Speaking for myself, I usually tune out when they cover the WRC 2 stuff. The teams themselves get little time in front of the camera so I don't care who wins or loses. I'm not sure if I could even name 3 separate drivers from that bracket.

Personally, I would **not** be interested in Daily Highlight videos doubling from 25 minutes to 50 minutes due to the addition of thorough WRC2 coverage **if** this caused the WRC+ subscription price to increase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly?

I forgot that's even an option. So rarely do I use namespace aliases that I never remember it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, gotcha. Sort of an "apprenticeship" then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get what you're saying, but as you said reality is more complex.

Companies don't take advantage of allowing employees to work remotely. Stop clustering companies in one "hot spot" area. Look for employees in other states. Allow them to work remotely if they can't, or won't, relocate. 

Besides, your example doesn't entirely sound bad. Now twice as many people are employed earning twice as much. What a terrible outcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd agree that I can't really think of a reason to use `var` except for when necessary, but I'm definitely guilty of using it instead of writing it things like `IEnumerableSome.Long.Namespace.To.Avoid.Ambihuity.Compiler.Errors myObj`  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I always use braces with a single expression if (required in C#)

What?

    if (someBool)
        Foo();

Will compile. They're not required.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What syntactic sugar do you avoid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently going through and cleaning up my company's flagship project. Most of the C# isn't *too* bad but I've moved on to the JavaScript and there's been some real head scratchers.

One thing I've noticed is missing semicolons in many places, which I've corrected. I looked up why this doesn't blow up, assuming it was up to modern browsers' JS engines to fix this. Turns out JS has a feature called [automatic semicolon insertion](http://stackoverflow.com/a/2846298). Which is something I strongly dislike the entire concept of.

However, it seemed a little "hypocritical" of me as I love things like ternary expressions, not encapsulating single-line statements in braces for an IF or a FOR statement, and using var in place of especially long types.

I know a lot of developers dislike at least those last two examples as they can make things harder to read / less standardized / less explicit.

Just made me wonder what are some features, particularly of .NET, that you don't take advantage of due to personal preference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is "OPT"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
 Secondly... if you pay high enough, then you eventually just poaching employees from another company

That doesn't really make sense. Companies only have a need for so many developers of certain skill levels.

It's not like one company is going to just horde teams of engineers and not do anything with them solely to"starve" the competition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * US employees too expensive?
* foreign employees underpaid? 
* failed US educational system?

I'd say it's a combination of these 3. Probably in order from Most Significant to Least Significant in terms of how we got into this situation.

 Employers view IT as a necessary evil. An unrelenting, all consuming pit of money and they don't want to spend a dime more than they have to. So they don't want to pay the high wages American IT workers demand. ^*. I used to work for an international US Bank. Located in the States, on my office I worked on a team with 4 other individuals. 2 Indians over here on an H1B, a woman who held dual citizenship, and a guy who might have been a US citizen but I'm not sure. Anyways, in my physical office, I was the only one *from* the US. My team consisted of the 5 of us and 10 others in a different state. 10/10 on my other team were all here on H1B's. And I can guarantee you the work we were doing wasn't exceptionally demanding -- not in the "We can't find qualified American workers" sense that is often used as a reason to justify needing H1B's.

Couple that with being able to import cheap laborers who have very few, if any, rights and suddenly you've got a very desirable thing. You hire these people on work visas and either they pull their weight and don't ask for anything, or they suck and you cut their visa and send them packing. What are they going to? Sue for improper termination? Fat chance.

And as you said, our education system. I don't have "IT grad numbers" off the top of my head, but it's only getting more and more expensive to go to school. I, foolishly, went to an over priced private school. It's actually worked out pretty well for me, but I honest-to-god tutored some of the goddamn **dumbest** fucking kids. When I was getting my Bachelor's the IT chair asked me to tutor the Associate level students 10-20 hours per week. I had this one kid who was one semester from graduating who couldn't write a comment. He couldn't do anything. I spoke to the chair about my concern and he was wholly indifferent. I spoke with one of the student's professors and he basically acknowledged the kid was a moron, but if he passed his assignments and quizzes, well, what can you do.

But yea I do believe there's an attitude of, "We don't care about your education so long as you keep writing those tuition checks" in this country. Certainly in a lot of private colleges, but I wouldn't be surprised if many public colleges behave the same way. A friend of mine initially earned a BS in Business Management because he didn't know what he wanted to do in life. We were talking about it the other day and he mentioned how that program was, by a large margin, the largest program at this major state college churning out thousands of these degrees. Talk about market saturation...
 
---

^* Fun Fact: I recently did some research about labor laws. I knew I was ineligible to earn Over Time working as a programmer but I wanted to learn the specifics.

 Section 13(a)(1) and Section 13(a)(17) of the FLSA (Fair Labor Standards Act) provide an exemption from both Minimum Wage and Overtime Pay for programmers, analysts, engineers, and other similarly skilled workers in the computer field who meet certain tests regarding their job duties and who are paid **at least $455 per week on a salary basis or paid on an hourly basis at a rate not less than $27.63 an hour.**

I pulled that from a PDF on the Department of Labor's website that I pulled up on my PC. Trying to pull it up on my phone but it just automatically downloads the document so I can't link it but simply googling "DOL computer overtime" should yield it.

Anyways, in 1990, "Computer Employees" were added to the overtime exemption list of they made at least 6 times more than minimum wage. 

In 1996 the law was changed to 6 times what the minimum wage was in 1996. And the law hasn't been changed since then.

The laws dictating whether or not I am entitled to getting paid for the amount of work I do is so old that it could legally buy a beer ^^^if ^^^you ^^^could ^^^find ^^^somewhere ^^^which ^^^serves ^^^alcohol ^^^to ^^^legislation.       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you know how to count cards you can make money at black jack, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty much it for me. Same thing with Angry Joe.

They both of have good and insightful opinions, but I don't want to watch a low-budget G4 TV show. (It was called 'G4' when Tech TV sold out, right?)

The characters and the presentation are painful to get through for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When has investing ever *not* been seen as gambling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still surprised MA beat other states to the punch, in New England.

I guess I don't know how good/bad of a shape CT is in, but RI is a mess. They could've made a killing if they legalized marijuana first from all the tourism.

Instead MA did it and now just like before there's almost no reason to go to RI for anything ever.

I know Maine legalized it too, but yea... Mass shares a border with every other state in NE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3-4 years ago it was like $30/share. News article came out that they out sold certain Audi, BMW, and Merc models.

I immediately thought, "I wish I could afford some Tesla stock". The next few days it went from $30 to $50 to $100 and beyond.

Just graduated college and had zero dollars to buy anything. Not that I could have even afforded a life-changing number of shares, but even still... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted a gif of this the other day and it got removed as a repost... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping you were going to blow up a stuffed animal :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  YOUR #14 SOURCE FOR AUTOMOTIVE NEWS

10/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 05:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. I was just staring at the temperature. It snowed today, for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DOGBERG THE UNDEFEATABLE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 05:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a programmer and I like cars a lot, yea.

5 More years of these fucking $1K/mo student loan payments, then I can start having some *real* fun :o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird. Nothing.

Called and set up an appointment, showed up, both times the dude was busy so he just gave me the keys.

I'm in my twenties, long hair and missing a tooth too so it's not like I even "look good" in terms of how a sales person might judge potential customers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I certainly miss it, but I had to get rid of it. The Fiesta is a super fun car, and way more convenient.

Snowy northeast, lost my job where I was able to work from home 5 days a week. New job was pretty far away. So between having to face the winter, significantly higher gas consumption, and having moved downtown and needing parallel park in the Z *every single day* was shit.

I miss the sound of the V6 more than anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gearbox isn't in the business of giving things away.

"Pony up, or GTFO" - Randy Pitchford, probbaly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I've read, they literally just replaced the old PC model with Duke. Allegedly, the lips don't even sync right to the voice because it uses the old model's animations, which is obviously proportioned differently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Invent a time machine and go back a couple of years.

I'm not saying it's impossible to find work, but I feel bad for anyone graduating without having an internship or pet project on GitHub or anything in addition to your expensive piece of paper.

I don't mean to sound all "doom and gloom" but IT is a very competitive field. What school you went to, what your GPA was doesn't mean much to most employers. You need to be able to demonstrate you can actually get shit done.

Start talking to your professors or TA's if you can. Meet people. Get involved. Find projects. Do things.

I went on at least 5 interviews while getting my degree because my professors passed my resume off to someone they knew. I didn't get a job that way, but at least I got interview experience. Full disclosure, I went to an overpriced school with very small class sizes (5-20 people) so in class it was very easy to talk with and get to know your professors. I assume you went to a more traditional school with big lecture halls where the professor doesn't know anyone's name.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I thought it was early 2000's.

But in any case that only furthers my point :P

So they've basically been building cars for a decade. And 1 of the 3 models they've built was solely to drum up interest in the brand / tech, not a "mass market product". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Piercings.

Eyebrows, nose rings, lip / tongue piercings are all major turn offs for me.

I don't mind discrete (discreet?) nose studs and earrings don't bother me, but everything else I just find tremendously distracting. Like it's really hard for me to *not* start the piece of metal protruding from your face.

Ironically, I'm really into tattoos and weird hair colors and things like that. And a lot of women who are into that stuff are often into piercings, too :/


RE: Eyes -- the girl in the photo you linked doesn't bother me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What made you decide to test one if you didn't like the brand? And what sort of things did you learn about that you couldn't have found through the myriad of YouTube videos and internet forums?

Given that you were already disinterested in the brand, I'd assume you're not going to research them too thoroughly on your own... But that's your decision.

There is little stopping most car buyers from doing their homework before buying a new, or 'gently used' cars.


I guess I'm just jaded because I'm in my 20's and owe more in student loans than I make in a year *before tax*. I just googled "car sales commission" and the first article I found suggests:

  "Typical commissions range from 20-30% of the profit. So if a car sells for $1,000 over Invoice the sales person would get $250 on a 25% commission"

So for someone like me, that's a lot of money. Especially factoring in, again, the fact that 3/3 of the salesmen I've purchased from played zero role in my decision to buy the car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that due to a lack of dealerships, or due to the fact that they're a company that only **really** started producing cars in the past decade?

The Roadster is like 15 years old now but the Model S has sold approximately 160K cars since its inception in 2012, according to Wikipedia.

By contrast, Toyota sold approximately **360K** Corollas in the US in 2015 (also from Wikipedia)

In one year, they've sold over twice as many vehicles as Tesla has in half of a decade.

They have a lot of money, but they are still a young company working to ramp up production numbers.

Not to mention they use... Well it's more common now, but I think you could still call it unconventional technology. So that's going to make it even harder to deal with.


In any case, maybe they do provide a valuable service in those regards but I was referring strictly to the sale/purchase of vehicles.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even today they still have that sort of, "This thing will kill you" reputation because of their early generations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I more so meant buying cars from one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say yes.

$150-200K cars are certainly ludicrously expensive for most people, but I think they are in a different category then 250-500K cars. And absolutely in a different league than anything more expensive than $500K

I'm sure there are some people who buy sub-200K cars who make, at most, $500K. To these kinds of people a 20K difference is a lot.

Not everyone who buys one will be some filthy rich car baron. 

No idea how much money my boss and his wife make but they have a Z4, X5, and he got rid of his 911 for an i8. The Porsche was just too expensive, he said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree with his point that these obscene markups are bad for everyone, but what is "incredible" about this article?

I don't think a single person on this sub would tell you they like dealerships. Not unless they work for one, anyways.

Kind of just preaching to the choir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no no, we can't have that. Dealerships provide a valuable service to customers, don't you know? Go ask anyone who works there and they'll even tell you themselves!


For real though. Fuck dealers. Maybe once upon a time they actually had a reason to exist but nowadays they don't do a thing. Every car I've ever purchased from a dealership, I went in already knowing I was going to buy the vehicle so long as there was nothing wrong. Really earned your commission there, fuckface. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ford wouldn't even let me drive a focus st. 

The fuck? When I was selling my 350Z I had no issues driving ST's. Went to two or three different dealers trying to find the right one.

I test drove a Focus ST at one dealership and the dude was like, "Here's the key, come back in 30. I'm finishing up with a customer right now."

Ended up coming back to that same dealer 6 months later for a Fiesta ST; same exact thing. "Here's the keys, see you in a bit".
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It kind of is, yes. Reddit is predominantly against Trump and people often knee-jerk downvote anything "Pro Trump".

Besides, it also helps to show that despite disliking and disagreeing with him, you are at least somewhat open minded and are willing to consider his individual actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would actually be kind of cool, especially as a kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  mining sounds pretty sweet to me

On paper sure, but dat Black Lung... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that coal mining was a huge industry in this country, particularly in certain regions... But what does one do at a *coal mining museum*?

That just sounds like the worst, most boring school field trip destination -- and most of my field trips growing up were to textile mills. Not exactly exciting, either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think from pure technology standpoint, it's pretty neat.

But what an awful *use* of the technology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  no proof to illustrate your point

Every major auto manufacturer in the world, at least in the EU/NA markets. Those stupid "engine covers" just make it harder to work on vehicles yourself. Like yea it's just 1 little thing, but it's a very common-place practice nowadays and it does literally nothing. It's just *yet another thing* they threw on there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna know what happens when you turn the hazards turn on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Depends on how frequent you need to replace it.

Probably often due to people rear-ending you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Fuuuuck*. VR Doom. I need that now. And also $800. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  decided i couldnt keep waiting forever

Good call.

Nissan hasn't said a peep about a 370Z successor. There's a COMPLETELY UNSUBSTANTIATED [rumor of a successor at this year's Tokyo Motor Show](http://blog.caranddriver.com/nissan-z-concept-coming-production-car-could-reach-500-horsepower/), but again:

* Nissan hasn't said a word
* That is a blog post article which doesn't cite a source
* The rendering is from someone unaffiliated with Nissan
* Any other article reporting this just cites this shitty C D blog as their source

So yea... You'd be waiting like at least until 2020 honestly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sort of, but I think the bigger problem is that it *starts* at a few thousand dollars over the Camaro, Mustang, Challenger, and Genesis Coupe.

Each car is a little better than its competitors in all of their own ways, but ultimately the Z doesn't bring much to command a higher price. Especially considering that the Base trim doesn't even include an LSD so really you should be looking at Sport trims or better -- only further raising the price.

So between being more expensive than American 2-doors, and the fact the today's generation just doesn't have the *income* for a $30K+ performance vehicle that is overall fairly average... who are they trying to sell it to? Like don't get me wrong, I'm a giant Z fanboy and I'd buy one if I had the cash, but I fully understand why many don't / won't.

Another thing is that the 370Z tries too much to be a GT car; comfy leather seats, nice (seemingly) interior with decent materials and such. It's fairly heavy (though again, lighter than the American options)... But then what's the point of the G35/G37? Those are simply a more comfy, more luxurious Z. Sooo why don't we strip out a few hundred pounds worth of luxury shit in the Z, make it a nice proper lightweight sports car and then have the comfy G series for those who want that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Front](http://i45.photobucket.com/albums/f53/texchris71/100_1793.jpg)

[Side](http://www.trackhq.com/forums/attachments/f303/4681d1339346331t-readers-poll-styling-350z-v-370z-11-rearviewcomparo.jpg)

[Rear](http://dustrunnersauto.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/350Zvs370ZFeatured.jpg)


If you're not into Z's / Nissan, I can absolutely understand how they might look damn near identical. Especially when you're actually driving and see one.


Major differences are Nissan's atrocious "hook" headlights design on the 370Z, though strangely I prefer the 370Z's taillights. Hood and bumper are a bit more aggressive, but again if you're super into Z's / driving, it's quite hard to discern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that's a fair comparison.

The interiors are certainly *styled* in an almost identical manner, but  the quality did go up between the 350Z and its later generations, as well as the changes brought on by the 370Z. The 350Z's cubby hole door was some shitty hard plastic thing. Looks like it's a nice soft leather in the 370Z?

I can't say whether the interior is up to par for a vehicle that *starts* at $30K, but I mean you can get a used one for a reasonable price and it's really not that bad.


That said, I think the 370Z's steering wheel is ugly and the gauge cluster on the dashboard is ugly. I get it, it's an iconic thing with the series but I remember thinking it was quite worthless and missing key features in my '03 Z. From what I hear of the 370Z, they're really not making much better use of it. But hey at least one of them can display the fucking clock now.

I wish the climate controls + radio would switch places with the cubby hole above it, but then where would they stuff the intotainment crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of context, I actually really like it. The exterior, at least. Not huge on that interior, and that's coming from someone with the matching [orange](http://fordstnation.com/member-chad-albums-2013-fiesta-st-3d-picture1022-2013-fiestast-interior-04.jpg) recaros for my Fiesta.

Like [the side profile](https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/tpldk0lxykahgx06ena3.jpg) looks pretty cool with the black wheels and decals.

Within the context that this is nearly a decade old car that wasn't even a huge "generational jump" over its predecessor in the first place... Nissan pls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  THANKS FOR PARTICIPATING, YOU WILL RECEIVE AN EMAIL IN THE **NEXT HOURS** IF YOU HAVE BEEN GIVEN A KEY

Hm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF there's no way Netflix is 20 years old

 Founded 	August 29, 1997; 19 years ago in Scotts Valley, California, U.S.

^^^- ^^^Wikipedia

What the fuck how is Netflix 20 years old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I accidentally left the rear passenger side window down one night. Live in EV.

Came out the next morning with everything still in my car (not that there was anything of real value) and the door was still locked.

Does that count? Good luck, hambone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     bookCompletionValue = new Random().Next(100);

It'll be be finished, but seem like it being worked on with every page load! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here I am spending my 60 Amazon dollarydoos on a new fucking vacuum cleaner :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this even a thing.

Why do I like the fact that it exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a discussion thread on here earlier this week or maybe last week talking about the same thing.

"Open World Fatigue", you could call it.

When you have the freedom to go anywhere and do anything in any order, and have a mini map chalk full of Points of Interest, it can ruin the narrative / feeling. Nothing is important. Everything can wait.

I recently purchased Grandia 2 on the PC, which I've never played before and I've been really surprised at how much I'm enjoying it. You don't sit through countless tutorial popups. You don't get bombarded with countless things to do. You just do your job, explore cool maps and fight shit. It's well paced and just generally a breath of fresh air from "modern game design philosophy". Don't get me wrong, I do wish certain modern-day features were in G2 but for a game that first came it in 2000 it's held up very well.

That said, I think the issue is ultimately a player-controllable problem. Pick a quest and stick to it. Don't get side tracked talking to every mook in every village. Get an objective, see it through, and come back.

Of course this isn't a perfect solution. Sometimes it just doesn't make good sense to skip something in the same area, or maybe stopping to do this one other thing first will get you a helpful item. These are certainly valid complaints, and I'm not entirely sure how to address them from the perspective of "open world gaming".

I think in general a lot of people are starting to get tied of every game being an open world with a million side quests and points of interest. It can be a mile wide but only a foot deep. While this can describe many games, obviously some do it better than others but in either case I think the only "real" solution is simply for a shift in the way games are made.

After playing Grandia 2 these past few weeks I'm definitely looking for more turn based RPGs that are less "modern" in that you just buy the game and you get a game. No dealing with N different game library managers. The main menu doesn't need to fetch DLC advertisements. Multiplayer isn't shoehorned in because everything needs multiplayer. The tutorial is minimal and optional.

That last part is honestly one of the biggest things that annoys me about modern games. So many games assume you're a brain-dead vegetable who has never played a video game before. Like I get it, some tutorial is a good thing and some games do tutorials very well. But when it's telling me to use W or the D-Pad or the Joystick to move forward and look around I groan every time. And then you open up the menu and holy shit you get 100 tooltips explaining every single UI element and entire mechanics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reason #659 of why I live [where the the air hurts my face](http://depressedalien.com/143). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you're thinking of Nor'easter Entertainment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this effect your seat positioning at all? Like did you push your seat back in order to "feel normal" again?

I don't have especially long legs and have sit a little closer to the wheel than my arm's would necessarily like, but if I move back then it is uncomfortable to fully depress the clutch so I just end up sitting too close. So if I need to push the seat back then I think the clutch would be too bad for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [4 Minute video explains it fairly well from a technical stand point](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xeoLRWCNGcA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  just wanted to distance from the toxic individual ASAP. 

 Admittedly not a slickest PR move on my part. Note taken.


Admin sounds fine to me you guys. He's only trash talking a customer on their forum.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US: Takes one to know one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't know if he tried that or not.

Here's what this dude's job search would be like:

* Doesn't list his most recent employer as a reference
* Will either shy away from questions about why he left, flat out lie, or be completely honest. None of these are good.
* Employers might contact WF. They're not supposed to do much more than confirm he worked there, but hey they're also not supposed to retaliate against whistleblowers or open fake accounts so who the fuck knows what they'll actually tell your prospective employer.

The deck is kind of stacked against you even if you try to get a bookkeeping job at some small local company or a teller or anything related to money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  However, an Oklahoma City pharmacist was convicted of first-degree murder in the 2009 fatal shooting of a 16-year-old robber inside the pharmacy. Prosecutors said the teenager was left unconscious by one shot from the pharmacist, who then chased another robber outside the store before returning inside, picking up a second gun and shooting the still unconscious teen several more times.

What the fuck does this have to do with the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I just got fired and have been unable to find a new job for 1-2 years (it's not unreasonable to continue searching in your current field, IMO) my first thought isn't going to be, "Well let's add on tens of thousands of dollars in debt so I can go to college and hopefully get  an Entry Level software gig here in LA. Surely a company will hire me instead of a dirt cheap H1-B"


In any case, OK say I immediately opt for a career change upon getting fired.

How will I pay for tuition without a job? Where will I live without a job to pay rent? How will I get to and from class?

You act like "pivoting your skills" is an overnight change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did they meet / kidnap this poor victim?

The article is laid out poorly on mobile. It started to describe the woman's room, then interjects a block about how the married couple met. At first I thought it was saying the guy abused his wife rather than a different person so I had to scroll back up and confirm they're married and were abusing a third person.

In any case, I don't even know what to say. Bunch of despicable pieces of human garbage.

I'm all for rehabilitation of criminals and things like that, but such depravity and at such an old age? I think some people are beyond rehabilitation... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ish.

Dude got fired in 2010.

I suppose the article one says "he wasn't able to find another banking job" so he probably wasn't unemployed but rather "underemployed" for 6-7 years.

In either case, that's a very long time to either go without pay, or work jobs at severely diminished pay while probably paying legal fees to fight WF in court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know the full details of the guy who got this $5.4M settlement, but if I got fired right now I'd be heavily fucked. The article said he wasn't able to find a job in the banking industry, so I'm going to assume that means he's been unemployed since then rather than working odd jobs.

Student loans, rent, and a car payment would drain what little savings I have in a month or two, tops.

My only option would be to move back to the state I grew up in, live with my parents, go on Income Based Repayment for my student loans and try to get a job which is hard because they live in the middle of fucking nowhere. And then try to undo any damage to my credit and social life.

At least they have an "extra" vehicle so I wouldn't need to save up for that first, somehow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You will hardly have 5 million to dick about on

Because of taxes, I assume you mean?

Even if I were him and had, let's just say, *only* had $2M I wouldn't care if I got fired from WF a second time.

That's plenty of money to:

* Move the fuck out of LA to somewhere affordable
* Buy a modest house and car, if I don't own my current vehicle
* Invest and collect interest
* Work literally any job. With no overhead from a car or mortgage, literally any full time job would cover monthly expenses such as food and utilities.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any idea how long he's have to be President ...

Don't worry, with a track record like:

* Russian friends
* Stating he could shoot someone in broad daylight and not lose any voters
* Expanded military funding
* The sewage dump he replaced the proverbial swamp with
* Bet my life savings he won't reduce any FBI, CIA or NSA spying capabilities

It's probably not long until Trump scraps the  'Two Terms' clause and is winning "elections" with 90% of the vote every 4 years,   just like his BFF Putin .


I am being sarcastic, of course, but...
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Count me in with the, "Wait the R8 is **that** old?" crowd.

But it looks great dude. I love how excited your voice is haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't hate the Prius.

I just hate most people who drive a Prius, because they're often terrible drivers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got'chya.

Yea at first I thought it was a cooling thing, but that didn't make sense to me because you need them to warm up a little bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Sell a $3 million dollar car to good customers for $1.5 million, 

Full disclosure: I'm not into Ferraris so I know very little about them.

The LaFerrari is not really a "$3M car", is it? Like no doubt it's a spectacular piece of machinery, but it can't be on Bugatti / Koenigsegg / Pagani level.

I see they *auctioned* one for $7M but that doesn't count. If not for the badge it wouldn't have gone for that much.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did give Deadmau5, who is a car collecting rich celeb, a shitty time with his [Purrari](http://www.youredm.com/2014/08/27/ferrari-sent-deadmau5-cease-desist-letter-purrari/)

I'm at work so I can't check your link to verify if they mention it, but basically the only reason Ferrari cared was because he was going to sell / auction it.

(I still disagree with their decision, but it's not like it was going to remain his vehicle; there was cash exchanging hands at the end of the day)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can refuse to sell you a new or used one themselves though.  

Is this for countries where manufacturers can sell directly to consumer, since that's not a thing in the US (aside from where Tesla has fought and won the right to do so?).

Like if I walk into Ferraris'R'Us with a big ass stack of cash and said, "I want to order a new La Ferrari", how can Ferrari dictate "Don't sell that pleb a car"?

I guess they could say, "If you sell that pleb a car we don't sell you XYZ" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a fun track, though I don't think I'm familiar with it.

How fast were you able to get the Fiesta up to?

I've done one real track day in a 350Z, prior to any autocross experience. It was a lot of fun, but rather intimidating barreling down a straight at 130 and then slamming the brakes just before entering a very hard corner.

The one and only autocross event was in the Fiesta. Much more fun, for me. Maybe if I had a lot more autocross time I'd have enjoyed the track more.

I'd be a little wary of the Fiesta overheating, or melting its brakes as you found.

Super fun and nimble little car but I would imagine it doesn't like a day full of hard braking at high speeds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly are "cryo rotors"?

I tried to Google it but all I can find is marketing material, such as "Our cryogenic process helps improve the longevity of rotors" and uninformative statements like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does any Focus ST hardware fit the Fiesta? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a long shot, but I thought I'd ask.

A guy on my SCCA region's Facebook is selling some Focus ST goodies:

 Eibach Rear adjustable bar with new bushings/brackets

Doubt it fits, but...

 Steeda rear endlinks, includes both sets of bushings

Again, I assume the different rear suspension between the F*ST's this probably won't work

 Koni Yellows (the fronds are red because they were the prototype shocks) no leaks. Fronts also revalved for stiffer rebound (I forget the rate)

I'm less interested in lowering my car because I already plow snow a good bit in the winter, but cheap mods are cheap mods... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Circus performers killed his parents </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One recently opened up in my town but it's insanely expensive; $100 for a 'lane'.

It says it a lane can fit up to 6 people, but I don't know that many people willing to go throw axes; so really it'd be like $30-50 per person which is a lot for only 1 hour.

Edit: Rather, I don't mind spending *up to* that much for a fun night out, but chances have it you're going to be terrible. And at $30 an hour, I'm not going to be able to do it with any frequency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's millipup, not milliput </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the kind of clowny shit that makes me love this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on where he is. I live on the east coast and get emails from recruiters on the west coast. I usually don't even reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll admit that was a terribly unsafe pass from the Camaro, but the truck driver should've just got the fuck out of his way ASAP instead of purposefully cruising along side the trucker.

He did everything he could to escalate the situation, not diffuse it -- and he didn't have the "excuse" of being drunk for his poor decision making. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're just vindictive little turds who like ruining the other asshole's day.

I'll admit I'd be pissed if someone tried to pass me like that Camaro did, but the trucker was *asking* for an accident to happen the way he continually antagonized the other driver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had to guess, truck downshifted so the Camaro wouldn't see brake lights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was not expecting a feature-length film when I clicked on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Just wondering what would get someone to a dealership to test drive 

I'd gladly go down just to try it out if I could, no hassle.

 and potentially buy a Polaris Slingshot.

Oh. Er. Well. I'm not even remotely in a position to have that as a toy in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can be had for as low as like $7K for a 150K+ mile '03 or 10-13K with anywhere from 50-90K on 'em.

They're a great "I just graduated and can't afford a $15-20K+ car" car. 

Like you can get a nice Touring trim for that cheap; heated leather seats, possible navigation if you want it (I preferred one without). So it's pretty comfy for the price, too.

There's plenty of cars that are faster for the same (or less), or lighter ones, or better in some other metric -- but they're still solid fun. I miss mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whichever. The separate units for the two in combination look weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 cents? Well it can almost only go up from there!

Time to invest my life savings /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one time I've sols a car ('03 Corolla) off CL was pretty shitty. I posted numerous photos, milage, price, transmission -- everything. Most responses asked for at least one piece of information that was in the post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that's the attitude I have. I don't care if people think it's weird to go to dinner or the movies solo; it doesn't bother me. Just that, as I said, no energy lately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh I grew up riding BMX bikes, so anything that you're supposed to ride actually seated is very uncomfortable to be.

Also both of my roommates have bikes, there's really not room in my apartment for a third :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, yea the trend pisses me off too.

It doesn't necessarily look bad, but it's shit for visibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get them in AWD, but you lose the manual transmission if you do.

Honestly I considered one when I was looking to replace my 350Z.

But it's over priced and not as fun.

IMO the issue with the Juke is that the AWD trim offers nothing over a WRX. It's more expensive, fewer doors, and looks worse.

FWD only, not as fun as the Fiesta and also still more expensive.

The ground clearance would be nice (I live in the snowy North East) but honestly I live in the city and most of my driving is highway so it doesn't really make the much of a difference if it's got 3" of clearance or 10". Either it's a blizzard and I'm not going anywhere, or its been plowed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't love this thing, but at least it doesn't have derpy-as-fuck headlights like the Juke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean by "raked"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A margin of error of, what, 6%? Oh no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. I crossed it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh.

I decided to get out of the house and go see a movie last weekend (by myself -- not that that bothers me) just for the sake of getting out of the house for once.

My brother died a few months ago and while I've been coping OK I've just had zero goddamn energy. Work 5 days per week, force myself to be social two nights per week and that is all I have energy for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best part: we don't even need a ring! Just get us a cheeseburger or some video games.  

I can just picture a girl getting down on one knee, reaching into her purse and pulling out a burger in a wrapper and unwrapping it like you'd open a ring box.

10/10, would marry immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd wager that parking lots are typically private property and you can't be ticketed.

IANAL though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God forbid you walk 10 extra steps, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~I~~RL needs a graphics update  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

You're thinking about it all wrong. It's not about what you can "glue to a baby", it's what can you glue a baby **to**.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You're already making the data that you're so worried to protect available to your web browser manufacturer and the websites you use. Your browsing history is already being sold, just not by your provider.

This is such a bogus, irrelevant point - which the article already responds to.

Don't like a website selling your data? Use Adblock, use Noscript, go to a different website. You have options.

You don't have an option for ISP's.

And even if you did, at the end of the day, now this is just one more entity harvesting and collecting data that might appeal to black hats.

Furthermore, I'm already paying my ISP. I don't pay Google. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I thought what made the end of fossil fuels "inevitable" is the fact that it's nonrenewable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fencing you usually want to *avoid* getting touched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weed remains detectable for a very long time. Just because they find it, doesn't mean you were high on marijuana.

It's actually a major issue for states that have legalized it; they don't have a reliable way to test for it like the breathalyzer and alcohol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the term you're looking for is *pumpkinologist* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Thousands likely were highly inconvenienced from this mess.

I mean, probably, yes. But think if an emergency vehicle needed to actually get through.

Things like this could potentially be very serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Modern safety standards require cars to:

 The newest (2009) rule says that vehicles weighing 6,000 pounds or less must be able to withstand a force equal to three times their weight applied alternately to the left and right sides of the roof. The roof cannot bend so far that it would touch the head of a median-height-male test dummy.

Which is quite impressive.

That said,

 Experts agree that to withstand the forces of a real rollover, roofs should support about four times the vehicle weight, not three times their weight as the new rule specifies.

 Safety belts are not required to hold occupants in place during a rollover. As cars roll, occupants are pulled out of their seats and toward the roof. Most safety belts in use today won't stop that.

So while modern safety standards have come a long way... damn, that surprises me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/kGdNW9m.png

Beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....^^^^TIL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, well, that sounds like a relief and it will in fact have Steam support. I will definitely have to keep this on my radar now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why you pay [$3M](http://www.caranddriver.com/bugatti/chiron).

Side note: goddamn I would've guessed this thing was like half that. Damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er, honestly I thought this was an Xbox exclusive.

I've only got a PC so I never paid it very close attention because I simply knew it wasn't on PC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously it's implied that they're looking for people who don't stand to make money off it.

No unbiased, third party person is cool with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Implying I've physically gone to a bank in the last 5 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iw.net was awful. There were hackers everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got disposable income? Steam refunds exist. You're fine. 

Steam isn't listed as a vendor on the Preorder page.


I actually guessed this was going to be an MS Store exclusive; I didn't realize Activision was the publisher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100%.

I can fully live with missing out on the beta.

I'll wait to see what the reviews say of the game then pick it up. I heard mostly good things about the original, but on the PC there's plenty of other games like Destiny out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's not listed, they're going to go tell you to pound sand.

Ford / Dealership isn't just going to be like, "Well it's a different year but what the heck, we'll dissemble the whole thing and take a look."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean when we had literally any other president?

Yea I remember those days. Good times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get what you're saying, but it doesn't really matter. One way or the other you're a cog in the machine.

Live in the US and pay taxes? That tax money is going to fund or military which contracts these Defense companies.

If you work in the factory that is making the actual guns and bombs, or a school teacher -- it's all part of the American umbrella. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of like how us selling arms to Saudi Arabia has improved their Human Rights behavior *so much*?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Namely by all the Recruiters out there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Implying designers aren't going insane trying to make every browser display the same / center something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at work but I'll try to remember tonight when I get home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was known for a long time?

Doctors have told patients for years not to use electronics shortly before bed, try to get rid of unnatural light etc. to help those who have issues falling asleep at night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
