<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1493</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like some ret-con bullshit. Cheating on someone to prove their loyalty is insanity. Its like driving a car of a cliff to prove its reliability. 

Now maybe you weren't everything she wanted but she chose to handle it in an immature and shitty way. You can improve and get better (if you did have problems for her, i dont know either way though ) but you shouldn't be expected to stand by dishonesty and shitty behaviour.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 10:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the footage you're looking for? 


https://youtu.be/YQVCvj3efMo 

(south tower collapses at 23:53)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bible says quite the opposite actually. 

Matthew 19:24 "Again I tell you, it is easier for a camel to go through the eye of a needle than for someone who is rich to enter the kingdom of God." 

This is the new testament too, so it's what the majority of Christians claim to follow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And thats the most heinous crime of all brother  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only criteria for Christianity im aware of is a belief though. Thats the belief in the divinity of Christ. 

What acts define a Christian? Who decided what those acts are? Are they simply good deeds? If so isn't any good person a Christian?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The nebulous "reddits hypocritical" argument shows up in every thread. Some people don't understand that millions of different people use the site daily. It's like trying to say "well America voted for a Democrat but now they voted in a Republican, why are they so hypocritical?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 22:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Benefit of being a crown corporation I guess. They don't have to completely focus on income generation  if they don't want to and still stay in business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 22:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a Benjamin Button reference my friend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 18:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't have any of that pesky "critical thinking" either, no use for that in life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 18:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you nailed it. He's like Brad Pitt in old man make up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 18:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IANAL but she wouldn't win a lawsuit for a police report filed in good faith. If you know this woman did it then it's not slander/libel/perjury, you would have to know the info is false when filing the report for that. If you're worried about her simply filing one then ya she could always do that unfortunately. You can sue for anything. 

Really hope you find some closure with this man.  Some of these people are just absolute cretins, you deserve empathy and compassion not erasure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 17:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a beautifully sad story. Its so hard when they go but it sounds like Finny knew to the last minute how much you cared about him. Youre a wonderful person for providing that for him. 

Cherish those last few precious moments together as well, because they must have meant a lot to him. I lost one of mine to a car a year ago and no one was there for him in his last moments. I just hope he didn't suffer long :( 

Now I have to go pet all my other cats...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 17:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually experienced this situation unfortunately. Two of my cats were brothers, same situation as yours, never been apart before and they were very close to each other. A little over a year ago one of them was hit by a car and was dead by the time we found him. 

The surviving brother was pretty distraught for a bit. I'm fairly certain he knew his brother was dead because he never really went looking for him. He was just kind of lost and depressed for a couple weeks. He would wander the house meowing, calling out for someone, not sure what to do. My family and i supported him a lot during that time and made sure he knew he was well loved and that we were there for him. Today he's still the same playful/affectionate cat he was before. Every now and then though, I feel like I need to pick him up and let him know it's all OK and that he's not alone. 

I hope your cats have long healthy lives my friend. It really does suck when they go. 

RIP Summer, we're taking good care of your brother little buddy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit man sometimes I pause and take a breath mid-toke and that half second pause can make the whole thing noticeably harsher.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great show, great episode, I second the recommendation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moderation is to them what sanity is to the vigilant Christian. Elusive and terrifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The legislation hasn't been introduced into the house yet. The work hasn't even started so, ya no progress  unfortunately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 22:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/traps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if they do this elsewhere but the cops here in Ontario have a payed program for teens around 13-16  years old where they have them go into gas stations/convenience stores and attempt to buy cigarettes. So at least here there's the added risk of it just being a straight up sting operation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 16:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rusty Shackleford strikes again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 15:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben Carson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 04:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The allies estimated somewhere around 100 million dead between both sides in a full scale invasion IIRC  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A ship set sail beyond the pale resigned to meet its fate 

Ripples sent as the ship was spent resound along its wake

Reminding now of peril found replete within our seas 

And holds our hearts and souls still and cold till the waves reach our feet   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ravioli, ravioli](https://youtu.be/3Q12xOukVAI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 06:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It probably hurts a little too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 06:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The machines are attempting dad jokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 02:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like half my characters from Oblivion... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 19:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The person you're responding too isn't the original guy who commented  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely thought i felt some sexual tension between them. Could just be my dick talking tho...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 21:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trent Reznor did say he did it better though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 08:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They kind of suck at engaging their guests tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 08:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion it's not really that informative to a veteran smoker but it's also too incoherent and unstructured for a noobie to get much from it either. So it kind of just ends up being filler to me. 

Maybe a proper structure and actual effort put into the segment would help. They just seem to poorly improvise it every time as is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 08:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PRO TIP 2: Drinking alcohol decreases the distance needed to make it better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 07:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What is better, to be born good or to overcome your evil nature through great effort?" 

- Paarthurnax  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I think if you're going to have the death sentence it should have the strictest criteria possible to prevent innocent deaths. To me that would mean both a unanimous jury decision and judge approval and if both can't be met they get life. I don't like the idea of a judge unilaterally being able to sentence you to death, its too much power for one person in my opinion. I'm not even a US citizen though so my opinion might not count for much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Stephie.exe has crashed or failed to launch properly.  Please insert trans-installation media to repair this program." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U member  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Web-comic artist is a viable career!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish drug dealers knew this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need for Teeth 2: Dental Pursuit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 20:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understanding is at that point they just treat the symptoms individually because a primary cause can't be established. Pain meds for pain, seizure meds for seizures, etc. So the treatment can work in that it can relieve symptoms and make it easier to deal with but it doesn't work in that it will cure or stop the problem entirely because the underlying issue is unknown. 

Not a doctor, but have some personal experience with chronic illness for what that's worth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 08:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sniff glue sometimes too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 21:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: Birds (and reptiles/a bunch of other animals) have a dual purpose hole called a cloaca. It functions as both genitalia and as an anus for them.  


So my questions is: Does that count as two holes or one under UK regulation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 19:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only time ive personally heard him laugh 

https://youtu.be/zBWuKaTZq0k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 06:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/sIlNIVXpIns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would suggest seeing a psychologist or psychiatrist if these things interfere with your life. These checklists are generally meant to be used by a professional and are not a substitute for an actual diagnoses. Best of luck, and if your post was more of a joke then please ignore me lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 13:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fuck no" is an integral part of the Canadian vernacular  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guardians Of The Galaxy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 19:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least that video got straight to the point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 13:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A strawman fallacy is when you misrepresent someone's argument or position then argue against that misrepresentation as if it were the original position. You essentially create a "strawman" to attack instead of what was initially posited.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 00:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> door vendors 

Do you mean door-to-door salesmen?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 13:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liqa Madiq stole her away from him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 20:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My step brother is ~325lbs and if he doesn't shower for one day he absolutely reeks like BO and spoiled cheese. It's at least half the reason I won't use the bathroom near his room. It's disgusting and he doesn't seem to realize how much people notice his smell and how much they are repulsed by it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For what it's worth we all have your back here and are rooting for your success. Just keep pushing forward to where you want to be, it's a long road but it's more than worth it. Best of luck buddy, and remember that we're all your cheerleaders here :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orange Is The New Black. It's an original series on Netflix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 22:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's something like 4% of people executed in the US are innocent. That's 4% too high for me to be comfortable with tbh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 03:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That goes from a misdemeanor to a felony regardless of the weight where I am </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 21:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the advice! I'll definitely keep an eye out for those signs. 

I'm very lucky to have the mother I do. There's no doubt in my mind that she would help me in any way she could if I had a problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 20:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really sorry to hear that its got a grasp on your mom, I can't imagine what kind of pain that must cause you :( I was lucky enough to be born after the recovery so I've never seen the decline personally. 

You've given me a lot to think about here and I appreciate that. I'm already questioning my relationship with alcohol and I'm not sure what to make of it. So far I've struck what I think is a decent balance but how long will that last? I don't have any of the symptoms you listed, but it does feel like playing with fire a bit. I've got a lot of thinking to do about this it seems. 

Thank you very much for the advice and for sharing your experience! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 18:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to hear that you're beating it! Both my parents are former alcoholics and they've been sober for 25+ years each now. 

I'm just curious as to what the early warning signs of alcoholism are? If there are any. Since it runs in my family I'm a little worried that I might be predisposed to it (if that's possible). So far I only drink on the weekends and I don't have trouble managing it but I know that's how a lot of people start out. So are there any signs or symptoms I should be watching out for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 03:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much angst and edge in that game, it was beautifully cringey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 19:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If men go to prison when they're actually the victim, "they can handle it better" than if even one woman is falsely accused.

So men are tougher than women and therefore not complete equals? Women are too weak to handle prison but men are strong and capable and will handle it better? 

Interesting how the sexism goes full circle whenever it benefits them. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you interpreted it right, it didn't actually come out on the play store and app store until just a few days ago now. A whole bunch of people (myself included) were using a cracked APK of the app for a week or two before it came out. So there were people playing it in Canada prior to release, they just weren't playing the official app.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true and John Redcorn is pretty sad that he can't raise his own kid and that Joseph loves Dale like a father. Such a good show  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 03:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They either wake up or double down after 30 from what I can see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 16:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Dale, he got cucked so hard he's raising the other man's kid  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 16:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tabernac, les Canadiens francophone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 20:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their terminal velocity is non-fatal as well IIRC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worked fine in Canada over the last week. They just released the full app here yesterday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 22:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red: I'm angry! Everyone look how righteously angry I am! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 22:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TW: Anita Sarkeesian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 22:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget to install adobe reader  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 22:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point. You cant extract blood from a stone as they say. 

I'd be fine with them just holding it over his head as opposed to a lawsuit. 
Also I'd imagine the video they would make exposing him would make them more money than they would spend getting the information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 20:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who gets more chicks; airplane pilots or helicopter pilots? Interested because of... scientific research... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 18:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Danny Carey is God </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 18:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just check your neighbour's trash next time he puts it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 17:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this idea. Knowing Brett, his underlings are disposable to him and it probably won't be long until he banishes one of them that knows something about it. 

Only problem I can think of at the moment is that anyone with any in-depth knowledge of the situation would be incriminating themselves to a certain degree by coming foreward. The peasants could offer immunity from a civil suit as well as cash to balance that. Not sure what would happen if the courts decide to pursue criminal charges though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In space, nobody can hear you *whoosh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 21:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an interesting point. I can see what you mean for known slanderers and demagogues. The intent does matter and we shouldn't have to give them a platform or respect their opinions if they are using them maliciously. 

The thing i take issue with is banning any graduate from one of those schools regardless of whether you know their maliciously using their speech. Isn't that more like punishing* potential friends of murderers than punishing* murderers themselves? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 21:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  *If* the politics pushed at these institutions objectively prevent them from effectively doing their jobs

My only sticking point is that "if", i guess. Has anyone proved that, let's say a business graduate, from one of these places is objectively worse at their job? 

I do agree that a "be aware this is what goes on at this university" type message to HR would be fine though. I was more against instantly throwing the resumes out if they even had anything to do with feminism or SJW'S, like the OP had suggested. Not even meeting the person face to face just throwing out their resume because they might have some opinions that are aggravating. In that scenario they don't even try to see if the person shits where they eat. 

I'll fully admit that it may not be practical to vet every candidate this way. It would be far more cost effective to tell them to kick rocks. My opposition is largely a philosophical one stemming from the source of this thread. Which is us getting angry at an institution for banning someone for their ideas. While we call for bans on people from certain schools and who hold certain ideas. It really should be okay to do it or not, for everybody, in my opinion. Not just okay when we do it.  

One more thing, hypothetically would a liberal leaning company be in the right for banning conservatives or anyone who comes from a conservative leaning school? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 20:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we don't punish those who may have went to the same school as kidnappers and we don't punish those who have the same opinions as them either. We punish people who have actually committed acts or crimes. 

I said in another comment that I'm probably being too philosophical and not pragmatic enough. I just don't think we can really claim to be better than them if we act like them. And if we aren't better than them than where does our authority to judge their acts of exclusion (i.e banning milo) come from? If ours are just as bad, we don't really have ground to say theirs is worse and should be punished.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 06:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not really sure where i stand on this because i see your point, and i think as a business operator/owner you should have the right to pick employees that fit your company. I'm not saying that you have to hire crazy SJW's or increase your workforce diversity. Just that a blanket ban or increased scrutiny on anyone who attends certain schools or holds certain opinions seems so similar to what we are against on this sub. It feels anti-meritocratic, that people aren't being judged on their ability to do the job but on their opinions. 

Perhaps I'm being too philosophical and not pragmatic enough but the concept irks me the same way banning Milo for his opinion does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 05:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't that be restricting speech in the name of protecting it? Just doesn't seem consistent to punish people with  other views because they punish people with other views. Kind of like executing murderers, feels right but are we better than what we're punishing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 00:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think a form of protest you disagree with deserves potentially crippling injury? Wouldn't arrest suffice, or do you advocate corporal punishment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 19:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some Gen IV reactors have the capability to reuse their own waste as fuel. 

Under "Advantages and Disadvantages"

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Generation_IV_reactor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 02:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you've ever wondered what Tom Hardy's dick looks like, this is your movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 19:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about vegetables in a human state? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 21:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the glove don't fit; you must acquit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 21:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we charge Uwe Boll for murdering cinema? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 21:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Head up to Canada for Circle 9  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 19:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not the person you were replying to but I hope you have a wonderful Canada Day! Regardless of your writing skills :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 19:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Off the top of my head, Hitler took back the Rhineland, begun persecuting the Jews in industry and government , built up a large army and war effort, and annexed Austria and Czechoslovakia all before invading Poland. Britain and other allies then declared war, but only after allowing him to position himself for a large scale conflict.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
