<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5890</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does - thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Guess I'll have to play around with it a bit more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! How do you like that mascara?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I tried that one and it didn't quite work for my lashes unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize for the stupid, ELI5 type question. The search function wasn't working (again!) or I would have posted this in the Simple Questions post. 

Based on the picture, does the inside edge or the outside edge touch my lashes when using a brush like this? I *think* it's the inside one but I'd like verification, please!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Curved mascara wand - which side to use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're similar. This one has a shortbread-like crust instead of the graham cracker crust with magic bars, and there's no coconut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Planned Parenthood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea. They seem to always have plenty at the bulk store where I buy my nuts. :-P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Chocolate pecan pie bar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a sprinkles and quins addict! I can't stop buying them all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't mix. I mentioned in my post that all the primers and the CC cream are silicone based. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'll look into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, that's a bummer! I had wondered if their own primer would have worked better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are really sweet but sooo good!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Powder - CC cream - powder is how I usually apply my makeup. But throwing in primer is a disaster. I haven't tried doing it on top of the CC cream though. It's worth a shot!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so but I was wanting something to help with pores and texture which this CC cream doesn't do that much for me (or as much as I would like, I guess). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darn, that sucks! I do love this CC cream though so I'll keep using it and hope that the serum(s) I'm patch-testing will help my skin's appearance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silicone primers causes CC cream to separate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use IT Cosmetics CC cream and the primers I've tried are Monistat anti-chafing gel and The Ordinary's High-Adherence primer. All of these items are silicone based. Does anyone know why the primers would be causing the CC cream to separate on my chin after about 3 hours? They also cause it to cake/crust in areas I usually don't have any issues. My makeup looks SO much better without primer.

I haven't tried a water based primer because I wanted the silicone to help fill in pores and acne-related texture issues.

ETA: Both primers also make me super shiny. Blotting papers can't keep up!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
