<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5813</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 14:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UPDATE: Luna woke me up at 5AM with Cinder meowing by the doorwall. He's home and safe! Definitely sleepy though.

http://i.imgur.com/z5n4rbb.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is Luna. She's waiting for my other cat, her best friend, Cinder to come home. He's been missing for 48 hours... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 06:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 20:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A combo shampoo and conditioner is not good for your hair. Buy separate products.

Wrinkled clothes can be unwrinkled using a mist spray bottle of water.

Pickles are given with meals to eat after your dish to freshen your breath. Eat them last.

Don't wash pants after every wear. Once every 3 months is probably acceptable. Your pants will last longer and look newer (this might be anti hygiene but I'm throwing it out there).

Lemon or lime will get rid of smoke breath.

Use a lufa. They exfoliate.

Wash your whites separate with bleach. Unfortunately, this isn't common knowledge.

When shaving pubes, use a dull razor that your used on your face. This will help avoid cuts and razor bumps.

I'll think of more as they come to me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 02:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Christopher Columbus was a good dude. Seriously, fuck that guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 04:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To add to nileo2005's question, is the mold no ejecting from the same cavity consistently or is it random cavities? This can narrow down mold versus material issues.

EDIT: you just answered this question above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 04:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the ejector pins functioning properly? Is the operating temperature correct for the clear material you're running so it doesn't stick to the mold?  Have you checked the differences in material properties between what seems to be running correctly and the problem material?

Main factors to look at in an injection mold issue: cycle time, temperature, and material. It sounds like you run different materials through the same mold and they function fine, so I'd look at the operating temperature of the material personally. It could be sticking to the mold if it's running hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 16:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't give betting advice without knowing the format of the bet... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 17:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to believe, but I'm having trouble with the fact that the font is Times New Roman and the timestamp says "August 30 at 9:15pm" when it should say something more along the lines of "15 hrs".

Is there a way to change fonts on Facebook? Is it a certain browser? It could be that this post is just really old, pre-font change.

I smell /r/quityourbullshit material unless I'm missing something...To be fair, you didn't say when this actually happened even though the date stamp would suggest you meant it was yesterday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Son of a beach... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 20:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 19:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like a face swap with Justin Bieber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 17:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Gotye - Somebody that I Used to Know (Boyce Avenue Cover)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hBYymaN338E) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 15:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only gripe was giving away the ball that caused the first goal, but played well otherwise.

EDIT: Went back and watched the goal. Definitely Lallana. Whoops, bumbled this comment like Moreno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 16:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. How does your weight feel on your feet? You're standing pretty tall. Alternatively, you could choke a little further down on the grip and get more of a stance over the ball. This should help with balance and assist in correcting your takeaway by keeping your arms in at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 16:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When lining up with the ball, the position between your feet is different depending on whether it's a wood or an iron/wedge.

The ball should line up with the inside of your front foot if you're hitting a wood to allow the clubface to contact the ball with an upward motion (also when you tee up the ball with a wood, the standard height is having the middle of the ball halfway over the head of the club when it's resting on the ground). 

When hitting an iron/wedge, the ball should be positioned in the center of your stance.

This is pretty basic, but if your stance isn't correct it's going to make getting proper contact extremely difficult. Hopefully this helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellow Detroiter checking in; I'll bring the pitchforks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you really consider it a personal preference in regard to shaft flex? I have always considered swing speed to be the main driver in picking a flex.

[An example](http://www.truetemper.com/how-to-determine-your-shaft-flex-based-on-swing-speed-and-tempo/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Proximity of a quality course. Living in Downtown Detroit, I need to go 25 miles before I can get to a real top notch establishment. I'm usually battling tall rough, long greens, and terrible golfers on top of my own swing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 20:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I began using a technique that has really helped me in keeping my face closed on the follow-through and getting the distance correct. To start, the human brain can register the distance and location to a hole for around 5-7 seconds after you look away. Be extra cognizant of the location and take a few practice putting strokes. Take a long look at the hole before you look down and address the ball. Next, when you hit it, make sure to keep your head looking directly where the ball was before you did so for an extra two seconds. This ensures you don't peek and open the face before your club impacts the ball. This is vital to ensuring a proper line and I have found this to be a massive help.

To go along with practice, make sure you have the right style of putter. I personally feel that there are two types of putting styles, the "tempo" (mallet) putter and the "feel" (blade) putter. 

I started with a mallet putter and for the life of me I couldn't drop anything outside of 5 feet. My putting stroke felt inconsistent and I just couldn't seem to get distances correct no matter how much I practiced.

Enter the blade putter. I ended up at the local golf shop putting for an hour or so during my lunch breaks trying to figure out if there was something that a different putter could give me. Picked up the blade putter and the feel through the putting stroke was fantastic. I  was getting close or dropping everything. Turns out that my putting style was completely mismatched with my putter and I have been great at it since. Just something to chew on... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this rare Pokemon at the local bar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 21:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 20:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11/10 with rice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beat away, my friend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 23:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 20:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, this made my day! Great to hear and keep it up! Don't forget to inquire about limit raises every 3 months or so if you're paying your bills on time. Their low limit cards offer that flexibility. It will raise your score as well.

Congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 19:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I build things. Creating something from start to finish is incredibly gratifying and the sense of accomplishment even in just the progress is enough to feel better than shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you have two and you can only give your attention to one at a time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 20:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks for the tip, Arthur. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 21:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 17:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girlfriend used to have a cat named Kitler. I'd like to think your cat is named the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "WTF Sex Facts" for nice guys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 05:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 20:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having the same issue. Woke up to 80% charge the other day after having no issues for weeks. I have an Obliq slim case on it that I've had since I bought the charger. Hopefully someone has a solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 20:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clawed tooth and nail to get my undergrad. I'm now in a cushy sales/management position for an automotive supplier. I can't complain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's two types of people in the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 15:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 23:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11 IIRC. Worth every penny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 20:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rotate toothbrush contraption 90 degrees. Problem solved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 13:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they re-shot "The Goonies" in Europe, you have Sloth locked down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 19:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a spray bottle of water that I take with me when I travel and also use at home. Put clothes on, mist with water, rub out wrinkles and they're gone when they dry. Haven't folded laundry in years because of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 18:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mean to nitpick, but lion claw marks should have four lines instead of three. I would think that Monster might have something to say about that first design.

I dig the second set; nice job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 14:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Matchbox 20 - Hang](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hxv-weH5NXo)

Hits me in the feels every damn time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 20:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to say the Galaxy S7 but that surprisingly showed up today, so now I'm waiting for the charging dock and case I got for it.

Plz no drops beforehand... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 17:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see my apartment. Nice shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 16:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Sweaty palms intensifying* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At work before I vote in the Michigan primary. I'd like to think it's obvious who I'm not voting for. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 15:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 20:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't care if I get downvoted, but I read this as "micro penis". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop Calling Donald Trump Supporters Stupid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 19:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to r/politicswithunclejoe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 21:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone, and welcome to r/politicswithunclejoe. This subreddit is meant to be an amusing set of conversations with real people discussing the upcoming 2016 United States Presidential election. 

My goal here is to show my experiences as a liberal-leaning moderate interacting with my Uncle Joe, a pure-bred conservative. I am looking to post a few of these daily once I get the mass history submitted. I'm hoping to be caught up quickly.

Here is some background information:

Me  Mitch

29 year-old college grad with considerable student loans, a well-paying account manager position living with my girlfriend and her daughter from a previous marriage, working in Detroit, Michigan.

Joseph  Uncle Joe

High school educated managing a sales account for a sustainable energy supplier. Grew up in Memphis, Michigan (a very country setting), is married with five children, and has a very conservative viewpoint.

Joe cannot stop expressing his hatred for Obama, Hillary, Bernie, and anything liberal on Facebook every single day, multiple times a day. We all have people like Joe (in the US, anyway). I decided that I would say something to him about one of his posts after scrolling through them for about 6 months. 

Needless to say, I have over 100 of them to share since December. We both enjoy getting the last word which leads to some long and sometimes heated conversations, and Id like to think that they make for good entertainment. I hope you enjoy!


DISCLAIMER: Looking back on some of the things I said, I could have phrased a few items differently. There are probably some mitigating factors in there (coughbeerscough) so I apologize if some of the things I say can come off as harsh. I will do my best to explain them in the albums as they are posted.

Thank you for taking a look, any feedback is always welcomed.

Regards,

-Joe's nephew Mitch
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 21:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Links from the post:

http://www.truth-out.org/archive/item/83147:reagan-the-great-american-socialist

https://cofda.wordpress.com/2013/11/09/u-s-imam-muslims-can-take-the-property-of-christians-and-jews/

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Christian_terrorism

http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2015/12/11/texas-imam-forced-out-after-he-issues-warning-on-radical-islam-expresses-support-for-trumps-muslim-ban/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uncle Joe gets the ball rolling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 21:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 18:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same exact problem I have, and it's not going anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 16:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summary: Expandable storage will not be integrated with internal storage (a standard Marshmallow feature) because:

Samsung says their decision came down to customer confusion, they dont want people pulling out the microSD card while its being used for adoptable storage and potentially making a mess of things.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 16:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With only 32 GB of internal storage, reaching that peak will not be difficult as apps get larger and larger.

What really grinds my gears:

Get an app update? It moves itself back to my internal storage. Too many updates? None will initialize until I clear my cache/move apps back to the SD card. Wash, rinse, repeat every week.

How can Samsung not trust their users enough to not screw up simple expandable storage at this cost of a terrible system flaw that can be avoided if they thought we had a couple of brain cells? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most infuriating feature of my S5 will also be present on the S7. Why can't Samsung get this right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 16:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 16:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the most infuriating thing about my S5. 

Get an app update? It moves itself back to my internal storage. Too many updates? None will initialize until I clear my cache/move apps back to the SD card.

How can Samsung not trust their users enough to not screw up simple expandable storage at this cost of a terrible system flaw that can be avoided if they thought we had a couple of brain cells? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 00:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at the collections point; they are considered delinquent debts which is much worse, hence why it's important to pay those off immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 23:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paying off collections and paying credit cards on time were very large factors. Dropping hard inquiries helped as well. Keeping your limit below 30% consistently is an understated key. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 22:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On top of this, don't worry about paying off your student loan debt right away. Those types of loans build a good credit history as long as the payments are on time, which is better for your score than paying them off completely immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 22:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple of things:

-Pay off the collections immediately. These are the biggest factor in your score at the moment.

-After paying these off, your score should rise enough to get some low-end credit cards (do not get retail cards; real credit cards). By paying off your collections first, your score will reflect that you are of less risk than before paying them off. This will get your better rates and better limits. Don't get cards with an annual fee and shoot for ones that have a graduated credit limit increase with timely payments.

-Ensure that you acquire a couple of cards and use them for a trivial purchase monthly in order to ensure that the cards are reflected on your report. Pay these off in full every month (shouldn't be difficult if you really stick to the "trivial" aspect of it).

-Get a credit score tracker of some type (preferably a FICO score tracker, though the Credit Karma VantageScore is a decent model). Most come with a simulator of some sort which can give you guidance into how to best raise your score.

Personally, I have found that Capital One has some great cards and tools for recovering credit scores, including graduated rates, a tracker, and a simulator. My score has jumped over 100 points in a year coming from a similar situation and I am looking to buy a house myself.

Hopefully this helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 17:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uninstalled the day I read the article about Facebook purposely breaking their Android app to test customer loyalty. Haven't missed it in the slightest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 00:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The neckline is actually the easy part. The transition line from sides to top is difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 23:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the key part: that cash. I have been cutting mine for 11 years now. Only need a 25 dollar set of clippers, barber scissors, and a hand held mirror. I've saved myself hundreds of dollars for my booze budget since then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 23:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I cut it myself actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 23:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/IyiTaCQ.jpg Just got off work. Cheers to Friday, kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 16:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My tuition was $16,000 per semester. $10,000 a year would have been wonderful... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 14:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $70,000, paying $750 a month. Luckily my degree does a good job of paying for itself (spoiler: I'm a mechanical engineer in Detroit). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 22:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welsh Xavi has evolved into Welsh Pirlo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Higher than I thought" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 15:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sixteen fedora's detected. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 14:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 17:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you play [crack baby basketball] (http://vignette3.wikia.nocookie.net/southpark/images/4/4d/CBAA04.png/revision/latest?cb=20110526062404)  by any chance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 17:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my case, it involved critically thinking about every step. It wasn't "Oh, I got the right answer for this step so I'll go on to the next part". It was "Why did I get the right answer for this step, how does it relate to the next step, what are the signs from the previous step that I should be using the method I just used?" and so on. Focusing on the actual comprehension rather than the answer was key.

I had massive personal issues in college as well. It's important to not have that at the front of your mind or you have very little chance of absorbing additional information. I taught myself to leave my issues at the door when it was test time. I think that's where the music helped with studying; it was enough to keep my mind from wandering without being distracting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 15:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Engineering grad here; I had the same issue. Never studied, never did homework, walked in and aced every test in high school. College was a shock to my system that almost had me dropped due to poor grades. I had to actually develop a strategy to study.

Turns out that I studied best locked in my room with ambient music playing. I refused to leave until I learned the material. I generally did this by following proper techniques line for line until I learned the methods rather than reciting exact problems. I would get a half hour TV break every couple hours to keep my sanity.

Developing a study routine is the only way you're going to get there. You need to figure out what works best for you in order to succeed. If you were like me, this will be incredibly difficult but it gets easier once you "get in a groove" so to speak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lottery is essentially crowd funding for a random person to become a multi-millionaire. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 15:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 19:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cook bacon and leave the grease in the pan. Cook the grilled cheese in the bacon grease; it adds a fantastic flavor to the sandwich, plus you have bacon.

Bring on the heart attacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 20:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops. Gronk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 17:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bortles

A. Robinson

Baldwin

Hightower

Woodhead

Aiken

Boswell

Texans

5 points from breaking the all time league high in points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 07:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went Beckham/Gronk first two rounds, pick 8 in an 8 team snake draft. Won the championship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 18:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 62 moves. Had to use Bortles, Baldwin, Hightower, Woodhead, Aiken, Boswell, and the Houston D for the championship win. 

They replaced Brees, Odell, McCoy, Running back X (changed every week), flex, Santos, and the Cardinals D (which admittedly worked out with either team).

Started 2-4 and rang off 12 straight for the championship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 16:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops. Thanks for the heads up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 03:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Takata knowingly spotted millions of faulty airbags for years even though their facility in Auburn Hills proved that they were faulty via testing. They're getting theirs currently, though.

Source: Worked there in 2004 during the testing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Download "Google Messenger". The text message drop down is app dependent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Called it just before the punt... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 06:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 19:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this case, bad. The wheels and axel provide extra friction and actually slow your car down. Because your car is on a line, the trajectory is set. The less the wheels are on the ground, the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 03:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carve your car into a bullet shape. Most aerodynamic and lightweight way to go. Source: raced CO2 dragsters in vocational engineering in high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When one of your crew trips up and tries to play it cool. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 19:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 16:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Nope, just Detroit: from my balcony.](https://i.imgur.com/xNyaWhk.jpg)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 15:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've obviously never been to midtown, New Center, Boston Edison, Eastern Market, Rosedale Park, University District, Rivertown, Belle Isle, Indian Village, East Village, Woodbridge, Corktown, or many of the other great parts of the city that aren't downtown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 20:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use a spray bottle full of water on "mist" to remove wrinkles from cotton clothes. Spray, wipe the wrinkled spot, and the wrinkles are gone.

I haven't folded a shirt or pair of pants in 5 years with this; I just pull it straight from a clean clothes hamper to wear and put it in the dirty hamper when done. No more folding laundry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 18:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't think of a better way to get it. Those kids don't care about the reason behind it, they all have nice new backpacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 19:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, too, am disappointed that I can't vacuum my wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 16:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful cut; he's going to be fantastic.

The only thing that makes me nervous is he runs with the ball off his body, making him more prone to fumbles (his big issue in college). Hopefully they work with him on that; we saw enough of it with Reggie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 14:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fantastic. I would like to get this printed. One request, though: Can you pull the dashboard in front of Brady so it looks like he's sitting in the seat? It appears that he's sitting on the windshield.

Great job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
