<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2116</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some shameless self promotion, I write queer horror exclusively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am excited! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 22:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I KNOW!!!! I love them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 09:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking as a gay trans man, people who look like me are not treated well in any genre, but especially horror. When queer characters magically show up, they are often the gay best friend doomed to die. I can't think of a single trans character in a mainstream horror film, and if there is, they were probably dead before the half way point. We, to put it bluntly, are not treated well.

Probably some of the greatest comments about my stories are all the private messages I receive thanking me for writing explicitly queer characters and that I inspired them to write their own (I've been promised so many murderous lesbians!) The worst are comments asking me why I write exclusively queer characters, which I would not receive if I was writing straight one - like, fuck me because I write characters who look like me, it's making the straight audience uncomfortable!

It's very, very annoying, but I keep hoping that some young LGBTA+ youth is going to see my shit and be inspired to write their own stories, because that's the only way the horror culture is going to change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 04:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably Leo, the main character of my current series, or his BF Auguste.

Shit's about to get so crazy for those two lovebirds soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Woodland Butcher [Part 2] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 00:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [part i](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/59lwto/the_woodland_butcher/) | [part ii](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/59xast/the_woodland_butcher_part_2/) | [part iii](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5azyem/the_woodland_butcher_part_3/) | [part iv](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5bpy1m/the_woodland_butcher_final/)

---

The funeral for Jackson Karl, the first known victim of the still unrealized Woodland Butcher, was held a week before school started. Our whole class was there.

It was overcast and humid, a sea of black and bowed bodies gathered around a hole underneath a pearl gray sky. The women were lamenting, the men mournfully stoic. Auguste had a mouth like a cat, always pointed upwards and unsuited for frowning, and our fingers brushed as we stood in the back.

People looked at us like they expected us to cry the hardest as they shared nonsense stories about Jackson, just because we knew what his insides looked like. The people telling the most stories about Jackson, I noted, were the ones who liked him least in life.

"When I die, I'm going to make so many new friends," Auguste murmured into my ear as they filled the hole with dirt. I had to turn my snort into a cough.

Eventually, the mourning crowd dissipated back into the September day, and Jackson was left to rot under the earth. Life turned on. School was starting soon.

---

Auguste and I had Creative Writing together after lunch, and it was agony not to hold his hand as we walked through the crowded halls.

The teacher had put the desks in a circle, and on his own there was a bust of a beautiful man crowned with grapevines. Auguste and I sat next to each other, knees pressed tight as we talked in low voices. Auguste's hair kept falling into his eyes, and I wanted to brush it away in a raw sort of way. Auguste had almond shaped eyes, bright and dazzling as he deliberately ignored everyone trying to catch them. He held the attention of the whole room without a word and didn't care at all.

There is no one quite like Auguste.

He leaned over to me to whisper in my ear, cupping his hand to cover his rosy mouth, "Maggie Castelo is holding a party on Saturday. It'll be boring if you don't come."

"Yeah?" I replied, but the other things I was going to say died when the teacher walked into the room.

Mr. Fall was young and scruffy in an attractive way, glasses slipping down his nose and leather elbow patches on his blazer. The girl next to me let out a dreamy sigh, and I filed the information away because it was the sort of thing Auguste liked to mock.

He sat a stack of papers down on his desk before smiling at us. Auguste moved to sit forward, but he still had his ankle hooked with mine. The touch was comforting.

"Hello, everyone!" Mr. Fall said cheerfully. "I'm so excited to join your school. Now I majored in both English and Classical Studies, so we'll pull a lot of stories from Greek myth"

I wasn't paying attention. Auguste's fingers were tracing nonsense patterns across the fake wood of the desk. He might've been telling me some secret.

"now let us go around the room and say our name and our favorite Greek god."

He was aiming for a quirking sort of cool. It was working. I spoke before Auguste.

"I'm Leo," I said, like everyone didn't know me by my birthmark. "And I guess Dionysus? He's got some cool stories."

"He's mine, too," Mr. Fall said, pointing at the bust. "We'll read the *Bacchae* later this year."

Then Mr. Fall's gaze snapped to Auguste. Everyone's did. He smiled like he knew something hidden.

"My name is Auguste," he said, sweeter than sugar. He tapped his bottom lip as he considered, and the movement was hypnotic. "And I'd have to say Apollo. I like poetry, and he's associated with poetry, right?"

He looked at me, and I blushed at the memory of reading him all my terrible love poems. Auguste smiled wider. Mr. Fall's face was unreadable until the next person spoke, and he smiled again.

We walked together out of class, the last out, and Auguste ran his thumb over the knob of my wrist before the door swung shut.

"Mr. Fall is jealous of you," Auguste sing-songed as we walked.

"Is he?" I asked. I was an easy person to be jealous of.

"Mhm," Auguste murmured. His charcoal lashes spread across his high cheekbones. "Everyone is going to be jealous of you. They should be."

I just smiled at him, bumping his shoulder before we had to part. The crowds parted for Auguste, and no one looked at him dead on for the same reason people don't look directly at solar eclipses.

We came together again at the end of the day so I could drive Auguste home in my battered Subaru.

"I can't believe you own such a dad car," Auguste said as he clamored into the passenger seat. "It's like you should be driving me to soccer practice."

I groaned. "Please don't make the joke"

"What joke, *Daddy?*" Auguste asked innocently, before bursting out laughing at my expression.

"Little asshole," I grumbled at him, throwing my backpack in the trunk.

"I'm going to assume the new kid is blind."

I turned to look at the big truck parked across from me, where the lacrosse captain Eric Lawrence and all his friends were standing. My brow furrowed  for all his frat bro tendencies, Eric was never a huge dick to anyone.

"Why else would he hang around you?" he finished, proud. Auguste leaned out the door, cat smile upon his face, and his eyes crawled up and down Eric's frame. He puffed out his chest, grinning.

"I have great eyesight," Auguste declared, and then went back inside the car, door slamming shut behind him. I got into the driver's seat as Eric deflated.

"Auguste, just ignore him," I told him. "I've been dealing with dicks my whole life."

Auguste pouted. "But he was mean to you. Friends defend each other."

"Yeah?" I said, smiling despite myself. "We're friends?"

Auguste settled his hand over mine where it sat on the gear shift, and didn't move for the entire drive home.

---

On Saturday, the weather was cooling rapidly as it realized it was finally autumn, and the threat of a drizzle hung in the air. In my bedroom, I opened up my window and popped open the screen, shimmering down to the ground. It was ten and my mother was asleep in front of the TV; Auguste lived two streets down from me. The cold and wet air broke my skin out in goosebumps, and I tightened my leather jacket around myself.

Auguste had said, rather flippantly, that his dads were out on date night and didn't really care about what he did. Doctor and Mister Veisi seemed to realize stopping Auguste from doing what he wanted was a fruitless endeavor.

I knocked on the door of their beautiful home, and a GQ model opened the door  dark skin to match his tousled hair, sharp stubbled jaw, and tall nose. He looked at me, I looked at him, and he arched a perfect brow.

"You must be the boyfriend," Auguste's brother said. "Auguste won't shut the fuck up about you. Leo, right? I'm Julien."

Julien let me into the house, leading me with long strides to the living room. He tossed himself on to an artfully messy white couch. "Auguste is busy preening."

"...Why?" I asked. The thought of Auguste looking anything less than good was...weird. A little unsettling. It's hard to explain.

"Because he's a vain motherfucker?" Julien offered. His phone was buzzing; the bored swipe of his thumb told me he was on Tinder and was very picky. "I come home for the weekend to visit my family and they all fuck off to be romantic."

I snorted despite myself  while they looked completely different, Julien spoke with the same flippant, melodramatic tone Auguste did. I liked him.

"Did you know that Auguste used to not respond when Papa called him by name?" Julien said suddenly. "He learned that he was named after the Emperor Augustus and refused to responded to anything other than *Princeps* for weeks"

"JULIEN!"

Auguste stomped down the stairs wearing a pair of very deliberately ripped jeans, He plastered himself to my side, and I hugged his waist.

"You're going to freeze when you're standing on the street corner," Julien mused. Auguste stuck out his tongue at him.

"I want to go now," Auguste told me plaintively. "I'm sick of Julien."

"Wow," Julien said dryly. "Leave me here to die alone."

Auguste tugged me out of the door, and when we stepped out into the street, I hugged him close. He made a happy noise. The night seemed quiet and empty, the silence echoing through the trees, and I became hyperaware of how the needled branches of the trees rustled in the wind. Every noise was a threat, and I half listened to Auguste's gossip as I moved him deeper into the safety of my arms.

Maggie's house was on the edge of town, her backyard slowly becoming the woods, and I felt relief when I saw the gaggle of cars and the muffled thumps of music. Auguste left my arms to bounce up the steps, and I followed sedately behind.

The party was in full swing when we stepped inside, the hallways lit by the eerie glow of Christmas lights. The colors formed raindrops on Auguste's ivory skin and glittered in his hair, blurring the edges of him until he became unreal. The music was rhythmic and hypnotic, lulling me to someplace else.

Auguste stepped into the kitchen, in front of a line of liquor and wine, pouring us both wine in a little plastic cups.

"Cheers," I murmured, and we tapped our cups together before drinking. The wine stained Auguste's mouth red, and all of him was vivid and hazy all at once, an impression of something beautiful and terrifying

"Auguste! You made it!"

We were swarmed with followers, entranced by Auguste's effortless charm. I stood behind him like a long shadow, immensely fond as Auguste regaled the gathering crowd with impossible stories. When he turned to look at me with playful eyes, my smile was so wide I thought it would split my face.

Eventually, Auguste got sick of the others and dragged me to where the crowd could swallow us. Our fingers were gently entwined as we stood in front of a great bay window that overlooked Maggie's backyard and the woods. The contrast between the artificial Christmas lights and the soft moonlight was strange, casting us in two halves; in this odd twilight, I looked white and Auguste looked red. I almost told him this, but the woods made my words catch in my throat.

The soft breeze made the trees dance, high against the velvety sky, and the darkness between the trunks gave me pause. It seemed to *shift,* becoming a creature of sinew and shadow, and some primordial instinct deep inside me yelled to grab Auguste and go. I almost did.

The body of Eric Lawrence smacked against the window, loud and wet.

There was a rope tied around his ankles, and he had been tossed off the balcony. What was once in his ribcage and belly spilled down to the porch and splattered across the window. I pulled Auguste close to me, tucking him into my jacket and covering his face.

People were screaming. I stood there in surprise. Eric swung, propelled by the breeze.

"The cops are coming here," I said. "We should go."

Auguste agreed.

It was easy to slip out of the panicking house and to hide behind a hedge until the sirens wailed by. We walked back to Auguste's house, taking the stairs two at a time to his room. I don't know where Julien was.

I took off my shoes and jacket before sitting on Auguste's bed, and he clamored into my neck, arms around my neck.

"There's a serial killer," Auguste said, and giggled. "Oh gosh."

"Only you would laugh about that," I said fondly, tracing patterns across his back. "But yes, there probably is."

"We probably know them."

Auguste looked up at me with glinting eyes.

"We have to know them, right?" Auguste said. "They're killing people we know. We know a murderer."

"What does a murderer look like?" I asked.

"They look like everyone else," Auguste said, before bursting into even more giggles.

He fell asleep, soft and sweet, in my arms and his breath tickled my neck, but I couldn't sleep.

I did know what a murderer looked like. They look like my father. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
