<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9761</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://media.giphy.com/media/xT5LMMK4O2wBJe1iy4/giphy.gif

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thrawn Trilogy.
I was hoping this is what TFA would be. I loved this series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serious question: Help with what exactly? How would one know if they need help? How can this help be measured? Are goals set at the beginning of therapy sessions? 

I've considered going to a therapist, but I'm not sure I have "problems" a therapist can "fix". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went back to school for a graduate degree from the same university that I got my undergrad from. I got a call from the alumni association for a donation. I told them 
I currently owe them money, to the tune of about $50k, and told them I would need to pay my debts before donating to charity. The guy on the other end of the phone sighed, went through his speech and hung up before I could say no thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Run for office. Serve the community. Fight for a cause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went back to school while working full time. I only have myself to blame but everyday is a deadline of some sort and I always feel like I'm behind and struggling to catch up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harry Potter.

As I was reading the books all I could think was, how the fuck did he survive that? And, shouldn't he have been expelled? And if he had been expelled, wouldn't he have been killed almost immediately? This is my major issue with Harry Potter and why I never get along with potter-heads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Singular sensation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we calculate taxes paid by "Muslim Immigrants"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to figure out the amount of taxes those that may be banned, or could have been banned, by Cheeto Benito's most recent dumbfuckery.

If it isn't obvious, let's compare taxes paid by muslim americans with those paid by our commander in griefer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My general rules about finding stuff the following:

1. Can you identify a true owner; meaning did you see someone drop it? Is there a name or other personally identifiable information on, or with, the item? If so, return it.
2. Can the owner identify the item; meaning if you were to turn it in, is it likely the true owner would be able to claim it via an unknown mark or initials or if it is a unique item.
3. Does it look like the item was left on purpose; meaning was the item found on the ground in relative disarray? or was it found placed on a post or leaning up against something like someone put it there? Basically, would someone come back looking for where they left it.

If there are no distinguishing marks, have no way of contacting the owner, and it looks like the item was accidentally dropped, misplaced, or discarded, I have no issue with keeping the item. If I think that the item is special or valuable, I may go out of my way to post a sign or ask around, but this is not required.

I use to work at a computer lab in college and people would leave shit behind all the time. At first I'd turn things into security and just be done with it. Then I found out that security was either taking things from their lost and found box, or just giving the items away to anyone. I started my own lost and found after that. This leads to my last rule about turning in items: make sure you get proof of the item being turned in. If someone comes looking for it you can prove where it went. I'd give receipts for items turned in. Imagine if someone left a flash drive somewhere with all of their school assignments for their entire school career and when they came back it was gone. Imagine you had found that item and turned it in thinking you did the right thing only to find out the person you turned it into was dishonest. Wouldn't you feel a little bad/responsible? I did, and that's why I do what I do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the gay station manager. 
And... I think there were a couple of other misunderstandings related to people thinking Fraiser was gay. But who could blame them. He drinks Sherry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liverwurst anyone? High in iron! Tastes great on rye with some deli mustard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES. mmmm I gotta find me a good recipe for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love me some gefilte fish. I've only had it jarred and am hoping some of my more jewish friends can bring me back some homemade from sedar this year.

I buy gefilte fish whenever it goes on sale. Luckily most stores don't really know the difference between the major jewish holidays so it's on sale for about a week in the fall(rosh and yom kippur), about a week in the winter(hanukah), and then obviously in the spring for pesach. It is surprisingly expensive for what is essentially ground fish. Not even salmon, it's white fish and carp I think.

I'd be curious to know if there is any other way to eat it besides plain and with a fuck ton of horse radish(red or white).

When I tell people how much I love it they always ask about the jelly. You don't eat the jelly. I mean some people like it but...that's where I cross the line.

Gefilte fish is essentially jewish SPAM. Or for more fancy folk, fish pt. I also like liverwurst and chopped liver. 
I want to see the merits of a gefilte fish based diet plan. I mean, it's fish right? So it can't be that bad for you? Maybe it's got a lot of salt?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like it's time to get a hobby. 
I am in a dead end job that pays the bills but really there is little hope of further advancement, and I'm fine with that. My new years resolution this year was to try new things and find something I want to be good at. I'm planning a hike through yosemite later this year and am thinking of taking up glass blowing. A few years ago I tried learning guitar but gave up after 5 or 6 lessons. Maybe this year I'll take up saxophone?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 18:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free transportation is provided to poll places. You may not need it, but it's out there and bi-partisan. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is this? I saw a sign for 95, but 95 doesn't run through Pittsburgh. I"d say Philly but wouldn't it be dangerous for this guy to be wearing Steelers gear in Eagles country? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peter Wrongway Peachfuzz checking in.

I think someone sprayed our country with goof gas.

This episode is oddly prophetic: https://youtu.be/XujPnUNcB74?t=1316 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 07:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Audacity of Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 17:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What type of leather is good for a watch band? I don't want something that'll fall apart, but I do want something that's comfortable. 

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for advice on a new brown watch band(style, material, etc.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 03:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     Hello MFA,

I have a casio BEM-507L-7AV and never replaced the stock band. I love the clasp so I'd hope to be able to move that to a new band. Suggestions on style, material, or other thoughts?

Here's a link on Amazon: https://www.amazon.com/Casio-BEM-507L-7AV-Beside-Leather-Chronograph/dp/B0063B3S6I

Here's a picture: 
http://www.casio-intl.com/product/image/1425420314590/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 03:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I tell people I paid for my college myself without any student loans. But I had a scholarship for my first two years and moved back home for my senior year(school was only about 10 miles from where I grew up.) So I paid for it with some major conveniences most don't get. Still...graduated debt free from a large east coast university. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 22:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be curious to know how Ben Shapiro would respond to your situation and letter. I place the blame for the rift in your family, and many families, on far-right sensationalism.  Mr. Shapiro gets to speak from a place of comfort and normality. His children didn't have any issues from conception to birth. Congratulations. That should disqualify him from trying to influence the opinion of others. 
 You know how many abortions happen in the third trimester in America every year? It's 100. That's it. And ALL of them are from severe abnormalities, chromosomal defects, and 100% fatally dead children. All of them.

I'd like to see a source on this. Not because I don't believe it, but because I do think this is a more accurate representation of the world in which we live. I'm not sure of the motive behind such severe legislation when the positive impact would be so small, and the negative impact so large. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 05:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the tutorial. Where does it explain this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, if you take a closer look, it says 19:01, which I believe is a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question: Why are there two clocks? One in the upper right, one in the upper left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting started with a Magic Mirror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 21:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello All.

I finally have all the materials(I hope) for my magic mirror.
I'm planning on doing this with an old tv(LCD). I have the pi, the tv(35"), the flash card, and reflective film.  I'm not sure how I'm going to frame or mount it yet.

Can someone explain a)is there a reason my old tv would not work, and b)do I need plexiglass between the reflective film and the screen? Why not just put the film on the screen?

Also, I've done a ton of research and haven't found a great, step-by-step instruction guide. If anyone can link me some guides and links to the OS I should run(I have 2 that I found but I figure there might be a new one out there?)

Any and all help is welcomed and appreciated. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 03:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm planning on doing this with an old tv in the next few days. I have the pi, the tv(35"), the flash card. I'm going to buy some reflective film. I'm not sure how I'm going to frame or mount it yet.

Can someone explain a)is there a reason my old tv(LCD) would not work, and b)do I need plexiglass between the reflective film and the screen? Why not just put the film on the screen? 

I'll post a new thread when I finish. Thanks any and all help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
