<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6750</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back story? If you don't mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh trust me I know lol. Have you seen the documentary on YouTube about it? Western culture is not dominant outside of the west. Most people that live in the west don't really let go of their cultural traditions.
Source: Myself. I'm first generation and see these things allllllll the time even though most the people I know we're born and raised here like myslef  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know that people from Burma we're  "tribal" as in the way the community is set up.  Parents pressuring for marriage and what not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouuuuuchh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. Didn't know they were into the whole tribal arranged stuff   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love italy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so happy for you. The whole arranged thing sucks.  Something tells me your middle eastern.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a driver. But have been the weird patron. A group of us we're going to downtown and the uber driver looked sad. I (being the sober one) sat upfront and saw she received a text it said "He was an asshole anyways" followed by a bunch of other supportive texts. I asked if she would stop for a booz run and she did. After grabbing a few bottles I got her a little cactus. It made her smile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you are alive. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
