<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know, but now he says he's going to sign it, so maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw that he said he'll sign it. He must be pretty depressed, though. He didn't get much of what he wanted. I do hope the border drone program is successful, so someone can talk him out of that stupid wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After reading this, I'm prepared for a tweet storm tonight. I'm not sure Trump will sign this, even if it passes both houses of Congress. ETA: I now see he's said he'lll sign it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats in the spending agreement? We read it so you dont have to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If you won't play by MY rules, I'm going to take my toys and go home!"

"Mommy, they were being unfair and mean to me! They kept asking me hard questions!"

JFC. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say a worse President. I just said "worse." Worse things, worse times, worse conditions, worse disasters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you imagine the tantrums if Trump was re-elected, but had a democratic congress? It would be worth buying popcorn for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we might show up this time. It's going to get much worse over the next 18 months, especially if they succeed in deregulating Wall Street. GOTV efforts have never been more important.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They won't care. Their motto is "I got mine, screw you." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not as he stands now, but you never know what could happen once he became President. At least he "sort of" supports green energy, but he did endorse and stand by Trump through everything vile he did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forget, 32 states have Republican legislatures and they only need 38 to ratify it. If we don't stop losing states to the Republicans, they could easily repeal it if they wanted to, and make both freedom of the press and freedom of religion obsolete. They could, in fact, make the U.S. a Christian nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were assuming people had morals, but evidently, we no longer do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has no one caught yet that abolishing the First Amendment also covers freedom of religion? If he did away with freedom of the press and freedom of religion -- well, you can imagine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh PULEEEZE tell me we won't have Ryan as President. PULEEEEZE!!!! Oh - wait - next in line is Orrin Hatch then Rex Tillerson. We're screwed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know how you know he's insane? He keeps doing the same things over and over with the same results and not getting why it's not working out for him. Sort of the definition of crazy, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. Knowing and accepting are two very different things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, politics in Washington is much more like Scandal and House of Cards than The West Wing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Tulsi is not in her teens, and she is aligning herself with someone who goes against what she purports to believe. The problem isn't that she is Hindu, it's who she is following and what she has said that contradict each other, I think. I have to read more about her, but this looks a lot like what happened to Jill Stein. She chose a VP candidate who is a racist and has hated white people for years, yet she was asking a whole lot of white people to vote for her. 

You have to be careful not only what you do, but who you associate yourself with. Look at the whole Russia problem. Maybe Trump was involved, maybe he wasn't, but by naming a lot of people who were involved wth Russia to his cabinet and as advisors, he paints himself with the same brush. 

Don't you remember the flack they gave Obama about his minister (forget his name) and how he dropped him like a hot potato? This isn't real life, this is politics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that's it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't find where I read it, that she is actually pro-war and just saying what is expedient to get power, but there is this, which is interesting.

https://www.pastemagazine.com/articles/2016/11/tulsi-gabbard-is-not-who-you-think-she-is.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know what the 25th Amendment was about until Trump took office and they started talking about using it to remove him. Of course, I knew parts of all the biggies, but not all of them. I know a lot more now, but if they gave a test that included all of them, I'd probably fail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see him doing that now, reaching out and explaining to people exactly HOW Trump and congress are screwing them. He's a great communicator, and his biggest strength with these people is that he keeps repeating the same thing over and over. They do not have long attention spans, so repetition is the key. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You truly do not understand these people an intimately as I do, having grown up around them. It's personal. They think of Trump as one of their own. They have disavowed whole branches of their families for less. I lived in a VERY VERY smal town where every other family was named Shealy, and they even had streets and roads named after them. None of them would claim each other. Nobody knew the whole story, but it had to do with a son from one family screwing the father from another out of money, and soon enough, none of the relations were claiming each other. It's crazy how that works in the South.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to help! It helped me sort of decide what the possibilities are. I had a strange idea about what an affiliate site was, but seeing these cleared that right up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will get you started. Smart Passive Income ROCKS!

http://www.cloudliving.com/examples/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried applying for other jobs? There are in need of L3 writers for PDs right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm so sorry you're struggling financially, but I don't wish to be doing the same, so good luck and goodbye." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because there are people on Textbroker who will write for 1.4cpw, that's why. Blogmutt pays $8 for 250 words, and they always have a surplus of writers. Seriously, most writers don't know what they are worth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you know your ESL, you can tell the Asian clients, especially the Chinese. I never do business with Asian clients. They are the most likely to stiff you, and you have no recourse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't that be "mutually beneficial?" Again, never do business with someone who can't speak and write proper English. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We would be reciprocate..." 

My no. 1 rule is to never do business with someone who cant write or speak proper English grammar, or maybe they just didn't proofread very well. Either way...nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IF they university would let him. They do not like protests on campus, especially those that may get violent. They may deny him the O-Dome just on that premise alone. They would call it something like "security reasons," but they probably wouldn't let him use it. 

Hey, he can always rally at the Waldo Flea Market! Lots of his supporters out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People like you, Patrick, make me feel like a slug. Good job, man, good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "the cheap seats," is a euphemism for the higher up seats, sometimes called "the nosebleed seats." Has nothing to do with money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watch Fox all the time. You have to keep track of your enemies. That's one problem with his supporters. They only listen to right-wing news. They have no idea what is going on with the other side, except for the twisted interpretation by Fox news. They are the most uninformed and oblivious people in the entire country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I said "During the school year." The seats would be taken quickly by students before the red guard could move in. If anybody hates Trump, it's most of them. Yes, there are conservative students, but they are mostly liberals. UF is a very liberal college, and Gainesville by-and-large is a dot of blue in a sea of red.

The problem would be he would only advertise the rally to the rural areas where his supporters are. I see him more likely to have a rally  in some place friendlier overall, because even if we couldn't all get seats, we would be outside protesting.

Besides, I don't see the university letting him use the stadium, do you? So where would he rally? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We survived the Civil War, suffrage, two world wars, the cold war, Viet Nam, the Civil Rights movement, Clinton's impeachment, and two Iraq wars. We survived Nixon and Shrub. ETA: We've also survived all the chemicals and toxic medicines they have thrown at us; DDT, Dioxins, Dursban, Diazinon, Arsenic, Lead, etc., etc. We can survive this asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And don't forget that most people who fall into that 50-64 age group have pre-existing conditions, so if he hurts them, the AARP and all senior groups are going to come down on him  and congress like stink on shit. Most people don't realize how powerful the AARP is, but it's not just people over 65. You can join in your 40s (not sure of this age) as long as your parent is a member. It's HUGE and well-supported and has beat back every attempt to do away with just about anything that applies to SS, Medicare, Medicaid subsidies, and anything else that pertains to seniors. They are a big part of why pre-existing got into Obamacare in the first place, otherwise, most of their 50-64 members would have been locked out. 

Once most of the boomers die off, it may not be as powerful, but right now, it's a big dog and a hard one to fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL! Probably, except he promised long-term, well-paying jobs. Remember, he doesn't ever pay his contractors, so they'd better be handing out cash at the gate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they won't accept that they were wrong. You're talking people who have been kicked down their whole lives, and who have fought and scraped for everything. Plus, there are the white supremacists who see him as their hero. Hero worship is hard to break.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know who else holds never-ending rallies? Kim Jong Un. You know who did it before him? Hitler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only been 100 days. Wait until they repeal Obamacare and toss most of them off insurance. The other day Tucker Carlson mentioned disability as being where the long-term unemployed turned who don't qualify for welfare (no kids, etc.). Do you have any idea how many of his able-bodied but unemployed people are on disability? I do. I grew up with them. If he takes that away, or cuts into any of their entitlements, he is going to be turned on faster than a skunk on a hunting dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are actually SHITLOADS of dems. They just don't vote in mid-terms or primaries. If we could get them off their butts and to the polls, we could turn everything around. Then there is the gerrymandering....always the gerrymandering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it scares me when the Progressives talk so lovingly of Tulsi Gabbard. She is a warmonger of the nth degree, and is using Bernie to gain power and recognition. I don't trust her as far as I could throw her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad he always holds these rallies in places that are 90% red, so he can be sure the dems won't fill up the seats. Whoever chooses the venues is smart that way. I doubt he would ever have a rally in LA, for example, or even Gainesville, FL during the school year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's summer, and he hasn't repealed Obamacare yet. Once that is done, you will definitely  see huge protests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is most shocking to him is that Obamacare is so popular among his base. Does he even know who his base is? Why does it surprise him that poor people need health care? Sooooo out of touch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll never get rid of the protection for pre-existing conditions. There will be riots in the streets if they do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so reminiscent of what the dems went through with the Blue Dogs, and what they will likely go through when the Bernie Progressives take over a large block of congress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything he does is contrived. Honestly, he criticized "Hollywood types" being at the correspondent's dinner, but most of them stayed at home. Some went to the parties, but not the dinner itself. 

I think he thought that as a celebrity himself, that Hollywood would flock to him, and when they didn't, he turned on them just like he turns on everyone who doesn't adore him. Defunding the arts was one way of ~~doing that~~ getting revenge on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He even went ballistic over SNL. Who does that? I would consider it an honor if SNL made fun of me. They make fun of all the Presidents. It's just a "thing" with them. How did he not know that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This country has survived worse than The Donald, and it will survive him. The problem isn't surviving him, it's taking back congress, so we can take back what's left of the country and put it to rights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why he holds rallies still. I wonder what will happen when people stop showing up to those rallies? He couldn't even fill the cheap seats on this one. The tide is turning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, when that happened, something broke in this country that has never been able to be repaired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, he's said that! "You can't sue me. I'm the President!" He truly has no clue of what the Presidency is and isn't, but he's learning the hard way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This man has zero ability to learn from past mistakes. ZERO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After we destroyed Baghdad, a lot of Iraqis said that Saddam was bad, but at least they could mostly go about their business in a normal way every day, and their city was not in shambles. I think the invasion of Baghdad gave birth to ISIS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think his fiscal policies would have reigned in Wall Street before it got out of control, but we'll never know. Would 9/11 have happened? Would be have gotten mired in Afghanistan, or would we have let the CIA take care of getting Bin Laden? It's all just a pipe dream now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think about that all the time. This country went completely downhill after the 2,000 elections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is exactly why these idiots who put everything they do on YouTube and shows like "Extreme Preppers" will be the first to die. 

I was raised with guns in a family of farmers and hunters. You don't have to be a right-winger to know how to defend yourself. I have a sign on my outside door that says "Fuck the dog, beware the owner," with a nice pic of a pistol on it. I do a little prepping, as much as I can in my tiny apartment, and I know how to grow my own food. Grew up camping and know how to sterilize water and even make an emergency water distiller if I need to. The one thing I never wanted to learn was how to skin and prepare a kill. I'm thinking that wouldn't be too hard to learn. I do know how to fish, shrimp, crab and clean all the above if I could get close to water. I've studied wild edible food for a few years now, so I could probably survive in the wilderness if I could find water. 

Do I want to have to use any of those skills? Hell no! But I grew up in the South with survivalists and even some hard-core militia members, so I can if I have to, and they know we differ politically, but they would take me in (as long as I keep my mouth shut). Hell, a militia member taught me to shoot a rifle. He was my cousin, but nevertheless, family is more important than politics in the South when TSHTF. You see this during all the major catastrophes such as Katrina. Anybody with a boat was out there in the 9th ward rescuing black people. They didn't care that they were black or poor. They were Americans, and they needed help. 

What most people don't understand about the South is that being a fellow Southerner is more important than being red or blue when hard times hit. My accent alone would get me help in any Southern state. Nobody asks your political affiliation in those circumstances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, most Americans would. I probably would.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that, I truly do. After all, you have to serve and survive a long time to get to be a general. I'd almost like to see a military coup at this point, where they would take over the government long enough to get rid of these jokers (including congress) and start all over. My fear would be that once they took control, they wouldn't want to do the right thing by cleaning house and giving it back. Sometimes, I think that is the only way to fix it, though. Just get rid of the parties and have popular vote elections and let the citizens take back their states and country. Not saying much would change, especially in the red states, but at least it would be what the people vote for, not what they are gerrymandered into having. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know much about corporate law, but I would suppose a private corporation could do that. He's not on the stock exchange, so it must be private. I do think you need to have at least one non-family member, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they are conning us into getting fatter and lazier and stupider. Mass mind control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I truly believe that Fox News and right-wing talk-shows are a huge brainwashing experiment to see just how easy it would be to manipulate the masses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having lived through the 70s and watching the Kent State shootings on the evening news over and over, I cried too. It made me want to fight harder for our freedom, even if they call out the military to shoot me. I'd die for this country, but then, I'm old, so my death wouldn't mean much, but I would.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This, along with his comments on the Constitution, are literally terrifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That may not work. The red states still have the Gulf of Mexico and some of the Great Lakes. Plus, the interior has most of the army and air force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You joke, but actually there is now something called "vanity sizing" where clothes are actually one or two sizes larger than their stated size. If you've ever seen a woman saying she's wearing a size 5 and she weighs 150 lbs., you  know what I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His business if a conglomeration of corporations. Under law, they have to have a board of directors, but I doubt if any of them would ever have the balls to stand up to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see this, I really do, and if the time comes, I'll take up arms to stop it with the best of them. Still, there is nothing wrong with watching and waiting and being prepared if the worst should happen. 

Preppers are looking really smart right now, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can only hope, but remember - Flynn was a general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was important when people were all spread out couldn't defend themselves. That's why they had forts around wilderness towns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, if you feel that way, don't watch it alone. The third episode had my hair standing up on my arms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I admit, I didn't think about that. I'm glad you all have such integrity - or do you all? Military coups happen ~~every day~~ all the time in countries with constitutions. If history has proven anything, it's that the military doesn't always do what the constitution says it should do. ETA: Case in point, waterboarding and Abu Ghraib. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did you violate it in the past? How? You can't just keep violating it and getting it back. You screwed up. This is your punishment. Stop being so smarmy and use programs the way they were intended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but easily fixed, only the gun nuts won't let us. If we just changed it to "well-armed militias sanctioned by the U.S. military for the supplemental protection of local areas," that would put a lot of those nutjobs out of business. ETA: Or made them register their guns like they do their motor vehicles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read it, but book endings don't always become real life endings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wimmen folk! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scariest part of that is that there are way more red states than blue states, so getting an amendment passed to give Trump more power is actually a possibility. The conservatives have taken over so much of the country, that a confusingly enough written amendment that could be misrepresented to the people might actually breeze right through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, we no longer really need state militias, which is what that clause is all about. When that was written, they needed local militias to protect themselves against attacks by any number of entities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what constitutional amendments are for, and why it's such a long and difficult process -- so some ahole like Trump can't just come in and change what he doesn't like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He hasn't SEEN protests until he tries to suspend the Constitution. I'm talking torches and pitchforks, and a few million 2nd amendment people who aren't going to tolerate that shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you been watching The Handmaid's Tale? Updated to fit today's scenario, it's terrifyingly like what is happening here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too true. The party of the constitution has given themselves over to a dictator and don't even seem to fucking care! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not archaic if interpreted the way it was intended, back in the day when states needed militias to protect themselves. It has been reinterpreted way past its original intent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily, we have a constitution and Congress is the only one who can change their own rules. Short of a military coup, that isn't going to change, but the way he is hell bent on building up the military, I wouldn't rule out that he would try that. After all, if he ordered them to remove everyone from Congress, they would have to do it. Nothing anybody could do. 

This man has to be stopped, but I'm afraid that it will be another country that will come in and stop him, since our legislators don't seem to want to do jack shit about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was watching The Handmaid's Tale and it's totally frightening how we are moving toward just such a scenario by letting the religious right and the military have so much power. It's crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't actually been able to verify this, but I've heard that they are trying to cut out the Medicaid subsidies that pay premiums, co-pays and deductibles for poor Medicare recipients. If that is so, many poor seniors will become much poorer (since premiums are taken out of their checks automatically) and they will not be able to afford health care due to the high co-pays and deductibles. This may be something hidden in this bill, so someone needs to read it carefully. If they won't let Dems read it, I don't know what we can do except keep calling our reps and senators. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the while, the county and individual businesses are suing him for all the money he has cost them. Yep, still crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it can do that to a 6 foot man, imagine what it could do to a 5 foot woman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Elon Musk is working with him to establish a Mars penal colony. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That LITERALLY means he isn't running the country. Anytime he only gets ONE choice, someone else is making the decisions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read that he watches 4 hours of morning shows, reads a lot of newspapers, finally gets to the oval aorund lunchtime, then knocks off at 5 p.m. -- oh, and he doesn't work weekends, just plays golf.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also has a much better work ethic -- or any kinds of ethics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he'll quit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every day now, I wake up, scan the headlines and say "Yep, still batshit crazy," and go about my day. This one actually made me double over in laughter. Beyond insane now -- totally out of touch with the real world. I think he honestly thought he could just turn it over to Pence and his staff and go about living life as usual. Next will be "Why are they so mad at me about playing golf? This job is so haaaaaard! I need to relaaaax! WHAAAAAA! WHAAAAA! WHAAAA!"  

Somebody please stuff his pacifier  back in his mouth and get him to STFU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, pretty soon, Sessions will have recused himself from so many things that he won't be able to do his job at all and will have to resign. One can dream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://app.blogmutt.com/help/links-in-posts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think maybe the average person doesn't understand the national debt.

Maybe? Probaby 99% of Americans don't understand the national debt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've heard this before, but his policy is set by the last person he talked to or the last news item he saw. This man is un-effing-believable!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no idea what it was like when quotas were in place. You could be turned down for government housing if they hadn't met their minority quotas. Bussing started because of quotas. Businesses could get sued by the government if they didn't meet minority quotas. At one point in the 80's, historically black colleges were forced to admit more whites or have federal funding cut. They were literally giving away full ride 4-year scholarships to any white person who wanted to attend. I'm not sure what that situation is now, but I was flat out told by the manager of a government apt. complex I lived in during college in the early 80s that she already had her quota of blacks, which is why I got in ahead of others in line. I'm not making this shit up. I'm not a millenial. I lived through this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
