<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8234</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone see the Samsung 50" 4k TV for 999$? That was the best deal I saw today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a stronger person than I am. Eating that way irks me in a way I don't quite fully understand..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 03:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got it. 21 year old audio tech. I've been working local gigs for a while and noticed it a year or two ago. Usually I don't even notice it, like some others have said, but sometimes it becomes extremely "loud" and actually hurts my ear.. I don't really know how to explain it. Had a hearing test done and I'm good on all frequencies. I'm more careful about wearing ear protection these days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 02:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my first time power washing. Is it supposed to look so choppy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Borrowed a power washer for my shutters and ended up taking it to this old deck. (3264 x 2448) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 00:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 03:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think my favorite so far is La Folie by New Belgium.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 07:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because I'm fairly sure the 1 year warranty they include with every purchase covers that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 07:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Witcher. Seriously one of the best games I've ever played. It's like controlling a movie, IMO. The cutscenes are so cinematic. I get so absorbed in the story that I lose all semblance of time. It's like skyrim, but better. Every side quest is unique, ties into the main story, and you can feel the amount of time put into the game. Not to mention they have something like 16 free DLCs coming out and a paid expansion that adds 30-40 hours of gameplay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 01:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to school with the guys who created this whole Free Intelligent Conversation thing. They had a kickstarter that wanted something like 50k to fund it to build signs and make shirts and pay for airfare. I think they got 1000$. It was hilarious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 17:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've dropped my WD 1TB from desk height and it was fine. Wouldn't recommend doing it often though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 17:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Western digital. They make MyPassport drives that are fantastic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 04:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, are you referencing the entire movie not being believable or just the ending?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 03:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this would look a lot better with an LED bulb like the Philips hue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 07:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm, I go to an ultra conservative Christian college and before you start classes you have to sign a waiver stating that you will not have sex, masturbate, watch porn, drink, smoke, do drugs, or cheat, all under penalty of expulsion. Only one year left in this shithole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 23:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you thought about getting some Sweetwater? They're based out of Atlanta.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 13:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's what I'm planning on doing now. I guess my main concern was whether or not my experience would be competitive enough to be able to get in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 23:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently working under the department chair as his RA and TA. I am lead author on a paper, with two other professors as coauthors, that I submitted to a journal for publication. Got another paper I'm about to submit, and I've presented at ~5 conferences so far. I actually taught two or three classes for my advisor when he was out for a week with the flu, and he told me he would be sure to include that in a letter for me. 

I guess I'm just wondering if this experience is enough to make me competitive enough to have a shot of getting in. I've got a 3.85 GPA and I'm taking the GRE in August.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 21:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the campus life like? This is probably more applicable to psychology, but did you get any chance to interact with instructors? 

Also, what was the application process like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 08:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my best friends has a SO that works for MAC, which apparently is a makeup company
You could literally chisel the makeup off of her face  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 07:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because no matter what team you support, there's a certain amount of respect and just plain decency that you need to portray. Letting people like that user troll other subs not only makes our sub look bad, but Hawks fans in general.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 07:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Paul Desmond's stuff. His Take Ten album is incredible IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 09:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You joke, but I've had to use microphone cable on the job befote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 06:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does everyone always blame this on Crow? He saved our asses tonight. It was a bad line change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 01:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean some of it definitely caters to tourists, but the beignets and cafe au lait are still incredible. 

Source: Louisiana native </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 06:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to be a dick about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really love the graphics from Penrose brewing in Chicago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 00:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're into beer I'd recommend Revolution Brewing or Piece Pizzeria   Brewing in Wicker Park/Logan Square </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 07:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you see his latest one? Filmed at MSG in New York. Really great stuff. Just got added to Netflix. I loved it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 20:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you using a Mac? Because Boom is an app on the Mac App Store that EQs the output audio of your computer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 05:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got access to the paper, do you know of a good way to link it?

edit: here's the dropbox [link](https://www.dropbox.com/s/s83y8r14642j8l2/nooney%20et%20al.pdf?dl=0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 05:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should report them the same way the literature does, but indicate that your model was not significant. Insignificant results are just as important as significant ones, because they can contradict previous literature on the topic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 05:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have an actual screenshot?
Usually, those numbers in brackets correspond to the variables on the left. So (1) would be v1, (2) would be v2, ect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 05:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, they're asking if differences in socioeconomic status is a significant catalyst for change in the novel. Think of it this way: in Hinduism, you have a caste system:
1. Brahmans- top class, priests and teachers
2. Kshatriyas- under brahmans, nobles and warriors
3. Vaishya- merchant class 
4. Shudras- bottom class

That is a class difference. So, is the difference between the bottom class and the top class causing a movement for change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 04:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it not reporting a p value at all? Because if it reports a zero that means your F value is significant to p.000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 16:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Follow what you're passionate about. If you're not passionate about microbio, don't do it. You'll be working with a professor researching basically full time for ~5 years. You'll be miserable if you're not excited and motivated about the research you're doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 16:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GTA, IMO. At first it's a bit slow but once you get to the heist missions you'll get hooked. Especially the final heist. So much fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 02:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Castle Wars, but I thought Trouble Brewing was really underrated  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 22:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i just made these for lunch and i loved them. I'm calling them Mediterranean.. 

Wraps- just take any wrap (I used a low carb tortilla) and fill it with cucumber, tomato, and onion slices. I put a tablespoon of hummus and homemade cucumber sauce. Homemade hummus are even better. You can find that recipe [here](http://www.inspiredtaste.net/15938/easy-and-smooth-hummus-recipe/)

Cucumber sauce: take a cucumber and skin it. Depending on how much you want, use either half or the whole cucumber. Put it in a blender/food processor. Take plain greek yogurt and mix it with the processed cucumber. Mix in a pinch of dill and some salt, to taste. 

I did this for lunch and MFP said I was around 400 calories for two wraps. 

If that doesn't appeal to you, try doing a greek salad (I use a lemon juice/olive oil mixture for dressing), hummus, tabouli, or even stuffed grape leaves. All pretty easy and straightforward. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 06:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad it's gonna be Jason Momoa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 05:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fucking fuck. We dick around with them for two periods and then decided to turn it up in the last minute? Entire third period was sloppy. 

Also, fuck the wild.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 06:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 22 and have never been in a relationship or even been kissed.. Should I be worried? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 17:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any shred of evidence proving that he actually gave anything to Russia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 16:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't put it past him to actually have a dick pic in there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 06:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me about it. I had heard about this for a while and was so excited to try it.. I spit it out. It tasted like a mix between cough syrup and something like stomach acid (like when you throw up in the back of your throat). Idk, I wanted to like it so much, but I couldn't do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 01:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/V9HCr.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 14:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel your pain. My brother is a Blues fan..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually shocked that Saad didn't get one on that breakaway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel your pain. I have a total of two friends who follow hockey  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 15:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently doing research on the Psychological Refractory Period, as summarized by Jiang, Saxe, and Kanwisher (2004). Basically, it's a theory that there's a bottleneck to the amount of information you can handle at once- a lot of the research I've read has to do with task switching. Not once have I ever read mention of any negative impacts on brain physiology by frequent task switching. I have zero idea where OP is getting this from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 15:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not neuropsych, but psychology here. 

For starters, the "dopamine release that comes with task switching" is something I have never even heard reference to. It's like he pulled it straight out of his ass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 00:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I was just saying that because I frequent /r/sex and there's a ton of people on there with the same problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 21:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See if you can find anything from Seventh Son. They've got a few ales that are killer. 

Also, I'm sure /r/brewhio would be able to help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 21:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! As a guy, I can't even imagine how frustrating it must've been not to be able to orgasm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 16:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this for undergrad? If so, I would arrange a tour at each of them if possible. You need to be able to see the departments, meet the professors, and see for yourself whether or not you're interested in living there for four years or more. Most universities will assist with travel costs for tours, and pay them in full if you enroll.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 22:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to try that. Thanks for the tip! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 19:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought it at a store, it's a fairly big bottle, says 1 Pint on the label </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 18:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I was pretty disappointed it was 15$ for a pint.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 17:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it was. It was around 9:30 this morning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 17:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, I had Big Luscious on tap at my favorite bar when it was out and I loved it. I kept the Blushing Monk for a week or so (refrigerated) before I opened it.. Think that could have anything to do with it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 17:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. You learn something new every day. I figured they were filming or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know what was happening here?they were lifting metal boxes on a pallet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 16:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 00:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just tried Abita's harvest strawberry lager. Delicious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 00:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did a tour at Abita Brewing today. Had a blast. They open up their bar and let you try as much of their tapped beer as you want. Awesome guys who have a passion for their craft. I highly recommend it if you're ever in the area!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brewery Tour at Abita Brewery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 00:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 13:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Audio guy here. Can't go wrong with the Shure SM58 for vocal mics. brand new they're 100.. they hold up really well and work well for just about all vocals as long as you can EQ them right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 05:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That page has turned me on to so many good beers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 02:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone see the prices of their watch bands for these? Cheapest is the sports band for $50.. That nice chain link one? $450.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 13:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/nhlstreams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 03:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crow made some amazing stops. I don't want to jinx it but I think he might have his mojo back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 18:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This hit me really hard. One of my best friends dad has a glioblastoma. Has a year to live. Really tough watching him wither away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 06:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 03:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that was quick..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 05:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't ever had anything from Sierra Nevada. Any suggestions on what to try first? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 05:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem! I think you'll love Alabama shakes if you're into female vocalists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 05:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I got this. I'm on mobile so I can't link you but here's some blues stuff I like:

Bands:
Alabama Shakes (female lead)
St. Paul   The Broken Bones(they did a tiny desk concert with NPR, check it out)
Jeff Healey
Stevie Ray Vaughan 
Albert King
Buddy Guy
John Lee Hooker
Luther Allison
BB King

Songs:
Out of My Mind (live)- John Mayer
Broken Bones   Pocket Change- St. Paul   the Broken Bones
Little Wing-SRV
Blues at Sunrise- Albert King w/ SRV
Life by the Drop- SRV
Always Alright- Alabama Shakes
I Found You- Alabama Shakes

Hope this helps! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 05:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link it through the title maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 23:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. Just added uou </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 23:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 19:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I'm at 46 and I thought that was impressive haha
Just added you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 19:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some cool ancestry! Just added you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 19:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 15:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, same here! I just added you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 05:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your user? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 04:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even at 50 yet unfortunately.. Working my way up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 04:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 04:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added, thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 01:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just added you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 01:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome name. Added! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 01:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
