<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8579</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dark Lord Funk you up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 11:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need the most views on this video that me and my group have made in order to win a competition at my university, please watch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need the most views on this video that me and my group have made, in order to win a competition at my university, please watch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 21:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladies, Dan Osborne </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 01:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 21:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww that's great :')  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet my little beauty, cocoa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 16:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questionnaire: Can any university students please take some time to fill out this questionnaire as part of my assignment, would be a great help, thank you in advance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 14:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 22:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I guess we just like to have a good moan about everything, plus it is split opinion with everyone! I love people.of other cultures, my ex boyfriend was from the Czech Republic and most of my work colleges and two of my best friends are from other countries :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 21:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's horrible! They shouldn't judge you for your accent! In terms of people just asking where you are from and what you do, they may just be showing an interest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who have moved from one country to another, was there discrimination against you when you first arrived? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 16:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there still discrimination against you? If it was resolved how was it resolved? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "seriously? A cat selfie?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 00:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finally managed to leave them behind! I had to invite them somewhere and leave them there! It was a pain but at least they're gone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 03:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will do when I get back on it on a little while, thanks for the advice :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HELP!! Visiting sims won't go </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 01:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I am playingbthe sims 4 and have other sims from the neighbourhood come and visit, so I let them in and we sims chat etc only now they are not leaving. It has been a week in sims days and they are still at my sims house eating the food and sleeping in the beds. I know what your thinking, just use the 'say goodbye' option of 'ask to leave' but they are not showing up in any interaction list! Please help, they are driving me insane and running my fun! 

Thank you in advance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 23:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying being 5 1/2ft it's a nightmare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 12:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello there 
http://imgur.com/GXGWbDT


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 16:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you get the tent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bic for her pen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 18:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the gardener in your life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 18:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 02:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's a disturbing image for such a light hearted thread  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 02:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) http://imgur.com/TRRzku6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 03:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gus: I don't think I can take it anymore 
Dottie: If I stay still, the dot will come back!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every work area needs Christmas decorations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 14:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GIF] After handing in my last assignment before Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 00:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 01:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are apparently working on new "entertainment rewards" for customers 
http://m.bbc.co.uk/news/business-30440928 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 10:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to school with him. I spent 5 years sharing the same classes with him, laughing at his jokes which were sometimes dark humoured but we always thought of them as jokes. One of his friends in highschool was Muslim so I was very shocked when this was discovered, I just can't believe that the popular boy that made all my classes entertaining is now in prison for terror offenses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wizards and texting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 03:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goshdarnit Matt! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 18:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 01:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should sell the idea of the "M.A.M.E" certificates! I know a lot of potterheads would love something similar! Including me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 02:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I will let you know if it works :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheats for moving objects in sims 4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 01:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the sims 3 you had the cheat "moveObjects on" that allowed you to put any object anywhere with no restrictions. Is there anything similar for the sims 4?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why 7 horcrux's? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 15:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did Tom Riddle always intend (and successed) on making 7 horcrux's? Why that specific?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'It's fantastic!' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 19:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Actors/entertainers who have worked in a house of horrors or something similar, what is the best/worst reactions you have received? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 01:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My latest crush </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 02:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 16:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I'm not very good with spelling, never been a strong point for me. 

Thanks for pointing it out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is female masterbation such a taboo subject to talk about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 12:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Men talked about masterbation openly for a number of years now, so much that we have come to accept that male masterbation is to be expected and we don't even give it a second thought when it is brought up.

However, female masterbation is still seems to be such a hush hush subject, not only publicly but between friendship groups and relationships aswell. I, for one, have friends that cringe and shy away or quickly move on to another subject if it is brought up in casual conversation and within the last year I have talked a friend into trying masterbation for the first time and she did and she loved it (we are both nearly 20). 

I guess what I want to know, is your thoughts and opinions on why it is still so hushed up when we seem to be living in a world that seems to be embracing sex more and more.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 02:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need to be this worried about it. So what you haven't had a first kiss yet, it will just make it even more special when it does happen and hopefully it will be with the right girl at the right time. It will happen when it happens and even if it doesn't happen in that way, at least you have a lifetime to make the perfect kiss happen 

(a soppy girl comment, I know haha)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 02:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was suffering from depression, you're an arsehole for posting this comment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 02:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the whole world should just be quiet for a few minutes, just out of respect of him and to let the news of his death actually sink in  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 00:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a cat that likes to hunt bee's, it usually doesnt go well for her  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL after a study carried out by Kyle and Mahler, it was shown that an employer would be less likely to hire a person with blonde hair simply because of there hair colour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 03:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Viewing 300 out of 8,438 planes in the sky's right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 01:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quite possibly the best chat up line ever? Haha </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 01:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 02:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not let your grandad get drunk of red wine before the speeches so that he interrupts them all by trying to talk over them very loudly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 02:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how potato cakes are marked as "potato scones", makes it even more British!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 11:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no words  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 11:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that was cheerful  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apart from r/Aww, what are some of the best animal based subreddits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 10:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 02:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "smell my butt, smell it!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 19:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a boyfriend like this, at first it was cute but then I realised how annoying he actually was  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your worst 'clingy boyfriend' experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 17:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Lily, how many other boyfriends did you have before James?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 03:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
