<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2082</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The music was [reused a bit too much though](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8S6myWz3Kzg), especially that "slider" theme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also hold on to your old apps. There seems to be even less of an effort to preserve old applications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like they mostly ripped off [this article](https://electrek.co/2017/02/18/tesla-battery-cost-gigafactory-model-3/) by Fred Lambert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A quick search brings up various topics recommending to replace this PSU. It had a bad reputation.

http://www.overclock.net/t/1360121/600w-diablotek-el-series-how-good-or-bad-is-it

http://www.tomshardware.com/answers/id-1745323/long-power-supply.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like they used an Atari 2600 with a MOS6507 (6502 variant). Here's the paper: http://biorxiv.org/content/biorxiv/early/2016/05/26/055624.full.pdf

And here's the [Team 6502](http://www.visual6502.org/) website, which decapped and simulated the processor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diablotek EL 500W PSU

Weren't those the ones that had a reputation for catching on fire? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Games can still be playable at 20fps but frequent framerate dips diminish the experience. There's a reason why some game companies target 60 fps. Most Nintendo games on the Wii U are 60fps. Super Mario 3D world never dips below 60 in any situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's $300. And it's amazingly powerful for a handheld. They might have been able to design something more powerful based on Nvidia X2. But they didn't. There probably were price or time constraints. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It amazes me that a sound file could contain an exploit. I generally consider video and audio files to be safe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It shouldn't be a problem if the inputs were properly sanitized, but I see how a single developer might make a mistake in their implementations of QR codes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 06:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would the camera and mic be vulnerable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need a video of the Dolphin devs dancing to [this song](https://youtu.be/wN2WdO4c_jM?t=6m14s) for the next update ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You're going to be disappointed when it happens.

Oh, so it will happen?

Not to be rude, but it didn't seem like you put much heart into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The name and branding are pretty terrible, IMO. That big green cockroach is ugly. But who cares I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 08:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a new Front End called [Med Launch](http://medlaunch.asnitech.co.uk/releases).

I like it. (Windows only) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You recently said that robots should pay taxes. In essence, this will be a tax on corporations. While I think this is a good idea, don't you think that this will be hard to enforce in an environment where corporations successfully exploit international tax laws to minimize their tax liabilities to very low levels? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the [FAQ](https://rpcs3.net/quickstart):

"Typically, you want to dump your own PlayStation 3 games and software from your own console. We believe that this is the most efficient and safest way to migrate your disc-based games and digital games from your console to your PC. To do this, you will need a PlayStation 3 system with a custom firmware and various software tools that are used to rip/dump games from your system's Blu-ray drive or internal storage.

You can also dump games using select compatible Blu-ray drives." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're interested in CGA graphics, the [8 bit guy](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=niKblgZupOc) has some pretty good stuff on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try Mednafen. There's a new Front End called [Med Launch](http://medlaunch.asnitech.co.uk/releases). It only accepts the BIN/CUE format though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 02:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. Your GUI looks even better :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have 30 games that you want to play, then I wouldn't worry. It could take you a LONG time to finish those games.

As everyone else said, development is unpredictable. Xbox emulation is still not a reality despite being in development for 10 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks great. Do you know about [OpenEmu](http://openemu.org/)? It has a great UI, especially for controllers and could serve as a source of inspiration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could always check out emulator source code. For example, [Mednafen](https://github.com/OpenEmu/Mednafen-Core/blob/master/mednafen/psx/gpu.cpp). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 06:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume the same still happens with Blu-rays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any pictures? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, half the time between ME1 and ME4 has been between ME3 and ME4. Extrapolating, we'll get ME5 in 2027. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any development builds? The only build I see on your website is an [undated 0.2a release.](https://www.supermodel3.com/Download.html) Would be nice to have a date. This could be very recent or very old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](https://github.com/mamedev/mame/blob/master/src/mame/drivers/namcos23.cpp) is the MAME driver. Development seems to be somewhat active. 

No expert, but it looks fairly complex, using "custom polygon hardware". Maybe /u/mamehaze or another developer can give an estimate of how far along development is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They could have tried sending it there. But they're probably short on staff and/or trained to mechanically follow procedures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great! I guess the lesson is: "Never ascribe to malice that which can be explained by incompetence."

I'm a natural pessimist however, and if you've shared all of my disappointments in life, I suspect you might be as cynical as I am.

:( I hope this at least cheers you up for a while. I wish you the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to what's been said, some games require more accurate emulation of low level features. For example, on Dolphin, some games require MMU emulation which is very slow. Most games run fine with a more basic emulation.

 In general, emulators are full of hacks and high level emulation, except for a few low level emulators like bsnes/Higan that emulate older hardware. When these hacks can't be used and more accuracy is required, emulation gets slower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Microsoft is out of touch. Their focus on TV when the XboxOne launched was embarrassing.

[Here's](http://kotaku.com/how-a-small-game-studio-almost-made-it-big-1696997142) how they mismanaged a new IP from a small studio. "

"Darkside was in the very early stages of development when E3 came around in June of last year, and some at the studio say they were shocked to see Microsoft announce Phantom Dust there. They were even more shocked to see the game announced through a pre-rendered trailer that nobody at Darkside had worked on, according to studio sources. Perhaps most frustratingly for people at the studio, Microsoft wouldnt tell anyone that Darkside was developing the game. Darkside was put on a gag order; though the game had been announced, they still couldnt tell people they were making it."

And there are other bizarre moments. Microsoft kept adding demands while not increasing the budget. According to this account, dealing with Microsoft more like dealing with a bipolar, unpredictable bureaucracy. It's the opposite of nurturing a studio. 

Microsoft cancelled Obsidian's exclusive RPG Stormlands that was due to be released for the XboxOne launch. [Fergus Urqhart](http://ign.com/articles/2017/02/02/why-kotor-2-devs-xbox-one-launch-game-was-canceled-a-ign-unfiltered) puts it down to "not having a champion" at Microsoft.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most sales happen around release. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rimworld, Dwarf Fortress and Prison Architect have build times and it works well. I agree that it could be fun.

The reason is probably the added complexity (these games are already complex enough), and also the fact that simcity games are now a niche (e.g. dead) genre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP Iwata. He was only 55. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to rumors, Tim Schafer is not the best at managing money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heres Why This Cat-Spotting AI Is Different (uses probability based AI) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main menu is available through the main interface. There's no onscreen menu like mednafen or mame though.

Overall, Dolphin's UI is one of the best IMO. Then again I've been using it for too long to really be objective about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Convenience is also the biggest factor for me. It's also something that emulator developers tend to be a bit dismissive of:

"UI design is not important." 

"You can do X already: you just need to edit a text file, download this and this, and jump through a hoop three times. No need for me to add this feature." 

In reality, if a feature is more than a few clicks away, most of your userbase will not use it. The 80-20 rule says that everytime that you make your users jump through a hurdle, you lose 80% of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LmCZMkfICAs) it is in a less sickening greyscale.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was originally a mobile game. Watch the trailer on [Steam](http://store.steampowered.com/app/278420). It looks pretty neat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nevermind, read the PR, they'd just complain about where to get the keys.

I don't know how Citra works, but Cemu has a very simple system where users store all the keys in a keys.txt file.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of these games don't make much money. Here's a [talk](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r30CIneO534) about the Indiepocalypse. Waking Mars (included in the bundle) made $800k and took 3.5 person-year to make. That's pretty good but their most recent game "Spider 2" made around $200k and took 9 person-year to make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the line between a robot, and software, which can also replace people?

I agree. A simple computer running software can replace workers. Maybe we should just tax Windows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ars Technica](https://arstechnica.com/gaming/2017/02/horizon-zero-dawn-is-the-best-robot-safari-adventure-game-ever-made/) - Horizon Zero Dawn is the best robot-safari adventure game ever made - Sam Machkovech - Ars Approved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you have managed to get this format successfully running in mednafen then let me know and I will add that extension to the launcher.

You're right. It's not supported.

Thanks. The GUI is really nice overall. I don't really like the mednafen and medlaunch logos and color scheme, but that's really nitpicking. 

Do you know about [OpenEmu](http://openemu.org/)? I think it could be a source of inspiration. It has a really nice, clean design, probably the best of all multi emulators, and I love the controller setup screen. Keep up the good work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice GUI. Doesn't seem to support .mds/.mdf files.

Edit: I would recommend removing the top menu. Having two menus is a bit confusing. 

Also, scanning for CD images doesn't seem to work very well.

It would be nice to have an option to configure controllers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only a few games have bugs, like Alone in the Dark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing that I don't like is that it's closed source. Strange, if they're based on Freedo, which is open source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. It also claims to be based on Freedo. Can't say if it's better than 4DO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are still a few inaccuracies, as you can see in their [compatibility list](http://web.archive.org/web/20170112082136/http://wiki.fourdo.com/Compatibility_List). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is 4DO (3DO emulator) dead? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [website](http://web.archive.org/web/20161213021202/http://www.fourdo.com/) appears to be down. This is an archive.org link. Last release was in 2015. 

Digital Foundry just featured the previous incarnation, called [3DO play](http://3doplay.do.am/), in a [video about Need for Speed](https://youtu.be/FjLXLhaGfFA), maybe not realizing that it was outdated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There seems to be a loader for the Taito games. Haven't tried it myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing your experience. What is your mod? (if that's something that you want to share).

I get how it would be nice for modders to get some reward out of their work. But I'm afraid that it would really change modding and potentially ruin the community as modders stop sharing and mod pirates rip assets and mods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to find someone who wants to work on the emulator full time first for whatever meager pittance he will get from Patreon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if /u/byuu 's roms and scans could be donated to Archive.org. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Interplay did go under. The sales of both Fallouts were a disappointment.

According to [this thread](https://www.rockpapershotgun.com/forums/showthread.php?3616-How-do-old-game-budgets-compare-to-new-game-budgets) (Not the best source, I know):

"The budget for Fallout 1 was $3 million"

"Games like Grim Fandango cost a hefty $3 million back in 1998. Full Throttle cost just over $2 million to produce, and Psychonauts had a whopping $12 million dollar budget back in 2005, equivalent to the $12 million dollar budget of gPotato's 2010 AAA MMO, Allods Online. Yikes.

(...)

the original Gears of War only had a budget of $10 million

(...)

There's also another factor of game budgets a lot of people don't talk about...see back in the 1990s and early 00s, video game budgets were mostly centered around artists, programmers, designers, QA and testers. Nowadays, a huge portion of a game's budget resides in marketing, in fact, for some games, 200% of the budget will go into marketing while the game itself will cost anywhere between $10 and $20 million to actually design and produce.
In the early 90s, video game budgets were around $100,000  when Doom was released in 1993 it had cost $200,000 and was touted as one of the most expensive games at the time."

150k copies * $20, would mean a gross of $3M for the developer, just enough to recoup the development costs.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the explanation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question. The atmosphere was amazing and unprecedented. The visual design is still awesome. The same guy who did the concept art went on to work for Arkane on Dishonored. 

One reason might be that the story is not THAT engaging. You mostly run from point A to point B, never having deep interactions with anyone. Also, FPS games have improved on almost all of the mechanical aspects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [trailer](https://youtu.be/lkYhWses6pQ) looks surprisingly modern IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  . Maybe I'm embellishing this time period but I firmly believe it was the golden age for innovation and gaming. Developers could try out all these new ideas without the fear of going bankrupt.

Eurogamer in one of their recent videos (about the Fallout 2 sex formula) talked about how Black Isle had a "frat house" atmosphere at that time. Developers just added things because they thought it was funny. This didn't always lead to good content, but it did lead to a lot more creativity. 

Also developers didn't have to cater to the needs of a large, mainstream audience. They were mostly making games for a small fairly nerdy audience. I can't find exact numbers, but those numbers are [floating around](http://www.nma-fallout.com/threads/how-many-units-would-you-say-fallout-1-2-sold.200521/page-2):

"Baldur's Gate (all formats) 500,000

BG expansion pack 156,000

Fallout 144,000

Fallout 2 123,000

Diablo 1,300,000

Revenant 37,000

Darkstone 75,000

Ultima IX: Ascension 73,000

Planescape: Torment 73,000" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to hear that but you did know you were doing something for free. It's like if someone expected to be paid after doing volunteer work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or not. I wouldn't count on Bethesda fixing the CK just because they're getting free mod money. They'll probably figure out that they're making 95% of the money without any of the cost, so why hire an employee to maintain the CK? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why was the thread about [Submarine games](https://www.reddit.com/r/Games/comments/5uletu/silent_hunter_v_came_out_almost_7_years_ago_where/) deleted and all the comments removed?

Seriously, I don't get it. It was "too specific?" It's not like there's much interesting on the /r/games front page right now. And it was a nice change from the usual discussion about super-mainstream games. Why not let users have a discussion?

But even if you delete the thread, why go after the individual comments? People were reminiscing about old sub games they used to play, as well as discussing current ones. It's not like they said anything offensive or racist. I don't understand the mods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matrix Games has a super detailed naval wargame that includes [subs](http://www.matrixgames.com/products/483/details/Command:.Modern.Air.Naval.Operations.Wargame.of.the.Year.Edition). Never played it, but one DLC scenario is about a war caused by Brexit called [YOU BREXIT, YOU FIX IT!](http://www.matrixgames.com/products/640/details/Command.Live:.You.Brexit,.You.Fix.it!). To be honest, seems to be more about the Navy in general than about subs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ingestion of titanium dioxide (TiO2) nanoparticles from products such as agricultural chemicals, processed food, and nutritional supplements is nearly unavoidable. The gastrointestinal tract serves as a critical interface between the body and the external environment, and is the site of essential nutrient absorption. "

"Overall, these results show that intestinal epithelial cells are affected at a functional level by physiologically relevant exposure to nanoparticles commonly ingested from food." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Titanium dioxide nanoparticle ingestion alters nutrient absorption in an in vitro model of the small intestine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Food additive found in candy, gum could alter digestive cell structure and function </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  hose people will still be out there, and associate my name with their first impressions from those stories.

IMO, it's only a few people. The articles all took your side. My advice would be to pad out your Patreon to explain your project well. It's important that people get a good impression and understand what you're doing. Also, adding a link to your Patreon on your website couldn't hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And now I've burned through most of the good will that took me over a decade to build up. 

There's no such thing as bad publicity. It wasn't bad publicity anyway. I know that you're very anxious about this but this could be an opportunity. Now, more people know you. You could use this to promote your Patreon, get money to preserve games and spend more time on Higan. You could even start a Youtube channel (ok maybe not your style).

 Don't freak out about reimbursing people. If they gave you money, it's because they want you to have it. It's good to be transparent, and even offer a possibility of refund, but I doubt anyone will be interested. I'm sure patrons would rather you use that money to complete your project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great job on the Patreon. It feels a little bare though.

I think you just need to a part about: "Why start a Patreon?", explaining how you're collecting money to pay for this package, but have been doing preservation for years, and just saying a bit how you intend to use the money after that situation is resolved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why you make it part of a larger effort to fund game preservation. 

Be honest and say that you need the money for buying back these games as it's your most pressing need, but that if the games reappear, or if you get more money than you need, you'll use the money to fund other preservation efforts. It's not like the money will go to waste IMO. You can use it to pay for more expensive shipping and better insurance.

Also, don't worry about the haters. Nobody on Reddit seems to believe that you're a scammer. Any sufficiently famous person will have haters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most game sites don't cover Indie games. RPS (rockpapershotgun) has pretty good coverage. IGN also reviews some of the most prominent games. They said that they do it at a loss because they find it important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way to quickly add all the Steam keys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ars Technica: [Prey: Nothing like the originaland all the better for it](https://arstechnica.com/gaming/2017/02/prey-hands-on-preview-impressions/) Not a full review. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen that story: [How UPS Screwed A Popular YouTube Car Guy Out Of $10,000](http://thegarage.jalopnik.com/how-ups-screwed-a-popular-youtube-car-guy-out-of-10-00-1738255686) . This was UPS, not USPS, but still not super encouraging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they might want to sell the company at some point. Also, you can still sell shares to some investors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When I say cap out I mean my internet stops. I can't browse to a website, chats will disconnect. It uses ever last drop because Valve's infrastructure is so massive it'll take it all. 

I wouldn't call that a feature.

I didn't say that they had to do this. I'm just saying that this money would probably be reinvested into games if it went to game developers instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's listed as [design lead](http://www.mobygames.com/game/windows/neverwinter-nights-2/credits) with Ferret Beaudoin while Chris Avellone was creative director.

Edit: Thanks for the downvotes btw. I was just providing objective information... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think that most games that offer romance options tend to go for a hamfisted wish fulfillment approach. 

True, but isn't that what games are? Most games, including RPGs are a power fantasy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have 3 VR games in development. 

4000 games were released on Steam in 2016. If they were to release 30% of the games on Steam (because they collect 30% of the revenues), they would have released 1200 games. That's obviously a bit silly because many games are indies, etc. But their average of 1 game a year or so is not in line at all with the amount of money they rake in from Steam. It's more in line with what a mid-sized games studio would crank out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Great stories are about characters, not worlds. They focused a lot on the world building and epic aspects, but forgot about characters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An 8% increase in revenue and 27% in profits for the full year is really good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better source: [Dear Esther Landmark Edition out tomorrow on PC, free to owners of original](http://www.pcgamer.com/dear-esther-landmark-edition-out-tomorrow-on-pc-free-to-owners-of-original/) -PC Gamer

"Last year, The Chinese Room released a console version of its flagship non-combat exploration game Dear Esthernamed the Landmark Editionand suggested it would one day land on PC. It's now doing exactly that, the developer has revealed, and will be completely free-of-charge to owners of the original on Steam as of 6pm GMT/10am PT tomorrow.

With it comes remastered audio and developer commentary for the game which is widely considered to have sparked the 'walking simulator' genre. It's been ported from the original Source Engine onto Unity 5 and has additional accessibility options, large subtitles, a crosshair, multi-language options, and a smattering of trophies and achievements.  " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the Unity version. It was originally a Source game, and a hl2 mod before that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There isn't really a way for a third party to get 100% of the money from their sale no matter where they sell it (Unless they sell it themselves on their own website).

Yes, it's true. But the more different stores there are, the more pressure there will be on Steam to reduce their cut. If they were to become a monopoly, they might increase it to 50%. If they have to compete hard, they might be forced to lower it to 15%. That's why competition is important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. "Just in the last package of 100 games alone, I found two ROMs that were marked "verified" in other sets, but had corrupted main character sprites due to some kind of bit-rot. The games were Fatal Fury 2 (PAL) and Spider-Man   Venom (PAL)." -Byuu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's one-off custom hardware. Plus, it requires time and effort and expertise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Byuu said that he should have sent the games in smaller packages. But hindsight is 20/20. 

Flying all the games by making dozens of trip between the US and Germany is just not realistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Byuu has custom hardware that he says he didn't want to risk. Also, I think that he's a bit OCD (in a good way!), in that he will use the same process every time, scan all the art and the manual, and by doing it all himself he insures that it's perfect. I don't think that many others would be willing to dedicate the time and effort to do this perfectly. He's aiming to create a reference copy of the ROM so it has to be perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As /u/ROverdose said, private companies have shareholders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say it was. I was responding to a comment that said that Steam's lack of curation was good for indie devs. Well, not so much. It's better than not being allowed in, but it's not as good as a curated, yet open store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been updated but on the level needed for HL3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They reinvest CSGO and DOTA money into those games. That's separate from steam.

SteamOS, Steam link and the Steam controller are not super exciting. And they're not reinvesting in games.

Having indie devs come work at their offices?

Not sure what you're talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. A game that sells $100M will have had a big marketing campaign. If they got featured on Steam, they probably paid for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Frankly, I expect Valve to use the money better than they ever could. 

Steam will not invest the money back into games. It should be obvious at this point. Most of it probably goes to Gabe Newell and the other shareholders.

Game developers are much more likely to reinvest money they made from a game into another game. Valve doesn't have any reason to invest money made by a store into games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one way to look at it. But in reality having so many bad games (many of which don't even start or work properly) poisons the well for legit indie game developers. Legit indie games like, say Jotun, will not get the exposure they deserve because they spend 10 minutes on the front page and then disappear and are drowned by a 1000 shitty games that don't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also checked that I'm not in the Beta. Steam wants to update almost every single time I start it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how stores lure customers. They know that customers would prefer to have all their games in one place. But they need to force them out of the Steam ecosystem to reclaim that 30% of revenue.

Activision Blizzard had a revenue of $6.6B in 2016. If they had to pay a 30% cut to Steam, it would amount to almost $2B! They could develop a few new IPs from scratch with that money, or return it to investors. There's a huge incentive for them to move away from Steam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's true that it's annoying to have multiple storefronts, which naturally leads to the most popular stores becoming monopolies. However, this is pretty bad for developers and consumers since it gaves immense power to the most successful storefronts. At 30%, the Steam tax is pretty heavy. If a game has revenues of $100M, $30M will go to Steam and $70M to the publisher. That's a huge cut  just for handling the digital distribution of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had to take a guess, they don't want to affect their profit per employee, as this would hurt their valuation. And they might be afraid that they'll be held liable for an offensive game. One solution would be to outsource this game review process.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like frostfall but I stopped using it for this reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't assume anything. It's not. Companies shut down and lose stuff. Even TV and radio archives get lost. National Libraries keep a copy of every book so these should be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could start a campaign to fund SNES preservation in general. Kickstarter or Go Fund Me. Stretch goals could be NTSC, PAL games, Japan or whatever. I think people would be willing to help you. Especially if you make tshirts or mugs or something as a reward. "I helped HIGAN and all I got was this lousy T-shirt". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'd need someone who speaks German to tag along with me because holy hell it sounds terrifying to travel internationally alone. I know you guys will say 'it's cool', and I have no doubt Germans are all awesome, but yeah. Too scary for me.

That's the last thing I'd worry about. Germans speak English really well. As long as you have enough money to pay for your trip, there's nothing really scary about travelling alone in Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They could make a special exception for mods, not just Skyrim mods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure it's newsworthy. It would probably be useful in any case to set up a gofundme or have a paypal account so you can receive donations. Donations tend to spike after the article gets published then die down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it interesting that people are defending Valve's right to make a 30% cut. They're already making an insane amount of profit compared to the service they provide. They can only charge this because Steam has some monopoly power at this point. It is THE platform that everyone wants to be on. Bethesda actually developed the IP. They deserve the money more than Steam IMO. Steam has already recouped their costs 100x over.

Skyrim sold 11,5M copies on steam. At a conservative $40 per copy for 11,5M copies, they've already raked in $138M, while Bethesda got $322M. I think they've already paid for the simple download functionality they offer many times over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you should be singling Emil Pagliarulo like that. He may be responsible, but we don't know much about him and the design process at Bethesda. It's unfair to make this personal and call out for his resignation IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This highlights nicely what I think Bethesda main flaw has been in FO3 and FO4: just not thinking through their ideas at all to form a coherent story and a coherent world. The original FO designers and Obsidian really thought about how the world could possibly work. I'm sure that some details don't match, but it's obvious that they thought about the world and the story and about what second order consequences could stem from the elements they put in place. Factions have coherent motivations. Beth just doesn't seem capable of thinking that far. What are this faction's motivations? What is the most efficient strategy for them to achieve their goal? Who is blocking them?

Some of their ideas have absolutely no depth. Take Megaton. There's a city with a bomb underneath. A cult worships the bomb. You can either set off the bomb for no reason and be super evil, or not do it. It's not an intelligent nor an interesting choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's much easier to write a semi-incoherent series of jokes than it is to write a coherent story that tackles serious themes.

Especially when the quests are not written by professional writers, but by level designers. Everyone writes their own little "funny" quest on their own. There's no need to make sure it all fits into a coherent whole. No need to even write a design document. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the time, I was sure that other games would come along that would eclipse or even equal Mass Effect. But it seems that it was an almost one-off success.

It makes sense though. Games are very expensive to make and good stories are fairly rare. There's no perfect formula for producing one. It's a rare thing that all the pieces come together perfectly to make a really good game. That's what happened with Mass Effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What Miyazaki said was that " anime suffers because industry staff is made up of otaku who "don't spend time watching real people" and are "humans who can't stand looking at other humans." [source](http://www.animenewsnetwork.com/interest/2014-01-30/miyazaki/the-problem-with-the-anime-industry-is-it-full-of-otaku).

I think is point is very valid and also applies to games, including Fallout 4. The games industry tends to be mostly staffed by nerds who reference other games and nerd culture (like the red wedding). There's nothing wrong with that but it makes that culture very insular. Fallout 4 suffers from that IMO. The story doesn't seem to be connected to real themes from the real world. It doesn't make any point about our society. All the ideas go nowhere and fizzle out. And Pagliarulo might very well be an example of the kind of designer that Miyazaki was criticizing. I admit there are some good sequences in FO4, but overall it fails to tell something important or to create real characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
