<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4819</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ANyone familiar with the jab comic "The Wrong House" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You turn the "light" on during daylight? Regardless, how are they supposed to see if the light is on through a door? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gargoyles watchthrough topic. (SPOILERS) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On season 2 now episode 2 "Metamorphosis" .  Damn, Xanatos is such an asshole. I can't believe he turned Derek, Elisa Maza's younger brother into a monster freak hybrid thing just to further his little chess game with the Gargoyles and Elisa. That is such a jerk thing to do, and I think the only time I truly hated him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait so based on some of the posts so far... this is actually a case of truth in television?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do American homes and bathrooms not have locks on the doors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so popular in many TV shows to have the classic "x character pops in on y character while they're showering the bathroom" trope and I honestly cannot understand how this ever became a thing. Does one not lock the door when they use the bathroom in American culture? 

It's mystifying. Such a common trope that I've always wondered about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why doesn't USA use the metric system and Celsius instead of the imperial system and fahrenheit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's up with the childish thumbs up/thumbs down arrow system of this site that doesn't stimulate conversation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be playing ac 4 now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol clones of what?

Also what happened to Desmond's posse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but why.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me answer your question with another question, what makes you think I didn't play those other 3 games? And why didn't you include ac 1 and liberation while you're at it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And..? "Juno is freed" that doesn't really  mean anything to me because the game doesn't really establish what that implies besides "bad things will happen" and generic terms like "enslavement" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, it's worse than a Shitty ending. Ending implies a conclusion to the story, and we weren't even given that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a goddamn shame because there's a good game here, so I hate that they sacrificed quality to get it put out on a 2012 release date. And for what, because they were using that stupid "the world will in 2012!" meme as a major plot point of the story? What a waste. There was a good game here and it's clear there's a lot of effort behind it. Really could have been great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Erm... what exactly happened at the end of AC 3? I feel like I missed something. *Spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 09:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a scene missing? I go down the bridge with the Desmond team, there's a glowing sphere at the end, Desmond is about to touch it and then minerva and Juno pop up and start arguing with each other. Desmond does touch it, gets electrocuted and dies.  

Then the game ends. I am so confused. Did I actually beat the game or is there more?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did "hashtag" go from a computer term to a phrase everyone started using on social media venues like twitter and in the real world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. And isn't that what everyone would appreciate from a significant other, maybe even want? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does seem to be leading that way... she met gil first after all. But I love how Tarvek starts off seeming like a villain jerk but ends up doing everything for Agatha, it's prime fantasy wish fulfilment material  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... Team Tarvek or Team Gilgamesh? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just so hard to choose, I just don't know! I love them both and would be happy to see all 3 of them together, like a menage trois three's company type thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does a woman wearing heels look "good" ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do a lot of women wear uncomfortable shoes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's everyone's life here like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well at least someone got it :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barmasters did... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess none of the people on this forum are video game players... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love this guy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a man? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah fair enough. I'm definitely liking the suggestions itt of just putting cornmeal at the bottom, that should solve the problem : ) ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is cornmeal better for pizza dough than typical flour? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just wondering about that. The problem I've noticed with some pizza and pizza places here is that the bottom of the pizza is all powdery and has that uncomfortable dry/chalky feeling when you hold the pizza slices, because of all the flour. 

But with cornmeal I don't get that dry chalky feeling that flour gives. It actually feels quite nice, has an enjoyably rough texture to it. 

Wondering if cornmeal for pizza dough is something people use over other types? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was still only an adolescent, but I still thought it was really intriguing, and I can remember the opening despite not seeing it in 15 years

"You see there's this stuff called quicksilver that can bend light..."

https://youtu.be/dVQ3DU6apfQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone else grow up with this show? I thought it was really interesting but don't know anyone else who has seen it   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> the invisible man tv show of 2000. I loved that show as an adolescent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've had breasts my entire life and I wish I could get them... off my chest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bit of a literal understanding of this forum's moniker but nevertheless it's true, I've always felt self conscious and embarrassed by them, and wish they wouldn't exist on my body.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the point of the internet if countries and regions put individual restrictions on content they have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The uploaded has not made this video available in your country" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the point of the internet again? To enforce the same restrictions of real life? All these regional restrictions that Google products have is beyond frustrating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no such thing as a sedentary lifestyle before cars and internet... save for like, the occasional royalty or 2 who are carried everywhere by slaves. But there were no cars to transport you from place to place. You HAD to move on your own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they are dried, they came in a little vial and everything. It was just an impulse purchase I made when I was out shopping and I decided to use them up in as many dishes as possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bought some mixed herbs, the label says "great for pasta sauces" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My question is, when making a spaghetti sauce, Should they be added while making the pasta sauce, or after the fact when it's put on spaghetti? Was just wondering when is the best time for them to infuse the flavor of mixed herbs onto the pasta sauce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bought some mixed herbs. Should they be added while making the pasta sauce, or after the fact when it's put on spaghetti? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was just wondering when is the best time for them to infuse the flavor of mixed herbs onto the pasta sauce.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do people in real life even go to find people with the same interests in movies and shows they have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did people in ancient times even get fat before fast food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KL? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's scary, I wouldn't joke about that. Type 1 or 2? Also I know that the seasonal varieties (like screme egg) are seasonal, I'm talking about regular creme eggs, or as I've mentioned the creme egg twisted, which is the ultimate example of decadence in how easy it is to transport the fondant filling into your mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why aren't creme eggs more popular than all the other brands of chocolate in the world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are creme eggs so goshdarn diddly delicious? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironically your logic there is fundamentally flawed, but then again we haven't really discussed what exactly should be considered intelligence, be it book knowledge, natural ability to grasp complex mathematical equations, or simply the ability to be cunning and think quickly on your head.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more you know the less you realize you know... the smart thing to do is not to let that realization cripple you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alcohol is also something I wouldn't consider to be fun or enjoyable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am neither of those 2 things, but great job projecting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But green is more aesthetically pleasing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does intelligence lead to isolation, sometimes even depression? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... it still has red and yellow. *Yellow*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If knowledge is power, and power essentially corrupts, does that mean knowledge, essentially, corrupts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When will fiber internet be available everywhere? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 09:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 09:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh I guess that's true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 09:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds... naughty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 08:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearly all of them from what I've seen. It's such a nice considerate thing to do, completely against the goal of a profit oriented business.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do so many hotels offer complimentary breakfast? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 08:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I ask the question "How does the reddit bot even know if I'm asking a clear and direct question?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Itt: my childhood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 06:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does the reddit bot even know if I'm asking a clear and direct question? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 06:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1000 years in fact. And I'm really hoping this is the explanation, I'm gonna go with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be first in line, guaranteed critical success I'm sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IT does! That was so eloquently put, you should be a writer. Have you ever thought of writing screenplays for the movie business? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moana question. [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was Maui really gonna leave Moana trapped inside the cave to starve or die of thirst to death or something? It's played for laughs but when you consider the fridge horror logic of it, kinda makes you frown a bit. Even Shrek didn't put the boulder to cover the cave on Princess Fiona back in Shrek 1 (although that was because Donkey cried at him not to) so this is especially surprising. 

It's one thing to keep throwing Moana into the ocean (although as dark as Pirates of the Caribbean marooning their pirates on an island, perhaps darker since there's no pistol with a single shot to use) but to leave her trapped in a cave and purposefully put a boulder on the entrance...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spring is the season everyone loves, but in the middle east it's the season filled with dust. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 10:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate that. Spring is usually depicted with beautiful growing fields of greenery and scenery, flowers and butterflies. 

But here in the middle east we are plagued by extreme dust storms. And it sucks. They're very depressing to look at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was particularly noticeable with te fiti giving that not amused look to Maui that says it all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 12:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've felt like disney movies have been like that since the disney revival with Tangled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 06:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emoting through facial expressions and body language is something that Disney has really perfected in the computer animation age, Moana is proof of that. The animation is so darn fluid and wonderful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enlighten us on the meaningful stuff you do on this dump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I think me and another user established  that it might just be an outlier that caused Frozen to make a billion when back in 2013, there weren't any movies to compete against it, while now in 2016 to 2017, there are a ton of movie properties all coming out at the same time and competing against each other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually felt like I wasn't sure what "the joke" with the assistant was supposed to be. I mean if he's anything like Schmidt he would have been gunning for Schmidt's position... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That *does* make a lot of sense... I may not understand the appeal of that star warsy stuff and fantastic beasts, but the fact of the matter is they do exist and they are super popular, so Moana did have a lot to contend with... while in 2013 there really weren't any movies for Frozen to compete with were there, since this was post Avengers and we still hadn't seen the game changing winter soldier or guardians of the galaxy yet or the revitalization of the star wars franchise with ep 7.

Yeah I guess it makes sense. Still wish it made more, but I guess them's the breaks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually wondered how good green lantern tas is. I saw part of an episode with star sapphire once and I liked what I saw, wondering how the overall quality of the show is like. 

This also reminds me of how bullshit it is that "DC Nation" block of Cartoon Network failed. They were touting great shows like Batman The Brave and The Bold, Young Justice, and Green Lantern The Animated Series, so it should have been a very successful block, like the Toonami of comic book shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol the way I read that reminds me of the Halloween episode of Suburgatory's second season where George goes "yeah but ***they're everywhere***, aren't they" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And as evidenced by the 0 thumbs up arrows this topic has currently, said people might be lurking on this very forum with us. Unfortunate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I just wonder if that's true. I'm more concerned with this topic getting no thumbs up  arrows for purposes of discussion, while a topic that's literally just a movie poster gets a bajillion comments and thumbs up arrows. I don't get this dump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know what that means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I'm even more bewildered they didn't make this a summer release or something. Why not have released it in March of this year same as Zootopia last year? Plus that way they wouldn't be competing for the Best Animated Feature Oscar in the same year...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doctor Strange also made not as much as I would have hoped, but I can't believe fantastic beasts made 800 mil... smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zootopia was fantastic though. Frozen while nice suffered from obvious re-writes that still plague the movie and I still remember thinking "that's it?" when the anticlimactic ending happened. And similarly remember being disappointed over Wreck-It Ralph not making as much money because it made me tear up a lot, such an amazing movie. Same as Big Hero 6, though that one has flaws that are constantly pointed out to me and I can't help agreeing with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that let it go was popular in America, but I thought the soundtrack for Moana was much better and is stuck in my head way more. Plus there was no garbage useless troll song (which now that I think about it has a double meaning) in Moana like there was in Frozen with the rock trolls and the *entire* soundtrack of Moana was useful for the story and completely enrapturing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because garbage like CBS's entire lineup gets a billion views and 10+ seasons while something quirky and unique like Happy Endings/Better Off Ted gets canceled. This is why we can't have nice things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moana captured me way more than Frozen did (a great movie in its own right, if a bit of an anticlimactic ending clearly showing the many rewrites it had since *The Snow Queen* was first proposed as a Disney movie...) so I can't help thinking it's strictly the last part of your post, with Moana being about non-white characters. 

I'll admit I **am** confused over why Disney released it in the very same year as Zootopia and not made Moana a summer release. Why release 2 amazing stellar movies in one year instead of spreading them out? I just don't know... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Weisman curse of cancellation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gargoles 1994 - One of the greatest shows of all time, my childhood cartoon. Suffered in the ratings and was canceled by Disney.

The Spectacular Spider-Man 2008 - Greatest adaptation of spiderman to date, went unnoticed, eventually canceled after Disney acquisition of Marvel and the rights of the show up in the air with Sony and Disney disputes. Never got the full 6 seasons and a movie it deserved.

Young Justice 2011 - Best post DCAU show, with an interesting beginning and huge amount of potential. Cance *wait they're reviving it for a season 3 this year???!!!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm starting to think America and/or the rest of the world really is racist and prefers seeing white characters... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What in the actual hell, Moana only made 500 mil at the box office? That's just HALF of what Frozen made. Why did it not also get 1 billion+ box office gross? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Moana was great, fantastic, and just really all around amazing. I knew I was gonna enjoy the movie, but I just had no idea how much I was going to fall in love with the art, the animation, and the soundtrack! It's really a stupendous movie.

Nearly every song in that movie was amazing. I particularly love the islander type music, which is why it's so amazing, and I don't know if I have a favorite song, but I did deeply enjoy you're welcome.

That scene where Maui makes his pecs dance, that was the moment I knew the Rock voiced him even if I didn't know the rock was in this movie simply because that is such a thing The Rock would do lol.

And though the song is essentially to trick Moana and steal her boat and leave her trapped in a cave (without even a box of scraps) I still can't help loving it and being captivated by him.

Such a fantastic, deeply emotional movie, I had to watch it twice in succession because it was just. that. good. 

But what the hell at that box office gross? Should have grossed at least a billion if not more.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does the auto-moderator even work when it starts automatically deleting questions you ask if it's just a bot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should old acquaintances be forgot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand just red for the character that would later become red robin, but for dick Grayson robin I like green to work in conjunction with red and yellow, just like the robin in btas has it done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They... already have a stealth mode for their suits, the all black version.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did Robin's costume not have any green on it, just red and yellow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the green on robin and it works so well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What can I say, except you're welcome? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if I have a favorite song, but I did deeply enjoy you're welcome.

That scene where Maui makes his pecs dance, that was the moment I knew the Rock voiced him even if I didn't know the rock was in this movie simply because that is *such* a thing The Rock would do lol.

And though the song is essentially to trick Moana and steal her boat and leave her trapped in a cave (without even a box of scraps) I still can't help loving it and being captivated by him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, I don't think anyone thought that Rapture was meant to be seen as successful or rational... Objectivism is and always has been seen as something incredibly ironic and contradictory in and of itself, not least because its own author ended up doing the exactly the things she preached against in her books.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moana was great, fantastic, and just really all around amazing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew I was gonna enjoy the movie, but I just had no idea how much I was going to fall in love with the art, the animation, and the soundtrack! It's really a stupendous movie. 

By the way the stubbornness of Moana makes me realize that I'd really like to see a new Disney Extended universe  where Moana, Tangled, and Frozen all meet with each other in some capacity, like the avengers thor iron man etc.

But yeah everything about this movie is completely on point, I haven't felt this great about a Disney movie since they released another amazing stellar movie in the same year (Zootopia) what was up with them releasing 2 fantastic movies in one year instead of spacing them out and not letting them compete with each other over the same oscar. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Is a man not entitled to sweat?" "No" says the man in Washington, "it belongs to the poor." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I rejected those answers, and built this city, my city... **Rapture**.


I absolutely loved Bioshock. Bizarrely weird tonal shift in ending aside ( the "good" ending at least) I think I just played one of the best games of all time. Even as someone who hates shooters, I absolutely enjoyed this. Mostly because of the whole powers thing, which allows you to get creative as opposed to rooty tooty pointy and shooty stuff of the genre.

I love how atmospheric and sometimes even creepy the game is, combine that with the old school pre 50s art and instructional videos on the powers, and it just works. so. darn. well.

The city of Rapture is probably still one of the best environments in gaming ever, and I hope something that entertaining can be matched by games in the future because it's been 10 years and no game has come close! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Is a man not entitled to sweat?" "No" says the man in Washington, "it belongs to the poor." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just assumed your autocorrect changed berries to babies. It happens to all of us, at the most inopportune times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bears don't eat babies... they eat berries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I needed a sign before I resign from my job. Well I got it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told the other company that I needed a week or 2 in order to complete the paperwork for my resignation and work for them, but the truth is I was just nervous about how to approach my manager and tell them I'm leaving. 

I felt like I needed a sign, a proper motivator, and let's just say I got it today. After all it's nothing personal, just a better opportunity... right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of Rio, that children's cgi movie. I didn't see all of it but saw a few scenes here and there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are baby laughs so cute? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 11:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. But tell me more, what kinda stuff do you do with your parrots, do you buy him toys, what kinda housing situation have you set up, and do you have any more pictures of the parrot? I'm just very interested in finding out the lifestyle of parrots as pets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 10:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would be more hilarious if we add "even bigger bird" and put like a giant hawk or eagle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 09:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do parrots ever fly away if you leave the window open?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 09:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this show, can't wait to see it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 09:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know they exist but I can't think of any right now, because I can't stop thinking about what a great movie Amadeus was. That laugh the actor for Mozart does I pretty much 10/10.

Such an entertaining, captivating movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minimunsters? You mean... this?

https://youtu.be/SuDSDtgEoAU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know they could twist their head that far! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't understand if most console gamers sit with their face just inches away from the screen to not be able to notice what I notice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, I have never liked anything scary either... or that is, anything in the horror/thriller category. But Gargoyles is something unique and wonderful. Plus to be fair the only episode that ever really scared me is the jackal episode, and I know this because it's one of the episodes (or a particular scene from the episode) that I still remember to this day, *over 20 years later* because that's how scarring it was for me hehe. 

I don't know if it will come to that american invented streaming device known as netflix, all I do know is that disney like all the other big name companies are going to be starting their **own** streaming service as they have realized the success of netflix but don't want to give them any money, so want the netflix userbase for themselves. If that means we'll get gargoyles, who knows. There's a topic on this very reddit website that states that disney is streaming the gargoyles show on youtube for what that's worth, but you'll have to find out for yourself because it only works for americans (like most youtube "official" streaming content) not for the rest of us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait a minute.... that's 99 luft balloons! You lied to me Miss Lemon, you said we were friends!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who constantly watches the first 3 seasons of 30 Rock, all I can think about in that picture is how proud I am of Jack for losing all that weight that he did in the 6th and 7th seasons, kudos on him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eye candy is a pretty stupid term. And using the word porn to mean "a smorgasbord of x thing" such as food"porn" is just as stupid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 06:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It bothers me because it shows the underlying stinted vocabulary of the population, and the fact that reddit embraces it by calling their subs "foodporn" or "shoeporn" or whatever only encourages poor vocabulary and lack of variety in being able to express oneself through words using the English language.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god she's so flat chested... I literally love her. Does she do creampie scenes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this an old photo or did she lose the weight she has put on recently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone deserves to be treated equally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get where you're coming from. Although, You'd be surprised what kids would like. There's a working theory that kids like to be scared. There were a couple of episodes of gargoyles that absolutely terrified me as a kid (which I laugh at now in hindsight) but my eyes were always glued to the screen, not wanting to miss a moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the 80s to 90s was the best time for disney channel with shows like ducktales, gooftroop , darkwing duck, and all those quality programming. It was the perfect time to be a kid watching TV. 

It should have been as popular as my other childhood cartoon show, batman the animated series, which had the popularity it deserved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen ac 3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why wasn't Disney's Gargoyles more popular? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That show was my childhood, I simply devoured the stories of the gargoyles, and Goliath's voice gives me goosebumps every time. I also loved Elisa Maza.

Had so many of the toys and action figures, some when the gargoyles were in stone form, others where they were in regular form. 

I particularly found it cool when in school we started learning about Shakespeare plays and I realized where names like Demona or Puck came from.  

But when I joined the internet I found out this show struggled with the ratings? It's not fair. This show should have been watched by all, it is amazing.

Any memories you have concerning gargoyles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 days 'til the fist of Iron Fist, get hyped! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does ultra HD seem to have a... very faint, blueish tinge to it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 10:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's just the lighting in the store or the fact that they were showing off HD with an ice sequel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 10:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check my my post a few scrolls up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 07:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not asking for billboards but... do you really not feel like the text size is incredibly small? It feels like you need to be someone inches away, eyes glued to the screen, to be able to read it. And it's always been said that sitting to close to the tv is bad for your eyes... whether true or not, I myself like to sit at a comfortable distance away. But even when it's only a meter away it's still tiny, like the ac 3 example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeez how do so many gamers put up with that, even if they aren't interested in reading ingame manuals and databases and the like. 

But hey if it's true that ps4 actually has a zoom feature for every single game then that's a huge positive! Honestly I'll take it   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful, thank you so much. Sir robin truly is a great man who bravely ran away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it not possible for font to be bigger... *and* at high resolution? In menus there's so much damn unused space and yet the blurb or item description occupies a tiny tiny bit of the screen while the rest of the screen is just wasted space. It's utterly unfathomable how this is accepted practice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Day At the Races and My Jiggly Ball are some of the best episodes of television so I don't know what to tell you man. My Day at The Races is particularly inspiring on a personal level for me because I remember watching that episode as a teenager and thinking "by the time I hit 30 I hope to have accomplished plenty myself" as well as of course, be fit enough to run a triathlon. 

There is of course, a clear noticeable difference between the first 3 seasons, and then season 4, season 5, and onwards. In the beginning while the show still had a lot of quirky moments it still had a lot of... dark stuff. But by season 4 it really becomes lighthearted, a change that's mostly marked by the fact that Jordan lightens up considerably and acts just as goofy as the rest of the cast, when in season 1 she was the antagonist and "typical ice queen bitchy character" type person. 

Then season 5 happens and it's even lighter, but still has a lot of emotional moments. As a matter of fact I think some of the emotional moments hit even harder because of it (like the Dr Kelso episode where the song Sideways plays)

Season 6 is where the drop in quality happens, but since I love the show so much I don't even care, because it still has some great moments. But just throwing it out there. Season 7 they try to bring it back to form but also simultaneously suffered from the writer's strike, and finally we have season 8 which sweetly wraps all the old cast's lives in a nice bow even if they wasted way too many episodes and scenes of episodes on the new interns, which is even more infuriating when you realize they didn't even bother using said interns for the spin-off! So basically they wasted season 8 and our time with those new interns for no reason. But ah well no biggie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This conversation is over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, Scrubs has *always* changed character personalities on a whim to suit the joke or story arc, like having JD be the homophobic one in season 2's beginning and Turk being cool with it, but then Turk being the homophobic one instead throughout the rest of the series, then Carla being one way in an episode, Elliot being etc etc

Like most people that watched the episode I just kind of adopted the it's always sunny gang's way of thinking and said to myself "just move past it" in favor of getting to the good part of the bahamas wedding episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, they did drop the Turk being religious thing pretty quickly once they decided to only have Nurse Roberts be christiany type one of the hospital gang. 

I do see him occasionally wearing the t necklace in post season 1 episodes, but otherwise they kinda didn't bother with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have a gif/video of Turk/JD saying "my head hurts" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in season 4 episode 21 my lips are sealed where carla is talking about how she can know how to trust turk telling her she can trust him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do people say that? Very strange, I don't know if there's something topsy turvy going on with my tvs, but when the games like Red Dead run at less that 720p resolution, the font is actually bigger, not smaller as you say. 

Well not bigger, more like... wider? Like the screen is stretched. While a 720p and higher resolution makes everything... sharper true, but also smaller to fit everything onto the screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A shed type thing similar to what my neighbors use for their chickens might be a good idea to house the rabbits in? 

As for digging I really doubt it, we don't really have that kind of land... I'd definitely say the ground is hard, I mean we have to ship in the dirt/soil from someplace else just to be able to grow something! Date trees are the only thing that survive due to you know, being part of the desert climate and all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *googles* ohhh that stupid contraption. Yeah not a fan either. But of course I'm not gonna see it often compared to traditional cigs due to its high price. Wish that if cigs weren't illegal, they'd at least be 20 times the cost they currently are to dissuade at least some percent of the population to not buy it... then again with some addictive goods, price is never an issue so I doubt it would matter... Ah well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh cool. I'd like to visit Australia some day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm... we don't have any of those predators (though I've always wanted to see a real owl in the wild! Love their hoot hooting) and our garden is definitely fenced... well not fenced so much as brick walled. Hmm how to explain it... here in the arab word, how most houses in a neighborhood or cul-de-sac work is that each house is next to each other but separated by a brick wall type perimeter on three sides (back of house, right of house, left of house) so that it is inaccessible unless you enter from the front of the house, and the garden in question is at the back of the house. which is surrounded by these walls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely not a glasses issue (I myself was recently given an eye test among others for a new job health checkup assessment and passed with flying colors). All it takes is seeing a game from gen 6 or previous gens with their large font to compare and contrast and realize that there is *definitely* something up with gen 7 games and their tiny font, and it doesn't look like gen 8 is faring any better (but rather worse, if possible) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I see it, you can have your vices as everyone does, as long as it does not intrude on someone else's life, on their very health. And smoking does that. I don't care if someone drinks too much soda or goes drag racing in the desert. But smoking is something that impedes my ability to simply breathe without having that horrible smell literally enter my nose and mouth while I'm talking.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much what I say when I wake up everyday here in the middle east. The fact of the matter is smoking isn't viewed as a problem compared to other things (things that the west practices every day and finds normal) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides the possibility of alley cats, there aren't really any predators to rabbits here, although extreme temperatures (that being, heat) could be bad if shade and plenty of water isn't enough. 

Not really worried about crop destroying or garden feasting since we just have palm trees with dates and doubtful a rabbit could climb a tall tree to get said dates (plus we have more than enough to go around)

I'll check out some posts here as I'm interested in what kind stories people have to tell about rabbit care here, as a first time visitor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arabia, so that's what we call it, "" based on the english word saloon (since the british empire occupied the middle east for a pretty long while in the region's history) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I... I *am* in Human Resources V___V . That's the department I'm talking about v_v </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you're still lucky because it's just one person. Now imagine living in an ENTIRE society of smokers, where 10 people on this floor alone, are all smokers, 2 whose cubicles are next to yours, and they do what yours did... 

I literally equate it with feeling trapped hehe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I see. Anyway appreciate the quick and detailed response! I've been checking out some literature now. For a while I've been perusing the pet food section of the grocery store, talking with my friend about what he used to feed his rabbits, and that sort of thing. I don't want to necessarily keep the rabbits caged all the time, I just would enjoy seeing them whenever I stroll through the garden, just roaming around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or rather, it's just that they need a vice to engage in since alcohol and drugs are prohibited, unlike in the west. At least from what I noticed. But education is also needed, for **soo** many things. 

Sucks about your parents, sorry that not one but *both* were smokers, that's just unfathomable. I remember when I found out that my dad was actually a smoker in his youth (quit by the time he married and had us) and was utterly shocked, namely because he is a doctor, and when I'd complain about the presence of smoking in this culture and how it could lead to lung cancer, he'd just go "naahh you're just overblowing the issue" which left me incredulous at such a response. 

Oh well what can you do. Most just don't want to hear the lecture, and I'm not interested in lecturing them. I just don't want to breathe it in, that's all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, no amount of perfume can cover the smell. What's particularly bad is when the smell of perfume combines with something like BO or cig smoke to make this superfunk that's just too awful to breathe in, and god help you if there's no window to crack open or at least SOME kind of ventilation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true, you read my thoughts exactly. 

What I also wish is that this particularl region of the world (mideast) could notice the hypocrisy of repressing people in everything from clothing to public display of affection, but smoking and sheesha and killing our kids with second hand (sometimes even firsthand) smoke is perfectly ok and not worth enforcing any law over.

Just frustrating you know? And it feels lonely to be in the minority in feeling this way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worse part is, and what smokers don't realize, is that no matter how much cologne and perfume and air freshner you spray, that underlying, horrible smell of smoke is still there, and way worse because it's like the high pitched whistle that bothers your ears but too soft to pinpoint, only applied to your nose and smell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What health and behavior reasons if I may ask? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm wondering what's up with the downvotes, but I have been wondering this with nearly every topic I make on the reddit website that's not a vapid newstory about x y z happening.

I mean look at all that unused space! It's insane how there are so few complaints about it by gamers.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, that sucks. Diesel fumes are pretty bad too... but at least they're on the street. I can't even go for a walk on my jogging route without someone passing by and smoking. 

It's why I love nature so much and traveling to europe (or usa) and just roaming around the mountains, breathing in as much greenery as possible. It just totally elates my mood, makes me feel constantly happy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want a pet rabbit/bunny to have roam around our garden, but everyone tells me that they bring rodents and/or disease? Is that true? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always loved rabbits and would love to have some as a pet. But I was told that they will attract other types of rodents like mice and rats into our house, or bring diseases of their own, and I need to know if that is true. 

In fact I'd like to know as much about rabbits and rabbit care as possible, and more importantly personal anecdotes and stories from people on here about your experiences with them, in any context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And taste permanently...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't know. As a compare and contrast, I go back to play old games from the snes, n64 and ps1 era on that very same tv and while they're all pixelated as hell, they still have text that's way more readable than in HD games of post gen 7 because the font is so huge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean, with an HDMI cable? Yes. But let me ask you a question, how far do people typically sit away from the tv when playing a console game? Because from the lack of complaints, I get the impression that some gamers have a chair that they prop up just inches away from the TV while I like to sit a good few meters away, especially with a large tv in the living room type setup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't need to, we have them here... developing world is a whole different world. Which is annoying because at least in america, smoking has a bad rap and it's banned in workplaces/restaurants/malls and that law is *enforced*, but in developing countries smoking is still perfectly ok and done everywhere. I actually am considering walking around in a gas mask. Rather be ridiculed and get looks on the street than spend one more day of one more year of my life breathing into my shirt to try and avoid that horrible, horrible stink of cigarattes and whatnot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But... my TV *is* an HDtv and I have this problem. As a matter of fact when I switch resolution from 16:9 back to 4:3 that's when the font gets bigger. Well not so much bigger as... wider. When I shift to 16:9 everything becomes smaller so that more of it fits the screen and I'm like, I don't need to see everything all at once game companies!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When BO is really bad, you can definitely smell it...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're glad? I'm ecstatic! I was getting really annoyed with the trolls on the forums of the websites gamespot and gamefaqs consistently denying the font of ps3 (and I assume, 360) games are small, when they absolutely are. I remember trying to read the subtitles while playing this game called Red Dead Redemption and just throwing my hands in the air out of frustration. 

Another one is Assassin's Creed 3, a game with a huge database but Ubisoft almost seems to be saying "fuck you, don't read this" because not only is the text absolutely minuscule, but the screen actually has near epilepsy causing lightning-esque flashes constantly to simulate the Animus loading screen look. Every time you open the menu. Every time. 

For the life of me, I cannot understand how this isn't something that's brought up more. Really feel vindicated in finally finding others who share the same viewpoint concerning this issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet they still roll the windows down when smoking in the car (forcing me to roll my windows ***up*** to avoid inhaling that awful snell) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who "have their shit together" wouldn't be posting on an internet website... they're out with friends, making a family, having a life... I mean all the people I know who actually have friends, a social life, a girlfriend, a husband, a child, a bunch of friends, weekend plans... they wouldn't have even heard of something called a "reddit" much less posted it on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do smokers handle that smell 24/7? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does no one else find the font in games since gen 7 incredibly small? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AKA the "HD" gen? It seems in an effort to squeeze as much of the  game's graphics onto the screen as possible, the post gen 6 games seem obsessed with making the font (either for subtitles, or in-game database) incredibly small, and for the life of me I can't understand it or understand how no one has mentioned it. 

I mean the font is noticeably small. I sit about 4-5 meters away from the tv, a 65 inch one. I don't know what everyone else's setup is with console games, but there's definitely a difference between the font of a snes game or ps2 game, and then a ps3 game. 

It's one of those things in video games that I wonder why no one mentions, as someone who personally enjoys reading, especially in-game databases of various types of games, from rpg to action adventure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does no one else find the font in games since gen 7 incredibly small? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AKA the "HD" gen? It seems in an effort to squeeze as much of the  game's graphics onto the screen as possible, the post gen 6 games seem obsessed with making the font (either for subtitles, or in-game database) incredibly small, and for the life of me I can't understand it or understand how no one has mentioned it. 

I mean the font is noticeably small. I sit about 4-5 meters away from the tv, a 65 inch one. I don't know what everyone else's setup is with console games, but there's definitely a difference between the font of a snes game or ps2 game, and then a ps3 game. 

It's one of those things in video games that I wonder why no one mentions, as someone who personally enjoys reading, especially in-game databases of various types of games, from rpg to action adventure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was TNBA though, not BTAS... same universe, and a direct continuation true, but different enough to make mention of. What I particularly like about that episode is them making fun of batnipples joel shoemaker (the guy who ruined batman enough to spur the creation of batman begins)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been reading The Batman Adventures (Batman: The Animated Series set of comics) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty much everything I ever wanted from a comic book but never found; great art and colors matching the cartoon show exactly, with the same writing, lighthearted at times, heartfelt at others, just great all around.

I definitely recommend them. I'm usually not into comics but I love BTAS so much that I knew I would like the comics as they're pretty much like reading a story panel for an episode of BTAS but in comic form. They have some characters that weren't in the show, some sillier than others (the perfessor, mr nice and mastermind, who are kinda 3 stoogesish but still have their moments of funny) and others have stories that pick up where the show left off. 

Definitely would like to talk about them with anyone who has read them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, say "words" with an s sound instead of a z. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is the letter s so difficult to say at the end of the word compared to at the beginning or middle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Wish the people itt would realize that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 09:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anecdotal evidence is the best kind of evidence isn't it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's another thing I forgot to mention and wanted to, also great. I like to think it started out as classic Winston and Cece messarounds, and then evolved into actual friendship and now close sisters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So overall... RX it is? 

I already had that in mind, just wanted to read people's confirmation on that choice since this GX model only recently started appearing (especially with ads on tv) so I was curious before I made my decision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mideast

digital marketing and content marketing is still only a theory that hasn't been applied for businesses. I've been trying to spearhead it to make a name for myself (for example, the company I finally went to didn't have any social media presence and I suggested for them to at the very least have a facebook and twitter account. Just *something* to start them out and actually post in it, not make it and leave it dead, a classic mistake that I've seen often) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a fan of a saloon car (or sedan as I learn you americans call it) so I always liked the RX for being pretty big size. I did go ahead and check some of the 2016+ models but they seem to have gotten... smaller since my car's days. Not a fan of that, I like it big. 

As for driving while I don't really go driving in the desert often, it's nice to have just in case I do since other people use the car to go to the chalet and stuff. I just like a bigger car for comfort but not too big that parking is a hassle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Price isn't relevant since I live in the middle east not where you live, however I simply wanted to ask your thoughts on the LX, just out of curiosity feature-wise, not necessarily as a substitute to the RX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don Draper was in advertising. Marketing is not advertising, a common misconception. 

But I agree concerning nearly everyone in this topic being extremely defensive and giving my posts those thumbs down arrow things instead of acting like human beings.

It's funny you mention Don Draper though, as someone who watched Mad Men I like to tell people I chose my major because of the show (not true but just something I say to get people to watch the stellar show) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 14:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's from season 2 episode 4 when Luci, Dan and Ameni are going to a sex party mansion type deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 14:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, *I'd* be worried about you saying sales and marketing are different when they're closely related and must have full constant coordination between the two in any company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
