<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2667</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 07:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eastern Europe, I knew they were making racist chants before reading the title of this pic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scene that follows is even funnier, please watch the movie if ou havent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> some one should do the superhero landing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A black guy asked to give up his seat gives an on point response. [Long] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6Lack - prblms [Hip Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 17:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How fluent are you now at speaking and understanding french </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that's more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oxford university was founded by the Aztec empire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking racists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did he say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, thank's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those quirky videos titled
"we need to talk"
"I am sorry"
"I almost got mugged"

Fuck off! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat a dead mouse whole!! From its feet to its head. I almost puked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pussy is pussy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walking away by Craig David and  you were the last high by the dandy warhols </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Penny dreadful and the last kingdom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haile Selassie's speech to the league of Nations.  They stood by and watched when Italy invaded Ethiopia and issued a toothless weapon's embargo on both Italy and Ethiopia which only affected Ethiopia; because italy already had an arm's industry. Haile Selassie went to the league and made a speech that earned him Times man of the year and a legendary status among world leaders  when he spoke the prophetic words "...today it is us, tomorrow it will be you" among a chorus of cheers and a few boo's from Italian representatives. And surely enough, Hitler invaded Poland shortly after, exploiting the league's appeasement policy- with the knowledge that the league was powerless to prevent it and started the second world war. 

Full speech
http://astro.temple.edu/~rimmerma/appeal_to_the_league_of_nations_.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 10:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok whitey. why don't you go  burn a cross or put a white sheet over your head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Movie director </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah fuck the critics the sequel was just as good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interstellar, passengers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a good mom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 14:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black lives matter is not an organization but a movement. It doesn't have a leader or any hierarchial structure, so it's not right to attribute the claim of a single individual to the entire movement. 
Just a thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wikepedia says the budget was 250 mil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 09:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what a dumb thing to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you lucky bastard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aged like wine. Beautiful woman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she is cute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 10:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i must have skipped it. But they are filming black panther and infinity war simultaneously so I don't know how they are going to fit it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 08:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but he is already in the marvel universe in X men days of future past </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 08:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is black panther going to be in infinity war? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 08:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so black panther wont be in there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 05:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is black panther going to be in Infinity war? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just watched an early screening for " A cure for wellness" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 12:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> impractical jokers, Nathan for you, The office  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is the link to her page? I also live in LA. If you really want to piss her off download  a free text app on your phone and set up a fake appointment reinstall app with different number and do it again. But as you said you were the sucker in this story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that'll do piggy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/imgoingtohellforthis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just got around to watch "Allied"- A well made and nostalgic rendering of Bogart's "Casablanca" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 07:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to this film with low expectations as I had read some lukewarm reviews that now, after my actual viewing experience, now seem like sour-grapes. This is an excellent film that is very much worth watching.

The war film genre, especially the ww2 war film genre, is not filled with a high proportion of truly great films - most descend to low brow action, jingoism and gratuitous content where any kind of thoughtful investigation of the characters' personalities, motivations et c. are left out.

Here is a film with an uncharacteristically low key, subtle and relatively flat content and plot line as we watch the characters interacting as time passes - we are presented with repeated scenes of Marianne (Cotillard) and Max (Pitt) talking, smoking, making love, making war and hanging out domestically - the result is we get a rather detailed insight into how these two live through what they are going through (not a typical war film agenda). The acting is impeccable, the script excellent and the production values very well done.

Robert Zemeckis has helmed a film that is in every respect worthy of his formidable talent and illustrious filmography. With him in the director's chair, Allied's great production values were more or less expected. The film offers beautiful costuming inspired by Casablanca and Now, Voyager, exhilarating and suspenseful action scenes helped by a humanized protagonist  and a very well-told, poignant story of happiness despite a world gone mad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is third world level of point blank blatant corruption right here, and I'm pretty sure it will be swept under a rug on the pretense of lobbying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use water to clean my bum so I don't have to worrry about that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing that Ethiopia was already embroiled with internal affairs of sucession, The Egyptians under the Ottoman empire invaded Ethiopia in thier conquest to create an empire in East Africa, though they were heavily armed especially In comparison to the Ethiopian army and had launching  pads in all four countries that neighboured Ethiopia, they under estimated the national fervor and unity  of the locals when they were under foreign attack, and were also held at a geographical a disadvantage. The entire Egyptian army was decimated and the khedive had to retreat, his son raised an army few years later and attacked in a feat of revenge, he too was defeated and Ottoman ambitions in eastern Africa were crushed. But the Europeans arrived a few years later and Italy had to learn the same lesson again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did he do  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is "Passengers" the "2001 A Space Odyssey" of our time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 11:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The comparison is  merited not because they are both space adventures but because both were grossly underrated at the time of release. Movie critics and goers alike walked out of  2001 ASO when it was first screened but today it is regarded as  one of the hallmarks on cinema. Passengers has a  1.4 score on Roger Ebert and 33% on Rotten Tomatoes, but I think it was one of the best movies on 2016 and definitely on of the best of its genre. The acting was great, pacing was good and never boring,the action sequence and the visuals were amazing as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cure for Bilharzia. The cure is a subtropical fruit called Endod in Amharic. It was only discovered  by accident in the 80's by an Ethiopian biologist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he is in the new black panther too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ya, we are thinking the same thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that'll do piggy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marvel's Black Panther is hiring Asians bartender and more extras </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like this mellow cover of "I feel it coming" than the hard bass original. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 07:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 04:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moana was my favorite disney movie of all time and my favorite movie of 2016.





















 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R rated or not, dont bring your kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R rated or not, dont bring your kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I havesnt even finished watching it the first time, not my cup of tea I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mummy. God knows how many times I have watched that movie.

Also,
Snatch
Bourne Trilogy
Man from UNCLE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Space song and blue bird by Beach House </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wire - The Story of the Ring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> indie movie I saw, I think it came out in 2010's maybe 2014. I cant quite remember the plot. But it was about this guy , I think he checked into a hotel and notices this rich young girl in a swimming pool who liked him. afterwards he along with her and her friends gathered for a drink and later he told her he has a wife and she told him she doesn't care who he goes out with as long as he is with her. I am sure there is a lot to the story and I just wrote a whole lot of blubber but that is all I remember. Me and my friends were talking about it but for the life of me I cant remember the title or anything about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They really should have included the Mirror Scene from Contact. 20 years on and its still the best camera movement no director has ever replicated since.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZD0_5HFMPIg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am always exited when I see a cinefix upload in my sub list </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Likewise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure this is a Repost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lighting in their face is off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a bunch of sad loosers. This makes me Mad to be a liberal. A country that sends athiests and "witches" to the chopping board, that tolerates rape and sexual assaults on citizens and Westerners alike. Which persecutes Christians and bank role hard line salafism in the world,  with majority of its citizens ill-opinionated against every thing "Western" . Why don't we all give them a standing ovation, you think they give 2 shits about you if you end up in thier jail because you were caught with a boose or showed to much skin ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammmn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another fun Fact slavery wasn't banned in Britain until 2010. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone should shop him into Hansel and Gretel and make him the witch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC- Niccolo Machiavelli (2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Not True"- Woman Admits She Made Up Claims that Led to Emmett Till's Brutal Lynching </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Rules: Stop Apologizing- Bill Maher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 10:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2013 it was reported that Israel was sterlilizing Ethiopian Jews by the thousands telling them it was a vaccine instead. Sad irony

Source- http://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/israel-admits-ethiopian-women-were-given-birth-control-shots.premium-1.496519

http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/israel-gave-birth-control-to-ethiopian-jews-without-their-consent-8468800.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a baggage of the Bush administration. America was in a recession when he entered office.  Obama helped America out of the recession. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joaquin was robbed of his Oscar for his performance in "Master". I honestly haven't watched a performance as compelling as his before or since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain the Ending of La La Land </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 06:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone explain the ending of La La Land </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 06:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 06:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sadly no :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 05:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well it wasnt me, but tnx anyways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> joke is getting old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][Movies]Indie Movie that came out in the early 2010's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> indie movie I saw, I think it came out in 2010's maybe 2014. I cant quite remember the plot. But it was about this guy , I think he checked into a hotel and notices this rich young girl in a swimming pool who liked him. afterwards he along with her and her friends gathered for a drink and later he told her he has a wife and she told him she doesn't care who he goes out with as long as he is with her. I am sure there is a lot to the story and I just wrote a whole lot of blubber but that is all I remember. Me and my friends were talking about it but for the life of me I cant remember the title or anything about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alright I'll give it a shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy getting shot Infront of my eyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A proper Viking funeral </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone should give Penny dreadful a shot. Eva Green is enough of a reason, but if you are looking for more, the story is good , the script is brilliantly written and the cinematography is top notch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just started watching Netflix's "Love" very funny series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you live  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mel better win this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seeking help to find a reasonable/cheapest car insurance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a 22 years old college student in Florida, I have had my licence since 2015 but this will be my first time buying a car. I am thinking about buying a used car with a couple of miles on it and I am looking for a bare minimum car insurance that a college student can afford. 
Thank you in advance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Effective use of Colors in Movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump supporters react to a person of color at inauguration. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least they said thank you for your cooperation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 22:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually the movie I am anxiously waiting for in 2017. God knows I would watch a forklift manual directed by Guy Richie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tnx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tnx  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT]Name of CLassical song here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/6i9cKgdBUfA?t=607 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frontline -Divided States of America II (2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frontline- Divided States of America I (2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PBS Frontline - Divided States of America I (2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 01:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fergie from black eyed peas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sort by controvertial </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/nottheonion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trollhunters, American Dad, Rick and Morty, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you lower your standards you can buy a girl for 50-60 bucks too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if you are a straight gal or a gay dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wash my butt with water and make sure it's squecky clean. Not only is that hygienic and sanitary but it also feels good.

Edit- Apparently some people are not getting it. I mean  After taking a shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a nsfw euphemism I don't know about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 11:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get upset when others do it too, but its perfectly fine with me for cinefix to throw out any hyperbole cliches. Those guys know thier craft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 00:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya, the bbc link is in my Edit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 00:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> check out my Edit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC- Inside Obama's White House : Obama Care (2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That a Jordy accent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you wipe your ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't they just ask 2 chainz to perform....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 69 haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it go away if you hold your shit in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like on the vj or everywhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold up let me just bookmark that right quick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you a dude and secondly are you a citizen of the Soviet Union?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other being... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The time he barged in on the Chinese and indian prime minister and other BRICS members secret meeting during a climate change summit in 2009 and was like are you guys going to make a deal or what. That was the most gangster shit I have ever seen.

It would be great if some one posted a video source. Since I am on my pgone. I saw it on a BBC documentary called inside Obama's Whitehouse

**Edit- Here is the link below albeit a bit flumsy, watch till the End**

https://youtu.be/jefb_THcty4?t=2489 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Vikings wash/ clean themselves from the same Bowl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 12:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This  has been referenced in many  movies and TV sows and I wanted to know if there is truth in this somewhere

13th warrior
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3XoTXuPjzpE

Also feutured in Tonights episode of Vikings and other Viking Movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The way of the Flesh by Adam Curtis follows the story of the special cells cultivated from Henriettta Lacks post mortem and how things soon grew out of control. BBC (1998) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chill Bump - The Memo [Hip Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 10:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is it canceled?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Gadget man with Richard Ayodade still on air? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 03:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Travel man and Gadget man are one of my favorite shows to watch. What network and time is it on if its still on air? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok tough guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 15:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *wind and solar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coal-loving Wyoming legislators are pushing a bill to outlaw wind and power. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 14:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 09:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> loool , this shit is funny man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 07:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes it is! tnx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [Song]Always sunny in Phili clasical song pplaying in the back ground </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XCfe7xAvbD8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 00:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many fans of the genre including my self that believe that many of the horror movies today resort to  cheap jump scares than concentrating  on  plot development and camera style. What is your take on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 09:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when is that exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> roast master </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Okay, if my fiance Kim is a hobbit, then how come it uh how c- then, okay, if she's a hobbit, then how come she don't live in a hole in the ground? BOOOOOOM! All y'all just got lit up, cuz!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait so we they for or against Russia? This whole debucle looks like an episode taken from Rick and Morty. Very confusing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Endless sex on deck, now thats a life hack. But many of them check it it's fake so that won't prolly work.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 09:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SHM its you're </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 09:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the show has ended incase you didnt know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Penny dreadful brilliant depiction of the supernatural in this scene where Vanessa meets the "Cut-Wife" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Penny Dreadful || the Nightcomers attack Vanessa and the team || </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Penny Dreadful || the Nightcomers ll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Penny Dreadful | 'An Ancient Language' l "Mischief is best enacted in small groups at very close quarters." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Penny Dreadful | The Wolf of God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Penny Dreadful |"Seance"| Autopsy of a Scene [Eva Green was twice snubbed an Emmy for her Sensational Performance as Vanessa Ives] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Penny Dreadful - The Nightcomers Scene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haile Selassie's motorcade ride with JFK- 1963 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember this from a previous reddit post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> African slaves taken to the Americas  almost entirely come from western Africa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 10:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ethiopians are mostly light skinned and were never colonized or enslaved. Roast aside just some facts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jimmy Fallon Open Theme For Golden Globes 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 07:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
