<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2561</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find your card on rankt. There will be a link on the page to the corresponding reddit thread. Go to the reddit thread and post your link there. 

Note that there are minimum karma requirements for posting to the referral threads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the Hamilton LA tickets went on sale last week, there were several DPs of people having success through the concierge. You should also simultaneously try to buy the tickets through Ticketmaster/AXS with the Amex presale to maximize your chances </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delta did the same thing on our flight this weekend. 30K skymiles for the Delta Gold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll make a change to the Plastiq guide I wrote over the weekend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting - what link did you go to generate a normal plat referral from the ameriprise? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Are there any referrals for it that I could use to give back to this community? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pulled up the Amex Ameriprise Platinum card and it looks like there is no lifetime language on it (with regard to the $0 introductory fee). Is this a known phenomenon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only for the specific card, so no self referrals unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just the ED and BCE showing up for me. Oh well, hope y'all have better luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Orleans takes down 1st of 4 Confederate statues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah gotcha, that's strange that they wouldn't allow it. I wonder if they've started cracking down with the influx of people starting to use it (I've been collecting DP's to update the FAQ thread on it).

Hope it all works out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bulk groceries and household goods. Normally I don't think its any better than going to a grocery store or Costco, but with these deals it makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey just following up to see if everything worked out for your SO with the FFDs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct, they are treated as debit cards on Venmo. However, be careful as Venmo will shutdown both your and your recipient's accounts if it suspects any strange activity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Got $25 back on $65 for Boxed.com on three of my cards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it can only be used at that store, then it won't count towards 5/24 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They certainly can be! I'd recommend reading some of the threads in the sidebar which can guide you to which cards might be best for your situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think any of those cards provide enough rewards to outweigh the 2.5% fee, unless you are close to a specific redemption and need to quickly get some points. 

Plastiq charges your card when they issue the check, thanks for mentioning that. I'll add it to the guide.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check your pending UR points, mine showed up there before the transaction posted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend signing up for the Amex Everyday card as well. It is a no annual fee credit card that's worth keeping long term because it stores your MR points. 

Unfortunately, the sign up offer isn't the best right now (historic high is 25K/$2k) but you can currently get 15K/$1k via referral.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get it on the full purchase price </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I log in to the Chase app on my phone, it has a banner up too which says "Get a Chase coupon", which then takes me to a page where I can request the $300/$200 banking coupon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Centurion cars gives Delta Platinum Medallion status. It'd be great even if the Amex plat gave Delta Silver status for the free bag  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First and foremost I'd use a card that you plan to keep long-term. When you close a card you lose the warranty protection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, added a link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers! Thanks, and I've edited the post with your image, and given you credit for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volkswagen ordered to pay $2.8B for cheating on diesel emissions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they should give you a statement when you get the referral because it counts as activity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep they will on your next statement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're trying to reach a minimum spend then it could be worth it. However, I'd recommend taking a look at Plastiq, which allows you to do much the same for a 2.5% fee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Guide to Plastiq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **What is Plastiq?**

Plastiq is a service which lets you pay "any bill" with your credit card for a fee. Essentially, you pay Plastiq with your card and they will cut a check to your recipient. This allows you to pay for things such as your rent or mortgage with a card even if your landlord / provider does not offer a pay with credit card option. The standard fee is 2.5%, though occasionally there are promotions (i.e. there was a 2% promo for Amex cards earlier this year).

**What does a Plastiq check look like?**

Kind of like a paper check!
In all seriousness, u/Lazy_Gremlin graciously uploaded a [photo of what the check looks like](http://m.imgur.com/GAZ66vx?r). It mentions you (the customer) and is addressed to your recipient. 


**How long does Plastiq take to send a payment?**

Generally, it takes 5-10 business days from the date you schedule the payment for your recipient to receive the check. However, whenever you schedule a payment, Plastiq gives you a date by which the recipient will get the check. It's always good to double check this and make sure you pay early enough so that you don't end up with any late payment fees from your landlord, etc. This is especially important if this is your first time paying a recipient.


**When does Plastiq charge your card?**

They charge it when they process your payment, which is when they'll send the check out. Your recipient won't get until a few days later. 


**Does paying through Plastiq count as a purchase or a cash advance?**

Based on our current knowledge, if you pay with an Amex, Mastercard, or Discover, your payment will process as a purchase. However, things get a little trickier with a Visa card. If Plastiq has a "prior relationship" with your payee, then your payment should go through as a purchase. A "prior relationship" means that you or someone else has sent a payment to that payee before. Thus, most of the big mortgage and rent companies are on there, but yours may not be.


But don't worry, if there's a risk of your payment being processed as a cash advance, Plastiq will let you know when you go to schedule your payment. If you get a warning, then DO NOT send the payment.


What should you do if you get the warning? The recommendation is to pay the recipient with another card (i.e. an Amex) first so as to establish a relationship with them. Then, for your second payment onwards, you can pay with your Visa. Just to be safe, you can ask your credit card bank to reduce your cash advance limit so that if Plastiq tries to process your payment as a cash advance, it will get rejected.

**Can I use Plastiq to meet minimum spend requirements?**

Yes you can, and it is a great way if you do not wish to do manufactured spending. While there have been discussions about Plastiq being considered a "cash equivalent", it has thus far been safe to use (no clawback of points) and in fact was promoted as part of Amex's Shop Small last December.

**Can I pay myself or a family member / friend?**

Perhaps you have a roommate who pays the rent and you usually just send them a check. Or you are paying back a friend for a trip you took with them. Though there is nothing stopping you from doing this, be warned that Plastiq may ask you to submit an invoice / contract / lease as proof. You should be fine as long as you can justify it to them.


**Can I pay my credit card statement with Plastiq?**

No you cannot.


**What are these fee-free dollars (FFDs)?**

Fee-free dollars are Plastiq's form of bonuses. While you are normally charged a 2.5% fee on any transaction, you can redeem FFDs to negate this fee. So, for example, on a $500 payment you would normally be charged a $12.50 fee. However, if you had 500 FFDs, you could use those to negate that fee. 

UPDATED: Currently, you can earn **500 FFDs** by [using someone's referral link](https://rankt.com/r/churning/referrals/plastiq/) to sign up for Plastiq AND making a payment of **$500** or more (so you can use the FFDs starting on your second payment).

If you refer someone to Plastiq, you will earn 1,000 FFDs (as of 4/24/17). Thanks to u/zackiv31 and u/ruxpin810 for this update.


**What is the deal with earning 3x on Plastiq payments?**

As of mid-April 2017, it appears that if you are paying rent or mortgage via Plastiq, it is coding on Visa cards as "travel", earning higher rewards points on cards such as the Chase Sapphire Reserve (3x) and the Chase Ink Preferred (3x). Since you earn 3x UR points per dollar and are paying a 2.5% fee, you can earn a net positive of 0.5% if you redeem UR points for statement credit or even higher if you redeem for travel. It is unknown how long this will last. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you go to schedule a payment on Plastiq, they will give you a guaranteed date by which the check will arrive. It should get there by 5/1/17 if set it to send out today. Because you're using an Amex, you don't have to worry about it being processed as a cash advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For my mortgage company, I had autowithdrawal set up from a checking account. I turned that off before starting with Plastiq and I'd recommend doing that so you don't accidentally get two payments taken out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The BRG from Amex is also good for advertising with 3x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I send the whole payment and haven't had any issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who made their first payment on Plastiq on Tuesday, did you get the double FFD bonus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep as long as they're available, you'll be put into the upgrade queue 5 days before the flight as a Platinum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing we have four MARTA lines for the railroads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that this is the best longterm play, but I'm not sure if you'd be able to merge MR accounts if you get approved today for the ED. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why's that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Oh! But I don't need the crickets. I just need to make the 
purchases.
/silence between the two/


 Exactly.
/extended silence/

username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Net neutrality protestors just Rickrolled the FCCs monthly meeting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should be no issue, since the mortgage company will usually send a tax form at the end of the year with the breakdown of interest and principal payments. I would suspect from the mortgage company's point of view, there's no difference whether you pay with Plastiq or via normal methods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend transferring them to SPG (10K), since that would give you the most flexibility down the road should you decide to use them for flights or hotels, rather than committing to a specific airline or hotel now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people haven't had any luck this month. What are you looking for specifically? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just the one GE credit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [T]wo well-placed sources confirmed to CNNMoney that O'Reilly does have a parachute. That's because O'Reilly signed a new contract right before being ousted.
The two sources, who spoke independently of one another, said the new contract was worth about $25 million per year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sources: Fox News payout to Bill O'Reilly will be tens of millions of dollars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep they're separate products and you can still get both bonuses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did the CSP start referrals?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll be fine using Plastiq to meet spend requirements </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple promises to stop mining minerals to make iPhones  it just isnt sure how yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend sticking with a visa card since it's much more widely accepted than amex.

Here are some recommendations from NerdWallet: https://www.nerdwallet.com/blog/top-credit-cards/no-foreign-transaction-fee-credit-card/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't think so as long as you don't need a visa to go there (i.e. if you're not a US citizen or traveling in and out of the Schengen zone) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nov 22nd. Not sure yet if I'll be able to make it but if we can't, I'll let you know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah thanks. Looks like some people are already selling on StubHub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I bought tickets and then wasn't able to make that show, are Amex presale tickets able to be sold back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Delta Platinum is the sweet spot as far as Delta cards go if you will ever be traveling with someone. Though you don't get the annual fee waived, in addition to the free checked bag you also get 1 companion certificate at renewal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I was able to see some of the orchestra seats via my phone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No luck for me either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's of a priest handing out Easter eggs at the launch pad today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's no risk in doing it the same day, but make sure you're approved for the Plat first. As others have said though, there is no need to do it on the same day.

edit: Also, remember to download and save the cardmember agreement on your application, in case any issues come up in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After delays due to rocket problems, next space station crew set to launch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once got a parking ticket on cloud nine. Park Cloud Nine is almost as aggressive as Park Atlanta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the facebook post he made: https://www.facebook.com/JasonChaffetz1/posts/10158423022140234 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alphabet will track health data of 10,000 volunteers to 'create a map of human health' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :)

Hmm, hopefully it'll still apply the 400 FFDs. They did say that even if parts of their website showed the wrong amount, they would honor the doubled values. And yep, it should be okay no matter whom you pay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Purrime shipping </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep it's usually pretty quick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that should work. While you have a Delta Amex open, you can redeem blocks of 5000 points for $50 off the ticket price, and pay the rest in cash. Skymiles will usually post to your Delta account within a couple business days of meeting the minimum spend. 

You can also get the $50 statement credit for buying a gift card on Delta.com and then using that for part of the payment as well. 

Also, if you go via a referral on Rankt.com, the bonus is 40K after $1k spend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's one day after they send their first payment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For everyone who referred someone to Plastiq and now sees "Not Eligible" in their referral list: this is normal.

The "Not Eligible" is a poorly worded design choice. From speaking with the Plastiq folks via chat this weekend, it means that person has already been referred to Plastiq by someone (in this case, you) and is not eligible to be sent another referral. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "Not Eligible" is a poorly worded choice on their part. It means that person has already been referred to Plastiq by someone (in this case, you) and is not eligible to be sent another referral. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, try the steps in this flowchart, you might be able to get approved: http://imgur.com/a/oXlPW

Personally I'd recommend holding out for the CSR because not only do you get the 3x UR points but the Priority Pass membership would definitely be helpful when traveling on long flights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah bummer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a net positive for sure. At worst, a UR is worth 1 cent if you redeem it for a statement credit so you'll come out at least $14 ahead. Of course, there are much better ways to redeem the UR points (travel, transfer to partners, etc.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a conservative-leaning newspaper publishing a story about GOP senators showing concern about the President's Mar-a-Lago visits, which makes it all the more interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Ernst says GOP members concerned about Trumps Florida visits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fyi i don't think you can pay a credit card via Plastiq, but you could maybe pay utilities or prepay your internet / cell phone bill with it. Good luck and post here if you run into any troubles! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get the 400 FFDs after you make your first payment of $20 or more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding the Everday card, I think in your case it would be worth it to get that and cancel the PRG. The current offer via referral for the ED is 15K MR / $1k spend, while the historic high (via incognito) is 25K MR / $2k spend. I think taking the 10K less now is better than paying the $195 AF (minus the airline credit if you can use those). It's also a good card to keep open long term so that you can always cancel other charge cards and keep your MRs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will usually work if the airline is in the UR portal, but definitely not otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep employed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The data points that people have been posting the past week suggest that the 3x only works for rent / mortgage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably someone who used your referral but hasn't made their first payment yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoke with a Plastiq rep about that this weekend. It means that those people have already used a referral link on sign up (probably yours) and thus are ineligible to be referred again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here, I'll swipe you an upvote :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on your goals. If you want to earn status, then PQD waiver is worth it (I am doing something similar with Delta). UR points will definitely get you more "bang for your buck", especially given the recent DPs that you may be able to get 3x UR points / $1 for rent on Plastiq. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11:59PM EDT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One awesome thing about booking via RR points is that they're fully refundable. If you find a cheaper fare on another airline between now and then, you can cancel the Southwest tickets. If Southwest has a cheaper redemption for RR miles for that itinerary, you can call and get the difference refunded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stipend of 28K, had no issues getting approved for a $10K credit limit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are trying to get in on the Plastiq promo that's ending today, remember that your first payment needs to be sent today. When sending it, select "Skip Scheduling and Pay Now" to try and get it in before the deadline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could try sending a check with Plastiq, though at a 2.5% fee it may not be worth the UR points.

Congrats on buying the engagement ring :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a good credit score and 1+ year of history, you can still get approved on a student salary (I'm a grad student and got it). If they deny you for insufficient income, you can recon and let them know you're starting a new job in the summer. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah that's a bummer. Do you know if they would let you add FFDs to payments you've scheduled? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Missed opportunity for a great slogan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems to be the same as previous polls conducted by Gallup. I think the more interesting thing is how little this has changed over the past few years, and yet this administration is full of decisions favoring the wealthy.

http://www.gallup.com/poll/1714/taxes.aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, that's a good point and in fact, the trend seems to hold over the past 25 years, looking at Gallup's historical polls.

http://www.gallup.com/poll/1714/taxes.aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe both Chase and Amex pull from Experian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome! Yes you should remove her as an AU first then refer her. You'd be eligible for the bonus 24 months after receiving the last one, so sometime in the next couple months. If you have your statements from 2015 you can see which statement had the points on there. 

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Majority Say Wealthy Americans, Corporations Taxed Too Little </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woops yes I meant your friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one caveat would be that you would lose purchase protection / extended warranty if you buy gift cards then purchase the laptop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can put employed and put your student stipend down as your income </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's usually 50 or 100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey sorry about my unhelpful comments, I misread that you were specifically looking at chase mortgages, not using a chase card to pay another mortgage. Hope you find your answer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad we have a banana for scale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hat trick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a thread a couple months ago about high advertising spend that you might find helpful:

https://www.reddit.com/r/churning/comments/5wlc7f/how_would_you_manage_ultra_high_spend_200k_monthly/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is, which is higher than the public 35K. It's not as high as the historic 70k from January, but if you have an upcoming need then I think it's worth it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a reminder that the [Plastiq double FFD](https://www.plastiq.com/blog/2017/03/promotion-earn-double-when-you-refer-friends/) promo ends tomorrow!

Here's the [Rankt referral page](https://rankt.com/r/churning/referrals/plastiq/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's also a new Amex offer today for $15 back on $50 at 1800Flowers, which can stack with those </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they sure dropped something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you pay with the Chase Amazon Prime Rewards Visa, you get an additional 5% back plus whatever you'd get from the cash back portals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
