<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4538</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 16:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost anything by The Neighborhood. Single and Crybaby are two of my favorite songs right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 16:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk, Froot is less vibrant I suppose, but it's got this sort of melodic, melancholy choir type thing going on, like in "Blue" and "I'm a Ruin". Electra heart was mostly all about female stereotypes and sex and society and all that, and I loved it at the time. But froot feels like a good departure from it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 16:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of this right here. And to make stuff easier OP, you don't have to work on all of these things at once. Pick one - say the hygiene thing - and then follow through with it for a full week. Then add to that, the week after, figure out what your bmi is and start counting calories a bit. Figure out your bmr and try not to eat much over that. Weigh yourself daily without clothing and chart your progress.

Start with the stuff that affects your physical appearance the most cuz that has the biggest effect on self-esteem. Then work your way on the other stuff. All the stuff that bugs you is 100% fixable, seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 23:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't think of a specific thing that got a lot of outrage, but I remember seeing something I was really surprised people *weren't* up in arms about. About two or three years ago, there was this askreddit thread about rapists, asking why they had done it and if they regretted it. The top upvoted comments were literally people confessing that they had raped someone and how it happened, and most of the responding comments were reassuring and forgiving them. It was kinda surreal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 21:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd cry happy tears if they made this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 04:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not offended at all - it's a good question, and I used to ask myself that a lot. At this point, I recognize that I'm the same person on or off medication. The main thing that changes when I'm on it is the tone of my thought process and my ability to get myself out of those black hole/pit/spiral of negative feelings that can sneak up on me.

Without meds, I guess you could say I am 100% myself - but I don't like being that, because that version of me is crippled. It can't stand on its own, it can't defend itself - and it has no will to do so. I'd rather be this version of me, altered with prozac in my body and brain, than the half-dead version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 00:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say so, yes. I've been on medication for about two years now. About a month ago I concluded, with the support of my doctor, that I was happy and stable enough to stop taking it. I tried over the past month to get off of it but - I can't do it. The difference in my mental state over the course of a few weeks was ridiculous. I went from having a mostly positive attitude on life to wanting to overdose. It's scary, the massive difference. If you can get your hands on the right medication and at the right dosage, you can feel completely different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 00:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I really just want to sleep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 23:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been in a bad mood for the past month. Like just alternating between want to break things and wanting to overdose. I keep overanalyzing and hating a bunch of aspects of myself. It sucks.

Coincidentally, I started a new job a little over a month ago, I stopped taking prozac because at the time I was feeling pretty good and it's such a tiny dose, and I stopped doing regular exercise.

I can see that it's mostly these three things that are making me feel way worse than normal, but all I want to do is sleep. It's easy to sleep. My boss just left a voicemail to call him back and I'm pretty sure it's to get me to pick up a shift tomorrow. Or sign a paper, not sure which. Probably both. 

I just feel like shit :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feeling pretty confused </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 20:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel extremely jittery and kinda angry and I keep adjusting my clothes. I'm not totally sure what's going on? My face doesn't look like me, or it does I guess. Um. I can't tell if I'm calm or not right now. I just suddenly feel like this. I think it started while I was putting on makeup after my shower and I was looking at myself really closely and I started feeling weird. My clothes feel uncomfortable, they're both tight and loose and it's weird.

I don't really know what to do. Does anyone want to talk to me until this passes? I don't really know what 'this" is anyway. I'm just pacing around in my house. Maybe I'm just imagining this feeling and I'm actually ok, but I can't tell.

Ok I changed my clothes and I kinda feel better but it's still weird. On a side note, I need to grow out my hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 15:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk man, most of the people I follow that say they are trans mean that they are genuinely transgender too. I never see any of that transethnic/transvegan-type stuff either except on troll blogs or tumblrinaction :p. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 20:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orange duck, caramelized orange carrots, a mix of wild rice and the regular kind, and then some kind of pie or cake for dessert. Our family's only got three people, so it's not a very elaborate meal, but it tastes great! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 01:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna say this as nicely as I can. No one likes it when you act like this and say these kinds of things. I don't know if it's some kind of a coping strategy to deal with parts of your life you can't control, or if you're just unhappy and telling yourself you're an intellectual who doesn't need other people's approval to feel satisfaction. Whichever it is, it's fine. Really. Just understand that no one - really, no one - is impressed by you. And hey, if you're not looking to impress people, then what's your purpose in making these kinds of comments? Does it really make you happy to be such a killjoy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 18:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha nah, I guess I should have specified - the band was made up of real people. I used to love that show though. Thanks for looking all the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 22:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, that's not it. We've checked that before, though it's possible it's a song by the same guy. If it is however, we haven't been able to find it. Thank you for looking all the same! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 21:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's this song my dad sings sometimes but we can't find it anywhere online. The lyrics are, "Sur la mer, il y a un bateau qui vogue, bateau qui vogue, bateau qui vogue..." We know that it's from the 1970s or earlier, it was on a record, and the singer was from Quebec, so it may have been a very local song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 21:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was this cartoon network promo for a band at some point between 2004 and 2008 where this girl with black hair is making this crazy music on a stage and it cuts to her saying "My name is [something] and I like making noise." I've tried finding the promo for ages so that I could listen to the band, but no luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 19:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vague-posting on facebook. 

"Ugh. Sometimes your 'friends' aren't really your friends."


"OMG I just had the best time with Him I love u bby!"


"Looks like I'm on my own again. Sigh. You think you can trust someone."

And then the inevitable comments saying "Hang in there babe!" and "Message me!"

Who are you talking about?! Why are you airing this out on social media?! And why are you so damn vague about it oh my god
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 18:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are beautiful! Excellent job, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 23:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like bad steak well-done and covered in salt and pepper. I like good steak medium rare or rare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 22:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James and the Giant Peach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 16:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One plate of hashbrowns with cheddar cheese and mushrooms from waffle house (cuz that shit's like 5 bucks at most) and a cup of coffee, please :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 16:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban for the Gameboy Advance. It was like a mini turn-based rpg, but with harry potter - two of my favorite things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 23:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to college in January and my family is moving house in December, so now's a bad time to get attached to anyone in the area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 04:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The VFD from A Series of Unfortunate Events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 23:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do no harm, take no shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 23:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, yeah. And it's not as thought they were both young and spry and the non-dying spouse could carry on living for another fifty years. They were both old and wanted to pass away together and in peace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 01:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For guys, I like black hair and high cheekbones. Broad shoulders and being relatively fit is also rad.
For girls, basically the same characteristics :p. Though I've noticed I care less about facial shape with girls. Actually, when I think about it, my preferences for girls are usually more emotion-based, like having a positive attitude and confidence. I don't care as much about how they look, but their attitude and personality is more important than for guys for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 20:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get one for 15 at Instyle salon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're so damn selfish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 00:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you get this far? I mean it, how did you get this far without your parents beating your stupid, spoiled ass like they should?

Outwardly, yes, we're very similar people - we went to the same middle school and high school, we're from the same white upper middle class area, and even our faces and voices are similar. But god, you're such a spoiled brat! Crying, complaining, moaning about something or other day in and day out. And it's funny cuz you expect me to listen. Do you remember how we became friends? Cuz you started ranting about gym class to me. I went along with it. I was small and gangly and unattractive - I didn't have anyone else to talk to, so I went along with it, as I have been for five years. Thing is, I don't really know why I still am? I grew into myself and I've got more confidence than I used to. I don't need you. The only reason I still text you back at all is cuz I'm still here for the next two months until I leave for college.


Do you know why your stupid self has been bullied since elementary school? It's cuz you have the emotional strength of a goddamn toothpick. Any form of criticism, jab, or minor prank, you react to like they personally insulted your mother. You snarl and roll your eyes. You might bang your fists on the table. You tearfully flee the scene to go cry in the bathroom. It's no wonder people target you - you're even weaker than I am. You need a therapist. Sometimes I think you should've gone to that hospital instead of me, but when I think about it, you would've just ranted about it as soon as you got out.

And another thing! Why the hell do you act like such an asshole to our mutual friend?! You complain about your life to a guy who literally had brain cancer and lives with his mom in an apartment that's less than half the size of your house. And he even listens to you! He's got so much more patience for you than I do, and yet you put him down because of your dumb fear of men and drinking and anything scarier than bible study. You're such a prick, and I hope I never talk to you again after I leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ariel needs legs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 22:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 18:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some more pics are available [here!]( http://www.ew.com/gallery/fantastic-beasts-where-to-find-them-jk-rowling-gallery) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 18:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try my best to do that. I've hesitated before in telling her because she's so sensitive, but I guess I gotta push through and tell her next time she comes to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 18:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She does need a psychiatrist when I think about it. I'm actually not sure why she doesn't have one at the moment, or a therapist. I'll ask her. And thank you for telling me I'm not the one to take care of her - she just sorta automatically comes to me and vents and it's hard to really deflect it. But it's helpful to be reminded I don't have a true responsibility to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 17:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconding this, it's a very helpful subreddit and is geared mostly toward women dressing professionally for work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's getting difficult to support my friend (warning, long post) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 17:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some background info: I've been friends with this girl for the past five years. We graduated high school in May and she started college in August. I chose to take a semester off and am starting in January, so I have no real experience of college yet.

My friend is naturally a very emotional person. She feels things strongly and she expresses her feelings openly. This has led to situations of extreme anger (ex: slamming hands on the lunch table, biting out angry words like they do in movies) and extreme sadness (openly crying) in public places. 

Here's the main problem. She has been bullied since she was young. From what I've seen, she appears to attract bullies because she reacts very strongly to jibes, pranks, and criticism against her. When they see how she reacts, they try to rile her up further.

Additionally, she's fairly insecure and unsocial. She hates drinking and smoking, which is understandable, but she limits herself socially because of it. She refuses to go to any parties or bars because she doesn't want to interact with any "drunk perverts" or experience a place that's loud and full of people. She struggles with anxiety as well and is prone to panic attacks.

As of right now, she's had some bad experiences with one of her roommates, who seems to like antagonizing her and, like others have done, riling her up. Additionally, she's also had trouble with schoolwork and computer problems, adding to her stress.

I don't really know how to support her at this point? I'm doing my best to give her emotional support and I reassure her that her future will be better, it's just a rough patch, she can change roommates next semester, etc. But it's kinda hard not to feel frustrated with her. Every time me or a mutual friend give advice, she automatically refutes it by some excuse or other. She's taking classes right now that I've always had an interest in but could never pursue because of family pressure. And she complains about them - assignments I would genuinely love to work on. Her experiences with anxiety and sadness mirror my experiences with depression and anxiety a few years back. Weirdly, I feel less sympathy for her because of this - I learned a lot and I pushed through it largely on my own and with tough love from my family. I'm jealous that her parents are easy on her, I'm jealous of the fact that she's never experienced the "tough love" that I did. I feel awful for feeling like this, but I don't know how to change my way of thinking.

I'm kinda at my wit's end here. I love her, but she's feeling miserable and I can't help but frustrated when we talk. Has anyone been in a situation like this? Or alternatively been in her shoes?

I just read over this and I'm sorry if I come off as whiney in this post :( I'm frustrated and sad that she's sad. I know this is a tiny struggle compared to what other women on here face, but I would appreciate advice all the same.

TL;DR: Friend is having life struggles that I'm finding it increasingly difficult to support her through them because I feel she's not dealing with them effectively or in the way that I would. Need advice on what I should do.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 02:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same! This thread makes me so happy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 01:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg that would be awesome! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 23:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rice. Just plain old rice bought in bulk and cooked with a bouillon cube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 23:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jude Law's voice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 23:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picking me up in the air, even if it's for fun or a joke or something. My thinking process is usually something like "oh wow, he just picked me up like I was nothing oh shit he could literally just pick me up and fuck me against a wall"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 19:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sentence honestly made me so mad :(

They're so sure of themselves! But they're so wrong! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 18:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very well-written. Saved the post for reference :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 19:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason I read this in cr1tikal's voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 23:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like what she said and I like the way she said it. It's easy to feel apathetic about shit, but not caring about your life doesn't make you cool or "realistic", it just makes you into kind of a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 04:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 19 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 21:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Also, men naturally have a higher basal metabolic rate, meaning that if you compare a man and a woman of the same height and weight, the man'll just naturally burn a bit more calories in a day than the woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 20:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend's ex-boyfriend's parents just named their newborn "Khaleesi". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 15:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genuinely wondering - what's the advantage to cooking rice in a rice cooker versus in a pot like I normally do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 02:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. Good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 19:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er. This wasn't about them masturbating, it was about me worrying they'd heard me going at it. I have no illusions about the fact that they do it. Honestly, I was just super embarrassed when I wrote that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 19:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's possible. They didn't mention anything this morning anyway, and I guess it doesn't really matter. I wrote the post late at night panicking :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 06:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant](https://40.media.tumblr.com/f77ed92ad651d9e30bc2aa708ac9949e/tumblr_inline_nwhv09PrvO1r8p8gp_540.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got caught in a dumb way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 04:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God okay so I was rubbing my clit reaaal quietly (but I mean it's under the blankets that brush up against it so you can still probably hear a tiny repetitive noise) in the dark in bed. I can't see anything but my phone screen. So I'm going along, not rubbing too much or anything, just getting myself relaxed when I suddenly hear a door close. I look up. The door connecting my room to the bathroom is wide open. The one connecting the bathroom to the hall, which directly opens right into my parents room, is shut. I never close one without closing the other. 

THIS MEANS THEY HEARD ME. They heard and were like oh god gross kid lets close your door. 

fuck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 03:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit he's handsome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like I don't really know who I am </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 07:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have strong opinions, but they're not really enforced. I can absolutely love a trend or a belief and then read an article bashing it and my feelings towards it'll completely change.

I feel like I'm a side character in a main character's story. My appearance was determined by an online trait generator. My back's 20 degrees crooked and I wear the same pair of boots every day because they make me feel tough. My face is both soft and angled - I'm pretty and ugly all at once. A mishmash of my father's nose and chin, my mother's cheeks and skin. I have a Tragic Backstory and I was a Troubled Youth for a while. I have daddy issues and I can't speak my mother tongue as well as I'd like. I'm even a Relatable Teen Character because I can't do liquid eyeliner and I love eating pizza and watching scary movies. Everything's just a trope. I can't tell if it's comforting or nauseating.

Nothing feels like it really matters. Nothing has any weight. It's just a story.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 04:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Full Metal Alchemist Brotherhood? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 21:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my dreams have come true I CAN FINALLY LIVE AS MY TRUE SELF: A GRUMPY OLD MAN.


HELL YEAH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 07:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 21:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was honestly so relaxing. And informative too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 02:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg c'est trop bon. Je pensais qu'ils avaient juste la version franaise de france....

Edit: I sent this to my very qubcois parents and they died haha. I'm considering getting this for christmas now :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 23:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn a a l'air cool. I'll watch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 06:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. In all honesty, I feel like I understand those two subjects better now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 18:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I get what you're saying, but you can't really compare a vid of evangelion to rick and morty. They're two very different shows. Rick and morty is, at its core, a comedy, albeit a dark one. Evangelion is a psychological, self-loathing series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 06:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, that was really good. I have feelings now brb gotta get rid of those </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 18:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody knows this game, but in Wallace and Gromit in Project Zoo for the ps2, there was this one level where you were in this snow/ice area with these baby polar bears and it was the shit.

Literally one of my favorite games of all time, but I've never heard anyone talk about it :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 19:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someday, I swear I'll buy this. I need it in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 19:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 23:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was really well-put. Thank you for writing all that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 22:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God dammit cobb county, why's it always gotta be you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 06:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 05:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bless this movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 01:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Syberia. The Broken Sword series. The Runaway: A Road Adventure trilogy. Wallace and Gromit in Project Zoo. Portal Runner.

Edit: Adibou! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 00:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks very much for the info. Even if it's not super recent, it's still helpful :p. Part of the reason why I'm considering joining the corps is because I usually work better under discipline and a tight schedule than without.

- How come do you think there were so few women that went through all four years? Like, was it a lack of interest, or difficulties, or a bad environment? 

- From the university's website, it says you get a $300 monthly stipend and a majority of tuition covered, so the monetary benefits seem to have changed since you went (but anyone please correct me if that's wrong). So I guess that's half of my motivation to join, especially with all the news about how awful student debt is these days.

- Also, about what the other guy's saying, would you say that military work (formations etc) was greatly prioritized over academics? And if so, did it affect you in any way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 22:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright. I'm gonna think about this.

Would you say you regret the year and a half you spent as a cadet? Both in terms of monetary stuff and just whether or not you feel like it was worth it.  Also, what field did you study? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 21:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. Can you give me any reasons why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 19:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an awesome offer! I really wish I could take you up on it, but I live down in Georgia unfortunately, which ain't too close to New Jersey. I hope you can find someone to take it off your hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any of you attend or attended UNG? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 17:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm headed there in the spring but was wondering what y'all thought of it. Additionally, I've been thinking about whether or not I should join the corps of cadets because it seems like they'd pay for a lot more of my tuition. Any advice or anecdotes regarding the university or its corps of cadets would be much appreciated.


Edit: Also, I dunno if this is of much relevance, but I'm a girl, and the website says only 10% of the corps is female. Would you say the dropout rate for girls is equal to that of the guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 21:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, feel free to send it my way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 18:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, you're assuming she was attractive here - she really wasn't, and she was also pretty manipulative. But hey, you can have her if you want :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 18:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liking avengers/minecraft/whatever pop culture nerd crap my first gf liked. I had zero interest in any of it but convinced myself I liked it cuz she did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 23:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get what you're saying. I don't regret having been raised by him. All the way up till the first two or three years of high school, my grades were excellent because of his ambition for me. I appreciate how much he cared for my grades. On the other hand, I'm left with a lot of self esteem issues that stem mostly from failed attempts to gain his approval and make him be genuinely proud of me. And this carries on to today, where I struggle with wanting to be *good enough* - whatever that means - so that he'll be proud of me, and not just in a "oh, in spite of all this depression stuff, you've done okay" pitying type of way, but in a real way.

So it's kinda complicated :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 01:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 17:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty helpful. It sounds more motivating that way, rather than that I *have* to do something. Thank you :) I never thought of that before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 17:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Disclaimer: I'm half-asleep right now and this is a little difficult to write about, so bear with me here :p

He wasn't a good parent for those years of my life. At his worst, he was emotionally abusive and controlling. At his best, he was just as caring and loving at any other parent. He was basically a "tiger mom", despite being a male French-Canadian immigrant.

I can't and won't try to defend him for how treated me when I was younger because he really did take it too far. Worrying that your dad's gonna do the head-fist-thing or scream so loud he starts shaking and making grabby motions with his hands like you're gonna get hit again because you just don't understand fractions isn't fun, and it didn't help me understand math any better.

Thing is, over the past 3 years, he's gotten better. I can't remember the last time where he got as angry as he did when I was little. We've talked and talked for hours about how he made me feel when I was younger. He's apologized multiple times since then. He tells me he loves me as often as he can.

He's a flawed man, but he's a good man who had good intentions. He wanted me to grow up better. His own father also drove him to the point of suicide. He was emotionally neglected throughout most of his young life, and sought to rectify that with me, and so I was smothered with attention, love, and control in his desire that I be the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 22:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really interesting that we had such a similar experience. Congrats on being a new person! :) As cheesy as this sounds, it's pretty uplifting to hear you went through similar stuff but came out alright. I'll do my best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 22:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Will do!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 22:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man. I'm honestly glad I sound normal. And I guess even though I wish I hadn't broken down, it's better for me that it happened a couple years ago rather than like, holding it in forever and then going batshit crazy from repressed emotions when I'm like 40-something with two kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 22:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I'll be careful :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 22:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! That sounds pretty rad. Will definitely put on my bucket list :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 22:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thanks man :) I wanna write the first half of your comment up and tape it to my wall so I can get reminded every morning. Actually yeah, I'm totally gonna do that. :p

Also yep, I am clinically depressed, but I think I've more or less accepted it at this point. I gotta move forward and do my best on good days, and then on bad days, I need to remember that it's okay to take a step back and not be too critical of myself.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 19:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Hannibal Lecter's pretty rad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 16:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He really is very cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
