<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9438</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://mises.org/library/why-nazism-was-socialism-and-why-socialism-totalitarian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It wasnt real socialism" every time. When you will guys admit that socialism is a failed ideology? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you get that idea that Republicans don't care for issues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A quick history lesson about how Venezuela failed and what we can learn from their socialistic experiment. Enjoy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuela Before Chavez: A Prelude to Socialist Failure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knew that socialism will fail. Hint: it always did and alway will. Here is a nice article about Venezuela https://mises.org/blog/venezuela-chavez-prelude-socialist-failure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub is left biased so why do you care? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you are using his user history to attack him. That is also bannable offense ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand with the facts. Here is a quote from Emory website: 
"All Undocumented Students (with or without DACA) who are admitted as first-year, first-degree-seeking undergraduate students, who have graduated from a U.S. high school, and who are determined by Emory to have financial need, will be awarded Emory financial aid funds to assist them in meeting their demonstrated need."

And who is this undocumented student?

"Undocumented students are **illegal alien** school-aged immigrants who entered the United States without inspection or overstayed their visas illegally"

source: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Undocumented_students_in_the_United_States </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humanist or Solidarus  encourage to reward criminals instead of law abiding citizens? I didn't know that. Thanks for clarification tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emory University is private and they want to pay tuiton for illegals. And how are they going to finance it? By taking money from students who pay their tuition. Also this is unfair morally because why should a student who is here illegally should get more than a legal student? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool blog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a link to this university site: http://www.studentaid.emory.edu/DACA/index.html

I feel like this is not fair. They are punishing legal students and give their money to illegals. How is this right? Either make all colleges free or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emory University to pay 100 percent of the financial need of students in country illegally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have an opinion against leftie hivemind this will happen ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares about /r/politics? I tried to discuss with them, same is in /r/europe but if you go against their leftie hivemind you are silenced and downvoted to hell. I'm just going to stick to this sub because I can actually discuss  different topics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously? Compare Ireland from 30 years ago and now. Because of very low corporate tax they lured big companies and its benefeting Ireland. Do you want to stop that? Competition is needed between countries because it leads to development. But he will not suceed in his plans because he will get a big fuck you from EU countries that are not Germany </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
