<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4170</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 14:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While there is [no concrete definition](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mountain#Definition) of a mountain, [several of the Wichita Mountains](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wichita_Mountains#Geography) fit most of the general criteria whereas only one needs to be met.

[Michigan has some](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Porcupine_Mountains), too.  Sort of.

You're used to city bus-sized mountains, though, not surprising that the Honda Fit-sized ones wouldn't be terribly impressive.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 12:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would he travel so far to hide it if this were the case? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 20:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize the teletubbies lived in Kentucky.  I guess that makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 20:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it's less dated than the current one somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 20:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't help but think "Baywatch" every time I see that.  I'm so sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 20:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Michigan one you linked to was [quietly changed](http://www.mlive.com/lansing-news/index.ssf/2014/10/worlds_best_license_plate_quie.html) a few months after it was released because no one could read what it said. It's kinda ugly now IMHO (at least in person).  I hope I never have to replace my "[everything but the Mackinac Island Fudge](https://goo.gl/images/iKc4T7)" type from a few years back, especially since they drew the Amway Grand tower to scale with the Ren Center in what I can only assume was a fit of whimsy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 23:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disney Infinity and its precursor Toy Story 3, if you're into that sort of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 22:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't arguing that it's not the case, I was arguing that Americans simply don't have much exposure to that sort of thing from day to day.  It's a big country.  Plenty to preoccupy a mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 22:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhere around two feet, personally.  I haven't examined it that closely (oh look, navel lint!) so I couldn't say why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 22:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A phosphate was an old kind of pop (*cough* soda/coke/whatever) so named by [the method of making it fizzy](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Phosphate_soda).  This was the kind served at soda fountains, as opposed to today's carbonic acid stuff.

I'm favorable to the idea that the full name is "soda-pop" and both usages are just contractions, and Coke is of course a [proprietary eponym](https://en.wiktionary.org/wiki/proprietary_eponym).  No harm done in using any of them.

 nbsp;

 nbsp;

^(...but it's totally *pop.*) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 22:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are talking right past each other.  I was arguing to expose the limitedness of *anyone's* experience, whereas you appear to be hung up on the idea that a well-traveled or simply European set of experiences should magically be exempt from any sense of humility in this matter.

Your initial argument, dialectically speaking, had nothing to do with the American educational system or media.  You stated that Europeans know more about us than we do them.  I never argued that point, I merely attempted to soften its clear subtext by pointing out there are good reasons for that.  You then implied that Americans were ignorant, using the European (for lack of a better moniker) operant definition of ignorance that I took issue with.

You retorted by flaunting your *bona fides*, apparently thinking them more relevant than they are, and countered my anecdote with one of your own, without knowing a single thing about where I've been or what I've learnt in my life.  So I tried to clarify my point in a friendly manner.

Twice you've pivoted to topics not at hand in my arguments: the state of the American media, and the state of the American Educational system, and now you are acting like that was the basis of the whole discussion. I also lack the willfully blind "MURICA"-ness that you are apparently attributing to me and my argument (I mean, no one else is around...). You're lighting straw men.

The *attitude* of unexamined "we know what learned is" is cultural imperialism, not the refusal to acknowledge the problems of our educational system, a refusal I *never came close to making.*  My reply to the assertion that the media is a mess was that it was all many of us have had access to until recently.  That is also not disagreement, but an attempt to make you see that it's arrogant to think that Americans should have drawn information from any other source.  I then attempted to head you off by pointing out that the Internet is too recent for our society to fully embrace its informative potential, and you argued that you'd never said that.  Not the point.


Please note that I went back and edited "saying the Internet..." to "thinking the Internet..." to better reflect my thought, which was merely to anticipate the response of, "but we live in an Information age," that I so frequently hear from people carrying the torch you hold.  You appear to have not gotten the point while affirming the reason I wrote that in the first place.  People don't change the patterns they're accustomed to that quickly.  It's not an American trait.

At any rate, I'm done here. You should know that your attitude, not the content of your position, is the reason why everyone else downvoted you.  Have a good day, and in the future please try to temper your European friends' opinions with the knowledge that they are just as flawed as us 'dumb' Americans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 20:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's not particularly useful at understanding entire populations of people.

Not in the way you apparently think I meant it, at least.  

I'm arguing the guy was ironically narrow-minded for judging me provincial because I didn't learn *his* language.  That's a human mistake, not a French or American one.

Your "honest criticism" is itself taken from a limited set of cultural experiences and assumes one culture should be learning the same things another does if it is to be "not ignorant / a dolt."  That's flat-out cultural imperialism.  And, more often than not, to be frank, it's offered as an insult, not friendly admonishment.

Learning a foreign language was used merely as an example here.  I think everyone should learn as many as possible.  That said, it's good for the skill set when you live 200 kilometers from where the language originated.  Not so much when the nearest foreign language starts being spoken over 2000 km away.

I live ~215 miles from Chicago and ~160 from Detroit.  I'm hearing news from both places *all the time* that I wouldn't expect someone in Paris to know about, but I'd be aghast if someone in Antwerp didn't know anything about what was happening in Paris. The scale of the person's locus of awareness is the same in either case.

Let's not forget that the American experience has until recently been limited to learning about goings-on from those sorts of media you are being so harsh about.  Thinking the Internet should have flipped a switch and changed that for everyone is presentism, and a higher standard than the one many in Europe are holding themselves to.

America is culturally, economically, and militarily dominant, for better or worse.  This means a people's exposure to American things will be disproportionate to the foreign things an American is exposed to.  America is also far enough away that one has to seek information out, even in this age, if one is to learn about things outside our borders.  That's just how things are right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 19:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you take away urban blacks, you also take away [a huge chunk of our concentrated urban poor](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/wonk/wp/2015/08/12/black-poverty-differs-from-white-poverty/).  That's not culture, it's economics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 18:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NH's main urban center is Boston.  Most of their population lives in relatively-well-off Boston suburbs. This skews their numbers.

New Hampshire is the [seventh state for millionaires per capita](http://www.cnbc.com/2016/01/20/these-states-have-the-highest-density-of-millionaires.html), at 6.8%.  Kentucky is third from the last at just under 4.25%.  That's a 60% difference.  New Hampshire has a *third* as many households as Kentucky, but only *half* as many rich households by this metric.  Thus I hope you don't mind if I extrapolate that the population density of rich people is *much* lower in Kentucky, which means that police, civil services and social services have a smaller tax base to pull from, irrespective of the politics of the area.  It also indicates that there is less money being made and spent per capita, which leads to a weaker economy.  This can be easily seen by looking at whether a company believes it can make money in an area.  Just an example: [Kentucky has eleven Targets](http://www.target.com/store-locator/find-stores?address=Lexington%20KY capabilities=), New Hampshire has [Nine](http://www.target.com/store-locator/find-stores?address=concord%20nh capabilities=), in a state less than a quarter the size by area with a third of Kentucky's population.


 nbsp;

New Hampshire [also has the lowest poverty rate of any state, while Kentucky comes in at 39th](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_U.S._states_by_poverty_rate).  Kentucky's poverty rate is more than twice that of New Hampshire's.  There are [*eight times* as many impoverished people](https://www.census.gov/content/dam/Census/library/publications/2014/demo/p60-251.pdf) in Kentucky as in New Hampshire.  

TL;DR: Actually, if we were just going on economics, there *is* that big of a difference.  In fact, Kentucky's doing pretty well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 17:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never disagreed with you that there are socioeconomic factors.

That's not *all* I said, though.  Sorry, the original person I replied to said murder rate and I didn't realize you were two different people.  I thought you were cherry picking my argument for the sake of a straw man. I'm getting in too many arguments here lately so I guess my hackles go up to quickly.  I apologize. :/

 nbsp;

You keep acting like this is a factor in gun crime, it isn't.

I didn't say population was a deciding factor, I said it was a *confounding* factor. I.E. A state with higher population indicates more urbanized areas, more demographic diversity, etc., whereas the bulk of NH's population density comes from the [Boston suburbs](http://www.nh.gov/oep/data-center/census/documents/census-populations.pdf) (PDF Warning).

Population density, IMHO, is not a good measurement in this instance because it doesn't take into account that the urban center associated with most of NH's population and density is in Massachusetts.  It would be like measuring Chicagoland's gun crime by the north end/suburbs instead of the south. Of *course* there's less need for Illinois' strict gun laws on the Gold Coast or in Winnetka.

Along those lines I'd argue that gun laws don't appear in a vacuum.  Laws, misguided or not, are pretty much always developed in reaction to a perceived need.  New Hampshire, under this model, would have fewer gun laws simply because they *have* fewer shootings, not the other way around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 16:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^(SHHH, you're stepping on my hyperbole!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 12:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really?

New Hampshire is fifth among states by per capita income. South Carolina is 43rd and Kentucky is 45th.  You literally just picked the fifth richest state and compared it to two of the poorest.

New Hampshire is also a fraction of the size of either by both area and population. You'd be hard pressed to find a more disparate comparison on a demographic level, too.

~~I'm not much for accusations but your ignorance of the economic side of my earlier comment along with the choice of a different metric and state than the one I mentioned doesn't exactly look intellectually honest.~~ EDIT: I'm a moron who needs to look closer at his phone screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 08:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have [Founders](http://www.foundersbrewing.com), and TBH it's not even the [second](http://www.breweryvivant.com) [best](http://www.perrinbrewing.com) [brewery](http://www.harmonybeer.com) [around](http://www.hideoutbrewing.com) [lately](http://www.mittenbrewing.com). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 05:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I can find is [Simon Savage](http://marvel.wikia.com/wiki/Simon_Savage_\(Earth-616\)) and (*shudder*) Anti-Cap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 04:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captain Marvel is actually a major, so she outranks Cap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 03:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Context? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd agree with you except to point out that he didn't limit his statement to Reddit.  It's in the topic, yes, but he spoke more generally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Switzerland's high gun ownership is mostly due to everyone having a military-issued weapon, and they generally aren't allowed to *load it.* For everything else, their laws are stricter than ours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vermont also has a lower population than roughly 30 US cities and an above US average per capita income. Confounding factors, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 01:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (I didn't downvote you but here's why I disagree)

My point was that people have more immediate access to know about us than we do about them.

I had a guy say something to me in French once.  When I told him I didn't understand, he said "typical American, never bothering to look outside his borders."

The question arises: When the hell would I use *French?*  I took seven years of Spanish, but then I had good reason: people actually *speak* that around here.

It's not willful ignorance. For most of us it's lack of exposure.  Indianapolis is the nearest state capitol that isn't my own.  It's about the same distance from me as London is from Paris.  They don't speak much French in Indy, so far as I know.  I'd have to drive *much* further than that to visit a place with a different language and culture.  Canada just doesn't count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 00:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yarp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 00:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost as if we were the last superpower, or as if everyone consumed our pop culture or something... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hungry investors seek Grand Rapids housing deals, rankling longtime residents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 18:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 18:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be careful.  I didn't include our fair state because I didn't want to be too vicious. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 17:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking as a former automobile insurance adjuster, the bay area takes the cake for "depraved things done to an automobile, provided they didn't take it outright."

Edit: off topic, but in case y'all were wondering:

* Los Angeles: this totally normal thing is a perfectly good reason for me to have totaled my car (often a light drizzle).

* Oregon/Idaho: I hit a rock again.

* Florida: IT WAS TOTALLY THE OTHER FUCKING GUYS FUCKING FAULT HOW FUCKING DARE HE ONLY FUCKING GO TEN FUCKING OVER IN FRONT OF ME. FUCK.

* Alaska: I rolled down the mountain because a moose appeared (there's a good reason for this--break a moose's legs and you ded).

* Utah: I'm a great driver, I just forgot how to Freeway.

* SoCal again/Miami/Urban TX (note most of our business was in CA and TX): I ran daddy's expensive car up a pole. I was just going out for ice cream, honest.  Drag racing? How dare you!

* Minnesota/Dakotas/Wyoming/Nebraska: I hit another deer.  You shoulda seen that fucker fly.

* Connecticut: America's hit and run King.

* New Jersey: For a state that gets this much flak, you'd be surprised how mundane our accidents are.

* Kansas or Oklahoma: We measure our hailstones in fruit 'round here.  This one was a watermelon.

* (North) Texas or Oklahoma: My car's on top of the barn again.  It missed the target we painted after last time, though.

* Gulf Coast: See we was having this party and a fight broke out.  My car was parked right there.  It's totaled.

* El Paso: Car's gone.  Cartels took it.  Yeah, that was it.

* Anywhere in the South: "Which Wal-Mart parking lot was your car damaged in?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 17:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said it before, I'll say it again: We have the Upper Peninsula, a rural meth problem, and a ton of slummy areas.  I love this state, but if Michigan had those laws, you'd see some *real* shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 17:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could meaningfully reword your comment to replace 'America/n' with a heck of a lot of other nationalities depending on context.  This sub is very used to getting questions along those lines (Americans, why are you so dumb/violent/right-wing/selfish/warlike compared to my country, X?).

I'd also ask you to back your assertion that there is "much more ignorance *from* America."  There's a reason this sub exists, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 17:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine had been named Squishy for a minimum of three days and I'd evolved a Flareon since getting him.  Still got a Jolteon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 16:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last one, unfortunately, is super important.  I have a three-bedroom house in a great school district.  My next-door neighbor drives a Tesla Model S to work.  I'm a ten minute drive from a downtown that's exploding with development and things to do, and my house cost me $115K five years ago.  My sister-in-law's folks just sold a similar house (on a lot 1/5th the size of ours) in the Bronx for $3 Million.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 16:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd been 3-4 days since I'd named him.  Lord knows how many app cache clears, force stops, and phone restarts I did in that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 16:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in a similarly-sized city, technically, but urban sprawl is a different animal here, so the amount of people living here depends greatly on how you define "here" (up to 1.5 million if you go out a few dozen km).  Our public transportation system sounds very similar to yours, except the hours are slightly better and we have a [BRT](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bus_rapid_transit) line that's M-F with another one on the way.  Our public transit system is award-winning and considered fantastic for a city of our size.  It's crazy good compared to Detroit's, even though their metropolitan area is three times as big. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 16:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In aggregate? No.  Is there an element here who has one? Absolutely.

I recently went to SAS (yeah, I know).  There was a thread about the Affordable Care Act ("Obamacare") which was linked there, and the groupthink was saying and upvoting things like "Of course they think their healthcare system is the best and nobody's could possibly be better" when the linked thread was 99% *brutal bitching about the ACA.*  

I don't see a difference between this and Redditors jumping to conclusions and upvoting said conclusions (I hate the word "circlejerk" with a passion) without anyone bothering to read *any* article.  DAE ~~PC Master Race~~ ~~Hillary = teh evil~~ ~~420 LOL~~ ~~the rich people and NSA are taking our freedoms~~ ~~hate SJWs?~~ *literally anything*.

Is Reddit *more* pro-American than other social outlets in your experience?  If so I'd have to ask if it's more pro-American because of all the Americans here as you hypothesize, or if it's just that there are more people accustomed to it here, warts and all, so there's less circlejerk (ugh).  Possible shades of the same thing, I know, but American != Pro-American. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 15:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had already named the existing vaporeon Squishy. Didn't work. He shall still be mine and he shall be my Squishy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 15:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it didn't work for me.  One named "Rainer" evolved into a jolteon.  I had previously evolved one into a vaporeon by naming it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 02:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it Loeks owned back then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 02:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually only 19 states *don't*.  I know this because we're one of them and our legislature was recently considering changing that.  Of course, they didn't.  Wouldn't want to look like they actually got anything useful done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 23:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought it was Colombian.  TIL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 23:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be brutally honest. Sorry in advance. 

 nbsp;

I've spent between a week and six months in each of the following: Mexico, Cuba, Honduras, Guatemala, El Salvador, and Nicaragua.  I have a college degree in Spanish that focused heavily on Latin American culture, history and literature.  

The first thing that popped into my mind when I read your question was how the US government stuck its nose in where it didn't belong to split Panama off from you so they could build the canal.

 nbsp;

...yeah, I know.  That was Colombia.

 nbsp;

I'm afraid that aside from knowing you were part of *Gran* Colombia, and that you have the Galapagos, there isn't much on my radar.

You haven't produced any authors of Garca Mrquez or Borges' quality that I can think of off the top of my head.  I can't think of a single Ecuadorean dish that isn't shared with someone else. I can't even think of an Ecuadorian telenovela or singer.

Maybe this is a good thing, though.  You wouldn't want to have the same kind of history with us that, say, Nicaragua had, right?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 22:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the old "call someone a liberal in a this-only-actually-works-in-my-echo-chamber attempt to discredit them instead of engaging with their argument, then pull an /r/iamverysmart to act like everyone's downvoting me 'cuz I'm just *not on their level, man*."

I ask this in total, straight-faced seriousness: are you 14? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 17:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I skipped over that because I can't help but hear "I wuv dis" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 16:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I didn't. I omitted it for brevity's sake. I put it back in, and to my ear it hasn't changed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 15:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took a TA from the Dominican Republic to the biggest Meijer (think Wal Mart without much of the suckage) store once. She stood in the beverage aisle for a hard minute then said, "I JUST WANT *COFFEE*." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 15:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't provide evidence to the *positive*. It isn't the world's job to disprove what you say, and "no one starved in the USSR because they were poor" is an /r/badhistory level assertion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 13:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no, we usually don't keep the words "Star Trek" in the abbreviation.  It would go something like this:

"You know, I wasn't expecting to, but I really love DIC."


...uh oh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 02:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I tried to go up to the home page of the site, but [Crashworks.org](http://crashworks.org/) redirects to [Ratchet and Clank](http://www.insomniacgames.com/games/ratchet-clank-ps4/).  Wha? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 23:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WE KNOW (breaks into tears) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 23:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might be saying this as an oblivious native of the Moo Belt, but I think that was a local thing.  I noticed a bit ago that the milk my wife picked up at Target the other day was from a dairy farm in Texas...a Minnesotan company selling Texan milk in Michigan? Screw that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 23:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were a fad in the Midwest a few years ago.  I wish they still were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 15:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swimming with tankers is just like swimming with dolphins, you'll be fine!

Actually I was thinking of the rocky parts, and I've never met a southerner who'd swim in Superior at any point of the year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 14:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have flair so I don't know which suburbs you speak of. I'm guessing you mean Chicago? The market I was talking about was the Schaumburg one near their library. 

I remember seeing trucks from out my way (Benton Harbor, Hudsonville, etc.) but the quality, selection and price were nowhere near as good as West Michigan.  

All of our farms have signs showing their location. There's very little produce from outside the area,  and I've never seen one from so far away as the quad cities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 13:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing with the trucks and farmers is still the case here, except our participants usually set aside some stock to be sold at one of the (literally dozens of) markets in this side of the state.  

Then there are a few organic/specialty growers, bakers, jam makers, coffee roasters, et al, that really only (or at least primarily) sell stuff through these markets.  The stock is generally a bit more expensive if you go to one of the bigger markets, but the extra stuff gets sold on the cheap at farm stores or roadside stands out in the country.  Also, the big markets take and incentivize WIC.

Agritourism is huge out here, too. Usually those farm stores in the country are attached to apple barns and / or U-pick operations that will offer different kinds of produce depending on season. This is where you'll find the best savings. My wife and I got six quarts of cherries for ten bucks a few weeks ago. Now we're on to blueberries and raspberries. Peaches are next.

And I should say that I know that this is the case to a large extent all over the place. What I've been talking about is that the popularity and wide variety available mean many people simply don't buy produce from a grocery store at this time of year.  Haven't seen it in that magnitude anywhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 08:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have family out in Northeast Arizona, and we would go on a biennial road trip to visit them for 3 weeks or so in the summer (parents were teachers).  I would always get used to the desert then could never believe how much green there was on the way home.  It's just so damn fecund. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 08:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brats are all over the Midwest.  There are several places near me with meat counters that have their own house recipes.  That said, for some reason I've always associated them more closely with Wisconsin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 08:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frickin' Wawa (Sheetz? not sure which side you're on).  Why won't you expand this way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 08:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kinda half-figured.  Don't mean to sound bitter but there are a lot of assumptions being made in this thread from people in CT/NY/NJ about the way other states live and eat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 07:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's more of a city-dwelling socioeconomic thing, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 07:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kraut goes on a brat, silly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 07:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We now have it in West Michigan.  Like, just a few months ago now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 07:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the third person in this thread from NY to look down their virtual nose at another area's eating habits, though.  Tone it down, guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 07:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch out! The Noo Yawk Food Police is in force in this thread.

Next thing you know, they'll be telling us the Midwest can't make a good sausage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 06:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're spreading.  WE ARE BORG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 06:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Maps of the area would disagree with you](https://www.google.com/search?q=midwest safe=active tbm=isch tbo=u source=univ sa=X ved=0ahUKEwj11Lyw44jOAhXHbB4KHSBqDesQiR4IgQE biw=1366 bih=640), but that's neither here nor there. I didn't say I was in the midwest, I pointed out that I'm more than 600 miles from an oceanic coast. Those are two different things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 04:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fat floats :D

I also haven't met a Michigander who couldn't swim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 03:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was really more a point about how insular the community was (better now, honest) that somehow my ancestors could go six of seven generations without leaving a very specific genepool, but yeah, I'm not going anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 03:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it's a deposit you pay when you buy the drink and get back when you return it.  I know, seems dumb, but it definitely keeps the litter down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 03:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I thought truck nuts were bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 02:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, don't be such an asshole.

Try to swim across one, then come back to me about your insanely narrow definition of a beach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 02:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....huh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 02:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I'm referring to the Great Lakes.  Trying to be creative about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 02:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you do.  We aren't bible thumpers and we hate that.  

And no, we (most of us) don't have words about Detroiters.

Fucking stereotypes, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 02:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work in a call center and got used to West Coasters saying I was on the East Coast when I told them I was in Michigan. They were only a skosh over 600 miles off.  I'd also tell them I hadn't been to the ocean in 5 years. I got a lot of shocked responses. Funny how people forget about our massive inland freshwater seas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 01:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was referring to the deposit amount where I live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 01:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be what I meant.  I said it was a West Michigan thing meaning that my coworker from Saginaw didn't get it.

Sorry for any confusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 01:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guilty as charged.  I can't even play Euchre! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 01:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, I think we have a winner.  WHAT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 01:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You aren't flaired.  Which state is this? We call them that in Michigan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 00:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree is all.  I feel like New Yorkers have an inflated sense of their pizza quality.  I live between Detroit and Chicago, two large places whose local styles I greatly prefer, speaking only of my own personal preference.  I've never been to Maryland and spent a total of two weeks in Florida.  I'm not willing to judge Florida's pizza by the obscenity they serve at Disney World.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 00:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Connecticut: someone in Southeastern Michigan just called *your* traffic an eye-opener.  **Get your shit together.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 00:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is good to hear.  I was hoping Schaumburg was a poor representation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 00:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chill, I never said Chicago was incapable of producing bad pizza.  Your comment made it sound like NYC had the market practically cornered.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 00:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh.  There's no excuse for that, KCK.  You're *way* too big. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 00:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBF I've had some pretty terrible (and good!) pizza in NYC. Can't say the same for Chicago.


^(...uh oh, here it comes...what have I done?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
