<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4566</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stephen Colbert plays Wait Wait...Don't Tell Me! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stephen Colbert on Wait Wait...Don't Tell Me! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This questioning is based on a false assumption. I'm calling out the drumbeat of slurs and encomiums based on ethnicity, which should end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Illegals" is used against Latinos as part of a concerted effort in conservative media to demonize non-whites through negative word association. Muslims only get talked about in terms of "radical Muslims," "Islamic terrorists," etc. Immigrants are only worth discussion if it's to foment anger at "illegal immigrants." Black people are reduced to "violent inner cities" and "racist Black Lives Matter."

So what word association do whites get? "White working class." Never any other race of working class. Whites only.

So now you know which races and ethnicities are the good guys and bad guys, thanks to the intentional efforts of conservative media to change how you think about people of different races and ethnicities by the very words used to discuss them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Until right-wingers start calling convicted white Americans "illegals," you don't get a special slur to spit at brown people who haven't been convicted of anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's bad. Shrinking the US population by millions will shrink the US economy, even if you don't give a fuck about people's lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the [Washington Post](https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/federal-agents-conduct-sweeping-immigration-enforcement-raids-in-at-least-6-states/2017/02/10/4b9f443a-efc8-11e6-b4ff-ac2cf509efe5_story.html):

A DHS official confirmed that while immigration agents were targeting criminals, they also were taking into custody non-criminals in the vicinity who were found to be lacking documentation.

---
ICE agents had raided homes, and were not just detaining individuals they are looking for ... but in fact, taking anyone else in the community, or in these homes who does not have immigration status at the moment, or who is not able to prove citizenship, Barrientos said.

In some cities, activists said that ICE had set up roadside or neighborhood checkpoints, where ICE agents, often in unmarked cars, appeared to be asking people at random for proof of citizenship or identification.

If you look Latino, you need to keep your ID on you at all times or you'll be detained. We're a "papers please" society now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Undocumented Immigrants Arrested Across U.S., Stoking Fears Of Trump 'Deportation Force' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Undocumented Immigrants Arrested Across U.S., Stoking Fears Of 'Deportation Force' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 key Trump mistakes that led to the travel ban court defeat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 Trump legal mistakes that led to court defeat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 12:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice double-meaning on "duds." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal ethics agency site crashes on day Trump adviser plugs Ivanka's duds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 12:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump 'to approve arms sales to Saudi Arabia and Bahrain' blocked by Barack Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 11:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump 'to approve arms sales to Saudi Arabia and Bahrain' blocked by Barack Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 11:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump 'to approve arms sales to Saudi Arabia and Bahrain' blocked by Barack Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 11:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump 'to approve arms sales to Saudi Arabia and Bahrain' blocked by Barack Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 11:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 10:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it fulfills all the functions of a physical teller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 06:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ones without the envelopes are actually the best, because the ATM tells you how much it counted, and you either confirm or get your money back. They can't dispute it later, because the machine counted it right there. With an envelope, they can say there wasn't as much in the envelope as you said, and you have no way to prove otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 06:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It also takes coins, dispenses $1-100 bills and coins, prints checks, you can get a loan by talking to a loan officer, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In-store advertising is common, you just aren't always aware of it. Companies pay grocery stores for displays, signs, things that activate as you walk past, etc.

Cable and satellite TV, of course, is the biggest example of paying for ads. About half of the ads on a cable channel are inserted by the cable operator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are places where you videoconference with bank associates in a central location. It's basically a call center model, where instead of staffing each branch with people who idle around when customers aren't coming in, you have a smaller workforce in one place that is called as needed. The ATMs are also capable of more functions, like taking coins and dispensing $1-100 bills and change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bank of America tests totally automated, employee-free branches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bank of America tests totally automated, employee-free branches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bank of America tests totally automated, employee-free branches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bank of America tests totally automated, employee-free branches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get Android Wear 2.0 for as little as $123 with the Fossil Q Founder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand why Android watches aren't sold everywhere watches are sold. Bright, animated faces showing all the different possibilities would definitely attract attention and sales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim U.S. Olympian Ibtihaj Muhammad says she was held by U.S. Customs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim U.S. Olympian Ibtihaj Muhammad says she was held by U.S. Customs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Hampshire Republicans Seem Really Determined To Make Voting Harder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 05:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["Osama bin Laden's hideout was named after me."](http://www.telegraph.co.uk/men/thinking-man/what-boaty-mcboatface-tells-us-about-the-great-british-sense-of/) Could have been a true card on Would I Lie To You. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the population centers like Lexington and Louisville, most people voted for Hillary, and Republicans are not exactly Trump Republicans. Trump voters skew more elderly and non-college-educated than Republicans in general, so not only are city residents less likely to be Republican, Republicans in those cities are less likely to be first-choice Trump supporters. And if you generally interact with Republicans at work, you'll be interacting even less with the retirees and non-college-educated folks who are bigger Trump fans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate GOP's effort to shut Warren up backfires </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Republicans just banned Elizabeth Warren from talking about Jeff Sessions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 05:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 04:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skin pigment isn't doing anything. A diversity of experiences, practices, understandings and backgrounds does. The most diverse quarter of companies in America are 35% more likely to [outperform profitably](https://www.forbes.com/sites/ruchikatulshyan/2015/01/30/racially-diverse-companies-outperform-industry-norms-by-30/), too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most Nazi words are German words for things. They're used as a sort of code online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most Latinos are white. 61.6% of Americans are non-Hispanic white. [Source](https://www.census.gov/quickfacts/table/PST045216/00) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say it should, but judging by your [username](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Panzer_division), it would stop genocidal fascists like you admire from collapsing Europe from within. It would also lead to economic growth, given Europe's low birthrate and need for new immigrants to keep the population and economy growing. Also, [more diverse countries are more successful](http://www.citylab.com/work/2011/12/diversity-leads-to-economic-growth/687/), just as diverse cities are a nation's economic engines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tulsi Gabbard in New Trouble Over Her Syria Jaunt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Europe isn't very diverse. Imagine if over 80 or 90 percent of America was white like most European countries, then imagine how much more successful campaigns against immigrants of other ethnicities would be. Just look at how whites vote in America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no Democratic candidate for Senate in Nevada less than two months from the deadline, and eight districts Hillary won have no House candidate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Royal Philharmonic Orchestra - Another Brick In The Wall [Classic Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 10:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this is a back-door pilot and it gets commissioned for a full series, that was fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 08:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rosie should be Trump. Kathy Bates would be perfect as Bannon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria has secretly executed thousands of political prisoners: rights group </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 08:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 06:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Kathy Bates would make a good Bannon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Good Germans" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ordinary Americans carried out inhumane acts for Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was not expecting that voice come out of that person. Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nicole Zefanya - New York State of Mind [Pop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon's supermarket of the future could operate with just 3 staff  and lots of robots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon's supermarket of the future could operate with just 3 staff  and lots of robots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon's supermarket of the future could operate with just 3 staff  and lots of robots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They prefer Saudi Arabia to be allied with the West than to form a wealthy and powerful Russia-China-Saudi alliance against the West. The alternative to the West selling to Saudi Arabia is not an unarmed Saudi Arabia. It's Saudi Arabia armed against the West. And Russia is very happy to promote discontent in the West over its relations to Saudi Arabia, Europe, NATO, all international relations, so that Russia can become the nexus of international relations instead of America and the West. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kremlin wants apology from Fox News' O'Reilly over Putin comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 11:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 18 dead after foot massage parlor goes up in flames, manager detained by police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 11:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 08:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you know someone who needs one of these prepaid debit cards, I highly recommend the [American Express Bluebird](https://www.bluebird.com) card, because it has no fees for normal use except an out-of-network ATM fee, and there are lots of in-network ATMs so you can even avoid that. It's just the best prepaid card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to get your phone drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just [tweet an Instagram to the White House MySpace](http://www.vox.com/2017/1/27/14399024/white-house-comments-line-closed-facebook-messenger) or something.

Edit: The White House comment line is still out of service, I just checked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House Petition Site Broken Since Inauguration Weekend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just do +++++. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've even [sued over 1000 reviewers](https://techcrunch.com/2016/10/27/amazon-sues-more-sellers-for-buying-fake-reviews/) for unscrupulous behavior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 13:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The audio is briefly weird 5 minutes in. A clean copy of the segment is [here](http://www.npr.org/programs/wait-wait-dont-tell-me/513277599/wait-wait-for-feb-4-2017-with-not-my-job-guest-mavis-staples?showDate=2017-02-04). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait Wait! 4 Feb 2017 (Faith Salie, Luke Burbank, Roxanne Roberts, guest Mavis Staples) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 13:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keeping 200 miles between herself and a Twitter troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Melania is hard at work combatting online harassment. That's her self-declared cause. After stating that a Jew [provoked](http://www.jpost.com/Opinion/Melania-Trumps-blaming-Jews-for-provoking-follows-in-a-long-tradition-454912) her [online tormenters](http://fusion.net/story/296757/melania-trump-julia-ioffe-antisemitic-messages/). (The lampshade and soap refer to products made from the skin and fat of dead Jews.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was parodying Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 07:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We disagree about whether Trump is going to change his policies because of Elon, or just use Elon, the way Trump pretended to listen to Al Gore, and the way Trump says in his books he gets people on his side by pretending to be interested. But even if you have more faith in Trump and don't think Elon is just there because Elon needs favorable regulations, Elon doesn't have to promote a "middle way" on an ethnic immigration ban as though outright opposing such a thing is unreasonable. He's telling us we should "offer amendments" instead of oppose Trump's unnecessary ban. Either Trump is using him or he's using himself to calm Trump's opponents. I'm saying I'd rather he do his lobbying in private and just talk to us about cool tech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I listened to it [here](http://www.npr.org/programs/wait-wait-dont-tell-me/513277599/wait-wait-for-feb-4-2017-with-not-my-job-guest-mavis-staples?showDate=2017-02-04), which doesn't have the issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He vocally promotes ripping up international agreements, alliances, and organizations. It's not like he's hiding his threat to international stability. This should be something everyone agrees with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two-thirds of Britons believe Trump is 'threat to international stability' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Voice transcripts are terrible at transcribing the right phone number to call back  the most important part </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google Voice transcripts have improved a lot, but they almost always get the phone number wrong, so I always have to play the voicemail so I don't call a wrong number. Does everyone experience this? Someone called me twice, each time repeating their phone number twice, and Google Voice got it wrong all four times in three different ways. I'm in the Northwest, so it's not like Google's having to decipher a strong regional accent. I assume the problem is that phone numbers are random digits that have no contextual clues from the surrounding words. But it's also just 10 digits to learn to distinguish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not there to advise Trump. He's there because all of his companies are heavily dependent on government policies and rocket orders. He has to be there. I wish he wouldn't pretend he could tinker around the edges of an ethnic exclusion policy to create something reasonable, or promote Trump to us as a moderate, and would just acknowledge the position he's in and change the subject to cars and solar.

Edit: This is a reasonable, non-combative opinion. Elon can promote his goals to Trump without promoting Trump to us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 01:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish instead of talking about Trump, Elon would just acknowledge he needs NASA to buy SpaceX rockets and needs friendly government policies to sell electric cars and solar panels. We can all understand the position he's in. Instead of repeatedly promoting his role in the Trump administration, just focus on the futuristic stuff we actually want to hear about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - The kids have done literally zero wrong and are guilty of nothing but existing. And yet again, **these are all 100% legal visa holders, the ones people who rant about "illegals" pretend to think are the good immigrants.**
- Fox News is just the most prominent voice in a giant echo chamber.
- Care to explain what I blamed whites for? I blamed Fox News for ethnically dividing America into us good white working folks and those illegal, radical, violent immigrant, Muslim, inner-city folks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my TV watcher a Chromecast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're proving my point. This is a story about completely legal immigrants. No one being kept out has killed anyone, they're totally legal US visa holders. And yet here you are getting all sanctimonious about illegals (a word that is never applied to Americans who are actually convicted of crimes, yet gets applied to kids who have done absolutely nothing wrong, and people who come here legally and just overstay a visa) which has nothing to do with this.

This is Fox News's goal. Whip up the supposed threat of (massively declined) illegal immigration, brush aside some throwaway phrase about how you're not talking about the good ones. Get it to the point to where Fox News viewers see a Latino, they suspect them of being illegal and harbor negative sentiment to them.

Whip up fear of terrorists, among an audience that is statistically more likely to die from virtually any other thing imaginable. Push aside stories of whites killing Muslims. Get it to the point to where a Fox News viewer sees a Sikh on an airplane, they worry about Islamic terror.

Only talk about the white working class. Don't even acknowledge that the working class is very diverse. *White* working class. It doesn't matter that their race has nothing to do with it, assign a race to workers, and make it white.

Ta-da: Fox News has meticulously explained to you who the bad guys are: illegal immigrants, Muslim extremists, and, oh yeah, the violent "inner cities" (black people on screen). All to be feared by the good guys: The white working class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're going after completely legal, peaceful Muslim immigrants. It's not about illegals or radicals. It's about immigrants and Muslims. The words "illegal" and "radical" are just there to convince you to mistrust them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US government takes animal-welfare data offline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US government takes animal-welfare data offline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because this isn't a temporary immigration order, it's an ethnic purification program. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't an immigration program, it's an ethnic purification program. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take a 2-liter soda bottle and tilt it. Why does the soda cling less to the top part of the bottle where the gas has been, than to the rest of the bottle where the soda has been? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 09:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, TellsRacistJokes. Did you know that a popular alt-right pastime is to spread racist jokes online to take the taboo off racism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the article confused production with productivity. Productivity is measured as output per person. They could have had a productivity (and profit) increase but a production decline. The source article does say "per person." It also says they plan to scale from 60 to 1000 robot arms. Well, they planned to. The source article is from a year and a half ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how TJ Maxx stays in business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selective enforcement is a valid criticism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are people who cannot handle their own affairs, cannot sign contracts, cannot manage their finances. Even a fully competent person is more likely shoot themselves than a burglar if they own a gun, let alone anyone who was actually going to murder them or commit a capital offense.

Edit: Here are the [FBI's firearm statistics](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/wonk/wp/2015/06/19/guns-in-america-for-every-criminal-killed-in-self-defense-34-innocent-people-die/):

For every 1 "justifiable homicide" by gun, there are:  
2 accidental gun deaths  
34 criminal gun homicides, and  
78 gun suicides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We restrict gun sales. People are indeed deprived of the ability to put bullets through things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House rolls back rule restricting gun sales to severely mentally ill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nordstrom Said to Wind Down Ivanka Trump Brand Partnership </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nordstrom Said to Wind Down Ivanka Trump Brand Partnership </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then they can [kiss Kai Ryssdal goodbye](https://twitter.com/kairyssdal/status/610824212656230400). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Than 1,000 Bodegas in New York Are Striking to Protest Trump's "Muslim Ban" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Than 1,000 Bodegas in New York Are Striking to Protest Trump's "Muslim Ban" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radio stations around the country reportedly hacked to play YG's anti-Trump song </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New FCC chairman gives monthly cable box fees a renewed lease on life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd go off the air if they were so oppressive as to axe everyone who hinted at a personal opinion away from work through a dog whistle. You're being unreasonably draconian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim Ban Throws TV Shows into Chaos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intelligence agencies don't go to foreign courts and participate in trials to find out what they did. Instead, Russian intelligence agents get [arrested and disappeared](https://qz.com/898168/three-russian-cyber-arrests-one-suspicious-death-and-a-new-twist-in-the-us-election-hack/) for telling us what they did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. makes sanctions exceptions for some transactions with Russian intelligence agency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not unethical to have personal opinions in your social life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a personal blog. I would judge a reporter based on their reporting instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Illegal immigrant" is just a way to glue a slur on to "immigrant," same with "radical Islam." If you're forced to watch Fox, it's all "illegal immigrants," radical Islam" and "violent inner cities" (they want to say "violent blacks" but the closest they'll go is "violent Black Lives Matter"), all the ethnic enemies of the white working class. No other races work. Just us whites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's executive order is just an ethnic purification program. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump dials up Iran rhetoric in early morning tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump dials up Iran rhetoric in early morning tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump dials up Iran rhetoric in early morning tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really does feel like he's trying to break up the democratic West for Putin's benefit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article is mistaken. The Gallup approval rate for Trump is [43%](http://www.gallup.com/poll/201617/gallup-daily-trump-job-approval.aspx). The disapproval rate is 51%. According to the mods, there isn't a rule against misleading headlines, or in this case, plain old false stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gerrymandering for 2020: Virginia Republicans are trying to rig Electoral College votes for next election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ellen criticizes travel ban with Finding Dory, the film Trump watched last weekend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect this will have the same outcome as other automated coffee kiosks: It won't really take off. The technology isn't the problem, but customers still think of a traditional coffee shop as better, and they're everywhere. This robot cafe looks particularly colorless and sterile. You're trying to convince groggy people to start their mornings with you. Looking like an abandoned laboratory may not work.

I suspect the automation of coffee shops will happen more the way Starbucks is doing it. Machines already make your coffee, and mobile ordering is growing, in which you order your coffee from your phone, including ahead of time. This reduces the staff at coffeeshops, sometimes down to one person, without publicly branding the cafe as automated, which some customers think of as dystopian, less friendly, or like a coffeemaker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robot baristas now serving in SF cafe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I don't know if quality frozen meals would be more than a niche, one big factor is that restaurant meals cost more, due to the staff and prime rents. Once automated home delivery, such as by self-driving cars, becomes possible, meals could be cooked on demand and delivered efficiently. While others are right that there would still be occasions to prefer a restaurant, this "restaurant delivery" at near grocery store prices would likely take market share from both restaurants and grocery stores. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 10:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is way too optimistic about how the media conversation will really play out. The debate will be over why participation was lower than expected, right-wing media will declare proof of a silent majority for Trump, as will the White House, and organizers will have to argue against the numbers. Big crowds of protesters are much better optics than minority participation in an event that has no dramatic videos or photos to share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> African Union slams U.S. for taking its people 'as slaves' but not as refugees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> African Union slams U.S. for taking its people 'as slaves' but not as refugees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Small amounts of deadly nightshade are common in homeopathy. A quick search found a website that practically prescribes it like a horoscope:

**Belladonna Type**

The person most likely to benefit fron belladonna is extremely hot-headed and intelligent. Typically, disease strikes unexpectedly, like a bolt from the sky. If treated correctly, symptoms are relieved fairly quickly. Telling features are a very flushed face and shiny skin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Fast Start Likely Puts the House in Play in 2018 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Fast Start Likely Puts the House in Play in 2018 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homeopathic teething tablets with belladonna could be deadly, FDA warns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the US, a lot of people seem to think "homeopathic" just means "natural," but it's actually a [specific useless thing](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Homeopathy) that is [rightly mocked](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HMGIbOGu8q0) elsewhere. Sometimes homeopathy is even promoted for serious diseases, meaning people could forgo real care thinking they're using a natural alternative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homeopathic teething tablets with belladonna could be deadly, FDA warns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 08:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Schumer already said he was prepared to leave the seat open.](http://thehill.com/homenews/senate/315524-schumer-ready-to-leave-ninth-supreme-court-seat-open) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 08:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Male guardianship is Saudi, not Muslim. My Muslim ex didn't seem to mind gay people when he was dating one, and you're supporting a policy that will kill gay people in Syria. I said he was acting to promote us-vs-them politics, and observed that his exceptions include countries where he has political and business interests. You're also proudly demonstrating the vilification you claim to despise in Muslims, projected onto Muslims. It's classic tribalism: Your excuse for hating them is that they hate us. That's the terrorists' excuse for hating us, too. But in reality, we don't hate Muslims, you hate Muslims. And Muslims don't hate us, Muslims like you hate us. People like you are the problem, everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More ad hominem. That is a crutch. You also present another fallacy: false dichotomy. All major democracies are republics. People vote for elected representatives who do the legislating. But all of them, at some point in forming their modern democracies, studied our democratic system and others. Many took concepts straight from us. None of them took the electoral college, not even the ones that also have "states" in their name, because it's a bad idea. Yes, your vote is worthless in Texas, and in most other states. It's a terrible system. You only like it because it benefits your political tribe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said nothing regarding either insulter's mental power or the merits of their insults. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be like a White ban, then starting with Africa.

He specifically highlighted that he only chose majority-Muslim countries, and that he is prioritizing Christians for refuge. The headline didn't call it a Muslim ban, and neither did the text. It accurately said it was based on religion rather than a specific event. No one from these countries has been involved in terror killings of Americans. Saudis have, but they're not banned, because like some of the other countries you listed, Trump has political and business interests in maintaining relations there. This isn't about our security. It's about us-vs-them politics. The radical Muslims. The illegal immigrants. The violent inner cities. These are the big threats to the white working class in our great-like-it-used-to-be America. Vote for the man who defends you from the Muslims ^^^politically ^^^useful ^^^countries ^^^excluded . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More ad hominem. The standard response to your original fallacy is that pointing out that something is old doesn't mean something is good. In fact, the electoral college is fundamentally anti-democratic, as it makes most Americans' votes worthless, whether you're rural or urban, and presidential candidates respond by ignoring most Americans. If you were honest with yourself, you support the electoral college because it puts Republicans in the White House. And spare us any false bromides about how the electoral college made rural farm issues important in this election, and the other standard smokescreens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an [easy to read explanation](http://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/no-barack-obama-jimmy-carter-9717520) of the differences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's ad hominem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's argumentum ad antiquitatem, or to use your words, a meaningless argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's voters are heavily [elderly](https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/where-trump-got-his-edge/), and less educated. They are not the most productive workers of society, if that's the insult-laden new excuse for Trump's smaller crowd sizes, including his smaller crowds on election day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, I thought you were saying Trump won because the left was name-calling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just as a data point, I'm [literally being called a cunt](https://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/5qx58p/protest_against_trumps_immigration_order_in_boston/dd3167h/) elsewhere in this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the election was a referendum on civility, someone forgot to tell The Donald, both the sub and the man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, did the Tea Party have an effect on 2010 midterms? Do angry hordes of voters get noticed by senators, representatives and local officials who don't want to get on the wrong side of those voters and who have the power to do things that please those voters? Did the Women's March change the national conversation from "Trump is America's new president" to "Trump is America's least popular new president?" It's not only an expression of real, measurable public sentiment, it also changes politicians' strategies when they see that sentiment materialized, and it changes the story of what's happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are two individuals specifically excluded by name, not a general ban. Also, it's an attempt to change the subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just taking the top horrible thing [you cited](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5ol8xm/julian_assange_under_pressure_to_hand_himself_in/dcl4tt5/) that was from the Podesta emails. Seemed to bother you a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good effort by a National Review writer to try to make it seem banal. But the real stories of who is affected cuts through that. Samira Asgari, a 30-year old Iranian woman who was on her way to the US to start a postdoctoral fellowship in genomics at a Harvard-affiliated hospital, was told her visa was no longer valid and denied boarding a US-bound flight in Frankfurt. Nazanin Zinouri, a Clemson engineering graduate of Iranian descent whod lived in the US for seven years and legally worked at a technology firm, was blocked from returning from a trip to visit her parents. Suha Abushamma, a doctor at the Cleveland Clinic with a Sudanese passport, was denied entry in the US and forced to leave the country. Now the world's scientists will avoid the US, and all that talent will go to other countries instead. International conferences will have to be held abroad to accommodate everyone, and to avoid the possibility of more chaotic surprise immigration orders. But foreign-born persons inside the United States can't attend, because they could be barred from returning to the US. This is not normal. This hurts the United States. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She wasn't at the DNC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump made a white nationalist immigration argument during the campaign that most media didn't notice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boston voted overwhelmingly for Clinton, and the US voted for Clinton by over 2.8 million. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a slightly different angle from an [official news account](https://twitter.com/NancyChenNews/status/825789351837708288).

Edit: I meant to link [here](https://twitter.com/NancyChenNews/status/825773424224194560). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For what, ethnic impurity? The order bans legal immigrants. It's an old-school genetic purification program. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Protest against Trump's immigration order, in Boston </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has [dual citizenship](http://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/could-mo-farah-banned-under-9714194). Dual citizens [are banned](http://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-visa-ban-also-applies-to-citizens-with-dual-nationality-state-department-2017-01-28). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was selective outrage by people who already opposed Clinton. Gosh, Podesta privately thought something would hurt Hillary but publicly said it was no big deal? How dare he downplay potential negatives. I'm sure we wouldn't see anything like that in every campaign ever. Certainly not the Steve Bannon emails we never saw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, can you name something the DNC did? The DNC did not act on that, and you didn't say what about the debates made them extremely favorable to Hillary.

However, Bernie Sanders did repeatedly lie about the DNC and the debates. He said they reduced the number of debates by falsely comparing the 6 debates they scheduled in 2016 with the total number of debates in 2008, when it turns out the DNC only scheduled 6 debates in 2008 as well (and also 6 in 2004, it's always 6), and that it's up to the candidates to agree to additional debates. According to O'Malley, Sanders refused additional debates, allowing the anti-DNC narrative to continue. Sanders also said the debates were poorly scheduled to hide them, when in fact the DNC scheduled the higher-rated broadcast debates earlier in the schedule where Sanders would get the most benefit, while the RNC delayed their broadcast debates and even cancelled the NBC one. All broadcast debates for Republicans and Democrats were scheduled for weekends, so Sanders said that was a Democratic attempt to hide the debates, when it's actually the networks who decide their schedules. And actually, Democrats got a Sunday debate, which is a high-rated night. All cable debates were scheduled for weekdays, just like the Republicans. And the scheduling was done way before the NFL announced its schedule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the lies about the emails, smeared across the internet, from feasting on blood to the widespread misbelief that Hillary's emails were ever hacked, harped and crowed about for months to [crowd out](http://www.gallup.com/poll/195596/email-dominates-americans-heard-clinton.aspx) anything positive. That was the same reason for all the other nothing-scandals about Clinton that mysteriously disappeared after the election. WikiLeaks dropped the first Podesta email batch just hours after the pussy tape dropped. It was all a game of misdirection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the Dem establishment DID undermine and cheat Bernie 

Can you name something the DNC did? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as he continues to attack The Other, they'll remain on his side. It's tribalism. The liberals are the evildoers, catering to the ^^^illegal immigrants, ^^^radical Muslims, ^^^violent ^^^inner-city blacks and other enemies of the white ^^^working ^^^class population </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Defense Secretary Robert Gates: Big Mistake for Trump to Exclude Members of National Security Council </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Dangerously Isolated President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sandi teaches Alan a new party trick - QI: Series N Episode 15 Preview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Government scientists launch 'rogue' Twitter accounts to 'spread the truth' and defy President Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Government scientists launch 'rogue' Twitter accounts to 'spread the truth' and defy President Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parliament can easily respond. Maybe it's worth it to a company to dick with lawmakers over some soda, but probably not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Super-Sized Global Gag Rule: Donald Trump did not just reinstate a pre-Obama ban on U.S. assistance to overseas groups that perform or even talk about abortion, he vastly expanded its reach. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats are putting up a tougher fight than liberals realize </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats are putting up a tougher fight than liberals realize </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats are putting up a tougher fight than liberals realize </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Super-Sized Global Gag Rule: Donald Trump did not just reinstate a pre-Obama ban on U.S. assistance to overseas groups that perform or even talk about abortion, he vastly expanded its reach. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I downloaded a fresh copy and it did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about the Android app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tl;dr: Completely legal immigrants, who are completely up-to-date on their paperwork and always have been, and who have never been charged with anything, can now be deported as criminals. Agents now just need to say a legal immigrant has done something "chargeable," and without any charges, they can be deported.

Legal immigrants were supposed to be the good guys, the ones anti-immigrant folks swore they weren't attacking when they branded immigrants as "illegal." But just like with "radical Islam," it's morphed into a demonization of the whole broader group. We now have ethnically classified good guys and bad guys, thanks to systematic word association. The good guys are "working class whites," and the bad guys are "illegal immigrants" and "radical Islam," with "violent and racist black ^^lives ^^matter " now also popular in conservative media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Immigration Order Expands the Definition of 'Criminal' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 04:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google Voice doesn't work on wifi-only devices like Hangouts does. :( Unlike Hangouts, Voice requires you to confirm your phone's number by sending a text message from the number in the phone's settings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teen retailer Wet Seal is suddenly closing all of its stores </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teen retailer Wet Seal is suddenly closing all of its stores </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the [study link](http://science.sciencemag.org/cgi/doi/10.1126/science.aah6524). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the [study link](http://science.sciencemag.org/cgi/doi/10.1126/science.aah6524). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girls are affected by stereotypes by age 6, new study shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girls are affected by stereotypes by age 6, new study shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moore's law isn't about clock speed, it's about transistor size. That's why they're talking about components smaller than atoms. And really, it wasn't proposed as a law, just an observation of past developments that has held ever since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mary Tyler Moore plays game show with rest of Dick Van Dyke Show in 1962 / in memoriam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mary Tyler Moore on panel game with rest of Dick Van Dyke Show in 1962 / in memoriam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: Experts, Who I Wont Name, Tell Me Torture Absolutely Works </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's an article.](http://washington.cbslocal.com/2017/01/25/protesters-climb-270-foot-tall-crane-at-d-c-construction-site/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giant "RESIST" banner near White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game show host gets very surprised at answer (Pointless) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge: Aetna lied about quitting Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge: Aetna lied about quitting Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ukraine lost its nuclear deterrent and got annexed. Russia doesn't mess with larger militaries. That's why Putin wants small former Soviet states to be left undefended by NATO. The US isn't rolling tanks into Russia. Russia is rolling tanks into its neighbors. The US and NATO are preventing further Russian aggression in NATO countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could also partly be an editing decision. The editors decide how much of each panelist you hear, mostly based on whether they think the comments are funny, as well as timing and other factors. Short quips that get laughs are probably the most likely to stay in, since they punch up the show at little cost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So press 1 for Russian, then... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really dislike call-in shows. Instead of quality content, we get complaints you can overhear at any bus stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show me Russia's war with NATO states. Deterrence prevents war.

Your vacuous ridicule is an ugly way to lose a debate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats won the most votes for Senate and president, and Republicans only got the most votes in the House because of uncontested hopeless rural districts. You can say Republicans entered office, but they hardly crushed the opponents who got more votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Dakota GOP will declare 'state of emergency' to repeal voter-approved ethics reform law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On this show, you're given a category like "UN member states" and you have to try to provide a correct answer that the fewest members of the public guessed. If it's a correct answer that none of the public guessed, it's "pointless" (the title of the show) and you get 0 points, with lower scores being best. In this round, the category was UK top 40 albums of the past year, and the host, Alexander Armstrong, had put out an album of classic songs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game show host gets very surprised at answer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 13:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deterrence is to prevent war. That's why Putin complains about the US military protecting NATO countries but no war ever actually breaks out. Putin wants to take back other Soviet territory like he did Ukraine and much of Georgia, but America's "war machine" has prevented war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, you can have some freedom of speech and not expel critics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump makes early move on restricting abortions around the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump makes early move on restricting abortions around the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
