<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8128</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downvote for irresponsible parenting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's true. [I was even in a unit that had a skull, cross pistols and lightning on the guidon](http://i.imgur.com/dp0yMFF.gif)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you go see a movie that you know is going to be filled with stuff you won't like? It's pretty obvious from the trailers what it's about, that's why I didn't waste time with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 10:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't get offended but I could tell by his reaction that people mistake his accent constantly and he was well past the point of humoring others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To my shame I once mistook someone from South Africa as being from New Zealand. Then I learned not to play "guess the accent" with strangers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are they supposed to accomplish? Impeach Trump? Not going to happen, at least not yet.

If they want to affect change they need to run for office or vote and not just in the presidential election.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 07:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would have been better if they had just  voted. I doubt these protests will do anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if they're "lounge pants" though?!
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds awful. I'm actually sort of near Swabisch Hall right now. That is surprising because the Germans around here seem so scared to talk to strangers unless they are drunk.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it easier for them to fade into society

Traveling has definitely made me realize how nice it is to just fit in. I've been overseas (from the US) for a little while now and, depending on where I am, I can physically pass as a local if I dress properly but as soon as I open my mouth and butcher the local language I keenly feel like an outsider.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know your experience but squats are one of those things you can really fuck up and not realize until you're lifting heavy and hurt yourself. Post a good video for a form check or get someone who definitely knows what they are doing to check out your form.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was the five rings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on where you go. I had a pretty good experience at the first one I went to, it was frequented by people in law enforcement and a couple of the instructors were state police. They routinely practiced grappling maneuvers, weapon retention and disarming people. I stayed at that one for about a year. 

The second place I went to wasn't too great they mostly did bag work and never went into anything that was remotely complex.

I've seen videos of places that are pretty amazing in that they appear to almost be prepping their students for extended urban combat but I've never been to one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are cultures that require it even if it isn't a law for the entire country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess that would depend on specifically where "home" is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/8buJ2-oD02E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole song is pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet karma. He'll just delete and repost the same thing later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find a hobby that you like. Usually you can find social groups for most of the more common hobbies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah you beat me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that is blurry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's everywhere](https://i.imgur.com/zYZdJKA.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ageism!!!111 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 10:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very smart. I've seen a lot of people who jump right in spending way too much money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice shot.

If you care about criticism, I would get closer so that the object in the foreground is gone. Also maybe do a longer exposure to brighten it up a little bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Creative Commons licensing seems weird to me. If you're building a community why not just communicate with the copyright owner and ask to use their image? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the cop said he was yelling something like that but not from the movie ~~*Tommy Boy*~~ *Black Sheep* it wouldn't be unheard of.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably named after the horse (Artax) from the Neverending story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
