<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4830</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. The GOP deserves a taste of its own medicine. This hyper politicizing of Supreme Court nominees does need to be fixed, but the GOP should be made to squirm for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see the cat burning part being a joke but as other people have posted, Fr Z sounds like a nut. I could also see a bunch of Priests getting drunk on Church wine and debating what to do if a mouse ate a Eucharist. I doubt that any answer they gave would make much sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had similar problems when I was younger and it caused a lot of problems. I would meet someone I was attracted to, but as soon as I thought they wouldn't measure up to my mother's high Catholic standards, I would basically sabotage any chance of the relationship going anywhere.

I agree with what other people are saying: it's your life, make your own choices. I ultimately married an atheist.

But some other pieces of advice that eluded me when I was in my early 20s.

Dating does not mean marrying. It's totally fine and fun, to just go out on dates without thinking, is this going to lead to marriage? Am I going to have to introduce this person to my parents? Go out with people who you find attractive and interesting. You will learn more about yourself too, what you want out of a relationship, what you like sexually, and what type of person you want to be in a relationship with. Don't rush the marriage issue. There's no reason to introduce everyone you date to your parents. If it helps, tell them you are going out with a friend. All of this might sound obvious to most people, but I didn't get it for a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should just pick up the phone. The FBI is too busy investigating all the Trump scandals. They have no time to look at stupid Twitter comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to understand why people who voted for Trump would be upset with a Trump Presidency. Since he was sworn in, it's just been an extension of his campaign. The daily (hourly?) scandals. The ridiculous tweets.He is even attempting to put a lot of his campaign promises into law, or at least executive actions.

The health care replacement was a big failure, he has totally failed to "drain the swamp", and he hasn't gone after Hillary, but otherwise he is pretty much right on the money with his campaign.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Perez wont apologize for insulting Trump and GOP leaders. Heres why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confirmation Watch: What to Watch: Senate Judiciary Committee Votes on Neil Gorsuch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will only believe it when he releases his score cards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five men shot at Pittsburg birthday party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since he can't do anything else right, I hope he at least improves his golf game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hide and seek </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps joyless presidency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 14:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Are Trump's White House Aides Worth? Read Their Financial Disclosures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White House doesnt sound so keen on granting immunity to Michael Flynn anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA chief Scott Pruitt is under ethics investigation for lying to Senate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The odds are growing by the hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sure took them a long time to paint some American Airlines logos on pieces of scrap aluminum or on a cruise missile cover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw that one posted on Facebook and was getting excited. I mean, it's not even April yet. Damn those early pranksters!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump White House is in deep legal trouble, according to the Trumps own standards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Jared Kushner employee: Trumps new innovation czar lacks expertise in how to innovate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cacti, Foxes, Solar Panels, and Other Bids to Unmake Trump's Wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Calling Nafta Worst Trade Deal, Trump Appears to Soften Stance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to find something that you aren't looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was funny up to the point they started talking about burning a cat. Fuck those people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be bigly awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh happy day! What's the over under on impeachment date? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's more American than the right to complain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Womp, womp, womp. Another day, another huge scandal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but by your metric, anyone saying President Trump is a crappy President with a record low approval rating would also be saying the sky is blue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize that the Berkeley City Council calling for impeachment will have no real effect, but it's still legit news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  reputable sites

It's from the San Francisco Chronicle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much like the tired "it's all George Soros' fault refrain from the right". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That qualifies as a source in Trump's America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Source](http://www.mediaite.com/tv/cnn-guest-berkeley-rioters-were-actually-secret-right-wingers-affiliated-with-breitbart/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTFY: ~~Anti-American communist~~ Extremely patriotic American elitists at Berkeley hate an extremely ~~patriotic~~ unpopular American capitalist with a highly pro-~~blue collar~~ rich people platform? Color me not shocked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that President Trump is taking on the Freedom Caucus and threatening to work against them in the mid terms, he just made some new enemies who are unlikely to support any upcoming Trump agenda items. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out President Trump's twitter feed. He is the biggest gentle snowflake there is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another thing that could push Republicans to impeach is the mid terms. If President Trump continues to have terrible approval ratings, that's going to hurt Republicans in Congress at the mid terms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those weren't Berkeley students, but paid Republican trouble makers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The probably figure Pence has even less chance of getting elected in 2020. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Let them fight](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XKdJ6DnPhzk). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Believe me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps unpopularity is historic  because it usually requires a war, a Watergate or a recession </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WATCH: Samantha Bee hits Donald Trump, Republicans for blaming everyone but themselves for health care disaster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Progressive Congressman Who Lost His Seat Because Of Obamacare Explains Why It Was Worth It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China Confirms Details of Trump-Xi Meeting at Mar-a-Lago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's going to take a lot more for Paul Ryan to accuse Trump of sedition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Expressing the sense of the House of Representatives that gun violence is a public health issue (H.Res. 90) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what happens when you throw vibrators into the ocean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New 'Bathroom Bill' To Ban Priests From Using Public Bathrooms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 07:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 07:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When you fail, again, to get the majority of the US public on your side

We didn't fail on that this last time. Hillary won the popular vote.

 One thing is a definite certainty, and that is after 6-8 years, the Left will be utterly broken

Just like the left was broken after 8 years of Bush and then elected one of the best Presidents this country has ever had.

 Lady Gaga has no power here.

Nope, Kayne West for President in 2020!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 07:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm far from an expert on Nixon, but it looks like a [Democratic majority impeached him](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/93rd_United_States_Congress). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman killed, 2 men wounded in midmorning SF shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Power to the people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those holligans were paid conservative protestors brought in to stir up trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a Republican Congress to impeach a Republican President, Trump would need to do something really crazy. Maybe burn down the White House or raise taxes on the wealthy. Our best bet for impeachment is getting Democratic control of the House at the mid terms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Berkeley calls for Trump impeachment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome sauce. I'm still looking for my first shiny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was all kinds of awkward talking about sex in my house. Basically, don't do it until your married, and you will be in a shit ton of trouble if you do before marriage. We never really had "the birds and bees talk". I was fortunate to go to public school at a time when a fairly comprehensive sex ed program was taught. But still, I had all sorts of issues around sex for a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm guessing this isn't supported by Rome - Association of Roman Catholic Women Priests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping to at least get a 100% IV Magikarp, but the best one I've got is 97%. I might evolve that one and then keep 400+ candy for when/if I find a shiny one or a 100% version.

These shiny fish are ridiculously rare. About as hard as it's been to find all the upgrade items. I've found 6 metal coats but am still missing most of the others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My precious... it certainly feels that way looking for a Shiny fish. I hope the shinies continue to be available but at the regular Magikarp spawn rates. The event has ended. I've got over 800 Magikarp candy, but no gold fishies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authorities: Cops shoot one of their own during celebration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, interesting. I didn't know there was a difference between shininess and accessories like hats. The Pikachu hats were only available for a brief amount of time. Do we know if the magikarp shiny variant will be available after this event ends? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The approach I've been working on is to:

* Keep the top IV of each Pokemon.
* When a level 1 IV is better than a level 2 or 3, I evolve it. ex: Pidgey has a higher IV than Pidgeotto, evolve it. In some ideal world, I would have a 100 IV of every Pokemon. 
* Keep best IV of each Shiny variant (so far that's the Pikachu and Raichu Santa and party hat versions). I'm still trying to find a Gold Magikarp.
* I'm starting to keep the best IV of each gender, when there is some visual difference in gender.
* For my good fighters, I keep more than one, and keep powering them up.
* I haven't found an Unown yet, but I plan to keep the best IV of each letter. Hopefully, I'll eventually find the full alphabet.
* In the recent software update I noticed they added gender icons in the Pokedex, so now that's something to obsess over, getting a complete set.

Is there a full list of existing shiny variants and a list of which Pokemon have visual gender differences? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump has successfully created an alternate reality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps assault on the planet: Undoing Obamas work on climate change wont be as easy as new president thinks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Senator Is Taking on the Pharma Companies Behind the Opioid Epidemic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Cold War Intrigue Can Tell Us About the Trump-Russia Inquiry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm advocating the cops to chill out, but disarming would be okay too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great! Thanks for making the video. I'm going to try this soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 01:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the shiny Magikarp only available until the end of the event? I'm still looking for one.

I reviewed my journal after using my Pokemon Go Plus on the drive home last time. A Lapris got away. Damn it!

A question about the shiny fish. Do they show up in their shiny gold on the Nearby radar, and when they first appear on the screen near you?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 01:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and it goes without saying that if someone is living in a house illegally, they obviously should expect to be shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTFY: "One small price to pay for humanity, one huge price to pay for the poor sucker who got shot by Trump's Gestapo Force." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why is ICE acting and behaving like the god damn SS?

Ummm, have you been following the news of our current Administration? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need to write a script that will have your computer browse all sorts of random sites when the computer is ideal, just to mess with whoever is buying this history data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you on the Domestic Terrorist label not being used nearly enough. Especially if the person with an itchy trigger finger is white, Christian, and the typical Murcia as Apple pie chacteristics. I thought the Bundy Ya'all Queda folks should have been given the Domestic Terrorist label from the get go, given their obvious political agenda. Same with all the home grown militia folks with their fantasies of over throwing the government.

America just isn't willing to make an honest assessment of all the problems firearms cause. Instead it's easier to blame people at the margins. Illegal immigrants and Muslims are the current favorites. Arguments about immigrants committing less crime, sanctuary cities have no higher crime rate, and the countries on Trump's travel ban attempts producing basically none of the terrorists who have attacked America--those arguments fall on deaf ears.

It would get really uncomfortable for a lot of folks if they looked at the news each day and read about America's latest home grown white Domestic Terrorist and people started debating how to restrict their access to guns. We can't even pass the most basic common sense gun laws.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump 'Deportation Force' Just Shot A Legal Resident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still on the first battery. It's been 3-4 weeks using it several hours each day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The faster I'm going the less likely it is that a stop will spin. My commute is pretty slow with traffic so it's easy to spin a lot of stops, and I can keep my eyes on the car in front of me and not the phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why President Trump has been very good for liberals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WATCH: Stephen Colbert throws Trumpcare into the cabinet of broken Republican dreams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political Calculus: A 2016 Review: Turnout Wasnt the Driver of Clintons Defeat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 13:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had one for about a month and love it.

* Works great in the car, and not as dangerous as messing with my phone. It doesn't seem to be affected by the "your going too fast" popup, and it often gets Pokestops that I could rarely get on the phone.
* Gain XP faster. Whenever the thing buzzes, I press.
* It sees Pokemon that are a little further away and haven't yet shown up on the phone.
* The different buzzing patterns (Pokestop/New Pokemon/Pokemon you already have) make it easy to play without even looking at it.

What would make it better?

* Rechargeable battery with USB charging support.
* Greater configurability. Currently, you can select if your want to look for Pokestops and/or Pokemon. It seems to weight Pokemon before Pokestops, even when I've got little to no Pokeballs. Would be nice to configure to skip certain Pokemon, or even set an order of priority. It only uses the basic red Pokeballs, and only throws one then gives up. More configurablity to use other ball types and throw more than one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've caught 513 and have 73 biggies, or 14.2%. Still no golden floppy fish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still confused at how badly Trump and Ryan messed this up. They had plenty of time to come up with a plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who are these ~~fools~~ people who still approve of President Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is giving a lot of mixed messages about whom to blame on health care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Par for the course: White House says Trumps golf outings to his courses were meetings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a tough one. I was worried this would happen when I got married, but thankfully the uber Catholic family and relatives kept their objections to themselves.

I would go forward with the wedding as you want it. It's your special day. I wouldn't cut your father out of the wedding or make threats. Instead, I would tell him how much he means to you and how much you want him there. He may not change his mind, but at least you are taking the high road.

As others have said, if you give in to his wishes now, the same problems will likely come up when you have children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This baby is ready for takeoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TVs gold standard: Trumps proposed budget cuts decimate network leading the way in climate reporting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boris Epshteyn, Trump TV Surrogate, Is Leaving White House Job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 13:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump played a game of chicken with House Republicans. Then he blinked. Bigly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This week in Donald Trumps conflicts of interest: The president gets a win </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a Call to The Times, Trump Blames Democrats for the Failure of the Health Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just checked, the iOS update is finally available. Downloading...

Edit: After downloading, none of the Magikarp I caught in the past few days are golden/yellow. Drats. The hunt continues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 22:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad, so sad.

If only the Republicans had years to craft a bill that was just right instead of trying to rush through a bill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glock 9mm offered as prize in California high school fundraiser raffle. Would be school shooters beware, must be 18 or over to enter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wouldnt want to lose my mammograms, male GOP senator says  then immediately regrets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York City's Youngest Councilman Grew Up in the Projects. Now He's Defending Them Against Trump. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 08:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of being a Manchurian Candidate for Russia, it turns out he is secretly working for the Democrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Thank you! Thank you! I have missed your great site and am glad it's back! As a fellow developer, I totally understand other priorities in life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Spicer just shifted the White Houses stance on Paul Manafort and Russia. Again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Greeting to Iranian People, Trump Leaves Out Their Government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California Supreme Court to rule on gun law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How easy is this site to use for people who can't read Japanese? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the most honest, accurate description. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Democrats Neil Gorsuch dilemma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Putin use Breitbart and Infowars to help Trump? The FBI wants to know </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump Organization Says It's Vetting Deals for ConflictsBut Refuses to Say How </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is surprising that he didn't get in trouble with his superiors. He stole money from the Church. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SJ Catholic priest found guilty of embezzling from parishioners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The real reason Senate Democrats are going to oppose Judge Gorsuch for the Supreme Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ivanka Trump is getting an unpaid White House job, will voluntarily comply with ethics laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> School Choice Fight in Iowa May Preview the One Facing Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WATCH: John Oliver doesnt understand Trumps budget proposal because he doesnt speak fluent toddler psychopath </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Trump Golfing? White House Shrouds Time at His Clubs in Mystery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 12:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leaving the Catholic Church has a surprisingly similar effect as the TV commercials for anti depressants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I started going to a Unitarian Universalist congregation I found there were some similarity to the structure of Catholic Mass that I enjoyed, but without all the baggage that I dislike about Catholicism. They do have candles but no incense (incense usually left me with a headache). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jake Tapper and the 3 basic truths of covering Trumps falsehoods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So much for the Russian threat: Putin slashes defense spending while Trump plans massive buildup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senators Ask Trump Adviser to Preserve Any Russia-Related Documents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 12:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It probably goes back to the days of DB Cooper. It's people like that is why we can't have nice things like no security checks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This week in Donald Trumps conflicts of interest: Who says foreign policy shouldnt make you richer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 13:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 06:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm genuinely curious, what do you think TSA should do, if they find someone carrying a firearm through airport security? Should there be times when they let people carry them on the plane? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get you point, it's not like the TSA stopped 58 potential hijackings or terrorist attacks. But, what should the TSA do? Let people carry firearms onto a plane because they forgot to leave them at home? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean if they just carried a security blanket or favorite stuffed animal, it would have the same effect and they wouldn't get in trouble with the TSA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Spicers angry, lonely defense of Trumps wiretapping claim, annotated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump and Ryan: Health Bill May Test Marriage of Convenience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mental gymnastics of observing Lent, celebrating St Patrick's Day, and liking corned beef </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Rabbi, a Episcopal Priest and an Ex Catholic Smoke Weed Together </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TSA finds 58 firearms in carry-ons at U.S. airports in a week, including 2 in Sacramento </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps new excuse for setbacks: It wasnt my idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trevor Noah slams Paul Ryans new health care bill: This is the crap youve been hyping for 7 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Border Wall Gets Billions in Budget Proposal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stupid people and guns don't mix. Especially when it's a .44 Magnum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 50? sounds like the grand jury wasn't trying hard enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This 2005 Donald Trump tax return is a total nothingburger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps tax returns: What do we now know, and what do we not know? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Mini Version of Trump Is About to Take Over the USDA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public Health: Obamacare Isnt in a Death Spiral. (Its Replacement Probably Wont Be Either.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 05:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would there have been an advantage for Trump in tax payments to have his business profits and loss reported as corporate business taxes and then Trump paid as an employee/share holder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing I don't get is: why is Donald Trump reporting millions in business loses on his personal 1040 form? How are the various Trump owned businesses organized? Are these some sort of sole proprietorship small businesses that make and lose millions each year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'll show the Senate who the boss is. Especially since they have to decide between Neil Gorsuch and the ultra left gun grabber that Trump also nominated.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The CBO just dealt a huge blow to Republicans Obamacare replacement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamacare architect slams Republicans American Health Care Act as a scam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fact Check: Trumps Critiques of the Affordable Care Act </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would quickly erase the national debt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carjackers shot and killed a Houston-area father because his car had a manual transmission, which they didn't how to operate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's next? CIA monitoring via dental fillings? Where's my tinfoil hat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mother and baby home at Tuam, Ireland, where friends just disappeared, one after the other </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yes, Kellyanne Conway just suggested Trump Tower could have been monitored through TVs and microwaves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kellyanne Conway keeps doubling down on Trumps wiretapping claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Democrat Just Emerged to Run Against The Richest Man in Congress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would just ruin porn. No more anal, or money shots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And most of reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New bill takes aim at men's masturbation habits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Years ago I took one of those "what religion are you" surveys. I still remember how one of the responses I got was "the Catholic Church is too corrupt for you." Yup.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP congressman offers strange Obama conspiracy theory  and even stranger explanations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumpcare and you: How will the GOPs American Health Care Act change your health insurance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Congressional Maps Are Struck Down for Discrimination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 12:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an interesting glimpse into the fantasy world of Conservatives. I love the part about getting paid based on the wealth you create for your employer. Fucking Communist Capitalists. Sure sounds a lot like: [From each according to his ability, to each according to his needs](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/From_each_according_to_his_ability,_to_each_according_to_his_needs). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This congressman apparently cried after his first missed vote. But maybe he was spared a worse fate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This week in Donald Trumps conflicts of interest: Everything is coming up Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the Hundreds of Officials Trump Has Quietly Installed Across the Government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 13:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Revised Travel Ban Is Denounced by 134 Foreign Policy Experts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 13:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 08:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto to that answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Thanks for the quick work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it's time for another leak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans are rushing right into charges of Obamacare hypocrisy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps alleged computer server connection with a Russian bank continues to be investigated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans Just Made Trump's Reelection a Whole Lot Tougher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bar in D.C. Sues Trump and Hotel, Claiming Illegal Advantage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stand Your Ground Could Get Worse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 07:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for all the hard work. It's a great app. I look forward to getting back to scanning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the actual fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you manually level up all 60 accounts to level 3 on your phone? Is there some trick to leveling up all of them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How large of a radius do you search? Do 100 accounts help cut down on captchas, with more accounts to cycle through? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but it's also an act of war to drop bombs on a country, and arm troops that will fight the official government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the update. I'm okay with buying a paid API key. Is that a one time purchase? I'm a little confused by this sentence on the API key website:

 The limits around RPM's are bound per license and last a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Official: Couple hundred US Marines go into Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is having dinner with Ted and Heidi Cruz. Here are nine things that might make it awkward. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Running List of People Who Hate Trumpcare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Republicans Are Battling Republicans on Obamacare Repeal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be interesting to see a dollar cost averaging graph. For data points, you could use initial investment of $1000, and $100 invested each month, with dividends reinvested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 21 times Donald Trump has assured us he respects women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WATCH: Conan plays recorded phone calls between Trump, Obama after wiretap allegations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans' Only Selling Point for Their Obamacare Replacement Bill Is How Short It Is </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard the iPhone argument from some conservatives I know. The idea must be making the rounds in conservative circles. iPhones are the new Welfare Queens. Where are people finding thes cheap ass healthcare plans that are comparable to monthly cell phone bills? I'm paying a lot more for my employer provided health care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8 times the White House punted on Trumps tweets  by saying they speak for themselves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Critics: GOPs Obamacare replacement plan will destroy the ability of millions of Americans to access any health care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Trump Administration May Be Skirting Its Own Ethics Rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the Trumps Arrival in Washington Means for a Luxury Mall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bigger concern is: what if something should happen while the ban is in place. That worries me more. What kinds of crazy laws do they have stuffed away in draws just waiting for the right opportunity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 07:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pew! Pew! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Do you have any advice for standing up to parents about a conversion?

You will need to determine how your parents might react if you want to continue with leaving Catholicism. Since you are living at home, it might be worth while to at least try out the Byzantine Rite Church, if only to say "I tried it, and it's not for me". As for how to get to the Orthodox church in time for the service you want to attend. What are your options? Are you wanting your parents to drive you? That could be asking a lot based on their initial reaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming the courts don't stop this one, what's the point of this ban? How would anyone know if it worked?

As has been widely reported, the people coming from these nations aren't the ones committing terrorist attacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Some days I really wish I didn't get out of bed. At least Ben Carson lives up to his reputation of being even crazier than President Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
