<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4680</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it. Can someone explain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OPB canvasser here. Donate! ;) 
Edit: Preferably when I come to the door but whatever works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're gonna be rich! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm the real Reno! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine life is a movie. Instead of seeing moving pictures I was looking at each frame individually and like, pausing to look around. The way I experienced time fundamentally changed for about an hour. It was way too intense for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first bong problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! My GF and I started smoking lately. We've been smoking out of a pipe for a few months (his name is Henry and he's beautiful.) but we finally invested in a bong! We were excited but after smoking out of it my lungs had never hurt that bad in my life. I was in so much pain and we both got really sick. Also I was so high I lost touch with reality and it was horrifying. But my question is what did we do wrong? I thought it hurt less than a pipe... it's a nice glass bong FYI, not bad materials that made us sick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does the bastard, orphan...

I'm waiting for it to happen. It's not happening... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just moved from Salt Lake, actually. My dad works in the fashion industry and we tried to open a smaller independent trade show during other parts of the year for brands that can't/won't go to this one. 

They sued us for a shit-load for taking their market. We had to cancel the project at a huge loss. I can't say I'd recommend working with these guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/fakeid

Check it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at one of his shows once and he mentioned it's a line from a book but that he's not sure what it means.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh god... Not again... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be nice. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen any. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean Whomst'vever it attacks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it. Crows are cool. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 04:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/mcbSTyw

Not exactly midrange. More aggro. Some streamer made it and reached legend a little bit ago but I don't remember which. Either way, have fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have it in a pretty rad demonlock deck I'm running.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you explain? I think I missed those clues. But I'm intrigued.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good work. :) I'm proud of you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love La Colombe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the "This book isn't about me so I don't like it" syndrome. If you can't relate to the characters or they don't share your social, ethnic or economic background, you're less likely to enjoy it. Just sorta by nature. Doesn't make it bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw. Of course.
I hope she finds the center.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. George Washington, who predicted infighting between political parties would lead to politicians choosing party loyalty ahead of rational decisions, among other problems, all of which are rampant in America's political system today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree deeply with most of this list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 06:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rec user. I'd love to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maintain good diet sleep and exercise pupper  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 08:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A beautiful story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 04:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend just called this a turn-up tulip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was illuminating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 07:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a long and incredibly well thought out  comment to be posted while browsing from work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 07:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hate Werther as a book about depression... it grossly romanticized and glorifies depression while never cutting close to what it's really like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 07:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry. Just responded but I feel the need to add to my response. Most books talking about mental illness talk exclusively about just dealing with it, which is beautiful and extremely necessary. But I feel like Infinite Jest is the only book I've ever read the nails the beautiful, confusing, painful, and ultimately fulfilling process of recovery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 07:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's long and rambling but I made it through and I'm a moron so you'll be okay. 

It's lovely and a beautiful expression of mental illness, and in particular the process of recovery. It helped me through and I hope you pick it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! I remember doing that haha. It's hard. I hope you're proud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please delete this before trump sees... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much extra time should I plan when taking the busses today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ride is usually thirty minutes. Should I double that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sif is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enough depends on person to person and you'll just have to experiment. It also depends on the quality of weed. 

New York is an illegal state so beware of that. The negative effects of the illegality of it are much worse than any physical or mental effects of the drug. 

And no, it shouldn't impact your grades if you're a good student. I think a lot of people who are just bad student who don't do their work blame their lack of good grades on their smoking, at least in my experience. Just wait to relax until after your work is done. But you already know that, I'm sure. Which is my point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jade Varley? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that... a demon ass? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this. I feel like it could generate a crazy archetype where you use the self-harming cards to gain tempo and race to kill your self before your opponent can kill you. Sounds like it'd be insanely skill-dependent to run but it sounds fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 04:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Adams?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also send this to r/longdistance even if you're not. They'll love the idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On it from Portland OR! I'll send it tonight or in the morning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking American heroes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Postmodern Literature:

Beginner: Slaughter-house V, The Crying of Lot 49, If on a winters night a traveler

Veteran: White Noise, Watchmen, Beloved

Expert: Gravity's Rainbow, Pale Fire, Foucault's Pendulum

Absolute Madman: Finnegan's Wake (arguably modernist but I'm counting it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! I fucking love Harney! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allergies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would chocolate spread work for firecracker edibles? I can't use peanut butter or Nutella. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes

Dr. Booms sex dungeon

His favorite color is salt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F2p of course </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F2p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 07:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wait no I figured it out. You get the hero if you're retarded. 

F2p too of course what am I a fucking scrub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an extra class in hearthstone. Not sure how you get it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today I saw a hunter on ladder AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to clean a kettle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey. I keep having the problem of my coffee and tea making me vomit and I think it's because of my kettle, possibly. It always has little floating things in the water. Sometimes it does and sometimes it doesn't make me sick.

How can I properly clean my kettle? Or should I get a newer one since mine is very very old? Or is something else the problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up some of the shorter stories. The Rats In The Walls is my favorite. It'll take an hour or two at most. Try it out and if you like it, keep reading. 

Also, Bloodborne's awesome. :) I'm glad you're enjoying it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 09:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's rad! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What book is that??? It's so pretty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About your Fifty Shades thing, yeah it's technically consensual but it's an example of very bad BDSM practice. Boundaries aren't set well, bad communication and aftercare, etc  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamas presidency was </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As dank as the Obama kush I'm smoking tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 00:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soulbinder + Librarian combo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is quite the question. The Mormon church believes in something called the words of wisdom, which is basically a bunch of rules that say how to take care of your body. It was written during a time in which Mormon society was falling apart due to wide-spread alcoholism. This included a throw-away line that says not to consume "hot beverages", which has, in modern times, been translated as coffee and tea. I have no clue why, and I think it's absurd personally, and a violent misinterpretation of the text, but that's just me.

Sorry for the ramble but I hope it helps to make sense of it. 

Edit: Spelling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Utah coffee drinkers represent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am... Rock hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
