<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3180</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 21:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a rule in my family - fruit pie is ALWAYS a valid breakfast food. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 20:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not OP, but growing up my grandma always made the most incredible vegan chocolate cupcakes with vinegar, the recipe was similar to [this one](http://allrecipes.com/recipe/16779/vegan-chocolate-cake/) and I think it's a pretty common recipe. We called them "Depression cupcakes" since they were originally made in our family not to be vegan, but to get around expensive food and then rationed food during the war!

I can attest that it makes amazing chocolate cake, and no one would ever guess it's vegan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's [this edible gold dust](https://www.amazon.com/Wilton-Pearl-Dust-Gold-0-05-Ounce/dp/B000PWKNUK) - I found it in the baking section in Michael's. 

You can either brush it straight on the shell (which is what I did for the shells that are shimmery all over) or mix it with a little simple syrup to paint it on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pink shells filled with champagne buttercream + strawberry preserves.

Not my best batch ever (maybe I shouldn't try to bake at 11PM...) and the filling got pretty messy (note to self: don't try to pipe chunky strawberry preserves. It doesn't work well.) so I'm hoping the decoration distracts. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy New Year's Eve! I made strawberry   champagne macarons for tonight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a wonderful idea! I remember reading about hard sauce in the same cookbook, we should have made some. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, we approximated a lot but I can do my best! According to the cookbook we used, mincemeat's original purpose was actually to preserve meat, so people would make and store huge amounts of it, and then just use some of it for pie, which is why most of the recipes are in large amounts.

The original recipe we referenced was [this one](http://www.bartleby.com/87/r1446.html) I believe (we had it in hard copy, but this looks right). Basically we then cross referenced with [this scaled down recipe](http://www.ourheritageofhealth.com/old-fashioned-mincemeat-pie-recipe-from-1798/) which calls for 1lb of beef instead of 4 - based on that, we mostly just divided everything by 4! Ours was a little overly spiced, so I might recommend bumping the nutmeg down a bit as well.

Edit: So I think what we ended up with was approximately:

- 1lb chopped beef
- 1/2lb beef suet
- 2 apples
- 1 cup dried fruits (we mixed a few we had on hand)
- 1/2 cup brandy
- 1/2 cup sugar
- 1/2 cup molasses
- 1/2 tsp each of the listed spices (we used more nutmeg based on the recipe but next time I'd use less) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little backstory - mince pie has always been my dad's favorite, but we'd usually make it the lazy way, by buying the pre-made filling in a jar. This Thanksgiving, over a couple of slices of mince pie, we decided to try making the real deal - meat included! We used an old Fannie Farmer recipe and scaled it down to individual pie size (the original recipe calls for 4lbs of beef...).

It was actually good - tasted nothing like meat. The spices were a bit strong (apparently the mince is supposed to mellow with age, so next time we'd use less) so it could have used a little whipped cream to mellow it out. This is a new Christmas tradition for us - old-fashioned recipe suggestions welcome for next year! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not the prettiest thing I've ever baked, but my dad and I re-created an old mincemeat pie recipe for Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fireplace floof </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 16:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 20:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's maybe supposed to be smoke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a chain, they're everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not even really shy about it:

http://www.cc.com/video-clips/dxhtvk/the-daily-show-with-jon-stewart-suppressing-the-vote

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 16:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By hand?! I can't even imagine!! 

Looks delish, did you add anything to the shells or is it salted caramel in the middle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those look amazing! I'm intimidated by chocolate macarons but tempted to try... Is that raspberry in the middle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up eating making and eating anise cookies for Christmas! We called them Kris Kringles. Just emailed my mother asking for the family recipe... I know we only ever used anise extract, but we put it in both the cookie and the frosting. 

Edit: She finally got back to me. Here's the recipe with all her notes. I'm sure these are not exactly what you're looking for, but I can attest that they're delicious!

KRIS KRINGLE COOKIES

- 1 cup butter
- 2 cups sugar
- 3 eggs
- 1 1/2 tsp cream of tartar
- 1 1/2 tsp baking soda DISSOLVED IN --
- 2 Tbsp milk
- 1 tsp salt
- 1 tsp anise (can use vanilla if not Xmas)
  --- anise oil will give stronger flavor, but anise flavor is fine.
- 4 1/2 cups flour

Cream butter and sugar together.  Add anise, milk w/ baking soda, and eggs.  Mix.
Then add salt and cream of tartar sifted with 3 cups of the flour (I don't usually sift).
Gradually add more flour to make a dough that may be rolled.  Chill overnight or for 
several hours.  

Preheat oVen to 400 degrees.  Roll on lightly floured surface to desired thickness
(I do about 1/4 inch).   Cut and bake on ungreased cookie sheet,  400 degrees for
8 - 15 minutes till lightly browned on edges. They will cool to very crunchy and the 
frosting makes them softer again if you frost.

FROSTING

- 4 egg whites
- 1/2 tsp cream of tartar
- 1/2 tsp anise
- 5 cups sifted confectioners sugar

Beat egg whites and cream of tartar in very clean bowl until foamy.
Add anise.  Gradually beat in confectioners sugar until it forms soft peaks.
This takes a while!  If desired, divide into bowls and cober.  Frost.  Add colored
sugar or toppings as desired.  Let dry thoroughly before storing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cinnamon applesauce! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are so cute and festive! They look like something out of a storybook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if this "features" the Andes mints enough (I guess it's an awful lot like shoving them in a brownie...) but I made chocolate mint cupcakes at one point that were delicious. I didn't use Andes mints, but I bet you could bake chocolate cupcakes, core them and fill them with melted Andes? And then sprinkle crushed ones on top of the frosting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 13:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!! Not pictured, all of the ones I ruined before I figured out what I was doing... :) Doing this many batches in a row actually makes it easier to figure it out, I think! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 13:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!! I didn't save many since I'm gifting them (so.. fingers crossed those ones actually taste good!) but I did bite into a couple along the way and [one fully finished one](http://imgur.com/bIjwPbb) last night - I think it turned out well!

I pulled up a million "troubleshooting guides" while baking these (especially after a whole batch came out cracked with no feet) and of course every issue could possibly be caused by several different factors... It looks like hollow is possibly too airy after mixing or undercooked? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Bonus pic](http://imgur.com/bIjwPbb): after biting into a red velvet that I saved for myself. This is before the customary 24 hours of "maturing" in the fridge, but since the cream cheese frosting is pretty moist the texture was great!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first macarons - holiday gifts for my team </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From left to right: standard macaron shells filled with peppermint chocolate ganache, red velvet filled with cream cheese frosting, and vanilla bean shells with egg nog butter cream.

They're not perfect and I had to toss a batch and a half along the way, but I'm happy they turned out so well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made a trio of macarons (my first ever) as holiday gifts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Boston and I don't know what the hell that cocktail is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monkey's toebeans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 19:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I was on the road I hit up Wendy's and got a small chili and the spicy chicken nuggets - delicious, super filling, and something like 400 calories. Highly recommend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've come to my apartment twice. The first time I had literally just moved in and hadn't even signed up for utilities yet, so I told them as much and just shut the door.

Then they came back several months later and I told them the same thing... works great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol what?? All he said was

I don't recall people saying that not liking Hillary is sexist. A lot of people don't like her, liberals included. 

Which is also his own completely valid anecdotal data. My point is that this is just as valid as you saying you haven't seen anyone complain about Obama's race.

You guys are literally saying the same thing from different sides of the equation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fine, talk about your individual experience as much as you want. Just don't try to "question the honesty" of the dude above you because his facebook wall looks different than yours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? That's not even what I'm talking about.

I'm saying you can't claim that talking about Obama's race must be uncommon because you haven't personally seen it, but calling conservatives racist and sexist is super common because you see it on Facebook the time. The truth is that both of these things certainly happen, and like this election showed us, we live in bubbles and we see what we want to see. Your anecdotal evidence does not mean it's reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 03:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
 Well it happened to me many times on reddit and people are still saying it today, so to be fair I gotta question your honesty here. My Facebook feed is just a wall of my friends saying they "can't believe how sexist and racist this country is". 

and then 

 I personally have never met a single conservative who has mentioned Obama's race. I'm not saying they don't exist but I haven't seen it personally so I can't believe it's as common as you all pretend.

Do you not see a little bit of a conflict here? I mean come on, can't we all just admit that both of these things happen more than we'd all like to admit? There are people on both sides of the aisle who say dumb things like this.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I've read several of those. Like I said, I understand the mindset and wanting change - it's why so many of us voted Obama the first time around. My overwhelming reaction to this election is just... sadness, because regardless of who won the election I don't realistically think there's much we can do to bring back manufacturing jobs to rural areas, for example. That ship has sailed. In 8 years I foresee small dying towns to be in largely the same position but with fewer healthcare options. I didn't vote Trump but I hope he proves me wrong somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally understand the economic anxiety and frustration in many places - I just can't wrap my brain around picking a billionaire Republican who has so often shafted small businesses as the guy who will apparently fix it. My dad grew up in a dying town in upstate NY, his family relied on food stamps and medicaid even though both of his parents worked, and as a result he and my grandmother have been lifelong democrats because of the party's support for entitlements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 17:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. They are saying he won but does not represent them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 16:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol why were you appalled that one political party was discouraging you from voting for a different political party? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 01:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what your point is. I was just answering your question... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 17:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You monster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 14:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/WzYv5foyAS8?t=14s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just thought I'd share my mother's birthday cake, made by my 14yo brother: a Clinton/Kaine yard sign. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 12:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 23:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh I think it would be rude to not invite them at all.

If your MOH plains the party on the east coast because most girls are there, you could probably get away with inviting them but making it clear that they don't need to feel obligated to spend the money and travel that far, and maybe you can separately have a night out with them in the midwest somewhere. But you should still be prepared for the possibility that they might want to come.

If you really feel like you don't get along with them and they wouldn't gel with the group, I might reconsider asking them to be part of your bridal party (since you say you have't already asked). Integrating different groups of friends/family happens in most bridal parties and is expected, but you have to get along with everybody to make that work I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disclaimer: I'm not Jewish so I don't actually know that much about Jewish weddings, but my sister converted and married a Jewish guy, so maybe I can give the good and bad from the non-Jewish guest perspective.

Things that went well:

- They were married outdoors under a beautiful chuppah! These make such a great backdrop for photos.
- They had baskets of white yarmulkes that male guests picked up on their way into the ceremony. These doubled as favors, and I believe they had the wedding date embroidered in them but it's been years so I don't fully remember. My family is Catholic but they all totally loved these and willingly put them on for the ceremony. Very cute.
- I think everybody gets a kick out of the glass stomp and hava nagila/chair dancing. Literally had family members say "ALL of our weddings should be Jewish weddings!"

The less good:

- The ceremony was mostly in Hebrew, so none of us had any idea what was going on. He would say some sentences in English but there was a LOT of Hebrew singing... Good call on planning for the whole ceremony to be in English.
- The rabbi insisted on a kosher reception. Not a major crisis, but the food had to be vegetarian because of the wedding cake. We had also already done a food sampling with the venue before we found this out from the rabbi, so we had to pick food without tasting it. It turned out really well (think super fancy ravioli, etc) but if going kosher is not important to you, check with your rabbi to make sure he's cool with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure Howl at the Moon has some sort of package for bigger parties that lets you skip the line and reserves tables/drink service up front... I haven't done it but recall someone saying it was a good deal. Worth checking out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not the bride but I'm planning my sister's bachelorette weekend - it's not until late June of next year and I've already bought and crafted all of the favors plus made a decorative banner (plus I have a detailed grocery shopping list ready to go). So... now I basically just wait for 7 months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunset and surfers, Windansea Beach, La Jolla, CA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 13:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 22:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am SUPER pale and blue is one of the only colors that looks good on me... My sister originally wanted blush dresses but picked blue instead because it looks better on pale people. Especially because you've given them such a wide range, there is NO reason they shouldn't be able to find a flattering shade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
