<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7761</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it makes it better, like I appreciate it on a different level. I'm not just enjoying reading, but mining for ideas. In a way, I prefer it when the book I study for coursework is one I don't like, because then it doesn't spoil it for me. XD

We have to write a Wikipedia-style article about conflict during the Industrial revolution, using specific sources. I took part in a similar activity earlier in the year which went well. I can be a bit of a control freak when it comes to coursework, so it was definitely a learning curve! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to go into video game translation at the time, so I thought it might be good if I had some coding experience. But C++ looked too intimidating for me, so I tried learning HTML to start. I enjoyed what I learned, but ended up going on to other things. I think I'm less good on the technical front, I tend to be better at creative things. 

I've been trying to write a short story collection. It's very difficult without having a total understanding of how writing works, but I'm muddling through it. I'd recommend creative writing courses, but I think it can be done without them. There's a lot of helpful information I've read online, and reading books of course helps. I analyse pretty much everything from a writer's perspective, films, video games, works of art, real life conversations. It gets to the point where it's hard to switch off. XD

Wow, that's quite a lot to get through! My course is part time till next year, so I have a much lighter workload for now. I have some work on analysing sources to complete, but there's a couple of weeks left till my next assignment, which is a group project.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I was a freshman when I did that essay. I'm near the end of my second year now. I suspect the word count will go up, though strangely this year it seems to have gone down. 

That's quite a complex subject, will it be your last essay, then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 11:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just the pronunciation you find difficult? I used to study Japanese, and I always found pronunciation the hardest. I wonder if there's anything on YouTube about French pronunciation that might be helpful? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 11:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My degree is English Literature and Creative Writing. Psychology is very interesting, if I hadn't gone with creative writing, it would probably have been my second choice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 11:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> International Relations, that sounds interesting, but certainly very challenging! Good luck with the 10k words, my longest assignment so far has only been 2k. What's the thesis on?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
