<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject792</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 22:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm refering to the fact that we've seen him making a host in his basement, but not the final product. Which gives the opportunity for the old switcheroo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 22:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah a lot of this ties in, and i personally wouldn't mind if they all turned out to be hosts. It would be a poetic irony if Ford and the others are just stuck in continuous loops. Ford keeps remaking himself time and time again as if its someone experiment to try and birth consciousness. 


However the problem is, as with a lot of theories floating about, this show is far from faultless and won't ever make complete sense of everything. And its not trying to. It will always substitute logic for entertainment value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm pretty sure the only reason he was shot in the arm was so he could smile in appreciation of some chaos, so we could chat about it on here. 


I very much doubt it was  a nod from Ford, becuase if it was, it would be more of an insult. As in, heres your chaos, but its still under my control you stupid c*nt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm sorry, but has this just got 20,000 roubles in 2 hours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 20:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, we don't know he's dead, if you mean ford. 

But that cornerstone is her anchor, her barrier to leaving. And whilst in the park, shes 'free', yes. But only as free as a host living in a world made for hosts. One that seems to be still bound to her programming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that urge comes form her cornerstone, which her entire 'mind' is built off. 


My question is, does she finally *accept* that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well it was a line about wanting to discover his true self that brought him back to westworld, that kinda sealed it for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maeve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, did she make it?


The way i read it was that Ford has sent her on her journey, helping her along the way (which goes some way to explaining the whole felix, sylvester nonsense). She's on her own journey of self discovery, but still one thats entirely orchestrated. Either way, she makes it to the train. Great. But has she actually changed? 


By choosing to go and find her daughter, is she finally accepting what she is, a host that lives in westworld? Or has she failed, and is just unable to shake off her cornerstone? 

Really she's no more sentient than when she first started down the path. Its only more information that shes acquired, shes no more conscious than when she first started 'rebelling'. 

But that choice at the end, was it through self reflection? I'm not so sure.


 Or, maybe thats the point and, just as with humanity, choice is an illusion.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep, he's keeping my MiB = host theory alive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think we know what Ford is/was trying to do. 

I think by dying, he's 'freeing' the hosts of god, of him. But to what ends i don't know. And the way he did it, which will result in a massive slaughter of everyone, which could potentially kill dolores or bernard, is odd to say the least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know tv shows need to keep pacey and push forward, and nearly all the time that results in plot holes/fluctuations/incomprehensible events. 

But, 100% those two fucktards are hosts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i totally think this, except for the 'became the music' line. Which is annoying, because i still want to know exactly what Fords end goal was/is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so wait, either they planted these getty images, and 'von weber' or they are trolling us. I can only see stuff as far back as 2012 for von weber, but there are a lot of pics of circuitboards n serevr rooms etc in there, so its possible that this was planned.


Either that or it is just stock image they used. Either way surely this means the whole thing is someones (hopefully Fords) narrative. Its like some kinda matrix meets the sims meets AI. 


Either that or they just used  a stock image. Which seems lazy for such an important detail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 15:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just waiting for the ozzie guy reviews.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 14:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> School.


For 10 years all you had to do was go to a place that teaches you things about the world. Nowdays i have to work my ass off all day for the time and money to do that.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 13:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad manners, in all apects of life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 13:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't trust anyone or anything. Lies and mistakes make the world go round.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ya gotta believe in yerself lad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not even these retarded referees are gonna stop us getting out of this shitty league </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope something along these lines is true. 

Take what hes said as true for a minute. After his partner was killed by a host, an 'incident' in the park. Ford builds another host in his exact image, to continue to work alongside him?! Wtf would everyone in the company think about that!? Youd think it would get  a mention here or there. 


The biggest mystery for me is what exactly Ford wants. What is he doing? Why all this effort, why allow 'faulty' robots at all? Everything hes not controlling, he's allowing at least. But to what ends?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well stubbs hasn't been killed, and is actually seen in the preview. 

Personally i don't think elsie is dead. Either way, the bigger mystery for me is whos orders bernard was acting on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything we've seen points to logan being the MiB, but they can twist it to whatever they want. 

I personally still think MiB is a host... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats kinda the reason i don't like her story arc tbh. I enjoy her as a chracter, but they way its come about is ridiculous. She didn't really have to try hard to make that leap to supposed 'consciousness'. It was just there. 


Incidentally, how did you interpret the scene where the two techs literally had the ability to finish her little uprising in their hands, to make her stupid or whatever, but instead chose to make her super smart etc?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hate to get all logan on you, but you know shes a robot right? ;) 

All her emotional scenes held no sway over me, cuz i knew it didn't matter. Altho, i really enjoy her as a character, for all the reasons you state. But how shes managed to get where she is, is what pisses me off. For me, they will have to do a hell of a lot of  (convoluted) writing for it all to make sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what makes them your fav?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad theres more people like you on here, cuz that opinion seems to shouted down a lot recently. People jump to the shows defense too readily. God knows why, because meaves story is ludricrous so far. I'm really hoping they make sense of it.


I mean, she's gonna die. I have absolutely no doubt she'll end up lying 'dead' in that hose down room. But they need to explain how exactly shes been able to get away with so much nonsense, completely unseen. 

(the shows awesome btw, its really only maeves story i have a problem with) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 14:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah interesting post. I do think there will be a few more reveals when it comes to hosts, the Bernard one was pretty obvious from the get go. Ford being one would actually tie in with a little theory i have with the MiB and delos,  about hosts that can age. 


The main point that you bring up that has hardly been discussed on here since its reveal, is the facts that bernard, or the (AI?) software in him, co-created the other hosts. This is such a huge point. Machines creating machines. It also suggests that Ford isn't the all knowing god that hes demonstrated so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 01:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this must be the case, but how theyve done so much without being noticed or flagged up is still (as it stands) an annoying plothole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 22:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did i get that whole scene wrong? because i thought it confirmed that those two idiots were hosts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 22:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what would class as 'true consciousness' then? How can the red pills get any more conscious? 

Besides, thats different to implanting your own consciousness into a host, which for all we know, may already be possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 22:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every scene with maeve infuriates me, but her character seems doomed anyway, so i cling on to the hope that it could be at any moment. 

Dolores is interesting, but also, i fear is doomed. She's stuck in a loop like all the others, altho someone is manipulating that loop for some reason still unknown, but i relly don't care at all what happens to her.


Bernard is the only host (i also still think MiB is a host btw) that i care about, but i wouldn't say i'm rooting him on. Well, maybe. It was confirmed last episode that he himself is a co creator of the other hosts. Which is a huge point (that isn't getting much discussion) that will be the key for future westworld funtimes. Machines creating machines, means 'we' don't know how they work. It means Ford hasn't actually got complete control and isn't all knowing. Its the reason why im rooting on bernard, because where his story will take him will reveal everything about westworld. 


But yeah, he's still just a robot ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 21:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> youre rooting for the robots? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MiB = a host in the real world that ages like a real boy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Theres no real difference between levels of cosnciousness between humans and hosts. But they are still robots. They intrinsically have less 'worth' than humans, from a human perspective at least. 

I'm not sure where they are going with Ford, but it seems like he knows that the hosts can be 'fully' conscious (incidentally, i'm not sure anyone else does?) but he doesn't care. They are his creations, they are still robots even if they can feel and think the same as a humans. I think he wants them to stay in the park. I think the maze is his test to see if the hosts can 'evolve'. If they do, i think he'll destroy them. Its a way of keeping the system working, matrix style. Any 'neos' will make it to the maze, then wiped.  



But yes, i guess the question shouldn't be whether they are as conscious as humans, but whether it matters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously (im not an aresnal fan) why do't they start him every match? It seems like arsenal struggle to win every time they don't play Giroud. Personally i think he's one of the best strikers in the league, seems madness not to start him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i wondered about this too. Maybe he is testing Bernard, but maybe he really doesn't know. Bernard could have been made by Arnold, possibly in his image, but Ford wouldn't know for sure when he was made.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> supplies muthaf*cka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 23:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shes def been on the maze quest before. Thats why she has the 'flashbacks' where she sees the steeple etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 18:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that was only slightly entertaining until the pan to jake jillianhaal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW Donald Glover returns to save us all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i dunno, but his whole character has me cringing hard. Massively over-acted, every scene with him is awful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please let it be this, as its the only reason that felix couldve possibly done all of that with maeve. Although even then, maeve managing to blackmail them was ridiculous. (i'm actually hoping they are hosts, that are programmed to be pliable) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, i hope its not turning into lost. Questions never get answered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah this is mildy infuriating. I'm hoping all the incompetence around the park is due to lack of funding, but even with that, these scenes were nothing but ridiculous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 15:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they on at the same time in the us? Thats madness. Especially for a show in its early stages </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 15:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i've thought about this a lot. There's a lot of discussion about completing the pyramid of consciousness etc and Dolores breaking free. But really, what else has maeve got do to be fully 'conscious'? The only difference is that her memory is wiped at the end of the day, but i don't see how she can be any more conscious than she is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 15:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's def something odd about the fact that Ford created everything in westworld, including the hosts, from the bottom up. He can control them at will. And yet, we are seeing some 'rebels' acting out and seemingly realising their consciousness. I don't buy it. I don't buy that hosts can somehow still remember their past lives even after their memories being wiped. Theres nowhere for that information to hide, they made every piece of tech and software in the hosts, they can delete if they need to. 

Ford is old, he's had his time. It sounds like the board have had enough of his shit and are looking to get full control. Whatever is happening with the hosts, Ford is controlling, or at the very least, is fully aware of. I'm not sure what Ford is trying to do but its in defiance of the board, he's not letting anyone take his world away from him.

So yeah, i can see him 'uploading' his consciousness into a host, if it hasn't been done already. But i also think HE will be the one behind the hosts going world war Z on the place. In order to protect it. 

Which, btw, reminds me that (i assume) any one of the hosts personality can be uploaded into any of the other hosts. They must be connected somehow and that information must be stored somewhere in some kind of mainframe. Everyone is connected, which opens up endless possibilities. All you need to do is hack one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 09:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it with all this logan bashing? He's not being an asshole at all, its A GAME. He's just playing along. Westworld is designed for it. Why do you think this fictitious westworld is set in the fictitious old west? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda, pnau is nick and pete, empire nick and luke. Theres a lot of crossover production wise tho, with peter mayes producing some empire stuff and a guy called Donnie sloan i think produced for both too. Empire started after luke featured on a few of pnaus earlier stuff and things 'clicked'. 

Nicks the driving force behind it all tho imo, the guys a genius.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sam la more is back on production so i'm expecting big things from this album! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who thinks theres any possibility of brexit not happening needs to put the kettle on, take a seat, and really think about your life. Don't waste time on this. No western government will overturn a democratic referendum of this magnitude. Parliament will not go against this decision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That smile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, i haven't seen this discussed at all yet, but its confused and intrigued the hell out of me. 

Right after having a pretty big argument where Logan comes across as a huge douche, that seems to not care at all about William. Then William abandons Logan as he's taking a beating, and i think he even cries for help. But just as he sees William leave, Logan smiles. Now i know he sees it all as a game, but especially after their argument, i wonder why he seems so genuinely happy that Williams going off on his own?


The last episode showed that theres a lot more going on with Logan, he's not just there to play the game. 


(to add on a  crazy theory, could logan actually be the MiB? Obviously assuming two time frames. Everyones latching on to william, but it makes more sense that its Logan. We now know he's a big dog in the real world, they have very similar temperments and treat westworld like the game that it is. Could it be the reason he wants to find the maze is because thats what William and Dolores were doing first time round?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 08:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that whole scene differently tbh. Wasn't he just attempting to 'hack'  a bird? and in the same episode that we find out there are transmitters being secretly implanted in the hosts by someone or some cause. It could be as simple as that. Felix is working with/for someone and has now finally learned  a part of the code. 


I think they only made it Maeve in the room to throw us, or just add to her story. But i can only assume it was Ford controlling her in order to stop felix. Ford is the only person we've seen who can control hosts and animal hosts alike. Atm theres no reason to think its anyone else, and felix has been found out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 23:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assumed this kid was the parks 'help'. He approaches anyone out on their own and supplies them with food or water if needed. Or have i missed something here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wish england had someone who could cross the ball like that.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 14:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never got why hans is a villain. Wasn't he just protecting his town from an ice witch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 09:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These already exist in th uk, but these look cool too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 18:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not to worry too much, everyone i know who drives a hilux would never dream of swerving to avoid a moose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 23:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An impossible question to answer. But shooting myself in the head, when i already know i can be brought back, would be pointless? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 19:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice catch, i don't think its anyone upset that theyre a host tho. I think its more likely Ford has told them to do it, maybe after a host wakes up. Ford looks angry and worried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, but 'infected' is just the metaphor, exactly how it happens is still a mystery. Did Ford really code a voice activated evolutionary step in the last update? I can't work out whats going on there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 20:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah agree with everything,  just not sure how maeve has managed to get to this point. Its the idea of self reflection that joins everything up, letting the hosts become 'conscious', which we assume was the last update. But it also seems that this function in maeve was voice activated by dolores, whispering her the line about 'violent delights'. 


Maeve is at least as far down the rabbit hole as dolores, even if shes the only focus of bernards attention. (which i suppose just adds to the time frame theories) 

 Which also i don't quite get what the shows saying here, cuz surely  maeve is as 'conscious' as anyone is ever gonna get in the last scenes of ep.4.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 19:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah true dat. Can everyone use 'timeframe' instead pls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> potentially  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 17:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But how did that pink unicorn get in there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 17:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tis a hard problem. One i don't think the show will attempt to answer, but will discuss. 

So what do you think? Is there a comprensible answer? Are you a zombie or something more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 14:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great post, not sure what to come back with....


 I think the idea of the self and self reflection is the missing part of the hosts. They won't step out of their loop without it. Those that do, will 'evolve', natural selection, i suppose. 

The show will keep asking the question of consciousness. Does it actually matter who is human? But i also think the show will eventually be cop out. One of the reasons why i think we'll never meet arnold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 14:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> absolutely. They'll probs be rotten angry zombies by the time they do. Why exactly theyll start attacking people im not sure of tho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 00:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah im completely open to him being human btw, i just don't think he is. Didn't he take a load of gunshots and not even flinch? Seems odd considering it knocked william off his feet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "being forced to" is key here i think. 

Shes being forced to change by being put into stressful sitautions. Its natural selection for the hosts. Those that die, that don't change, stay in their loop, they go no further. Those that survive, can learn from whats happened and it dominoes from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. I think the MiB is not only a machine, but also serving someon else. Someone we don't know about yet. Ford wouldn't need to scalp people to discover clues to maze.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 19:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it looks good n all, but who the hell made that ad? horrible to watch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 19:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was going to, and still might, do a post up making similar points. But with a different outcome. 

There does seem to be a real disconnect between how sophisticated the 'hosts' are and how well 'westworld' is run. Simple staffing numbers are worrying enough. How they could possibly lose a host or not notice when theyre tripping out, or going out of the loop. Plus all the points you listed. Its strange that they walked to look for the stray, not even going on horseback.

I think these points are because the park isn't what it once was, and has had budget cuts and reductions, just as a failing amusement park would. We know its at least 30 years old, maybe the novelty has worn off, customers are bored of it. Maybe there are other parks (that we'll see in future series) that have more interest now. 


I agree that this could result in the 'management' that we've been hearing of, selling off 'experiments' to whoever. But more immediately, it leaves Ford the space to experiment himself, before its too late.


I do think there are 2 time frames that we're seeing, one when the parks in full flow when an 'incident' will happen. And one set now, where things are about to majorly wrong/evolutionary leap for the hosts.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 14:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> agree, altho abernathy may have beeen replaced just in case the others versions are 'infected' too. Easy to assume that the update was applied to all versions. 


I do think there are other versions of the same characters tho and they will use the reveal as a dramatic plot point. Possibly when they 'wake up' in the real world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 14:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i really really hope it doesn't go the way of lost. So much intrigue and potential that utimately had absolutely no substance. I hope Westworld has a point to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah wicked, glad its still a full live show then :) I've seen so much live music from a wide genre of bands, and i genuinely put you on the top tier. God knows how you manage to hit those vocals out live on tracks like yours, especially immediately after smashing the crap out of the drums! Keep it up, can't wait to see you again.


p.s - hope you still have that (what i assume is a moog or korg) synth on stage with you. That thing made some of the greatest noises i have ever heard in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> love your stuff guys, been a fan since i heard the Alan Braxe rmx of 'Cult of romance', god knows how many years ago! Seen you countless times, which leads to this question...

Your live performances have always been next level, the energy, vocals and general noise. So, if or how, has 'downsizing' effected your live shows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GET OVER HERE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> has anyone been asking why the 'stray' smashed his own head in with a rock? Did i miss something here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i agree with a lot of that, but i'm not sure about anyone = arnold atm. We don't know enough yet, he could have been fords brother or creation or just his partner, but most likely imo, is that arnold was a real person. I think he put his trust in one of the hosts after tryign to give them 'consciousness' and was killed by one of them because of it. By accident or not. 

That one scene where Ford almost angrily reinforced that 'the hosts are not conscious' stood out. Especially when there are other scenes where he almost seems to father them. I wonder if he holds some resentment there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ask him what year it is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> be good if everyone who gets an interesting response posts it up, im in the uk and can't access it :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When was that? does it fit with the timeline theories? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 08:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that too. Maybe he was being so hard on the hosts only infront of the 'outside' hosts, the scientists, which i think includes bernard.

 He needs them to think they are real, to not sympathise with the hosts. Altho obviosuly theres  awhole back story to ford that we don't know yet, but hes very hard to read right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its a real possiibility there is no arnold. We are def dealing with different timelines. Whether its just between the dolores interviews or between that and the william story, we don't know yet. But also, we now have seen that a differnt backstory can be uploaded instantly! And considering we don't know for sure whos a host or not (altho i'll be amazed if Bernard isn't) we wil never be able to tell where we are until we see these characters all meeting. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes and we don't know where dolores goes after these interrogations. For that matter, for all we know there are several versions of her. I may rewatch the first episode, even watching it first time round, it clicked that these conversations might be looking backwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the maze is a dead end, or at least, its just a maze. Its meant for guests, not hosts. Which is why its not for him. The only way he found it was scalping someone? I think the maze was a specific game designed for some particular guests in some previous version. HOWEVER, i think there is now something hidden in it and or is being used beyond its original purpose.

 The MiB is absolutely some kind of 'host', but one that is serving an outside player. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i would amazed if bernard is not a 'host' or at least not a human. Why does he talk with delores at all? i think theres some connection there from previous versions. Nor sure if he's Fords or Arnolds creation, or even another version of 'arnold'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is part of a programmed storyline remember </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that was like that when i got here...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 13:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can't we do this shit out in the sea, where no one wories til its too late </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> glimpse into the new live show set up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> everyones like, oh its goos he's checked himself in, i'm glad he's gettign help. I'm fucking sad at it. I thought he was beating it through his music, sucks man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right, whos gonna continue this into a full opening credits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here he goes again, trying to flog his car anchors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 18:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is why i like humans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 18:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> luck?! His ninja training had nothing to do with luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i always wonder if a guy can see how hot his sister is? Attractiveness is quite objective in reality, so can you see theyre attractive, but still gross you out? or are they just your annoying little sister? 


(i have not got a sister btw) (only bros) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 22:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nick littlemore is probs my fav musician of all time. The man is a true musical genius.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 18:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad i missed this one, it wouldve been my 10th. You might be on to something about spreading themselves too thin thanks to other their festivals, but i think it was down to the lineup. Both poor ticket sales and the poor standard of festival goer can be put down to that. 


You should put those comparison photos in a seperate post. I think everyone was disappointed with the spaceport. And the mainstage has been getting worse year on year imo. They used to put loads of artwork round it, 'increase the peace' signs etc, now its reduced to 2 small screens. 

Calling it 'boutique' after everyone started to complain was a bad move. Altho tbh, i would love it to go back to how it was before it expanded, the vibe was much better back then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love these guys, hope going to a 2 piece doesn't ruin their shows, cuz they are faultless live.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but, the cows ok right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> R.I.P Bestival? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard a lot of terrible things about this year. I didn't go myself, as last year was disappointing and could see its heading in a bad direction. My friends went and have been absolutely slating it and won't be going back next year. Massive cut backs, poor line up and a terrible 'thuggish' crowd. Which seems to be echoed by lots of people across the socials. 


Wondering about anyone elses experiences? People who have been going for years, what did you think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been 5 years since he passed. 


Mehdi love forever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DJ Mehdi - Signatune [French Electro House] (2006) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 23:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT, YOU THINK YOURE BETTER THAN ME!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 19:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder how that baby turned out. The kid had no chance of growing up normal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MGMT - Kids [Alternative Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 19:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 16:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> every player needs to do this after scoring. The law would disappear in a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 12:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this sounds like the next facebook kinda fuckery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 19:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know if they've upgraded the lightning port at all? Every single one, on each of my iphones, has worn out over time. As in, i've had to replace each one once before i upgraded, because the would no longer charge because the connectors had worn down. 


Surely this would only get worse now, having to use it to listen to music aswell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like the reasons its closing, but somewhere else will take its place. Its not like its the end of dance music. It opens up scope for other venues to be the place that everyone wants to play at. 


Anyway for me, its height was in the mid to late 00's when there was loads of new sounds and crazy djs about, that all seemed to play there when in london. It felt new and exciting and edgy, something which its lost over the last few years anyway.


Shame to see it go, but its dance music. Its all about the new :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 22:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not the acting part i would imagine being hard, altho obviously pretty emotional. But its the press coverage and whole show and dance they have to do to promote their films, that is gonna be tough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
