<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject757</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe he's just screwing with you. Block all the ads and make it a non-issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  plus a browser that deletes everything when I shut it down

This is an excellent point and something I do also. By deleting "everything" it's deleting the key part - cookies. Don't need cookies when you essentially have a static IP though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firefox+Ublock Origin. The phone platform is always owned by someone though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just install ublock origin. Anything that involves installing something or even contacting them is giving them data on you that they collect since that is their purpose.

And if you're a Win10 guy, lock down with something like [Blackbird](http://www.getblackbird.net/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As my teenage daughter would say, "[Gotchu Fam](https://i.redd.it/7lrodxpy8ury.gif)". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should have a reality TV show where Louise Mensch and Bill Palmer get sent to Russia and told they are CIA assets and they need to break into the Kremlin. I would watch that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without a doubt. The top post looks like Alefantis battling the narrative with 20 alt accounts. Much of the same emotional-based wording in many posts while trashing and attacking ad hominem anyone that might suggest that ejaculating pizzas isn't normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This one](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W0QoocyfJWI)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sir, please pull over. It appears you've had too much to think tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This does not make you father of the year. As a security professional with multiple daughters older and younger than yours, I strongly recommend that you reconsider the personal information that you post online. I have had to provide expert testimony in multiple child harm/death cases in relation to logs and forensics showing pedophiles interacting with minors. 

edit: Took minutes to find his home address, names of kids (one of which I share and one of which my daughter shares), and that it would have been faster for me to drive over and tell him this than typing this out since I'm within a couple of miles of where he lives...until tomorrow when spring break ends and we drive back. But if someone cared, they would know where he lived, where his kids go to school, which night he's not home and a whole lot of other details that would make me very uncomfortable. He's also well armed fwiw. Good luck B.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a simple case of not knowing who is reporting to who. There are warring sects of Jews and the rest are caught in the middle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unquestionable grounds for a lawsuit. You didn't sign up for this shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost it at "thousand cock stare".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd trust putting a fork into an electric socket more than any person. 

The question is how long I could listen to CNN while resisting the urge to stick a fork into an electrical  socket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny enough, 'German immigrant professor'. He's just visiting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "No, they don't. I don't know what you saw, but it wasn't real. None of this is real." 

They did. I'm local and visited late last year. I will affirm the walls were consistent with the instagram. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The motherfucker PAUSES. He backtracks in descending order. "No, I mean, I have no reason to, I mean, I hope not."

"Follow-up: My dad got tired of me calling him a motherfucker so we skipped the next call." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Officials from all three agencies determined Russian hackers accessed both parties campaign servers and released damaging information about the Democratic National Party.

Officials never had access to anyone's campaign servers and there is insufficient technical proof for attribution. Fake news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I was being lazy. /r/bannedfromthe_donald is a real thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/bannedfromtd is over there --- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you're totally in the cloud like the rest of us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was he trading drugs for sex on the flight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Blackbird](http://getblackbird.net/).  It locks everything down. It will break O365 corporate email if that's part of your equation though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Dude, all of your comments are emotionally charged, 

You should try reading them with a calming voice. All the emotion is in your head and the rest of your post is known as 'projection'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I'll get right on that boss](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UEaKX9YYHiQ). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellow readers, please take heed that my, or any other comments not promoting North Korea, should be handled with suspicion. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You haven't made a single rational response about the actual topic. 

US is bad and now I'm a shill. Just keep attacking and avoid the topic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And...I guess you should move to NK; the land of milk and honey, and last bastion after the world falls to the Great Leader. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We know nothing about NK, seems silly to bomb someone based on "he said this..."

Well, "He" said he was going to nuke America... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feisty. Must be lonely being the last NK defender left.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you think of a better definition of a corporation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you've never read a [contract of carriage](https://www.united.com/web/en-US/content/contract.aspx) to know they were never there to begin with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Me too](https://reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/63bqek/data_patterns_suggest_trump_towerspectrum_health/dfsx7m3) fwiw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Step one of impeachment requires 218 votes in the House of Reps. It's not even worth considering with the Dems at 193. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 13:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pamela Anderson, CIA asset, appears to be fucking him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never understood the obsession with the location, or even perceived that other people were obsessed with it until the shooter. 

The disturbing video of Alefantis hosting a party and talking about murdering a baby is an unsettling thing to see in a pizza place, but a far cry from molesting kids on the pizza stone.

One other notable data points about the location is the proximity of all of the other DNC owned related businesses on that street. I would love to know how that came to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is she dead Jim? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not news. He campaigned on it and says it regularly.

They have structured the world so that you are either for Muslim domination or you are on the same side of the jews for a common cause of stopping it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like her defensive posture is to shift into highschool bully mode and start taunting him about how no one at school likes him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is that under the old rules, that option didn't exist. And you're right, telling the ISPs they can't look at your traffic is a joke. It's their network and they'll monitor every packet to every destination as they see fit including aggregating and selling "their network data", not your data. 

The FCC's take now is let's put everyone on the same playing field, remove the regulations that are preventing competition, make it easier to get a pipe to your house and open up the model to let you decide how you want to pay for your Internet access - "sponsored" or not and see what happens. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sell it as an aggregate of millions of other data points completely without your knowledge or interaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Sharing isn't "leaking" but she's most certainly MK Ultra and a CIA plant. 

The spy who shagged me - oldest trick in the spybook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you currently have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick question: If Google came to town and offered uncapped Gig Ethernet to your house for $20, but they would be selling your data as part of an aggregate, would you be interested?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sucker's bet; he meant Rice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yeah and that's where I think there's a disconnect between security professionals and the public, we don't explain that it's basically a best guess with what we know.

If you're anything like me, you're tired of explaining. It's a complicated topic that crosses two of the most 'special' communities, netsec and IC. There are pitfalls throughout both the technical information and the ugly mix of class and unclass information. If someone has the wrong conversation with someone they might both end up needing to report to their security officer. 

 If you wanna get into some deep conspiracy theory territory I've thought what if one of the groups (both apt 28   29 were attributee's) was the CIA, and the other was Russian, so it's 

I wouldn't begin to call that a conspiracy theory; that just how it works. This world is always more complicated and subtle than anyone realizes. Or as I often find myself saying about technical incidents in hindsight, "like all good problems, there were multiple problems". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I mean the argument against is pretty easy, it's well known in the field that with publicly available info attribution is almost always a best guess situation.

Agreed. In this light I have personally found it hard to accept most Red-scare type premises since the bedrock of the story usually infallible 'attribution to Cozy Bear'. It's almost like people have forgotten that other nations hack too. 

I seem to recall it was China that caused me to get a letter after the OPM hack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen all there is to see. Do you have something more to offer?

edit: You've made 107 mentions defending Crowdstrike in the past few weeks...wonder why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "When people talk about Russian meddling in the U.S. election, they usually mean the hacking of DNC emails or covert communication with members of Donald Trumps administration. But for former FBI special agent and national security expert Clint Watts, theres another problem"

AND THEN:

Russia stole information. [Trump] is still using it against his opponent"

That's the entire "article". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's is not sufficient technical evidence to attribute the DNC or Podesta email exfiltrations to any group or country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever watch a movie with a technical person and they ruin it telling you how fake and implausible it is?

From a security guy, in DC (let your imagination run wild), every mention of "Russia" turns me into that guy.

I know guys at Crowdstrike, I have read their 'report'; it's not a report. A couple of IOCs buried in 13 pages of bullshit is not a report. I create tools that automatically process thousands of IOCs per day and that's still weeks to months from any sort of attribution. They are opportunistic assholes and they are not respected in the security or intelligence community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former boyfriend of David Brock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right on cue! Good post! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious, do you know the first step to impeaching the President? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I smell a lawsuit or five. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truth is that time passes and people change...but some people never change and the same circle of people always exists. It's everyone's job to figure out the truth and motive and how to identify each scenario. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not wrong, as usual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DIA was Cheney's favorite to enact his personal goals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's silly, everyone knows where the pretty pictures come from, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The United States Constitution provides that the House of Representatives "shall have the sole Power of Impeachment" (Article I, section 2) and that "the Senate shall have the sole Power to try all Impeachments .... [but] no person shall be convicted without the Concurrence of two-thirds of the Members present" (Article I, section 3). The president, vice president, and all civil officers of the United States are subject to impeachment.


Basically, since the Dems control neither the House nor the Senate, impeachment is a mental jerk-off for the disassociated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an 18-year-old tshirt with a big octopus with tentacles labeled 'ECHELON', 'CALEA', 'CARNIVORE'..etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do some highfalutin poopin'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not a raging liberal obsessed with Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is the Chair of the House Intelligence Committee. He was being physically stonewalled from visiting certain IC sites (people should go to jail) so whistleblowers finally figured out how to show him the evidence without breaking any laws and it involved coming to the White House Executive Building to see the intelligence. 

The drama is that they have the Obama Administration dead to rights committing felonies against American citizens that they have to deflect to something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no connection between Nunes and Pizzagate or WL that I have heard of.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shooter complicates everything. I could go either way, or at least say it wasn't relevant if abuse occurred in a pizza place in the middle of DC (I live in the area). There is enough disturbing content and references that I don't think the "pizza" aspect is relevant, beyond "the symbol".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you draw the line between misinformation and the larger crime network? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Podesta's digitally-signed emails included mentions of multiple topics that have lead to additional questions and investigation:

- Some sort of code with food words that is attributed to pedophilia culture, or drugs, or both.
- Mentions of Comet Ping Pong combined with above which lead to sniffing out their instagram and youtube content. 
- Content, and comments on said content, ranged from distasteful to outright disgusting including the direct mention of murdering babies.
- Plus Tony Podesta's publicly displayed pedo and death related art collection. 
- Combined with a personal invitation from Marina Abramovi, occultist to the stars, with her youtube videos that include mixing blood and semen and throwing it on stone statues. 
- Combined with decades of known conspiracies with many links drawn between. E.g., Catholic pedo, UK Gov pedo, Hollywood pedo (see pedowood).

In depth:

https://voat.co/v/pizzagate/1467064

edit: [Other poster hit some points I thought about saying but neglected in my goal to eli5](https://www.reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/62wasx/can_someone_eli5_pizzagate_to_me/dfpk766/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Following Verizon's statement, [the EFF has actually taken the step of withdrawing its prior accusation of the cellular network's motives](https://www.engadget.com/2017/03/31/eff-verizon-will-install-spyware-on-all-its-android-phones/?sr_source=Facebook). The privacy body has pledged to investigate the matter further, but it looks as if it may have been a lot of fuss over what amounts to very little."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure that happens also, but I've also seen instances where the bot has malfunctioned and posted a hundred dups in a thread of that sort of thing. I guess someone could have been autistic though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. Take that food and give it to people that deserve it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are definitely bots. Look for patterns of dismissing any right leaning view with generic language.

"That's just crazy. No one seriously thinks that." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vodka...Sputnik...Gulag...Traceback (most recent call last):

File "hack-amerika.py", line 173, in module

main()

File "hack-amerika.py", line 167, in main

AttributeError: 'Russia' object has no attribute 'trump_dict'
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is my favorite one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're going to learn it, you might as well learn it the right way. You're trying to use python to interact with the command line, not interact with a database. It's like trying to learn to drive a car with hulk hands; it's less about the driving and more about the "why is he wearing hulk hands?". 

The best part is that doing it through python libraries is a whole lot easier than trying to reinvent the wheel there are tons of examples. There is a concept that you need to be aware of though and it's called a 'cursor'. You can just think of it as a session to your database. 

[Link to a pretty simple example](http://stackoverflow.com/questions/372885/how-do-i-connect-to-a-mysql-database-in-python#622308). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd poop on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     #Support Ubuntu
    if [[ `uname -a | awk '{print tolower($0)}'` == *"ubuntu"* ]]; then
            SOURCE="[SYSTEM - GNOME]"
            #get /usr/bin/gnome-keyring-daemon process
            PID="$(ps -eo pid,command | sed -rn '/gnome\-keyring\-daemon/p' | awk 'BEGIN {FS = " " } ; { print $1 }')"
    ----   gcore -o /tmp/dump $PID   /dev/null
            HASH="$(strings "/tmp/dump.${PID}" | egrep -m 1 '^\$.\$.+$')"
            SALT="$(echo $HASH | cut -d'$' -f 3)"
            DUMP=$(strings "/tmp/dump.${PID}" | egrep '^.+libgck\-1\.so\.0$' -B 10 -A 10)
            DUMP+=$(strings "/tmp/dump.${PID}" | egrep -A 5 -B 5 'libgcrypt\.so\..+$')
    	#Remove dupes to speed up processing
    	DUMP=$(echo $DUMP | tr " " "\n" |sort -u)
    parse_pass "$DUMP" "$HASH" "$SALT" "$SOURCE"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a big part of it - the whole implementation is bush league and not friendly to the public. I wouldn't install an app to park in one place. I might grab an app for Disney World, but I delete it when I'm done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't matter what I "make it seem like", the end result is the same. The market doesn't care about anyone's feelings. It's the common movement of a group of people in reaction to some stimulus. Unfortunately in this case folks were stimulated to be repelled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Update 2:** Following Verizon's statement, the EFF has actually taken the step of withdrawing its prior accusation of the cellular network's motives. The privacy body has pledged to investigate the matter further, but it looks as if it may have been a lot of fuss over what amounts to very little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it. I have an office there so I park for free but I'm still so disgusted I make it a point to not spend any money there.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://about.att.com/sites/privacy_policy/terms#aggregate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite being a Russian shill, he is my Senator. Can't wait to vote his delusional ass out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your post is better suited for politics. You're just whining.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conspiracy lost. No way a megalomaniac like Christie wasn't pulling the strings and it looks like he'll be slithering away to have another opportunity to shit on his fellow Americans in new and creative ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say $20M+. Moving enough money around that  people would compete to win your business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. Get that food to hungry people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **SUNDAY - SUNDAY - SUNDAY**


**Louise Mensch vs. Bill Palmer**

**Who Will Prevail in The Batshit-Crazy Olympics?**

It's a nail biter folks. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're conflating ILEC and ISP. LECs have been regulated since 1934. It wasn't until 2015 that the FCC came up with term BIAS - Broadband Internet Access Service and pulled any company that provided data under it's regulatory control.

Until this point, everyone was under the FTC's control, except LECs. Congress put them back under the FTC's control and now Congress should charge the Federal Trade Commission with enforcing clear and reasonable guidelines for protecting consumer privacy rights on the web.

Reference:

http://about.att.com/sites/privacy_policy/terms#aggregate

https://business.verizonwireless.com/content/b2b/en/precision/precision-market-insights.html;



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can, but no one will buy it. Your history isn't interesting to anyone except maybe your girlfriend. The way that the ISPs, and every other company, have always sold the data is in aggregate. The product is the representation of an addressable market. You alone don't represent an addressable market unless your in the .01% category. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the point of visiting a plant to see how coal technology works: 

 Im sorry, but what can living in a coal town teach you about whether coal is actually damaging to the atmosphere? 

 I am sure that very wonderful and deserving people benefit from mining coal. That has absolutely no bearing on the science.

The irony is strong. It's amazing to me that there are all these fancy technologies that are going to automate everyone's jobs but it's impossible for science to improve the process of coal processing.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I've been down this road before...


https://www.reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/5wor4j/its_a_bit_crazy_how_so_many_people_in_this_sub/

https://www.reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/5ubflg/this_sub_is_full_of_idiots_from_rt_d_and_its/

https://www.reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/5lwcfk/honest_question_for_trump_supporters_in_this_sub/

https://www.reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/5ysqxm/its_starting_to_be_more_clear_what_the_trump/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  reports showing that Trump and his associates were named incidentally by U.S. spy agencies monitoring foreign officials.

They weren't 'named incidentally', they were collected incidentally and named maliciously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Props for linking the correct document, but as a security guy that works with Feds doing this exact sort of work, that doc is shit. Claiming that publicly available malware is a foundation for attribution is bush league and fails to point to any actual "evidence".

As a comparative example, [here is a 110M PDF that details the investigation of the OPM breach](https://oversight.house.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/09/The-OPM-Data-Breach-How-the-Government-Jeopardized-Our-National-Security-for-More-than-a-Generation.pdf). The Chinese did that one but everyone seems to have forgotten that there are other countries in this world other than Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I love this guy](http://imgur.com/a/Xt9Uc). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder which 'fake news' is being blamed for influencing the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much of a conspiracy. T_D would be a better place for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His stance appears to be that all security breaches are attributed to Russia, but as a security guy, that works with Feds, that does this exact sort of work, I will say the evidence just isn't there for attribution. 



The whole thing is flawed from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I personally installed the CALEA taps as was required by law at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few API methods does not make a programming language. I added 15 methods to a class today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the libtards laugh and scoff completely clueless that they are surrounded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "  " </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then he finds out that ISP's are still bound by FTC's privacy rules and if there is any sort of breach or personal information sold then they will be fined and sued like hell...just like it works today for every other company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an idea why you're saying 'hard drives', but I think that's speculation. 

The more direct path is that 'intelligence products' normally only available to the Executive Branch within a keyword sensitive program, were able to be viewed within a SCIF that had computers connected to a database in that enclave. 

As for Exec branch intelligence; you could imagine that the Secret Service generates quite a bit, but ultimately, every agency feeds up eventually, including DNI and The Corporation and at other agencies trying to get some spotlight and real estate in the premier intelligence product labeled 'Executive Branch', the President's Daily Intelligence Briefing.



And yes, they are air-gapped, at least to a particular network that isn't going to be accessible in any congressional building. The congressional office buildings are public; you can walk in just by showing an ID and walking through a magnetometer. There are some secure areas but it's very a different ball game than trying to walk into some other Federal buildings or agencies. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
