<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 14:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not so much asking anything as much as I am just getting it off my chest and letting somebody know. 

I briefly spoke about it with my doctor. Told her all about my anxiety, said I was worried about side effects. She basically brushed it off with a sort of "you'll be fine", but that doesn't really do much for me. I also said I was concerned about my heart, but she said we should focus on one thing at a time for now and we'll get to that after addressing my BP.

I was pretty squared away when I left my last appointment. Even kinda excited and looking forward to starting the new med. It wasn't until I sat down and looked at the bottle of pills when it was time to take them that I realized I couldn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 14:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not aware of any drug personally that you can't "safely" mix with marijuana. As in, I mean I don't know of any drugs that specifically cause a bad reaction when mixed with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 14:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No offense, but that doesn't sound like an allergic reaction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Afraid to begin my medication.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 14:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been prescribed a drug to lower my blood pressure a few days ago. But I can't bring myself to take it. 

I have a very high hear bpm, and the idea of trying to lower my blood pressure while having such a high heart rate seems scary. I live alone and I'm afraid that this medicine could end up doing more harm than anything else, and I won't be able to get help.

It also doesn't help that I'm supposed to take it before falling asleep.. but the fear of taking it would be way too much to let me fall asleep with.

I'm not sure what to do about this. I really want to take it, but just the thought of it is making me incredibly anxious. I don't think I can bring myself to doing it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
