<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7081</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 23:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep my butt hole in neutral generally  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 23:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crochet, sewing, writing. I feel like creative things really get me out of the darker places in my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 23:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are these soft, fluffy tumbleweeds? The ones around here will slice you open then gleefully roll on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 22:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we get that in writing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 22:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is used to it according to his Mom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 22:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Misha is a manly boy dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 21:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #groomingproblems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 21:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Misha is a boy. Now that tongue poke is directed at you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tell me how you really feel, Misha! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 20:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 19:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister. We always tell her events start 30-45 minutes before they actually will. She is in her late 40s and has still not caught on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lizzie and Squirt, an unlikely love story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 17:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My daughter is either the Deer Whisperer or a Disney Princess </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 23:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 01:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't need no stinkin' badgers!

Someone had to say it. Nice work, he's adorable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 02:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you. Watching Alzheimer's take my Dad away piece by piece was excruciating. Be kind to yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 02:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I left it there for someone more deserving. I'm a "pay it forward" type of gal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gifts from the Toilet Fairy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 01:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 02:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the best way to get rid of crabs is to pour a shot of whiskey on your pubes, then a shot of sand. Then the crabs get drunk and throw rocks at each other. So that kinda checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 00:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but it helps me not picture John Cena in a Xena Warrior Princess cosplay so...worth it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 23:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Xenu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 04:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a hella casual NOPE right on outta there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 18:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just FYI the FitBit app has a food diary option </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did! I have 2 stories completed and a solid start on a 3rd. I am also editing one by my writing partner. I am planning to have 5 or more done and mass publish June 15th to get my new "career" launched.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 22:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must say, it is MUCH easier to write when you have no emotional stake in it. It's like taking a vacation from my main projects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 21:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between your advice in another thread and your book you have really motivated me to give erotica another shot. Just want to thank you for being so awesome and wanting to encourage others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 05:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just threw up in my mouth a little </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 03:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no Andy, only Rick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 17:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm, live in Southern Arizona. I have experienced a few snakes in places you do not expect to find a snake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got home from NOT leaving my kids at school due to a potential school shooting threat to hear of a school shooting. I don't want to live on this planet anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 00:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We adopted him. We just got super lucky that he was inclined like that. I ordered the training books to work with him through [Top Dog] (http://www.topdogusa.org/) and trained him myself. Like I said, he is not a formally trained service dog and I don't take him anywhere non-service dogs can't go. He is a lifesaver, though. If you are only wanting the behaviors, not necessarily the "take your dog anywhere" aspect I highly recommend self training through the Top Dog books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 18:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We got a dog shortly after my SAD got debilitating. Mal has been a godsend. He naturally took to me and has a lot of calming behaviors. I had worked in the pet care industry for 15 yrs so did research on anxiety service animal behaviors. He knows when I am having anxiety issues and is glued to me. He comforts me by licking my arm and wanting petted or trying to get me to play. If someone is making me anxious he places himself between us. Working on training him was great for me and him. He is registered through my Psych Dr as a Service Animal, as he meets the assistive behavior requirements but he is WAY to friendly to take him to stores and restaurants. We had him registered mostly so if I ever move I can have him with, I only take him places where non-service dogs are allowed. He helps me so much, and goes with me as much as possible. I don't want to give "properly trained" Service Animals a bad name by being "that guy". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 19:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, /u/Hippie-Geek , accept that I am, as a Purple, superior to all other colors because of my Button-granted right. In addition, I accept the Hierarchy of Purple and swear that my ultimate goal is to allow The Timer to reach Zero.
The Hand Shall Rise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 21:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had just 15 minutes ago said I was tired of waking up every day to hearing about shootings. Now they are doubling up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 16:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Fairy episode was in my hometown of Elwood Indiana. I wish I had grown up in TV Elwood. TV Elwood was super cute. Real Elwood...not as awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 15:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was adorably epic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 15:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kneel before Zod </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 06:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just pointed this thread out to my husband to show him it's not just me! It is anxiety/fear that I can control and I watch something horror related almost nightly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 19:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seven years later, it's still funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 17:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the only way I can get to sleep. If it takes me a while to fall asleep, they can get pretty elaborate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 20:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should marry him! Oh...wait. You already did. Good move! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 05:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just admitted my Dad to hospice today. He is 73. I am right there with you on Alzheimer's sucking the most. Internet hug </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 15:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish more people understood this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 17:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That just ruined my entire day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 15:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lovely and evocative. You did an amazing job creating a mood without tipping it over into being too morose or overbearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly writing prompt- **Lurking in the shadows.** </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 18:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you need to get your creative juices flowing? Do you need a mental break from your WIP? Write 500 words on the prompt- **Lurking in the shadows.**

Post your story in this thread for critique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 19:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have already started working on it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret Santa captured my varied interests!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 18:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly Writing Prompt- **And the band played on.** </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 16:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you need to get your creative juices flowing? Do you need a mental break from your WIP? Write 500 words on the prompt- **And the band played on.**

Post your story in this thread for critique.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 18:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to stress the point...

 Anyway, no sense getting bogged down in editing until the first draft is finished.

Get it done in 1st draft, then edit and use Beta readers to tighten things up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 18:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I can expand on what /u/Mr_Romeo said. In my own writing, I tend to view my 1st draft as "word vomit". I want to get the story out and onto the page as quickly as possible, and the mechanics are not worked out.It is rambling, too flowery and descriptive, and a little confusing to anyone not in my head. I feel like this is where you are with this work. 

When you go back to edit, it needs tightened up. Less unnecessary description and adjectives. I personally use [Hemmingway](http://www.hemingwayapp.com/beta/index.html) for this. You need to fine tune the character interaction to make it flow better. The dialogue seems stiff and forced. These are typical 1st draft issues, for me at least, and it seems for you as well. I hope this is more clear. 

Keep writing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 19:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never used to cry. In the last few years I cry at the drop of a hat and cannot stop. (39 btw) it really has become an issue. Internet hug, fellow weepy peeps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 19:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in a similar place. I have done the exchange twice and no gift. I signed up for rematch, sent a gift to my rematch person, and no gift from my rematch Santa. I hate to sound ungrateful, but a gift would he nice since I have sent out 3 with none in return. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 21:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My anxiety really ramped up to 11 about 3 years ago. I have been practicing for 18 years now. I found that many of my spiritual practices (i.e. meditation, herbalism, grounding and centering etc.) are really helpful tools to getting my attacks under control. If you have anxiety issues going in, I would maybe concentrate on these more "soothing" aspects to get started. Blessings to you on your GAD and your Path. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 03:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, those kids need to man up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least my kids have good taste! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 03:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 16:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [Video of me], [Ramsey Canyon Nature Preserve], [Hereford], [AZ], [USA] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Novice hiker at Ramsey Canyon Nature Preserve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 16:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 14:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All my daughter wanted for her birthday was to go horse back riding. I was well over the weight limit, and an adult had to go along with her for the trail ride. Having to tell my daughter I couldn't take her riding was devastating. She took it pretty well and we went to the movies instead, but it broke my heart. 

I let myself do Thanksgiving, then started the next day. Got a FitBit and started counting calories and steps. I am only just getting rolling, but it feels different this time. It's not for me, and not just to look better. I am honestly doing this for my kids.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 14:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing! You are an inspiration.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 17:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found it. It's called ASMR. [HERE](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Autonomous_sensory_meridian_response) is some info about it and [HERE](http://www.youtube.com/user/asmrVids) is a YouTube channel I found full of them. Hopefully this helps us out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 16:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am right there, too. I decided tonight I am going to try watching one of those "relaxation" videos on YouTube I saw on the Today show a few days ago. When I find them, I will post the link if anyone else wants to give it a try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We found a conjoined twin pumpkin. I hope we did it justice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 17:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 04:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost related, I am starting back from 0 with a novel I was about 5,000ish words into.

Yay for the reset! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 23:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the process. I live south of Tucson and might need to try this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 23:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "...according to the p0lice report,..." LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 19:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just grabbed it! Best of luck to you and congratulations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 19:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate that you took a look at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 17:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like an even trade off to me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 17:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is my thought. If you are a relative or good friend it would sting to know they didn't want to keep my signed book around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 17:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 16:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First I have to get used to people I don't already know wanting my book signed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 16:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two fantasy novellas. Hole in the Stone and The Gossamer Crown. I can send you the link if you want to take a peek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 16:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be devastated about the "signed to a good friend" part. I don't expect the average reader to be attached, but my friends I would hope would keep it around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A stack of squeaky clean lunch trays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 05:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 04:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just had my 1st book signing yesterday and I would be devastated if that happened to me in the future!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 15:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! I will be more articulate after more coffee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 02:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not in the house, I can promise you that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 02:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [HERE](http://www.dagorhir.com/forums/index.php?topic=18276.0) is a forum discussion on that exact thing! Hope this is more helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 01:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Manual of Arms](http://www.dagorhir.com/dagorhir/Rules.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 02:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Aussie, Malcolm Reynolds, approves! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 21:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Come check out my new YouTube channel about my life and my writing! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 22:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 04:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That made me giggle like a 12 yr old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 16:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. It was a rough road and I would not recommend it for everyone in that situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 16:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We lived in separate ends of the house and each had our own bathroom. It was awkward, but I honestly just pretended he was not there. After the 6 month period he moved back into the bedroom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 04:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I found out my husband cheated I told him I could not afford to throw him out. I told him I was done and our marriage was over, we just were living in the same house. I told him there was a tiny chance our marriage could be saved. He had until I could afford to take care of the kids on my own to convince me to let him stay. In the following six months he completely turned himself inside out to fix our marriage. 

After that 6 months, I agreed that we could work it out. We did counseling, and a LOT of very serious and painful talks. We did a the work and have come out ok. That was 5 years ago. I would tell anyone in that situation to only stay after a spouse has cheated if

a)The cheater can honestly commit to the amount of shit required to fix that kind of fuck-up. It's a big job and not everyone is up to it.

b)You can honestly commit to the amount of shit you have to wade through to work through it. Again, not for everyone and there is no shame in not wanting to walk that path.

c)You can find some way to live with it. It will always be there in your brain and will pop up and punch you in the throat at weird times.

Even though we are good, and possibly better, now, I wonder what would have happened it I would have had a better job when it all went down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 23:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause giving other humans head trauma is fun! Killing animals to feed your family is EVIL! (That is sarcasm, don't let my name fool you) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 17:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Mom works for Wal-Mart and they announced this quite a while ago. They wanted to give the employees plenty of time to get what they needed before the dress code switch became "official". I really hate Wal-Mart as a crappy employer, but this was a non-issue in the store my Mom works for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 16:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could only stand about 3 seconds. What is WRONG with people, that was terrifying and she is just happily flipping her tiny infant around?!?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 01:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a girl crush on your wife now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 06:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your snake in an unlikely place post trumps my snake in an unlikely place post. Have an upvote! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 17:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many feels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 22:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no one gets out alive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 18:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure if you live in town the critters will be much less. There is empty land around us, so lots of wildlife </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 17:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Water the other options, Carl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 05:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not talking about people "close to" closing time, I am talking about people at or after closing. 8:45=ok 9:01=douche </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 23:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They may NEED something for an important event etc.

A customers lack of planning is not a retail workers emergency. If you needed something "for an event" you should have planned better. Everyone has emergencies, but it is unreasonable to expect someone making minimum wage to put themselves in a potentially dangerous situation to solve it
EDIT format </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 16:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a creepy way to start my day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 03:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the Oscar goes to... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
