<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7668</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 03:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me too 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 00:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap I've seen a lot of felice fawn pics and love what she looks like even tho she's edited af but THIS takes the cake. She looks unrecognizable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats her? i think it might be someone else who looks just like her..unless this is just edited like crazy which isnt surprising lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 19:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly the reason I want to get my belly button pierced. It may prevent binges if I remind myself how horrible the piercing will look on my fat stomach  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i've actually heard its relatively common for victorias secret models to be photoshopped bigger and curvier than they actually are!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 14 pounds right when my ED was first starting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey! this post was posted a few times on accident. just thought i let you know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.instagram.com/p/BFxgxFDTPx8/?taken-by=viktoriabelany hl=en here she looks more like 99 pounds
https://www.instagram.com/p/12J6GLzPxp/?taken-by=viktoriabelany hl=en </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I can't really weigh myself bc my scale is so inaccurate but I see an ED team at my school who weighs me and sometimes the only motivation I have to go to my appointments is to find out my weight lmfao  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm attempting to maintain so that's why I want an accurate one :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need a scale on a budget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 19:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the scale I have is SO inaccurate and actually had been telling me I was 118 when I was actually 113. I only trust my weights from the doctors office. But I'm starting to get antsy and really wanna be able to weigh at home. 

What scales do you guys own that are accurate and not too expensive?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 02:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're everything goals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry for your losses. We're here for you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit this so annoying.. I would have lost my shit way before you did tbh, props to you!!! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 08:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also this is v important!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 05:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people have different definitions for the word "binge". 


For example, because i am used to restricting to about 800 cal or less per day, a binge is a sitting where ill feel like im uncontrollably eating and shoving anything in my mouth whether its fruit or chocolate cake. My binges have ranged from an 500 cal sitting or 3000 cal sitting on top of my usual intake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> when u in binge mode at a party and cant stop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 04:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 21:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh my gosh this post upset me :-( i cannot believe he would call you such a horrible thing. you are beautiful and deserve so much better than this jerk. being alone sucks at first, but it does get better. i hope you realize you can do so much better than him and get out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 05:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> woah I literally JUST watched this episode like 20 minutes ago  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 22:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This did hurt to read. but in my sick head tbh I would prefer if my boyfriend was honest about that shit. It would hurt so bad but id probably end up using it as motivation to lose. My boyfriend tries to tell me that I used to look better at 133-136 when now I'm 115 and still have my curves, but just a smaller waist and legs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 22:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is me when I used to b/p lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 22:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really needed to hear this today 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 19:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking love this post  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 03:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there's anything I've taken from this, it's to not reach out. I will only be coined as attention seeking and a waste of existence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 03:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hopeful you are able to support this user even though they have an ED and suicidal thoughts. Makes me hope you're not completely unable to empathize and aren't judging everyone so harshly. I just got lucky I suppose!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 02:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are the king of black and white thinking my friend. This isn't how to world works.
sleep when you need to sleep

IF ONLY! I lay in bed at midnight and can't sleep until the sun is rising 

eat if you need to eat

I wish I could! I'm trying to get there but I'm not there yet.

EVERYONE has issues. **EVERYONE**. Some people just don't deal with them as well as others and don't have the tools to cope effectively. I finally have come to terms with the fact that that is me, and to get better I have to put in a lot of really hard work. But sometimes it really does feel hopeless. 

I don't want you to grovel. I want you to learn to empathize. And see that maybe things aren't so easy to overcome as you have so successfully done in your life?? Even though you come off as a very cold and rude person who is most likely depressed themselves. It's not funny that you're parents died, it's very sad and I can't imagine the pain you must have been in. I lost my mother and am losing my father. It's scary. 

I try to be a likable person to my friends and family, but on the internet I am free to finally get the demons out of my head. And luckily, there are plenty of other people who share similar issues who can empathize.

I suggest you refrain from commenting on posts in /r/depression that suggest that the individual is just attention seeking or doesn't have a struggle that is worthy of feeling suicidal over. 


I finally reached out to /r/depression and felt relived that I came clean of all the horrible urges I've been dealing with, only to be told I'm an attention seeker. If u had posted the same bs a bunch of times and slammed the sub then FUCK YEAH I probably was seeking attention. You are being very unreasonable and hurtful. Does it make you feel good to harass someone online over their mental struggles?

You've had it hard. How's that going for you? Are you happy? You seem to know exactly what should be done in the *very obviously* black and white situation. Be my therapist. Show me the way! Tell me I'm worthless. a waste of existence. It'll change me! I *promise*.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 02:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw :-( our stats are basically the same and I can so relate. I wish I could be normal again when I used to not think twice about eating and feeling bloated and full, and not judge myself for everything I eat. *hugs*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 02:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow you sound like a great time! I'm gonna be honest, I just don't feel like responding to you anymore because I have better things to do.. As do you. Let's agree to disagree. 

You are one stubborn and mysognistic individual! I hope you can see that one day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 01:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ARE WE READING THE SAME POST?! The person has a dead bedroom, sees their husband sexually as any person in a relationship would see their SO, and is trying to have sex with their partner which is COMPLETELY REASONABLE. How is this gross? The reaction to accuse your partner of such a terrible thing is gross! 

EDIT: also "girls exaggerate" .....what in the fuck lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 01:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude did you even read the post??! Lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 00:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've encountered a bunch of different MEN on proED. Men do get ED's as well so I don't understand why you're ignoring that fact.


Also, it's so wrong that you seem to be assuming feminists are somehow immune to this disorder. I am a feminist. This disorder started out as a diet for vanity reasons, but turned into something that's eating me alive. It is now is addicting for the sense of control it provides me (while I know the disorder is really controlling me). 

Many of us on proED are unable to recover at this point in our lives. So we look for support. We're not MPA by any means and there are plenty of posts that are all about harm reduction and support outside of our disordered eating habits.

The obsessions I have about food and eating cycle through my brain 90 percent of my day, and being able to talk about them in a group with other people also struggling with a true mental illness like me is comforting because I know I won't be judged. Unlike in real like if I told people these thoughts they would laugh or judge me or just tell me to "go eat something, it's not a big deal. stop obsessing about it". 


Also, regarding that gross exaggeration of a post that may be about a family member being insensitive: can you give me an example? Because the only times I've seen responses where users will say the "concerned family member" is being unhelpful and rude is if they actually ARE being unhelpful and rude. If they are saying things like "just eat already" or "why can't you just eat normally for once" or "what's wrong with you! Just have a meal, it's not that hard" etc. there are very specific ways to go about helping someone with en ED. 

I'd take a look at this website:

http://www.nedc.com.au/what-to-say-and-do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omfg this is amazing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow this was very hurtful. about two years ago if you said this to me I'd be in denial about it being "attention seeking" because back then, my SI was mainly about attention. Though I did have very strong urges, I was never serious about them and didn't consider following through.

Unfortunately things are different now.


After losing friends because of my behavior and recognizing the shitty person I'd become, I changed myself with therapy. Two years of it. But I went cold turkey on discussing my issues with friends. I wear a really good mask everyday and people keep telling me how much better I am now. It's frustrating but at least people genuinely like me now and don't have to worry that I may harm myself. 



I don't kill myself because I know my father is terminally ill and would die faster if I died first. In the moment when I wrote this post, I didn't think about him and that's scary. He is the factor that holds me back. What ended up happening that night was I told my boyfriend I don't feel good and think I need help, so he held me and made sure he didn't leave my side. He didn't push me to tell him what was going on and I respect that. 


Your comment was very rude and as much as it hurts, I'm just more concerned you'll say something similar to another person who is struggling. Try to empathize a bit before you make such a harsh judgement about a person who is struggling. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow, this man really needs help OP. I'm so sorry this happened to you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 01:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bunghole lmfao  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 00:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooo I'm joining! 

EDIT: I requested you Glitter! Also I have no idea how this works lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 00:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend told me the way that I eat is a "turn off".. So there's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly how I feel too :-(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like my past week. I have been trying to eat normally and not think about it too much, which ends up in 3000 cal binges followed by a 300 cal day. Why can't I just eat normally and feel comfortable while doing it :| 

Anyways, we're here for you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 01:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DANG  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 00:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that sounds like something my boyfriend would say too! i guess they dont realize just how hurtful saying things like that are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 00:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im so jealous of your relationship omg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 00:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i never get true compliments either :/ once in awhile hell say something like "oh i like your hair" only after me asking him what he thinks of the new color. its never just like "you are pretty!" or "you are beautiful". i actually remember the couple of times hes said stuff like that so im sure its not just because i dont remember/recognize the compliments. it makes me feel so petty and selfish for requesting that he compliment me more :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 10:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 01:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Guinea pig snuggled in my boyfriends armpit.  http://i.imgur.com/jfayGNe.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 01:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use the girl my boyfriend used to masturbate to on Facebook as thinspo lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 01:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful bb  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 23:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok same to you!! If anything, whoever does it first can give the other person tips and stuff to go off of  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 23:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should really make the flair "thinspo" or "goal" because that's what you are  :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 23:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :D I hate my belly though so maybe when I get rid of that I'll feel more attractive lol. Also, he begged me to do couples counseling together so we're gonna try again. The cycle continues -_- 

Also I'm still gonna ho it up for Halloween by wearing whatever tf I want (he's had issues with my "going out clothes" before) and I'll try to just act confidently so I can feel confident too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 23:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preferably around Halloween weekend. I'm sick with a fever rn so I'm trying to eat more substantial foods to get better but I know I'll wanna drop any weight I gained by eating more so this is kinda perfect timing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> COULD HAVE TYPED UP THIS POST MYSELF. Seriously. Whenever people are nice to me I assume it's bc they feel bad and can tell I've got issues or something. 



When people hit on me or give me compliments, I truly never know how to process it. I just assume they haven't noticed how strange looking I really am and that when they do notice they'll be repulsed by me, the same way in repulsed by myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna join too! Could you keep me in the loop?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg please let me know how it goes! I've been a chocolate fiend since my ED started and I used to not even like chocolate lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 03:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is incredibly sad. I'm so sorry people seem like they don't care :-(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 00:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you're ok. We're all here for you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 21:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i always say this to my bf that i have no clue what my body really looks like to other people! it is so annoying. and then when people tell me i look good and stuff i dont believe them. i used to get way more compliments actually when i was 130 pounds because i was hourglass/pear shaped and had nice curves, but i just couldnt stand the number on the scale or my love handles. 

and aw :( i did something similar. i saw a picture of me from highschool about a year ago and was ew ill never get that skinny and lanky again. now i am that exact weight and want to lose more!?!? ah my brain makes no sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 18:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. someone gets it!!! Like I thought I was losing weight to feel more confident but now I keep losing weight and being excited by the numbers going down, but feel like my body isn't changing that much or still seeing major problem areas that make me feel fat or like the weight u lost hasn't been enough. My original goal was 120 but that wasn't enough. Now it is 110 and I'm about 112-113 currently, but still feel like I could lose another 10 pounds. I don't wanna keep moving my goal because it's a bad cycle but I just want to feel good about my body :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unsure about Recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 07:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is anyone like not really sure if they want to get better? I want my hair to stop thinning and i want to be healthy but i also dont want to hate my body. people are starting to get worried about me and i dont want them to.. i feel bad. I just am concerned that no matter how much i lose, ill still hate myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
