<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7578</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new GSA Field Guide is now online: 'Geology of the Baraboo, WI Area' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 23:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 06:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has, much like other volcanic eruptions dating ash layers can be used as marker horizons and is a relatively common technique: [Tephrochronology](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tephrochronology) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers at Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology (MIPT) have developed mathematical models and software that will enable Russian shale oil producers to reduce development costs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 02:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 01:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: Dee, M. W. and Pope, B. Anchoring Historical Sequences Using a New Source of Astro-chronological Tie-points. Proceedings of the Royal Society A. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archaeologists believe they have identified a new way of putting accurate dates to great events of prehistory. Rare and spectacular storms on the sun appear to have left their mark in forests and fields around the planet over the past 5,000 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 01:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 20:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Palaeozoic oceanic crust preserved beneath the eastern Mediterranean](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2784.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A piece of pre-Pangaea oceanic crust, nearly 340 million years-old, may be preserved beneath the eastern Mediterranean. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 20:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 06:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [Prediction of ground motion and dynamic stress change in Baekdusan (Changbaishan) volcano caused by a North Korean nuclear explosion](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep21477)

Related paper (open access) on recent findings with regard to partial melt beneath Mt. Paektu: [Evidence for partial melt in the crust beneath Mt. Paektu (Changbaishan), Democratic Peoples Republic of Korea and China](http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/2/4/e1501513.full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Koreas Nuclear Tests Could Bring Dormant Mount Paektu Back To Life, Cause Catastrophic Eruption,' Experts Warn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 06:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The relevant archaeological sites are all out to sea. 

For example research along the [Haida Gwaii](http://www.theglobeandmail.com/news/british-columbia/bc-researchers-may-have-found-earliest-site-of-human-habitation-in-canada/article20737278/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 11:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Postglacial viability and colonization in North Americas ice-free corridor](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature19085.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Textbook story of how humans populated America is biologically unviable, study finds. Using ancient DNA, researchers show how a prehistoric route evolved over thousands of years, revealing that it could not have been used by the first people to enter the Americas, as traditionally thought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 11:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 18:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YECs are not without their own fakes: [Paluxy "man tracks"](http://www.talkorigins.org/faqs/paluxy.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most comprehensive data set on the distribution of Neanderthals finds abiotic (climate   topography) drivers played an important role in shaping Neanderthals distribution during the Last Interglacial, and challenges the notion of Neanderthals as a species with preference for colder environments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 12:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ecological niche and distribution of Neanderthals during the Last Interglacial (open access) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 12:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piltdown Man is one of the most famous scientific hoaxes in history. A new paper in Royal Society Open Science provides compelling evidence that there was just one forger, rather than many. Also, the bones used to create the fakes came from a single orangutan specimen and at least two human skulls. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 08:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 11:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Inoceramus ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 16:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [Fluids during diagenesis and sulfate vein formation in sediments at Gale crater, Mars](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/maps.12668/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mineral veins found in Mars' Gale Crater were formed by the evaporation of ancient Martian lakes, a new study has shown. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 16:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 07:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [Fluids during diagenesis and sulfate vein formation in sediments at Gale crater, Mars](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/maps.12668/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mineral veins found in Mars' Gale Crater were formed by the evaporation of ancient Martian lakes, a new study has shown. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 07:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 22:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Voluminous plutonism during volcanic quiescence revealed by thermochemical modeling of zircon](http://geology.gsapubs.org/content/early/2016/07/12/G37968.1.abstract) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Traces of Failed Super-eruption in the Andes. Geoscientists from Heidelberg University have discovered accumulations of magma in the Andes sufficient to have set off a super-eruption but which, in fact, did not. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 22:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Paleolithic Sculpture Discovered: A paleolithic sculpture has turned up in the cave of Foissac, carved from a large bovine bone and, somewhat unusually, with designs engraved upon it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 01:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 21:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Timing and causes of mid-Holocene mammoth extinction on St. Paul Island, Alaska](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/07/27/1604903113) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the last known populations of woolly mammoths was wiped out 5,600 years ago by a lack of freshwater, research suggests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 21:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 12:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [An asteroidal origin for water in the Moon](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160531/ncomms11684/full/ncomms11684.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research of lunar samples shows that asteroids (a combination of carbonaceous chondrite-type materials), not comets, were responsible for the majority of water and nitrogen delivered to the Moon ~4.54.3 Ga. The study places important constraints on the origin of water in the inner Solar System. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 12:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 03:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [New insights into gully formation on Mars: Constraints from composition as seen by MRO/CRISM](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL068956/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New findings using data from NASA's Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter show that gullies on modern Mars are likely not being formed by flowing liquid water but mechanisms such as the freeze and thaw of carbon dioxide frost as being the major drivers of recent gully evolution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 03:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 03:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it isn't farmed, it's mined. While this is considered by some to be a diverse ecosystem that shouldn't prevent its potential exploitation, however, what *should* prevent its potential exploitation is whether or not the system can undergo reclamation. In other words, is the ecosystem capable of returning to normal under a relatively short interval of time once operations are completed. This is essentially the purpose behind this study:

In addition to this, the ISA has stipulated that prior to exploitation, a benthic biological baseline study must be undertaken for each exploration contract area.

Unfortunately, our knowledge of marine ecosystems is fairly poor to say the least when it comes to abyssal habitats, and it has taken the potential for resource extraction to motivate progress in this regard:

No megafaunal studies had been undertaken in the UK-1 contract area prior to licensing in 2013... 

Interestingly previous studies have suggested that these systems are fully capable of recovering:

In 1978, a dredge aboard the Hughes Glomar Explorer, operated by the American mining consortium Ocean Minerals Company (OMCO), made a mining track at a depth of 5000 meters in the nodule fields of the CCFZ. In 2004, the French Research Institute for Exploitation of the Sea (IFREMER) conducted the Nodinaut expedition to this mining track (which is still visible on the seabed) to study the long-term effects of this physical disturbance on the sediment and its benthic fauna. ... the biological activity measured in the track by instruments aboard the manned submersible bathyscaphe Nautile did not differ from a nearby unperturbed site. This data suggests that the benthic fauna and nutrient fluxes at the watersediment interface has fully recovered. 

 \- [Geochemical and biological recovery of the disturbed seafloor in polymetallic nodule fields of the Clipperton-Clarion Fracture Zone (CCFZ) at 5,000-m depth](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.4319/lo.2006.51.5.2033/abstract;jsessionid=63ED0723EF6D9A8B441118D25C26EBA4.f03t02?systemMessage=Wiley+Online+Library+will+be+unavailable+on+Saturday+30th+July+2016+from+08%3A00-11%3A00+BST+%2F+03%3A00-06%3A00+EST+%2F+15%3A00-18%3A00+SGT+for+essential+maintenance.Apologies+for+the+inconvenience.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 07:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How do geologists know when it's time to evacuate?

Geologists monitor volcanic activity using numerous methods. Note, however, that while we can say whether or not an eruption is likely, we cannot say with 100% certainty that an eruption will (or in some cases will not) occur. The best indicators are signs of increasing activity well above what are considered to be normal or background levels of activity. Sampling the composition, and concentration of gases and water, observing changes in topography using GPS and LiDAR as the ground deforms, observing changes in temperature using thermal imaging techniques, and most commonly watching for increased activity on seismic networks, looking for seismic swarms, harmonic tremors and in general - a substantial increase above background levels. However, *some* volcanoes are known for erupting without any warning. That is without seismic activity such as the more recent eruption of [Pavlof Volcano](http://www.ktva.com/why-did-pavlof-volcano-erupt-with-almost-no-seismic-warning-609/) along the Alaskan Peninsula. Certain types of eruptions may also lack warning signs, such as the 2014 phreatic eruption of [Mount Ontake](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2014_Mount_Ontake_eruption) in Japan. The devices in place (monitoring the volcano where 12 seismometers, 5 GPS stations and 1 tiltmeter) showed no surface deformation and no clear indicators of increased seismicity.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 00:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [Magma storage in a strike-slip caldera](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160722/ncomms12295/full/ncomms12295.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The build-up of magma six kilometres below El Salvador's Ilopango caldera means the capital city of San Salvador may be at risk from future eruptions, University of Bristol researchers have found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 00:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 11:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Figures 2, 3, 4 and 7 are not ammonites. It's difficult to say without actually resorting to the books and recalling specific traits, but I would lean towards a sponge, coral, or large [benthic(?) foraminifera](http://sepmstrata.org/page.aspx? pageid=730 5). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A professional grade personal seismograph. Plug it into your Raspberry Pi and start watching the earth move! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 05:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 11:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Abrupt plate accelerations shape rifted continental margins](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature18319.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers discover that plates move in 2 phases: a slow phase   a fast phase, explaining the differences between proximal and distal margins and demonstrating that abrupt plate acceleration during continental rifting is controlled by the nonlinear decay of the resistive rift strength force. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 11:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Otherworldly Polka Dots of Spotted Lake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 11:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 06:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A magnitude 9.0 earthquake has just occurred off the BC coast. A massive tsunami races towards land at the speed of a commercial jet. Preparedness Now simulates this hypothetical, but realistic disaster scenario and looks at what damage can be expected and what people can do to prepare themselves.

[Preparedness Now - ShakeOutBC](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t_IWJx-mOw0) (23:00) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 06:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may feel insufficient, but that's 1min and 30s to [drop, cover and hold on](http://www.shakeoutbc.ca/dropcoverholdon/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 21:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: **Dental Disparity and Ecological Stability in Bird-like Dinosaurs prior to the End-Cretaceous Mass Extinction**: http://www.cell.com/current-biology/fulltext/S0960-9822(16)30249-4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research on maniraptoran dinosaurs, the group that includes Velociraptor and modern birds, shows that having a beak conferred a survival advantage through the end-Cretaceous mass extinction by providing birds the ability to eat seeds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 21:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First B.C. offshore earthquake early warning sensor up and running: Once complete, network will provide up to 90 seconds of warning when the big one strikes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 12:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 12:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is simply no way we can [tell] these events from events that predict a super eruption.

Current activity within the Yellowstone Volcanic Field is not at all suggestive of an imminent eruption, let alone a super-eruption. Intense precursory activity (far exceeding background levels) at multiple spots within the Yellowstone Volcanic Field would indicate an eruption *may* be imminent; however, the small earthquakes, ground uplift and subsidence, and gas releases at Yellowstone are commonplace events and do not reflect impending eruptions - as is normal for any active volcanic field. 

Geysers spring up or stop working...

That's how hydrothermal systems operate. Fluids are transported along fluid pathways (open space filling) where mineral deposition occurs. Continued mineral deposition will eventually seal off the fluid pathway (hydrostatic pressure  lithostatic pressure). This causes pressure to subsequently build until it fractures the rock (hydrostatic pressure  lithostatic pressure) allowing fluids to be transported again, and the process repeats (this is similar to how the banding in agates is formed through several fluid pulses). 

the[re] are earthquakes all the time...

They are small and discrete, and to be expected in an active volcanic field. Suspicions would likely arise should they be sustained ([harmonic tremors](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Harmonic_tremor)). Earthquakes are also another means of sealing off fluid pathways until pressure fractures the rock permitting fluids to flow again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 11:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As per the [Yellowstone FAQ](https://www.nps.gov/yell/learn/nature/volcanoqa.htm):

Q: Will the Yellowstone volcano erupt soon?

A: Current geologic activity at Yellowstone has remained relatively constant since scientists first started monitoring more than 30 years ago. Another caldera-forming eruption is theoretically possible, but it is very unlikely in the next thousand or even 10,000 years. Scientists have also found no indication of an imminent smaller eruption of lava.

...

Q: How do scientists know the Yellowstone volcano won't erupt?

A: Scientists from the Yellowstone Volcano Observatory (YVO) watch an array of monitors in place throughout the region. These monitors would detect sudden or strong movements or shifts in heat that would indicate increasing activity. No such evidence exists at this time. 

etc.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 00:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....  how do we detect or monitor this?

As per the article:

According to Gualda, the decompression period would likely be accompanied by the expansion of the magma body which should have detectable effects on the Earths surface.

'Listening' to the distinctive tell tale signs of magma as it moves through the Earth's crust with the use of seismometers; watching surface deformation (mapping changes in topography) with GPS   LiDAR; and sampling gases from fumaroles for changes in composition are all currently methods used to detect and monitor volcanic activity, amongst others: http://volcanoes.usgs.gov/volcanoes/yellowstone/yellowstone_monitoring_47.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 00:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not overly familiar with the specifics surrounding the [Yellowstone hot spot](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yellowstone_hotspot) eruptive history... though it appears that Yellowstone is composed of [at least four calderas](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Yellowstone_Caldera_map2.JPG) with the last *violent* eruption occurring ~174ka. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 19:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [A post-wildfire response in cave dripwater chemistry](http://www.hydrol-earth-syst-sci.net/20/2745/2016/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When mineral-rich water drips from a caves ceiling over centuries and millennia, it forms rocky cones that hold clues to the Earths past climate. Now, for the 1st time, researchers in Australia   the UK have found that these structures can also help trace past wildfires that burned above the cave. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 19:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 19:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [The Year Leading to a Supereruption](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0159200) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super-eruptions may give only about a year's warning before they blow. That is the conclusion of a new microscopic analysis of quartz crystals in pumice taken from the Bishop Tuff in eastern California, which is the site of the super-eruption that formed the Long Valley Caldera 760,000 years ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 19:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 05:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Origin and implications of non-radial Imbrium Sculpture on the Moon](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v535/n7612/full/nature18278.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3.8 to 4 billion years ago, a protoplanet collided with the Moon and formed the Imbrium Basin. The new research also suggests, based on the sizes of other impact basins in the Moon, Mars and Mercury, that the early solar system was likely well stocked with protoplanet-sized asteroids. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 05:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 11:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research Paper: [Fortnightly modulation of San Andreas tremor and low-frequency earthquakes](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/07/13/1524316113) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Low-frequency earthquakes on San Andreas Fault triggered by gravitational tug of Sun and Moon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 11:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient B.C. tsunamis etched stories into Vancouver Island's sediment: Scientists have found evidence of ancient tsunamis from Port Hardy to Tofino and Ucluelet B.C. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 09:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 16:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research: [Assessing the volcanic hazard for Rome: 40Ar/39Ar and In-SAR constraints on the most recent eruptive activity and present-day uplift at Colli Albani Volcanic District](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069518/full?campaign=wlytk-41855.6211458333) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Colli Albani Volcanic District on the outskirts of Rome, previously dormant, could be waking up. Scientists have observed new steam vents, earthquakes and a rise in ground level in the hills and surrounding area. It has a recurrence interval of ~31ka, and it's been 36ka since the last eruptions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 16:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The oxygen level of Earths past atmosphere has been directly measured from inclusion gases trapped in halite. A direct glimpse of the composition of the mid- to late Neoproterozoic atmosphere, ~815 million years ago registers an average oxygen content of 10.9%. (open access - pdf) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 09:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 09:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research: [Assessing the volcanic hazard for Rome: 40Ar/39Ar and In-SAR constraints on the most recent eruptive activity and present-day uplift at Colli Albani Volcanic District](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069518/full?campaign=wlytk-41855.6211458333) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long thought to be dormant the Colli Albani Volcanic District (CAVD), outside Italys capital, is entering a new eruptive cycle a recently published study finds. In recent years, scientists have observed new steam vents, earthquakes and a rise in ground level in the hills and surrounding area. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 09:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 23:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an interesting paper, but it does seem to be pulling at straws in a number of areas. When the question of timing arises, the soft sediment deformation structures do not correlate with the formation of the Manicouagan Crater (a discrepancy of ~14 million years). 

The Manicouagan impact crater, 100 km in diameter and 2000 km from the UK in late Triassic palaeogeographic reconstructions (Fig. 7), might be considered a candidate but for its significantly earlier date of 214 Ma ago (Hodych and Dunning, 1992) against 200 Ma ago for the Lilstock Formation (Plfy et al., 2000; Hesselbo et al., 2002). Further, indirect, evidence for this age mismatch comes from soft-sediment deformation in the late Triassic (early Norian) Blomidon Formation of Nova Scotia (Fig. 7)(Ackermann et al.,1995; Tanner, 2002), 700 km to the north of the impact, and an horizon of microtektites and shocked quartz, dated to 214Ma ago, within the Mercia Mudstone Group of southern England (Fig. 7)(Walkden et al., 2002).

As per the discussion:

...no impact crater of the right age has yet been located and other evidence in support of a bolide impact remains inconclusive. The work of Cohen and Coe (2002) even suggests that a major impact was unlikely at this time. The impact of a
km-scale asteroid does provide a plausible explanation for the observed sedimentological effects in the Cotham Member across the UK, but the evidence is far from unequivocal. Even if ultimately confirmed as the cause, current evidence does not indicate it as a significant contributory factor in the generation of either the isotope excursion or the biotic changes through the TriassicJurassic boundary interval.

 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shadowed regions on Ceres may have ice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 15:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 05:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [A new Bayesian Event Tree tool to track and quantify volcanic unrest and its application to Kawah Ijen volcano](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GC006327/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A New Tool to Better Forecast Volcanic Unrest: In a retrospective study of volcanic unrest at Indonesia's Kawah Ijen, a new model was able to pick up on the rising probability of eruption 2 months before authorities were aware of the risk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 05:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 22:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps a mixture of minerals. Magnetic properties could arise from the presence of magnetite (Fe3O4), while the sulfur smell could arise from the presence of galena (PbS) and/or sphalerite ((Zn,Fe)S). The combination of these ore minerals would also explain the weight. 

As for the origin, SedEx or VMS deposits may be likely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 19:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [High-resolution seismic constraints on flow dynamics in the oceanic asthenosphere](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature18012.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study provides the most detailed view yet of how the Earth's mantle flows. The study upends a common belief that the strongest deformation in the mantle is controlled by large-scale movement of the plates. Instead, the study finds that smaller-scale processes have more powerful effects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 19:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By data mining a vast collection of novels, researchers have identified the six basic plots that all stories follow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 02:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers uncover stampede of dinosaur tracks in northeastern B.C., and although research is only in the early stages, it is already thought to be one of the biggest collections of fossilized tracks ever found in North America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 09:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opal discovered in Antarctic meteorite provides more evidence that meteorites and asteroids can carry large amounts of water ice. The opal formed before the meteorite was blasted off from the surface of the parent asteroid and sent into space, eventually to land on Earth in Antarctica. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 02:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oxygen escape from the Earth during geomagnetic reversals: Implications to mass extinction (open access) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 22:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 10:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It refers to the hydroxl group (OH^- ) contained within the mineral. A 'wet' magma or melt contains minerals that contain water in the form of a hydroxl group, and other volatiles. For example, basalt (olivine, pyroxene and plagioclase) is dry, where as andesite (plagioclase, pyroxene / hornblende and accessory minerals such as biotite) and granite are wet.
___

Basalt's primary composition consists of

Olivine: (Mg,Fe)2SiO4

Pyroxene: XY(Si,Al)2O6 *where X represents Ca, Na, Fe^+2 and Mg and more rarely Zn, Mn and Li and Y represents ions of smaller size, such as Cr, Al, Fe^+3, Mg, Co, Mn, Sc, Ti, Va and even Fe^+2*

Plagioclase Feldspar: NaAlSi3O8  CaAl2Si2O8

Notice how there were no OH groups present in any of those minerals? Now let's look at Granite.
___

Granite:

Potassium feldspar:  KAlSi3O8 or (K,Na)(Si,Al)4O8

Plagioclase Feldspar: NaAlSi3O8  CaAl2Si2O8

Quartz: SiO2

Muscovite:  KAl2(AlSi3O10)(F,**OH**)2, or (KF)2(Al2O3)3(SiO2)6(**H2O**)

Biotite: K(Mg,Fe)3(AlSi3O10)(F,**OH**)2

Hornblende-type amphiboles: Ca2(Mg, Fe, Al)5(Al,Si)8O22(**OH**)2
___

Should ascending magma come into contact with groundwater an eruption [would likely occur](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Phreatomagmatic_eruption). 

Because these 'wet' minerals are stable at depth, they will destabilize as the magma ascends releasing their volatiles. In essence the magma produces its own water, known as [magmatic water or juvenile water](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Magmatic_water) as opposed to meteoric water which is derived from precipitation (snow and rain) and recharges aquifers.

A more specific use of the term can be found in John D. Winter's Igneous and Metamorphic Petrology text:

A fluid-saturated melt is one that contains the maximum amount of a dissolved volatile species possible under the existing P-T-X conditions. Any volatiles present in excess of that amount must be present as a separate coexisting fluid phase. The term fluid pressure (Pf) is commonly used to describe the combined effect of pressure and fluid content in fluid-bearing systems. A melt system at a specific pressure can vary from fluid saturated (Pf = Ptotal) to fluid free (Pf = 0, also called dry), depending on the amount of fluid species available. Pf rarely exceeds Ptotal, at least not for long, because the result would be expulsion of the excess volatiles, often explosively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 09:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Groundwater is relatively shallow, and any magma to come into contact with the aquifer would, result in a phreatomagmatic eruption, if not in the very least a phreatic eruption prior to contact with the magma.

Wet and dry magma's are nomenclature used to describe the abundance of 'wet' minerals such amphiboles, and micas. For example, basalt (olivine, pyroxene and plagioclase) is dry, where as andesite (plagioclase, pyroxene / hornblende and accessory minerals such as biotite) is wet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why it's important to know when and how plate tectonics began, and what was Earths tectonic style before plate tectonics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 09:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 02:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colour: Amontillado Sherry (caramel E150a colourant added)

Body: Full bodied, smooth and waxy

Nose: Orange citrus, sherry, burnt sticks, and peat. 

Palate: A dry sweet arrival, cinnamon sticks, clove spice, cooked fruit, and orange marmalade all enveloped in mild cigar smoke

Finish: Subtle smoke, medium length and smooth

Score: 85/100

Notes: While not overly complex, it strikes a fine balance in flavours. No single flavour is overly strong and no single flavour over powers the other, and for this reason may be a good introductory scotch for those looking to venture towards smoke and peat, as it was for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review #10: Jura Superstition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 02:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 11:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NASA's Cassini mission has already done that on [multiple flybys](https://saturn.jpl.nasa.gov/news/2847/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 02:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Enceladus's internal ocean and ice shell constrained from Cassini gravity, shape, and libration data](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL068634/abstract) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A vast ocean of water beneath the icy crust of Saturns moon Enceladus may be more accessible than previously thought, according to new research, revealing that near the moons poles, the ice covering Enceladus could be just 2km thick, the thinnest known ice shell of any ocean-covered moon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 02:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 22:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Direct measurement of thermal conductivity in solid iron at planetary core conditions](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v534/n7605/full/nature18009.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study resolves Earth's geodynamo paradox by directly measuring thermal conductivity of iron at planetary core conditions for the first time, indicating that Earths geodynamo has persisted since the beginning of Earths history, and allowing for a solid inner core as old as the dynamo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 22:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 13:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of the data supporting the Snowball is highly disputed...

For the sake of clarity, [snowball Earth events](http://www.snowballearth.org/when.html) aren't what are disputed amongst the majority, but rather their extent - ie. hard snowball, slush-ball, refugia, etc.

Explaining away the wide spread repeated succession and distribution of glacial sediments (ice rafted debris, etc.) followed by [cap carbonates](http://static.skepticalscience.com/pics/cap-carbonate.jpg) other than by snowball Earth events has been met without significant progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 13:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. Any number of techniques are often combined to cross check one another between various data sets (for example, fossils, can provide general paleolatitudes as well as isotopic analysis to constrain latitudes), and if sample numbers are high enough they would either provide you with a data set in which they all average out (one which you could therefore use), or a data set that would tell you nothing with regard to the paleomagnetic data because the data would be far too scattered.

Maybe it wasn't the rocks and moved it was the magnetic fields.

When the poles move relative to a fixed reference frame (which they have always done) it's known as [apparent polar wander](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Apparent_polar_wander), when the actual poles move it's known as [true polar wander](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/True_polar_wander) (which has been used to explain the ~800Ma [Bitter Springs carbon isotope excursion](https://i.imgur.com/xDQQykX.jpg)).

It should also be noted that the further one goes back in time, the larger the margin of error. To that extent paleomagnetic data is often taken, by many, with a grain of salt when discussing older data sets as stepwise demagnetization of any remnant magnetization (thermoremanent magnetization, chemical remanent magnetization, depositional remanent magnetization, viscous remanent magnetization), should it exist, may not yield viable or valuable results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tales from a Westeros Geologist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 22:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 20:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tridymite may be found with basalt, but I don't believe it is of primary origin, forming from later alteration events as basalt does not contain enough free SiO2 (they're at opposite ends of Bowen's reaction series). 

Fe-rich olivine is relatively much less common, but it occurs in igneous rocks in small amounts in rare granites and rhyolites, and extremely Fe-rich olivine can exist stably with quartz and tridymite. In contrast, Mg-rich olivine does not occur stably with silica minerals, as it would react with them to form orthopyroxene ((Mg,Fe)2Si2O6). - [wiki](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Olivine#Identification_and_paragenesis) 

The following is from the study:

Tridymite Formation Pathways

... Many terrestrial tridymite occurrences are associated with silicic volcanism, which, by its nature, has the requisites of high temperatures and high-SiO2 lava compositions (dacite and rhyolite) for tridymite formation within its stability field. Vapor-phase formation of tridymite (along with sanidine and iron oxides) occurs in vugs and lithophysae in rhyolitic ash-flow tuff (2835). For example, the mineral stratigraphy within compound cooling units of a rhyolitic ash-flow tuff showed tridymite is most abundant (25 wt.%) in the central zone where temperatures were highest and occurs along with sanidine as crystals growing into voids; cristobalite and sanidine occur in cooler zones where replacement of glass predominates (30). Tridymite derived from oxidation of fayalite has also been reported in a rhyolite flow (Oregon) (36). At the Iwodake rhyolitic cone of Satsuma-Iwojima volcano (Japan), a tridymite formation pathway is alteration of rhyolite by volcanic vapors and acidic hydrothermal fluids at temperatures up to 900 C (3740). Acid sulfate leaching of rhyolite also occurred there, increasing the SiO2 concentration from 71 wt.% to 97 wt.%

 ... 

The temperature regime associated with basaltic and intermediate volcanism can also provide a formation pathway for tridymite when the requisite high-SiO2 material is present... In altered basalts from Stromboli volcano (Aeolian Islands, Italy) and andesites from Augustine volcano (Alaska), the high-SiO2 host for tridymite is the residue after acid sulfate leaching of primary mafic rock (42, 43).

As you mention, the amount of tridymite found is also quite telling:

... The high concentrations of tridymite (14 wt.% of bulk sample) and SiO2 (74 wt.%) for the Buckskin sample are not reasonably sourced from low-silica volcanics... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 18:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Recent Tectonic Activity on Pluto Driven by Phase Changes in the Ice Shell](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069220/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research bolsters case for a present-day subsurface ocean on Pluto: An updated thermal model for Pluto suggests that liquid water beneath the dwarf planets ice shell may not be frozen yet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 18:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 10:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under the assumption that the studies interpretation is correct, that the tridymite (SiO2) is primary and most likely volcanic in origin, it requires a magma source that is relatively high in silica as tridymite is a polymorph of SiO2. For magma to become rich in silica (SiO2) it has to undergo differentiation. Following [Bowen's reaction series](https://i.imgur.com/SaWgr2f.gif), the melt will contain a higher fraction of silica the more the magma is differentiated. Because of this, certain magmas typify specific geologic conditions. *Generally speaking*, magma erupting along sea floor spreading centres (rifts), and hot spots (Hawaii, Iceland, etc.) will be of basaltic composition resulting from partial melting of the asthenosphere; magmas erupting along volcanic arcs will incorporate more water from their position along subduction zones and be of andesitic composition; magmas that make their way up through continental crust will differentiate the most and are of rhyolitic composition. Magma rises due to density contrasts - once it becomes neutrally buoyant it stalls and crystallizes until a fraction of the remaining melt is positively buoyant again. This new melt composition begins to rise until it becomes neutrally buoyant, and [the process repeats itself](https://i.imgur.com/Y5EEUOO.jpg). Each time it stalls, the melt fraction will become more rich in silica as more elements such as Fe, and Mg are the first to crystallize (recall Bowen's reaction series) progressing as follows:

- Ultra mafic *(peridotite / komatiite with SiO2  45%)* 

- Mafic *(gabbro / basalt with SiO2 4552%)* 

- Intermediate *(diorite / andesite with SiO2 5263%)*

- Intermediate - felsic *(granodiorite / dacite with SiO2 6369%)*

- Felsic *(granite / rhyolite with SiO2  69%)*

Olympus Mons, by the way, is a shield volcano, similar to Hawaii, with a basaltic composition.

So what does this all mean? It means that not all volcanoes are the same, and their associated lava flows / magma can tell you about the geological conditions surrounding its formation. To find terrestrial tridymite, volcanic in origin, means it must have formed from a magma exceptionally rich in SiO2 (ie. dacite and rhyolite). The general view of Mars is that of a purely basaltic planet, however, the discovery of tridymite adds support to previous studies that infer high SiO2 compositions, and thus the geological evolution of Mars. 

Things can get quite complex, for example discussing the different polymorphs of silica such as alpha and beta tridymite, etc. but I hope I kept this explanation general enough to follow along and grasp the basic idea as to why the discovery of tridymite on Mars is not entirely expected, as well as important in understanding how Mars evolved as a planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 02:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [Silicic volcanism on Mars evidenced by tridymite in high-SiO2 sedimentary rock at Gale crater](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/06/07/1607098113.full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA Scientists Discover Unexpected Mineral on Mars: Tridymite, which crystallizes at low pressures and high temperatures from high-SiO2 materials, was detected at high concentrations in a sedimentary mudstone in Gale crater, a finding that may alter our understanding of how the planet evolved. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 02:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 21:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [Almost a spider: a 305-million-year-old fossil arachnid and spider origins](http://rspb.royalsocietypublishing.org/content/283/1827/20160125) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost a spider: a 305-million-year-old fossil arachnid discovered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 21:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 21:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [Almost a spider: a 305-million-year-old fossil arachnid and spider origins](http://rspb.royalsocietypublishing.org/content/283/1827/20160125) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost a spider: a 305-million-year-old fossil arachnid discovered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 21:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The same asteroid that contributed to extinction of the dinosaurs at the end of the Cretaceous almost wiped out the mammals as well, a new study finds. Their results showed that over 93% became extinct across the K-Pg boundary, but that they also recovered far more quickly than previously thought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 10:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 11:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It lays out the arguments, and highlights each of their weaknesses. With so many major problems for the 'blitzkrieg' hypothesis, I'm not ready to accept it as the primary contributor - as was seen in the case of the South American megafauna. In the end Hanes suggests it's likely a combination of the two, though this treads on *[argumentum ad temperantiam](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Argument_to_moderation)*. As more [evidence](http://www.cbc.ca/news/technology/woolly-mammoth-diet-mystery-solved-by-dna-analysis-1.2524015) is discovered, hopefully, the story will be told in full. For South America, at least, it appears that climate change was most certainly the primary driver with humans potentially acting as 'the straw that broke the camels back.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 10:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not familiar enough with the data sets available for various locations throughout the geologic past; however, I would be hesitant to support your statement as data may be scarce, as was the case with South America, until this study, which found climate change to be the primary driver which subsequently permitted humans to potentially have a greater impact. Higher resolution data in the future may yield [a different interpretation](http://www.cbc.ca/news/technology/woolly-mammoth-diet-mystery-solved-by-dna-analysis-1.2524015), and as the fossil record continues to grow the trend is to push the arrival of humans even further back. Perhaps more to your point, however, one should note that not all glacial and interglacial periods were the same. For example, it is known that ice sheets obtained their maximum thickness only during the last glacial maximum, and were thinner under previous glacial periods. Rates of warming, and cooling differed, as did the magnitude of warming and cooling, and their duration, etc. 

I'm not dismissing your point entirely, but rather suggesting a little more caution before leaping to conclusions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 00:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want a lengthy response, I would recommend Gary Hanes presentation, "Late Pleistocene megafaunal extinctions" hosted by the Royal Tyrrell Museum (available on youtube, 2012). If you want the short answer I would recommend [this article](http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-06-18/climate-drove-demise-of-south-america's-giant-beasts/7517222) on this study, which is nicely summed up in the opening sentence: 

Sabre-toothed cats, one-tonne bears and sloths the size of elephants all happily coexisted with humans for up to 3,000 years, but were extinct within 300 years after the climate of South America rapidly warmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bone artifacts suggest early adoption of poison-tipped arrow technology in Eastern Africa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 00:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 08:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emily Graslie of 'The Brain Scoop' covered these fossil meteorites in an episode called '[Fossil Meteorites](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6aEdhZP8g-s)' back in 2014, if anyone is interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 18:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To clarify your initial statement:

...zircons older than 3.8 Ga lack shock fractures...

Are you implying that prior to 3.8Ga there were no impacts events, and that the LHB did not occur?

Addressing the following:

Detrital zircons are created during subduction, that later turns up on younger sediment after their parent rocks have surfaced and eroded away.

Detrital simply refers to lithics that have been eroded, transported and later deposited by sedimentary processes (predominantly by fluid transport). It says nothing of the formation process of said lithic(s). Zircons do not solely form in subduction zones, and are formed through magmatic, metamorphic, and alteration (hydrothermal zircons) processes. Furthermore, zircons formed *during* impact events would obviously be devoid of shock features. Thus, detrital zircons are created by any number of processes and are later eroded and deposited elsewhere, no longer remaining in-situ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 01:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because unlike Nibiru (ie. planet 'x'), Theia has a substantial amount of peer-reviewed scientific evidence to support such claims - specifically from [lunar formation models](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Giant-impact_hypothesis). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 09:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Asteroid bombardment and the core of Theia as possible sources for the Earth's late veneer component](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GC006305/abstract) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study argues the collision of Earth and Theia could be the source of the precious metals on Earth, reviving the debate between the Theia theory and the Late Heavy Bombardment theory, with implications for the origin of life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 09:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 09:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emily Graslie of 'The Brain Scoop' covered these fossil meteorites in an episode called 'Fossil Meteorites ' back in 2014, if anyone is interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 02:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The extinction of mammoths, and other large megafauna, is still an area of much debate. Though the two major competing theories revolve around a [changing climate and habitat](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v506/n7486/full/nature12921.html), and human predation. An excellent summary is discussed at length by Gary Hanes during his presentation at the Royal Tyrrell Museum - "[Late Pleistocene megafaunal extinctions](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8WZ5Q2JYbLY)."   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 11:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking myself for locations within Canada where one may be able to view it / sample it. It doesn't appear to be an easy task to research, though the paper [Palynological and Iridium Anomalies at Cretaceous-Tertiary Boundary, South-Central Saskatchewan](http://www.ganino.com/games/Science/Science%201986-1988/root/data/Science_1986-1988/pdf/1986_v231_n4739/p4739_0714.pdf) (pdf) suggests a locality at [Morgan Creek](http://www.geonames.org/6078534/morgan%20creek.html), Sask.

I would suspect that the best localities would be where previous marine sediments were deposited. Paleogeographical reconstructions are likely to contain some degree of error but I would assume regions located within the Western Interior Seaway may prove to yield the best results [75Ma](https://www2.nau.edu/rcb7/namK75.jpg), [65Ma](https://www2.nau.edu/rcb7/namKT65.jpg), along with coastal regions. [Grasslands National Park, Zahursky Point] (http://earthsciencescanada.com/geovista/PDFs_en/vistas9_zp.pdf) (pdf) has a well documented outcrop.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A famous fossil trove in Argentina recently gave up a new treasure: the first fossil footprints ever reported of the saber-toothed cat Smilodon. The four tracks, discovered last year, are larger than those of todays Bengal tiger, measuringin one case19.2 centimeters across. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 12:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 23:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. I'll never grow tired of it, and have spent countless hours just staring up at the night sky wondering who, if anyone, is looking back. 

- Not the Milky Way, but it is "[in a tent in the middle of no where](https://www.flickr.com/photos/luxlaboratories/23693449703/in/photostream/lightbox/)"

- The Milky Way from the [Alvord Desert](https://www.flickr.com/photos/luxlaboratories/15143169535/in/photostream/lightbox/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wingsuit Flight Over An Active Volcano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 20:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 19:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research (open access): [Lasting mantle scars lead to perennial plate tectonics](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160610/ncomms11834/full/ncomms11834.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research suggests some major changes to geology textbooks. Super-computer modelling of Earth's crust and upper-mantle suggests that ancient geologic events may have left deep 'scars' that can come to life to play a role in earthquakes, mountain formation, and other ongoing processes on our planet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 19:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 08:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research: [Assessment of continuous (unconventional) oil and gas resources in the Late Cretaceous Mancos Shale of the Piceance Basin, Uinta-Piceance Province, Colorado and Utah, 2016](https://pubs.er.usgs.gov/publication/fs20163030) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USGS Updates Mancos Shale Gas Assessment. Estimates 66 Trillion Cubic Feet of Natural Gas in Colorados Mancos Shale Formation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 08:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lyuba, the worlds best preserved woolly mammoth mummy [OC][4608 x 3088] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 19:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #FridayFolds - Port Alberni, British Columbia - Haslam Formation (Nanaimo Group) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 19:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 17:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you? 

Also, should I try to improve my reviews, and if so, what recommendations do you have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 17:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research: [Exhumed hydrocarbon-seep authigenic carbonates from Zakynthos Island (Greece): Concretions not archaeological remains](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0264817216301611) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Underwater lost city found to be a natural geologically occurring phenomenon, with concretion morphology that resembles archaeological stonework of the Hellenic period. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 17:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took a while, but an idea finally took hold for how I wanted to photograph this expression. It's not exactly what I had in mind, but it works well enough such that I am confident in posting a review to accompany it.

Colour: Burnished

Body: Full bodied

Nose: Vanilla and butter, dried apricots, Orcadian peat and subtle wood smoke, Oloroso sherry.

Palate: Sweet fruity arrival, malt, floral - distinctive heather, wild honey and a hint of spice

Finish: Subtle smoke, dry, crisp, medium length and smooth

Score: 88/100

Notes: The position on the board is the final position from game 21, the final game, of the World Chess Championship between challenger Bobby Fischer of the United States and defending champion Boris Spassky of the Soviet Union. Fischer would go on to win the match 12.5-8.5, a crushing moment in the midst of the Cold War. On second thought I should have used game 12 to match the age of the expression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review #9: Highland Park 12 Year Old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 19:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 05:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ship_of_Theseus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mysterious Markings May Hold Clues to Origin of Writing: Geometric signs on cave walls and ancient artifacts may be some of humanitys earliest graphic communications. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 19:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planetary Resources asteroid miners focus on Earth observation with $21 million in new funding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 19:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 01:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Geology**: Naniamo Group Sediments, Haslam Formation (of late Santonian to early Campanian age ~83.6Ma): dominated by grey to dark grey siltstone and mudstone / argillite and shale, with thin interbeds of fine to coarse grained sandstone. Fine grained facies may be dark grey, organic-rich and laminated, are typically calcareous, with calcareous concretions, but are more typically bioturbated. Shelly fossils are present, in distinct calcarenite beds in some locations, but not usually abundant. Thin, interbedded sandstones are generally sharp-based, laminated and rippled, display partial (B-D) Bouma turbidite sequences, and are typically arranged into coarsening and thickening upward sequences several to tens of metres thick. In addition, overall there is a general coarsening-upward trend over the entire thickness. The Haslam Formation has been interpreted to represent low-energy deposition in marine shelf to relatively deep slope depositional facies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monocline Monday is a thing right? [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 01:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 seconds - Hole in the Wall - Port Alberni, British Columbia [OC][4608 x 3456] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 00:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 10:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (open access): [Trends in the Rare Earth Element Content of U.S.-Based Coal Combustion Fly Ashes](http://pubs.acs.org/doi/full/10.1021/acs.est.6b00085) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study of the content of rare earth elements in U.S. coal ashes shows that coal mined from the Appalachian Mountains could be the proverbial golden goose for hard-to-find materials critical to clean energy and other emerging technologies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 10:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Underwater landslide doubled size of 2011 Japanese tsunami </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 18:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 13:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research: [Prebiotic chemistry and atmospheric warming of early Earth by an active young Sun](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2719.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Violent young Sun may have seeded life on Earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 13:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 13:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your [Barite](http://webmineral.com/data/Barite.shtml) and [Witherite](http://webmineral.com/data/Witherite.shtml) are labelled incorrectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 23:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barite (barium sulfate, BaSO4) is one thing, [witherite](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Witherite#Risk_to_human_health) (barium carbonate, BaCO3) is quite another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 22:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fracking is fine when properly regulated...

What is considered to be properly regulated? Was [Texas](http://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2016-05/ssoa-hhb051016.php) 'properly regulated'? [Oklahoma](http://earthquake.usgs.gov/research/induced/hazards.php)? [Ohio](https://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/2rjqad/science_ama_series_im_robert_skoumal_one_of_the/)? [California](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015GL066948/abstract)? [Canada](http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/british-columbia/more-than-90-of-larger-earthquakes-in-western-canada-triggered-by-fracking-1.3510812)? Hydraulic fracturing, as well waste water injection are both capable of inducing seismicity, depending, in part, on the underlying geology.

...if the well casing is properly constructed there will be no water contamination.

It's not just about properly cased wells (of which many are not by the way), but [subsurface pathways](http://arks.princeton.edu/ark:/88435/dsp019s1616326). More recent studies are showing just [how much leakage is occurring](http://blogs.scientificamerican.com/plugged-in/methane-leakage-from-natural-gas-supply-chain-could-be-higher-than-previously-estimated/) and the [significant draw backs](http://thinkprogress.org/climate/2016/02/17/3750240/methane-leaks-erase-climate-fracked-gas/) such leaks create.

If the goal is to remain under 2C or even 1.5C by reducing emissions [by ~2020](https://andthentheresphysics.files.wordpress.com/2015/07/rcps.jpg), increasing natural gas consumption is [not the solution](http://www.vox.com/2015/11/30/9818582/paris-cop21-climate-talks) you're looking for. If that's not a concern, then it may prove as a useful transition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 19:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research: [Reductive weathering of black shale and release of barium during hydraulic fracturing](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S088329271530069X) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barium leaches directly from fracked rocks, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 19:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volcanic ash dating 600,000 years found in dump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 18:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dont Call Me Tarpan: How Eurasian wild horses from the last glacial period, their living and extinct relatives, and 20th century back-breeds all ended up being called the same thingand what is really behind that name </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 17:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 19:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research (open access): [Decimetre-scale multicellular eukaryotes from the 1.56-billion-year-old Gaoyuzhuang Formation in North China](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160506/ncomms11500/full/ncomms11500.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earliest Decimetre-scale Multicellular Eukaryotes Fossils from 1.56-billion-year-old Gaoyuzhuang Formation Discovered in North China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 19:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 00:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's world whisky day so what better time to introduce a new Canadian single malt, Shelter Point Distillery's 2016 Inaugural Run - sunsets and sea salt; Barley is grown on-site, distilled in traditional Scottish copper pot stills, and then aged in white oak barrels.

Colour: Pale Straw

Body: Full bodied, soft and round

Nose: Vanilla and malt, Citrus, Fruity apple

Palate: A bite of citrus zest with a spoon of marmalade followed by cooked fruit, and fresh apples carried on a summer's breeze by the ocean. 

Finish: An explosion of pepper, dry, and warming. Lingering layers of candied apples rolled in sea salt.

Score: 82/100

Notes: Although it carries a warm finish with a good bit of bite, it is exceptionally smooth for its age. A mere five years of age, aged in barrels from Maker's Mark, at 46% ABV it easily behaves like a ten year old. It's not an exceptional single malt, but for its price at the time of purchase ($68.99CAD) it's certainly worth a try if you can get your hands on it. This is the inaugural release, so I fully expect the distillery to perfect their recipe over the coming years and could easily bump the score up another 2 points or more.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review #8: Shelter Point Distillery 2016 Inaugural Run </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 00:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 20:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colour: Burnished Gold

Body: Full bodied, soft and round

Nose: Toffee, floral, pears, burnt sticks, sherry, and spirituous 

Palate:  Rich folds of ambling honey and toffee, lively floral and sweetness. Notes of dried fruit, and mixed peel.

Finish: Spice, black pepper, and subtle peat smoke

Score: 96/100

Notes: Perfectly balanced, and complex. Amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review #7: Highland Park 18 year old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 20:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did plate tectonics begin? - Geological Society of America's Guest Blog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 06:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 06:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you might be under the impression that induced seismicity is only generated from hydraulic fracturing, however, induced seismicity is also generated from disposal wells (waste water injection). In Texas, Mw4.0+ events have been [attributed to waste water injection](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016JB012821/abstract?campaign=wlytk-41855.5282060185), with minor events being attributed to hydraulic fracturing. The underlying geology and regional stress regimes are crucial factors to consider as to whether the play might be susceptible to either hydraulic fracturing, waste water injection, or both, through time. For example, in [Western Canada](http://srl.geoscienceworld.org/content/87/3/631), induced seismicity (Mw4.0+) has been attributed to hydraulic fracturing rather than waste water injection.

Perhaps I misinterpreted your statement, but I hope my statement may help clear up some ambiguity. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 10:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (pdf): [A Historical Review of Induced Earthquakes
in Texas](http://www.smu.edu/~/media/Site/News/NewsSources/EarthquakeStudy/earthquake-study-17may2016.ashx?la=en) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humans have been causing earthquakes in Texas since at least 1925, and they have been widespread throughout the state ever since, according to a new historical review of the evidence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 10:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 10:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper (pdf): [A Historical Review of Induced Earthquakes
in Texas](http://www.smu.edu/~/media/Site/News/NewsSources/EarthquakeStudy/earthquake-study-17may2016.ashx?la=en) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Two-step rise of atmospheric oxygen linked to the growth of continents](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2707.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two-step rise of Earth's atmospheric oxygen linked to the growth of continents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Big Oil Glut is Over, Says Goldman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 00:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 20:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jade (Jadeite or Nephrite) are not *very* soft. Jadeite has a hardness of [~6.5](http://webmineral.com/data/Jadeite.shtml) - 7.0 depending on its properties, while Nephrite (technically a rock comprising mostly massive microcrystalline to cryptocrystalline felted amphiboles of the tremolite - actinolite series) is around 6.0 - 6.5 again depending on its properties. While Jadeite (a pyroxene - single chain inosilicate) is relatively hard, it is not tough. Nephrite, on the other hand, is very tough because it is made of [felted amphiboles](https://dcgiaorg.files.wordpress.com/2008/04/april012.jpg) (double chain inosilicates) that act analogously as interwoven strands of rope.

Source: Geologist whose early work experience consisted of working for [Jade West](http://www.jadestores.ca/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 09:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Bayesian Probabilities for Mw 9.0+ Earthquakes in the Aleutian Islands from a Regionally Scaled Global Rate](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016JB012861/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study estimates the probability of a Magnitude 9+ earthquake in the Aleutian Islandsan event with sufficient power to create a mega-tsunami especially threatening to Hawaii. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 09:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> News | Second Cycle of Martian Seasons Completing for Curiosity Rover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 17:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 00:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - [Known planets by size as of May 10 2016](https://www.nasa.gov/sites/default/files/styles/full_width/public/thumbnails/image/fig8-new-20use20this20one.jpg?itok=5FjE-hKr)

- [Kepler's small habitable zone planets as of May 10, 2016](https://www.nasa.gov/sites/default/files/thumbnails/image/kepler_fig10.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA's Kepler mission has verified 1,284 new planets  the single largest finding of planets to date </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 00:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 23:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know of previous work with regard to lava bubble size and atmospheric pressure? More specifically, have they studied modern flows with known pressures to test the reliability of this proxy method?

The authors cite their previous work relating raindrop size to atmospheric pressure; however, I understand that such a proxy has been met with heavy scepticism, if not [out right rejected](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0012821X14007936) all together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 22:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Earth's air pressure 2.7 billion years ago constrained to less than half of modern levels](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2713.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early Earths air weighed less than half of todays atmosphere, new research suggests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 22:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 21:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Dehydration of chlorite explains anomalously high electrical conductivity in the mantle wedges](http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/2/5/e1501631) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dehydration of chlorite explains anomalously high electrical conductivity in the mantle wedges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 21:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Live performance INSIDE a volcano (Thrihnukagigur near Reykjavik) by Kaleo - "Way Down We Go" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 12:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JOIDES Resolution (Ocean Drilling Research Vessel) proposal "Chicxulub: Drilling the K-T Impact Crater" details (pdf) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 07:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 02:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's wonderful (and a pleasure to meet you). I hope it has driven more attention to your creative works, they're simply too good not to share. I know I've certainly added a number of your creations to my wishlist. All the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 01:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or so the theory goes. It's still not a well understood process, though [experiments](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3QoiTcQcyTY) are getting us closer to a more complete understanding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 20:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like sweet tweets and I can not lie

You other brothers can't deny

When a tweet pops up with an itty bitty radius
 
And a round thing in your face

You get sprung

...

TL;DR: Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 07:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And no watermark, very generous. Beautiful photography by the way, thanks for sharing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 07:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't my field of study, but as far as I understood it, nothing can escape (not even light) from a blackhole once it passes beyond the event horizon. The [energy](https://hub.jhu.edu/2013/06/14/black-holes-x-ray-light) you see being emitted (x-rays) is from highly accelerated mass nearing the event horizon, heating up, in the accretion disk. [Matter is also ejected](https://www.nasa.gov/mission_pages/chandra/news/black-hole-rejects-food.html) from the accretion disk prior to some other fraction going beyond the event horizon.

All the best to you in your adventure towards your goals and dreams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 07:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's presses all the way down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 07:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an excellent article actually and the figure seis-matters took is directly from it. The article is as follows:
___

**Mount St. Helens is Recharging its Magma Stores, Setting Off Earthquake Swarms**
___

[Image](https://www.wired.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/img1207-582x387.jpg)

*This GPS station on Mount St. Helens is one of the many ways volcanologists can monitor the day-to-day activity at an active volcano (even when its at rest).Adam Mosbrucker / USGS*
___



When it comes down to it, volcanoes spend most of their existence not erupting. If you look at almost any volcano, it might have a bout of eruption for days to months at a time, then go quiet for decades, centuries or more. So when you think about the activity at any given volcano, you should not only concern yourself with what might be happening when the volcano is actually coughing stuff up (erupting), but also when, at the surface, things look perfectly calm.

There are a number of ways to examine what a volcano was/is doing during these periods of repose. [My research](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0113157) is like that of a historian, trying to understand what was going on before eruptions that have already happened. I do this by [looking at the evidence of changes in the magmatic system recorded in the crystals](http://www.wired.com/2014/12/under-the-volcano-lassen-chaos-crags-crystals/) that are brought up during an eruption. There you find the record of intrusions of new magma occurring frequently, even during times when the volcanic system might not erupt for 100,000 years! So the real action at many volcanoes might be happening kilometers beneath our feet.

Now, if you want to be more like a journalist and look at what might be going in at the moments between eruptions, you can [turn to seismology](https://volcanoes.usgs.gov/vhp/earthquakes.html). At many volcanoes, there is a constant background din of small earthquakes caused by magma, hot gasses, hot water, or faults underneath the volcano. They can occur in swarms and across a [wide range of depths](http://volcanoes.usgs.gov/observatories/cvo/monitoring_seismicity.html)from the mantle source of the magma all the way to the surface. You can use the number of earthquakes and their depth to start to weave a story of how magma might be moving underneath a volcano during those quiet periods.
___

[Image](https://www.wired.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/img3313_900w_675h-482x362.jpg)

*Sometimes keeping a seismic station running during winter is difficult. USGS technicians Kelly Swinford and Amberlee Darold are shown here getting a St. Helens station back online on March 30, 2016.Seth Moran / USGS*
___

The [USGS](http://volcanoes.usgs.gov/index.html) and the [Pacific Northwest Seismic Network](http://www.pnsn.org/) has arrays of seismometers on many of the Cascade volcanoes to [watch these earthquakes](http://volcanoes.usgs.gov/volcanoes/st_helens/monitoring_earthquakes.html), so hopefully well know well in advance if any of these volcanoes are waking up. It isnt easy to keep the seismic array on these volcanoes running during the winter, as the picture of the seismometer on Mount St. Helens above image shows! So you should be impressed that we have the near real-time seismic data at our fingertips.

One such story of a volcano recharging is being written right now at [Mount St. Helens](http://volcanoes.usgs.gov/volcanoes/st_helens/) in Washington. Since the start of 2016 (see below), an earthquake swarm has been detected underneath the currently-quiet Washington volcano. These earthquakes have been occurring from depths of ~2 to over 7 kilometers beneath the volcano. [USGS volcanologists and seismologists are interpreting](https://volcanoes.usgs.gov/observatories/cvo/cvo_news_archive.html) this swarm as a response to the slow recharging for the volcano, where new magma is rising up underneath St. Helens as it slumbers. As the magma intrudes, it imparts pressure on the rock around it and it heats up water/releases gases that can add to that pressure. This generates small earthquakes as the rocks shift in response to that stress.
___

[Image](https://www.wired.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/13161701_10105525806501296_5840660615606753296_o-482x238.jpg)

*A compilation of earthquakes under Mount St. Helens from 1988-2016. Magmatic recharge swarms are marked, along with the most recent earthquake swarm. Click on the image to see a larger version.USGS / Cascade Volcano Observatory.*
___

Now, this might make some people nervous, but if you look at the compilation of earthquakes from St. Helens over its periods of repose since 1988 (see above), you can see that it has had a lot of recharge eventsand most of these dont directly lead to an eruption. In fact, if you look at the biggest recharge swarms prior to the 2004 revival of eruptions, it might have been 5 years between that big recharge event in 1998-99 and the [2004 eruptions](http://pubs.usgs.gov/fs/2005/3036/fs2005-3036.html).

Even in the time since the end of the 2004-08 eruptions, there have been little earthquake swarms: early 2012, early 2014, and now the most vigorous in 2016. These are all normal behavior for a volcano as active as St. Helens. As the USGS report on the earthquake swarm mentions, there are no other signs of potential eruption right now: no changes in gas emissions, no deformation, and no shallow seismicity (2 kilometers) that are generally associated with an impeding eruption. However, it does mean that even as St. Helens sleeps, the magma that will likely take part in the next eruption is working its way up towards the surface, likely stopping along the way to crystallize and interact with the residue of previous eruptions.

It might take a big recharge event to really get the system primed for the next eruption. This questionwhat might ultimately trigger that next eruptionis one of the big ones in volcanology. However, what we can say is that no volcano is truly dormant when its not erupting. Its just that most of the action is happening far beneath our feet.

\- [Erik Klemetti](http://www.wired.com/author/erikvolc/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 03:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: [Little Planet Factory](https://www.littleplanetfactory.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earth's Schwarzschild radius: the volume Earth would have to be compressed in order to form a black hole. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 03:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Global Topographic Map of Mercury Released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 00:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossil Hunters Uncover 71-Million-Year-Old Trove in Antarctica </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 23:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 19:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always enjoy your comments, informative to say the least. Note that the figure you provide is already in the article and discussed within:

Excerpt:
Now, this might make some people nervous, but if you look at the compilation of earthquakes from St. Helens over its periods of repose since 1988 (see above), you can see that it has had a lot of recharge eventsand most of these dont directly lead to an eruption. In fact, if you look at the biggest recharge swarms prior to the 2004 revival of eruptions, it might have been 5 years between that big recharge event in 1998-99 and the 2004 eruptions.

More information can be found on the Pacific Northwest Seismic Network for those that are interested in exploring some more data: https://www.pnsn.org/volcanoes/mount-st-helens#recent-seismicity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Tell Tale Sign of a Recharging Magma Chamber, Earthquake Swarms, Have Been Detected at Mt. St. Helens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 17:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 22:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I went back and clicked on the link to they study to read the abstract only to find that it's open access! :) A cursory read has raised some questions, but perhaps they will be resolved when a more detailed reading is permitted (time constraints). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 19:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asteroids are typically found orbiting between Mars and Jupiter in what is called the asteroid belt, with the majority within the [main belt](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v505/n7485/images/nature12908-f1.jpg), and are the remnants of the protoplanetary disk and are classified into various types by [their composition](http://www.philipmetzger.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/asteroid-and-meteorite-types.jpg). Because they orbit the sun, having a rather circular orbit relative to comets, they travel at lower velocities. 

Comets (long and short period) can have quite elliptical orbits relative to those of asteroids, so their velocities can be far greater. They are also thought to be remnants of the early solar system though they are believed, mostly, to have formed further away from the Sun (beyond the [frost line](http://www.ifa.hawaii.edu/~barnes/ast110_06/quizzes/Formation.jpg)), and have a composition that includes water ice, nitrogen ice, ammonia and organics, and are commonly termed "dirty snowballs." 
Long period comets tend to have randomly orientated orbits and originate from the [Oort cloud](http://global.jaxa.jp/article/interview/2013/vol81/img/img_03_l.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 11:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: [Orbital evidence for more widespread carbonate-bearing rocks on Mars](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015JE004972/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martian Carbonates Spotted by the Orbiter: The minerals identified by the Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter provide more evidence that the planet may have once been habitable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 11:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 10:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how strong the seasonal signal is, if there is one, as there is within the [Himalayan Front](https://www.caltech.edu/news/earthquake-season-himalayan-front-1364) during the monsoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 10:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "a planet-ending 6 km/s..."

The minimum impact velocity on Earth is 11 km/s. Typical impact velocities are 17 km/s for asteroids and 51 km/s for comets. The maximum Earth impact velocity for objects orbiting the sun is 72 km/s. - [source](http://impact.ese.ic.ac.uk/ImpactEffects/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 10:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title is disingenuous to the on going debate. There are still a number of unknowns, and to claim that the impact was the cause of the CretaceousPaleogene extinction event is jumping to conclusions. To highlight this fact, I would highly recommend the following public lecture presented by the Harvard Museum of Natural History in 2015: [The Cretaceous-Tertiary Mass Extinction: What Really Killed the Dinosaurs?](http://hmnh.harvard.edu/event/cretaceous-tertiary-mass-extinction-what-really-killed-dinosaurs)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 10:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Offshore oil and gas leases. Previous work has been achieved by obtaining core logs and analysis that were granted permission from oil and gas companies drilling in the area. I'm not sure what the status has been/is for the portion of the Chicxulub Impact Crater situated on land however.

If you're an oil and gas company with a firm understanding of underlying geology in your lease, you don't want that information published as it provides crucial information to your competitors, you want that to remain proprietary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In one of the most arid regions in the world a series of carefully constructed, spiralling holes form lines across the landscape. Known as puquios, their origin has been a puzzle  one that could only be solved from space. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 10:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 04:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me, if there was a strong link it would be everywhere...

That's not how geology works... at all. You can refuse to accept the literature, but it's out there, published, and definitive, and denying it won't get you anywhere. To be clear no one is saying that every seismic event is induced, let alone every event 4.0Mw. What the science shows, however, is that hydraulic fracturing and waste water injection can both generate seismicity 4.0Mw, and that attribution between the events that have been analyzed is robust. I should also state that this study on seismic events triggered by mantle delamination does not refute events already attributed to induced seismicity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 23:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it did not. That was the target depth for 1993 of which it never achieved, and it did not drill beyond a depth of ~12km. 

There are a number of research papers, and a growing body of evidence, that have definitively linked seismic events 4.0Mw to induced seismicity, either through hydraulic fracturing (see British Columbia, and Ohio(?)) or waste water injection through disposal wells (see Oklahoma, California, Texas, Colorado, New Mexico, Arkansas, and Ohio). 

It's somewhat out of date, but it contains good introductory material: http://earthquake.usgs.gov/research/induced/   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 20:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Kola Superdeep Borehole did not reach 15km depth, but rather 12.626km. As far as I can tell, this paper has little at all to do with induced seismicity, and does not dispute attribution of larger seismic events (4.0Mw) to waste water injection or hydraulic fracturing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
