<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4288</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whyte   Mackay Special tastes and smells like isopropynol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Uh, it at least requires not siding with corporations.

Because corporations could never, ever, *ever* be in the right legally. That would be impossible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh come on. That attitude helps nobody.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair that commentor is basically unchecked privilege incarnate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno how you are defining "actual song," but Jim Johnston wrote "the Game" for HHH, just like most of the Attitude Era music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At Mania it was super obvious that Triple H's theme is actually a few minutes long and Rollins is about thirty seconds looped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And a much, much better diet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 08:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Giving him a free pass from insults just because he's a former POW is pretty insulting, itself.

Giving him a free pass from being mocked *about being captured* is not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He may just be an untalented uncharasmatic bum that just looks like a superhero. 

Roman puts on awesome matches but isn't quite charismatic enough to not look silly reciting bad lines. The other problem is that his character comes off as a total douche bag much of the time (in one promo he said that Finn Balor, who is Irish, had "tator tots" instead of "potatoes,") but is constantly booked as a face - he gets to feud with all of the top heels, including Triple H (who is (legitimately) the COO now) at Wrestlemania last year, the Undertaker this year, Lesnar two years ago, etc.

It seems like the WWE wants to have it both ways now, with him being a face to kids (who love his merch because he looks like a superhero) and adults (who will buy tickets to boo him.) It's frustrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His parents. [He wants to inherit their house.](https://www.reddit.com/r/lostgeneration/comments/62ymfp/boomers_are_not_the_problem_the_rich_are/dfq8b8e/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 10:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much heat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked Dragon Age Inquisition right up to the ending. Ugh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People totally do wear Marlboro or Budweiser shirts. 

On the other hand, they usually don't brag about "blazing the phattest cigarettes."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm not in insurance, but I don't think suing someone else is not how you get life insurance paid out.

Not life insurance - car insurance covers liability for injuries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, was there any context?

Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but for the opposite reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What if people acted this way towards George Carlin, and tried to tank his entire career because he made some off color jokes?

 George Carlin was FAR more offensive than PewDiePie.

George Carlin used sensitive subjects to make points with humour. Pewdiepie uses sensitive material to upset people for attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Surefire HOFer

No kidding. I mean, other than Rick Flair, Randy Savage, Hulk Hogan and Shawn Michaels, who else is even in the conversation for GOAT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gah, Ambrose was on the pre-show? I guess I got spoiled :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anybody finds it awful, it's just that it was their second consecutive disappointment. Personally I thought it was better than Ghost Opera or Silverthorn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His posture is so poor. His neck is at a forty-five degree angle from his chest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clutch released a bonus CD of mostly acoustic versions called the Egg Basket

Clutch - [The Regulator](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S2nG4S7VkVM)

Clutch - [Basket of Eggs](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RbMXGtVPjbQ)

You also might appreciate roots/folk rock like Neil Young/CSN Y

Neil Young - [Rockin in the Free World (acoustic)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GfgC2Ph9VNE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly, but I would not have had the nerve to bring a suicidal man with a gun near someone who romantically rejected him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you suggesting that the "reaction to" an animation is more valuable than the animation itself?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Flynn had and was willing to say anything of value, [he wouldn't have made this request publically.](https://www.justsecurity.org/39426/explainer-flynns-request-immunity) This suggests he's worried but not likely to flip on anybody.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure most people are with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mercantilism is related to but not exactly capitalism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't the twins older?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's an invisible monster - if I recall correctly it's an extra-dimensional creature like Alexander.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Anti-Nazi** war propaganda.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently [this](http://acidcow.com/pics/20160707/behind_the_scenes_03.jpg) is the photo he took.

[Sketchy source, can't find better source.](http://acidcow.com/pics/82094-impressive-behind-the-scenes-photography-tricks-revealed-32-pics.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might have risked the girl's life too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with gwenthrowaway about the 'but.' Consider:

"**Although** the body encompasses a nexus of different systems, the brain is what captivates me the most"

"**Although** the body encompasses a nexus of different systems, **I find the brain most captivating.**"

"The body encompasses a nexus of systems, **of which I find the brain most captivating.**" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoving that hater looked so badass though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also would it be bad to pet it? I kind of want to pet it but I don't know if tarantulas would like that.

My sister has a [burgundy Goliath bird-eater (not her blog but the same speices)](https://tomsbigspiders.wordpress.com/2015/01/28/theraphosa-stirmi-the-burgundy-goliath-bird-eater/) and he is **aggressive.** He would definitely not let you pick it up, let alone pet him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting Axe Body Spray ads.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean... Roman overcame the odds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Campaign funds may be spent on meals, [when the meals are a ligitimate campaign expense](https://ethics.house.gov/campaign-activity/proper-use-campaign-funds-and-resources) (IE, a fundraiser or meeting.) They are explicitly not permitted for use on personal travel.

The primary ethical concern with Trump's travel is that it is occurring on the federal government's dime, not campaign donors.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 09:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The money doesn't go into the congressmen's pockets, it goes into their reelection funds. They don't get to keep it or spend it on themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't find it harder than Portal (though I suppose it probably would be if you played it first) - in particular I thought the slow difficulty ramp-up at the beginning of the game was very disappointing, since all of the first few puzzles could be solved by simply remembering tricks from the first game. I also didn't like the shinier art style, and although it was longer I still wasn't happy about paying full retail for a seven hour long game.

I was most disappointed by the abrupt tone shift from sci-fi horror with black humour to full-on comedy (though I'll admit it was hilarious at times,) especially considering the games ostensibly take place in the same universe as Half-Life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And, that although a cause and effect relationship between neonic pesticides and CCD has not been found, an association does in fact exist, suggesting that it is an actor in a bigger picture. A link about the affects on genes:

 http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0269749116315482

That neonicotinoids can damage bees is fairly well-known, but (as you noted) it still hasn't been shown to cause CCD (a [widely-cited study](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0118748) that treated actual bee colonies with "realistic" doses of imidacloprid showed no effects and certainly no CCD.)  

But you're right, it's still a suspect and could be one of many contributing factors. 

I would add though, that there are in fact papers that have found links between land use and management, particularly monoculture agricultural land, and bee biology and varroa infestations. I've attached one,it definitely needs further research, but the volume of research areas has expanded to the point where everyone is looking at something different.

http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0153531

This is definitely interesting, I wasn't aware of that.

All this beeing said, it's probably worth noting that US [commerical bee populations are stable and rising,](https://www.perc.org/sites/default/files/US%20honeybee%20colonies.jpg) and I am not aware of convincing research showing wild bees are in much trouble.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mafia's (mostly) [period soundtrack](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HwyOjeRzShs) really helped set the mood.

Same with Life is Strange's [indie soundtrack.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8Rst3w6W6zw)

[Neverwinter Nights](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XyoDgPwRLOU index=8 list=PLF59EAF7C6116B1EF) and [Knights of the Old Republic](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jSKvMyruPTA) had some epic tracks. 

[A Machine for Pigs](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_TSKgwvHgho) and [Dear Esther](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Ocfv0bOltk) were worth playing just for the gorgeous music.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It basically summarises that there needs to be more research into all the areas because we don't fully understand the problem yet, and that we should be looking at the whole picture.

True, but I wanted to highlight that neither monoculture farming nor pesticide use have been conclusively linked to CCD (in fact CCD is definitely not acute pesticide poisoning) and that there are other theories, especially varroa mites and migratory beekeeping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, I'll be serious.

[Reebok performance boxers - $10](https://www.amazon.com/Reebok-Mens-Performance-Boxer-Brief/dp/B01AKQF6X4?th=1 psc=1)

[American Eagle jeans - $65](https://www.ae.com/men-aeo-extreme-flex-slim-straight-jean-dark-indigo-wash/web/s-prod/0116_4008_913?cm=sCA-cCAD catId=cat8150191)

[Ancient shirt similar to this -$25?]( https://www.marks.com/en/product-list.html#q=Henley)

[Dockers Preserve shoes - $20 used](http://www.thebay.com/webapp/wcs/stores/servlet/ProductDisplay?urlRequestType=Base catalogId=10652 categoryId=166742 productId=5413979 errorViewName=ProductDisplayErrorView urlLangId=-24 langId=-24 top_category=136651 parent_category_rn=136651 storeId=10701)

Leather motorcycle jacket - $25 used

Socks - no idea

~$145 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both of those are [possible but speculative.](https://www.epa.gov/pollinator-protection/colony-collapse-disorder#why%20it%20is%20happening) The neocontinoid theory is much more popular on Reddit than in the scientific community.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The bees](http://www.slate.com/articles/health_and_science/science/2016/07/colony_collapse_disorder_is_no_longer_the_existential_threat_to_honeybees.html) [are doing fine](https://www.perc.org/sites/default/files/US%20honeybee%20colonies.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's actually designed to be inefficient.

[Not entirely.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/QWERTY#Properties) While it is primarily designed to prevent jams, the layout has the added bonus of minimizing the number of times you need to make consecutive keystrokes with the same finger (or even hand.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Portal was awesome, but Portal 2 was super disappointing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  (This is the same reason vegans don't eat honey.)

Wait... vegans don't eat honey? They're against insect suffering? I mean, aren't most cash crops fertilized by domestic bees?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prey is releasing in a month, so the writing is definitely finished.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If he wanted to be ethical, he could just not give her extra undeserved coverage, and don't give her money. I don't know, is that so crazy?

He offhandedly mentioned her (free) game *before they were in a relationship.* Why do you assume this coverage was undeserved?

Is it unethical to financially support somebody you are in a relationship with?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping he would just mute him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well, she was tripped by a guy...

Being tripped by a guy hurts more?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually beer, especially Red Racer IPA, or homebrew beer or mead. If a PC dies we usually drink a toast of rye or scotch to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also used to be pretty far-right before public opinion shifted against Dubya. He's a hired gun, just like Alex Jones and most fringe talk show hosts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Devin Nunes Says Hell Continue to Lead Russia Inquiry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jenner crushed the competition before transitioning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And most people wouldn't call that "getting rich and being successful," they would call that "staying rich."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trumpster Fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - The Wind-up Girl, by Paolo Bacigalupi

- Any Phillip K. Dick, especially Ubik and A Scanner Darkly (also a good movie)

- The Handmaid's Tale by Margaret Atwood

And just to be different, I'm going to recommend some short story collections.

- Pump Six and other stories, by Paolo Bacigalupi

- Burning Chrome, by William Gibson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure about Altered Carbon, but + 1 to Neuromancer, Lock In, and Halting State.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Chris Avellone and George Ziets are out of work... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not exactly. While the actual numbers are controversial, [renewable energy sources produced a nontrivial amount of carbon over their lifecycles,](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Life-cycle_greenhouse-gas_emissions_of_energy_sources) and rooftop solar produces more than most other sources - about a quarter of the lifetime emisions of the most efficient coal and gas plants, and nearly four times as much as wind or nuclear, according to a 2014 IPCC study. The relative difference between nuclear or wind and rooftop solar is nearly as large as the difference between rooftop solar and clean coal or gas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily, especially when parts are made in China.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not? Just because a source is renewable it shouldn't be taxed on the carbon it actually emits when produced or used?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, that comment did not make any sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but it exists, you can buy it, and it's less than $70,000. Comparing a Model S to a Bolt is like comparing an 3-series to  Prius. Sure there's an obvious winner, but it's irrelevent 95% of the time.

When you can buy (not pre-order) a Model 3 we'll see how well it competes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably what happens, but it doesn't make a good story or make anybody look good. Lesnar is still way less protected than pre-Goldberg, and the Goldberg story is nonsensical and depressing.

I hope Goldberg either loses super dirty or squeaks out a win while sustaining a kayfabe career-ending injury.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going to be salty if Goldberg loses clean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 06:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jaromir Jagr is nine years older than Zetterberg and still plays NHL hockey. You can go a long way with just brains and muscle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haitch: Challenges Seth, his employee, to a fistfight, then beats him senseless with a crutch

Haitch later: "We can fight at Wrestlemania, but you need to agree to not hold me liable for injuries..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, Metallica! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source? A quick Google suggests Dean makes $900K and Sasha makes $225K.

Which still isn't fair, but it's more reasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legit boos for Charlotte mixed in with the "Woo!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   It's the only thing women respond to.

This here is the Red Pill! Where making women uncomfortable and hoping that they lack the self-confidence to assertively tell you "no!" as you 'escalate' is the new masculinity!

: | </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "..too sexy for consent, so sexy they relent..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to be clear, "total weight" in Olympic weightlifting is the two best of three tries **each on two separate lifts,** so she averaged 260lbs over two lifts.

Which is, obviously, still nuts and would be near-world-class for a man her size.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kanye West and Kim Kardashian?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He's also making 1/2 of what Rollins and Reigns make.

That hurts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making fun of somebody's clothes or weight is being a judgmental dick.

Judging people for risking other people's lives and safety for a few seconds of convenience is being a rational adult.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Price check** of full system:

i7 3930K

Corsair H110i GT liquid cooler

Rampage IV Gene

Corsair 350D case

16GB DDR3

XFX 750W PSU

GTX 980 TI G1 Gaming

128GB SSD

ASUS PB278Q 1440p  monitor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not going to use the Pedigree forever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the (distant) second best of all time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 04:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five feet of fury! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was an undiagnosed schizophrenic. Now he is a diagnosed schizophrenic. He expressed remorse, [begged for death at his trial,](https://web.archive.org/web/20080809031829/http://ap.google.com/article/ALeqM5hx-mB9K812hwZqPx4HhsRsgjT7YwD92CEL700) and was in supervised treatment for six years. 

He did not decide to commit murder, is not criminally response for the murder, and has been deemed safe by the medical professionals who treated him for six years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hit a 5x225 set of squats today. Two plates! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been said many times before but that spear to Taker's back was a heel move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they were *predisposed* to doing it already, in fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Entrapment is when the actions of a law enforcement officer causes you to commit a crime that you most likely would not have commuted otherwise. This is a fact, and is indisputable. 

[Not exactly.](http://legal-dictionary.thefreedictionary.com/person) 

 Entrapment is a defense to criminal charges when it is established that the agent or official originated the idea of the crime and induced the accused to engage in it. If the crime was promoted by a private person who has no connection to the government, it is not entrapment. A person induced by a friend to sell drugs has no legal excuse when police are informed that the person has agreed to make the sale.

The rationale underlying the defense is to deter law enforcement officers from engaging in reprehensible conduct by inducing persons not disposed to commit crimes to engage in criminal activity. In their efforts to obtain evidence and combat crime, however, officers are permitted to use some deception. For example, an officer may pretend to be a drug addict in order to apprehend a person suspected of selling drugs. On the other hand, an officer cannot use chicanery or Fraud to lure a person to commit a crime the person is not previously willing to commit. Generally, the defense is not available if the officer merely created an opportunity for the commission of the crime by a person already planning or willing to commit it.

The officers did not force or persuade OP to assault them with their vehicle. They

1. Observed a (licensed but given the antilag almost certainly not street legal) racing car in town they probably don't recognize. 

2. Decide to shadow the car to see if they are in town to street race (reasonable) 

3. ~~Decide to~~ Tailgate OP, either because they are bad at shadowing (possible) or to see if OP races away from them (also possible and illegal but still not entrapment.) 

OP decides to assault them with his vehicle. The cops did not procure this crime from them at all, they merely gave him the opportunity to act like a reckless idiot. The cops were incompetent or stupid but absolutely did not entrap OP. 

 You're having real trouble with this concept aren't you? 

Why so rude?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. Entrapment ["is the conception and planning of an offense by an officer,](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sorrells_v._United_States) [and his procurement of its commission by one who would not have perpetrated it except for the trickery, persuasion or fraud of the officer."](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Entrapment)

In other words, provoking somebody isn't entrapment, telling somebody to do something illegal is. This is why bait cars aren't entrapment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Entrapment ["is the conception and planning of an offense by an officer,](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sorrells_v._United_States) [and his procurement of its commission by one who would not have perpetrated it except for the trickery, persuasion or fraud of the officer."](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Entrapment)

In other words, provoking somebody isn't entrapment, telling somebody to do something illegal is. This is why bait cars aren't entrapment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald, This I Will Tell You </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He seemed to enjoy his matches with the Miz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't look it, but Romney is already seventy (the same age as Trump.) Much as I'd like to see him take over the GOP I think that ship has sailed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ... even I know Ambrose doesn't usually do too great without the right opponent.

You don't think Corbin is the right opponent? He's not amazing technically, but his style seems to compliment Ambrose well. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He kinda wasn't. It was just a smart use of him in multiple person matches. He goes in, does his big moves and is taken out.

This is true of Ambrose as well. They've both been doing well with what they've been given though, and my expectations are high.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you are not exactly wrong. Electric motors are significantly more efficient (you're right that they can *in principle* be up to 97% efficient, but were talking ~80% for electric vehicles) than ICEs (about 20%) or turbofans (about 30%.)

However, these do not even come close to making up for the difference in fuel energy density. An electric motor may get 3-4x more omph out of a joule of stored energy, but that joule in batteries weighs fifty times as much as a joule of kerosene. So, you still need to carry about 12 pounds of batteries for every one pound of hydrocarbon fuel.

 The large trucks of tomorrow will probably use hydrogen fuel cells, since hydrogen has a similar energy density to gasoline. The planes of tomorrow... well, I'm not sure. 

Source: Doing PhD on fuel cell technology </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe, but they're already 30 and 31. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the smartest and a few of the dumbest people I know went to prestigious universities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course he won't. 

 Mr. Trump, in a telephone interview moments after the bill was pulled, blamed Democrats and predicted that they would seek a deal within a year after, he asserted, Obamacare explodes because of higher premiums. The president said he did not fault Mr. Ryan and said that he was pleased to move past his first legislative fight. He maintained that he was merely going along with the House bill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mr. Trump, in a telephone interview moments after the bill was pulled, blamed Democrats and predicted that they would seek a deal within a year after, he asserted, Obamacare explodes because of higher premiums. The president said he did not fault Mr. Ryan and said that he was pleased to move past his first legislative fight. He maintained that he was merely going along with the House bill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spicer is doing a surprisingly good job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should have a livethread on the press briefing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off its kinda homophobic to call being gay a 'lifestyle'

When desire is transformed into an identity with cultural traits and consumer habits then it's a lifestyle.

 I'm a sexual minority not some edgy kid going through a phase.

The entire history of Whites is an edgy kid going through a phase. Let's just hope you grow the fuck up before you end up murdering the rest of us like you almost did in your world wars.

  You get what you put into this world, you want to treat me like a sex offender and campaign for the criminalization of homosexuality then you can get fucked for all I care.

Girl, I'm not interested in the criminalisation of homosexuality. I want to dismantle Western conceptions of desire altogether and the identities that come with them. It's not my problem that this thread is filled with a bunch of Protestant-lite Muslims.


You spit in my eye and then expect me to turn around and support your rights, nice try not falling for it.

There's a kink joke here, but I don't want to upset the mods with my vulgarity

Also, the White homosexuals have never been supportive of communities of colour or faith, queer or otherwise. I don't seek your support or validation.

[Fight me! Loser bottoms.](https://www.reddit.com/r/islam/comments/60n9cb/getting_rid_of_islamophobia/dfa0vhv/)

Ugh. So fucking pompous. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Funny how we didn't get this response a few months when those black kids tortured the autistic kid because he was white.

Motherfucker that story was all over the front page for like a week! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump the Dealmaker Projects Bravado, but Behind the Scenes, Faces Rare Self-Doubt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then how come The Witcher 3, an arguably bigger game with more dialogue and NPCS, made with (I assume) a lower budget, animated everything by hand and absolutely killed it?

Because the Witcher 3 was developed in Poland, where the cost of doing business is only 35-50% of what it is in Canada. 

Also, most minor NPCs used procedurally-generated lipsync. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  NTHSA has reported 40% less accidents for Tesla drivers. If safety is your priority, Tesla is your car. 

Automatic braking absolutely is **not** exclusive to Teslas (in fact it's standard on all Toyotas) with similar results. It was also offered by Mercedes before Tesla had it available at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Good* memories? Obviously you aren't Ukrainian! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $600M, but yes. Definitely millions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Don is as wealthy as he says he is, [he would be first](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Presidents_of_the_United_States_by_net_worth)

Adjusted for inflation, next would be Kennedy (~$1B, Wall Street) and then Washington (~~$600B~~ ~$600M,Tobacco/slaves) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In no particular order:

All Democrats oppose the bill because it repeals Obama's signature achievement, costing them a lot of credibility.

All Democrats and some Republicans oppose the bill because it will result in fewer Americans having access to health care. 

Some Republicans oppose the bill because it maintains some aspects of the AHA (such as requiring insurance companies to provide ten "essential health benefits" and cover those with pre-existing conditions.) 

It's seen as the worst of both worlds by many people - too much regulation for a competitive market, and too little regulation for a planned market.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's definitely not all-core turbo. 

That being said, there is a [twelve-core 3.0GHz/3.5Ghz Broadwell-E](http://ark.intel.com/products/91750/Intel-Xeon-Processor-E5-2687W-v4-30M-Cache-3_00-GHz) at 160W, so sixteen cores at 3.1/3.6GHz seems ambitious but not completely impossible. The  the eight-core 3.0/3.7GHz Summit Ridge is 65W. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Exactly. That person's word is, at absolute best, no more credible than Trump's is.

Oh come on. Let's not go that far. Somebody on a street corner shouting "the End is nigh!" is more credible than Trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And/or drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they spell disaster for you ~~at Sakerfice~~ on Election Day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The problem with separate categories is if most of the runners are fighting for the amiibo category then you have Little Jimbo going for the amiiboless category and gets the (nearly uncontested) record, he's going to be claimed as an equal to whoever holds the real record despite being objectively worse

Alright, and either nobody cares or somebody better than him puts up a better time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  rapey

Oh that's real lovely. Imagine being told that your body's history is so disgusting that a blowjob from you without prior disclosure is "rapey." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best of the Attitude Era for sure. I liked CM Punk vs John Cena and Sasha Banks vs Bayley a bit more I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Foley, it was [sixteen feet down, twenty-two feet "including the angle of the fall.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Undertaker_vs._Mankind_(Hell_in_a_Cell_match\)#Match_details)

The extra six feet could be made up by flying fifteen feet horizontally (that would be a lot), or by considering Foley ('s centre of mass) to be a 3-4 feet above the top of the Cell and flying 8-10 feet horizontally. 

Fun facts: Foley also went through the top of the Cell (apparently this was an accident!) and ended the match with missing teeth, a large tear across his face, a concussion, a dislocated jaw, and a dislocated shoulder. The Undertaker started the match with a broken foot and jumped through the top of the Cell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
