<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8477</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 05:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right Sir/Ma'am. Which is why research and fact checking is so important. If you want facts you must do the work of searching for the proof yourself. I assume you have done this. Correct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 05:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! I'm sure Romney has your back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 05:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He got things done. You just refuse to accept it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 05:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone says it happened without offering a source or any kind of physical evidence? Seems legit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 22:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you should be seeing a mental health professional and not a general practitioner for mental health issues.

I was prescribed the Medication by a clinical psychiatrist. I tried to write that in a way that wouldn't sound like I was being a dick. I think I've failed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 22:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant make out all of the letters in the first line of the black banner but the last word reads "antichrist". Can anyone make out the first word? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 05:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adderall and time to myself in front of a computer. I have destroyed many great civilizations and buried at sea many brave men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 07:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been a month and a half. My dose is 250mg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 06:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to keep the amount of medications to a minimum. From what I've been reading in the comments, it should be as simple as a change of medication. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 06:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take her to an ER.

I'm very sorry to hear about your mother's current state. You must be very worried. I don't know if anyone has responded to you yet and if they haven't, I'm sorry.  

I'm not a doctor of any sort, and all that I can offer is my personal opinion based on trying to step into your shoes. If it was my mother, I would be worried. Worried enough to get her in a car and take her in for care and diagnosis. I would be scared and a bit fearful at such an abrupt change in behavior. I don't believe riding it out is an option.

This is 4 hours too late. I wish I had seen your post sooner. I wish you the best and i hope your mother gets better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
