<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2778</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 19:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Got to give that a try some time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 20:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recipe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst luck you've had with reforging? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 18:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently saddled with a 1.1m reforge on an amazing Blackguard, looking for a socket. What's the highest you've gone, or the worst roll you've had? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 00:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Sword of a Thousand Truths </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Katamari Damacy - On the Rocks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 21:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If at all possible, I'd like a looping segment of [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iMH49ieL4es#t=50) segment of the track.  
 
Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 23:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Antchamber. Stage a daring escape from an ant colony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 21:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch out with percussive maintenance, I killed a hard drive doing that one too many times. That was an expensive week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 17:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He genuinely sounds like a goat when he makes noise with his mouth full. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 22:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milton Jones. Unrelated, boring puns, and annoyingly "wacky" dress sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 01:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Thief and Dishonored are really comparable in some ways. Thief, at least for me, has always been a purely stealth game. Dishonored allowed you to be the assassin as well as the ghost, so it has more combat development. I loved Dishonored a lot, but Thief is still different enough to it that I can't compare the two side by side and say which is better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 03:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it's probably a 3rd person shoot 'em up tank game called Recoil. Not sure how famous it is, but it was built off the MechWarrior 3 engine, and was a fantastic game. Shame I can't find it anywhere now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 00:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [As a guy who doesn't fulfill any of these criteria](http://i2.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/original/000/330/958/a5b.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 03:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played 3 all the time in school. If you like that sort of genre, 5's not bad either (just a bit limited on the scenarios and stuff imo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 00:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never had a problem with I/O plates. I just press them on each corner from the inside of the case, and a few snaps later it's in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 12:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think for the sake of fairness all animations would take the same amount of time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Knife animations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 11:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I was wondering if anyone had any cool ideas for knife animations for the different knives you earn. It would be seriously cool if there were certain animations for specific knives, as it would make people want to pick certain knives more for the animations they give.  

I'll start with mine: The shiv could have something like a neckhold, with you stabbing the player 2-3 times in the back, and stealing tags when you release them. Let me know what yours would be! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 21:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The number 11 just makes sense.  

I was downstairs cooking, and my housemate Grant wafts in from upstairs, stinking of B.O. and cheese (his absolute favourite food). Having put a ready meal in the oven for 40 minutes, he had come to check on it, not realising I was downstairs. Now struggling to make conversation in the ever-growing awkward silence, he said "11 minutes. That makes sense." and left the room. It took a moment but I noticed he was referring to his meal, which had 11 minutes left on the clock. Of course, I should have known that in the first place, because *it just makes sense*.    

11 is the perfect number. 11 is life. 11 makes sense to **everyone**.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 22:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AS is stand by I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 19:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on Fongidangy's code, it looks to be "Calling anyone, this is OZ, please stand by."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 17:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's just a snippet of his actionbars, not his entire monitor setup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Claymoron </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 17:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 12:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think he knows about second breakfast, Pip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 18:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is also only 20 layers, so everyone can use it!

[Here's](http://pastebin.com/wd88VCgA) the code as requested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now the Battlelog's come back, I rejigged my Batman emblem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 14:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 20:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a special event, with first reveal gameplay of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 20:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://nooooooooooooooo.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 13:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it has to be Thief Gold. I had it when I was about 9 and I sucked at it. Could never beat the first level. After 10 years of improving my skills at stealth games I re-installed it and had a blast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 12:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately not, my mum came back shortly after the fish had exploded and went out to buy another one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 16:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mum used to go to the opera with friends in the summer, and everyone would bring a dish to eat in the interval. One time she asked me to make her usual piece - a whole salmon, poached and decorated with paper thin slices of cucumber for the scales and olives for the eyes. When it's finished, the dish looks something like [this.](http://p.twimg.com/ApcjnifCIAEOuKO.jpg:large)  

Having helped out many times before, I got to work while she went out to pick some things up. I put the huge salmon in the fish kettle (a very long steel contraption which has a tray in the bottom with handles to fish out the poached article) and went upstairs while I waited for it to cook.  

When I returned, the salmon had finished poaching, and smelled amazing. The final step before skinning and decorating the salmon was to transfer the cooked fish to the fridge to cool.  

Now, the fridge in my house was pretty close to the hob where I had cooked this massive fish, so transferring shouldn't have been a problem. All I'd have to do was grab the handles, pull the tray up and carefully put the fish on the pre-cleared shelf in the fridge.
So with the door of the fridge open, I extracted the monstrous and very, VERY delicate fish from the kettle. Things were going so well until I bent the handles of the tray slightly out of alignment. The tray was flimsy. The bottom twisted. And a large, perfectly cooked salmon unstuck itself.  

I watched in disbelief as the behemoth gently flopped off the tray.  

The sound of a well cooked fish hitting a pine floor is quite breathtaking. Think of the sound of vomit hitting a tiled surface, but condense the sound to an instant and add a light note of dropped brick. That's about the best way to describe it. The fish hit the ground perfectly on the left flank, and was utterly disintegrated in a shower of bone, scale, and delicately coloured meat.
The fridge door was spattered in gunge, lightly coated in a thin film of fishy oil. 

Cleaning that up was hell. But I did make another fish (without dropping it) in time for the opera.  


TL;DR: Redecorated the kitchen with salmon pebbledash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 01:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throbbin' Hood or American History XXX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crank off balance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 20:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,  

I took my bike out this morning and after coming off a main road, I shifted down to 2nd front from 3rd front. Immediately I heard a repeating grinding noise. I checked it out in the evening when I got home and found that in 2nd, my largest chainring is grinding against the front derailleur due to a wobble. How can I fix this, or do I need to take this into a bike shop?  

I don't remember it being an issue when cycling before the main road this morning (in 2nd), only after I shifted up then down again after the main road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 19:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My office keep pronouncing "schedule" as "skedule". It's very tiresome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 01:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the last thing you got there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 01:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a beta for one level. The tutorials will be available in the full version, but they're not included in this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elis Regina - Waters of March (Aguas de Marco) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-12 23:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
