<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1156</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Hanks on buying coffee machines for WH press corps: 'Those poor bastards need coffee' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The government of Turkey is blocking access to Wikipedia under a law that allows it to restrict access to material that is considered to be a threat to national security.

"After technical analysis and legal consideration ... an administrative measure has been taken for this website (Wikipedia.Org)," a telecom watchdog said in a statement, according to Reuters.


Turkish law allows authorities to ban entire websites if the content is deemed obscene or poses a threat to national security or the well-being of the public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Hanks=T-hanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mayor Bill de Blasio] ought to tell the Congress if we dont pay for it, New York City cops arent guarding it, and let the Feds put more people in, Schumer told the news outlet. Thats what I think he should do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schumer: NYC should refuse to pay for Trumps security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The committee also noted that 90 percent of the recruits have not yet filed official declarations of candidacy with the Federal Election Commission (FEC). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dems seeing big increase in midterm House candidates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are using the fund in election </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed with your point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Karen Travers tweets
Thanks @tomhanks-very kind of you to send a new espresso machine to the White House press corps. We appreciated the other ones-nice upgrade!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He explained that he first bought a coffee machine after visiting Bush-era reporters in the press room, where he saw an old Mr. Coffee machine. He decided to get them a new one to help "in their fight for Truth, Justice and the American Way," and has continued to offer upgraded coffee makers ever since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Nobody should be laughing, 'Aha look at how he's fallen on his face.' ... There is enormous damage being done in all sections of the government by his minions." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Moore: I'm not rooting for Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is best for gaming? Xbox or Gamer pc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Hanks on buying coffee machines for WH press corps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Those poor bastards need coffee' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has no right to block  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jonathan Demme's film Rachel Getting Married sums up the late director's greatest talents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead Gianforte kept his Russian ties secret during his failed run for governor last yea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greg Gianforte reportedly owns shares of funds that have holdings in other companies, including Russian natural gas utility Gazprom, that are sanctioned by the U.S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Montana GOP candidate has financial links to Russian firms sanctioned by US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Department of Fisheries, a frequent regulatory opponent of the oil and gas projects Harpers government was pushing, saw some of the deepest cuts: When it was forced to shutter the majority of its libraries, books full of irreplaceable research wound up in Dumpsters. Media access to government scientists working on climate and environmental topics all but vanished, and in several egregious cases individual scientists were directly muzzled, forbidden to speak at all in public about their work. Harper also pulled Canada out of the Kyoto treaty and became a notorious heel dragger at international climate talks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada fought the War on Science. Heres how scientists won </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive done that for Democrats and Republican administrations because those poor bastards need coffee,Hanks said. Its as simple as that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Hanks on buying coffee machines for WH press corps: 'Those poor bastards need coffee' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moscow is ready to cooperate with the United States on settling the Syrian crisis, Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearly 130 Emerge America alumnae have stepped forward and announced that they are running for office in 2017 in state and local races. Thats a woman for every day Trump has been in office plus 30 more. And we expect the number of Democratic women running for office to continue to grow with each day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's America? Not for long. Democratic women are taking our country back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monitoring groups have accused Turkey of blocking access to social media sites such as Twitter or Facebook, particularly in the aftermath of militant attacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The move is likely to further worry rights groups and Turkey's Western allies, who say Ankara has sharply curtailed freedom of speech and other basic rights in the crackdown that followed last year's failed coup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey blocks access to Wikipedia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey blocks access to Wikipedia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rash of executive orders underlines Trumps focus on reversing as much of the Obama administrations policy agenda as he can, even as the new administration struggles to find legislative victories in Congress </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump using executive orders at unprecedented pace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homeland Security secretary: Kim Jong Un 'knows what he's doing' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The young talent emerging in Ligue 1 "Kylian Mbappe" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House GOP introduces one-week spending bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tillerson on North Korea: 'Our goal is not regime change' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has used this position to exhibit many of the traits associated with a colonial overseer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When political opportunity knocked, Jason Chaffetz never failed to cash in </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flynn was warned by the Pentagon against accepting foreign payments following his retirement in 2014, according to House Oversight Committee documents out Thursday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sessions on Flynn: You dont catch everything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish opposition lawmaker appeals to European court over referendum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders says it is 'likely' he would have beaten Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved my previous life. I had so many things going," Trump said during an interview with Reuters. "This is more work than in my previous life. I thought it would be easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump reflected on life inside the White House, remarking that he thought being president would be easier compared to his past business experience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Claims about sanctuary cities often get muddled, so this claim caught our attention. It was a part of the White Houses response to a district court judges decision to halt President Trumps executive order from taking effect, pending litigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White Houses claim that sanctuary cities are violating the law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fate of efforts to repeal and replace Obamacare rests in the hands of moderate House Republicans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The race for votes on health care is on, once again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marine Le Pens party is facing allegations of Holocaust denial  again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The treasury secretarys credibility is an important national asset that could be needed at any moment. I am very sorry to see it squandered on behalf of a set of tax reform proposals that are at best a bargaining position, he continued </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Larry Summers: Mnuchin squandering his credibility with Trump tax proposal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hope we will not have to see these type of Brutal Head Injuries in upcoming World Cup. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Metropolitan police said there had been no injuries in the incident, but would give no further details. Pictures on social media showed forensics officers examining the scene and armed police surrounding a man on the ground.
Traffic was closed on Whitehall, the street that leads from Parliament Square to Downing Street, the official residence of British Prime Minister Theresa May. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK police arrest man in London security incident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huge respect for that man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an unusual move, the White House invited all 100 senators to attend the briefing at the Eisenhower Executive Office Building.
Sanders said such briefings are typically held at the Capitol in a Sensitive Compartmented Information Facility (SCIF) room, which is a specially and securely designed for highly classified congressional briefings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders on skipping WH Korea briefing: 'I did not want to be part of a photo op' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's rude awakening on health care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Job creation in the digital economy needs a jumpstart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knowing that the legislation will be blocked by Republicans who control the House, Democrats are hoping to squeeze the majority party so they can claim that GOP incumbents in competitive reelection fights are standing with a president who remains deeply unpopular. The move comes as Trump nears the 100th day of his presidency on Saturday, a milestone that he has mocked but that his administration has used as an opportunity to tout early accomplishments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Democrats to force vote on bill requiring Trump to release his taxes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Mr Macron offers no hope. In this case, people cannot stand by and do nothing, they have to stand up and fight."

Although Macron held his ground during Wednesday showdown over Whirlpool and the tension eventually eased, television channels repeatedly broadcast footage of the candidate being heckled, marking a stark contrast with coverage of Le Pen posing for photographs with workers.

She said in a statement on Wednesday evening that, if elected, she would not let the factory be shut down as planned in 2018 and she would bring it under state control for a time if necessary to secure its future.

"Marine Le Pen has said that, if need be, she could temporarily nationalize the factory to save the plant," the candidate's niece, Marion Marechal-Le Pen, also a National Front member and member of France's parliament, told RTL radio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Far-right leader Marine Le Pen has made a more impressive start than favorite Emmanuel Macron to the last lap of the French presidential election, a poll showed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But when reporters spoke with Cardin about the North Korea meeting scheduled for Wednesday afternoon  a highly unusual classified briefing for all 100 senators held on the White House grounds  he expressed genuine confusion about what the Trump team was up to.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A powerful senator has no clue what the White House North Korea meeting is about </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Tuesday nights episode of The Five  the 9 p.m. show that replaced The OReilly Factor after longtime star Bill OReilly was dismissed over mounting allegations of sexual harassment  the network played a clip of Ivanka Trump holding a microphone close to her mouth as she talked about womens rights at a panel in Germany. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox host under fire for remark about Ivanka Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PARIS French intelligence has concluded that forces loyal to Syrian President Bashar al-Assad carried out a sarin nerve gas attack on April 4 in northern Syria and that Assad or members of his inner circle ordered the strike, a declassified report showed.
Assad has said in two media interviews since April 4 that the evidence of a poison gas attack was false and denied his government had ever used chemical weapons.
It said the findings matched the results of samples obtained by French intelligence, including an unexploded grenade, from an attack in Saraqib on April 29, 2013, which Western powers have accused the Assad government of carrying out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So cutting off the payments is an existential threat to Obamacare, and Trump can threaten to do so because of an ongoing House Republican lawsuit that challenged the payments during the Obama administration.

A dizzying back-and-forth between House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi and the White House on Wednesday morning underscored how fraught this issue is  and it didnt provide any clarity about what would ultimately happen to the payments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White House wont say if it will keep making key Obamacare payments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News reporter defends complimenting Ivanka's microphone handling skills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ubers Jeff Holden said that these kinds of flying taxis represent the pinnacle of urban mobility  the reduction of congestion and pollution from transportation, giving people their time back, freeing up real estate dedicated to parking and providing access to mobility in all corners of a city.

Those are just the two most recent examples of a dramatic transformation in how we move ourselves and our stuff around. Were also seeing rapid progress on delivery drones, self-driving trucks, supersonic airplanes, and even rockets. In all, there are major transportation breakthroughs being developed today. Almost all of these technologies already have working prototypes. And all of them have well-funded companies aiming to bring them to market by the early 2020s.

Not only will these transportation revolutions make our lives safer and more convenient, they could also change how people feel about the economy and technological progress more generally. Seeing cars drive themselves and drones and flying cars zip over their heads could give people a palpable sense of progress  one thats been missing in recent decades </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weve gotten used to transportation technology improving at a glacial pace. Todays cars and airplanes look and work about the same as they did 25 and even 50 years ago. But two announcements this week made it clear that the pace of innovation in transportation is about to accelerate dramatically. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A NATO hub focused on cyber defense is training network security experts from about two-dozen countries in how to defend the networks of a military air base in the event of severe cyberattacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lib Dems sack candidate and former MP David Ward after 'antisemitism' accusations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US State Department and US Embassy in Macedonia are continuing to follow the Obama/Hillary left wing, George Soros-funded policy of meddling in Macedonias internal affairs, and it has wreaked havoc and perpetuated attacks on Macedonians ethnic origin and Macedonias sovereignty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps must take action in Macedonia to fix the damage done by Obama and Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The breakneck pace creates the appearance that Republicans are working very hard and maybe getting close to a deal. Thats what really matters, in the end. But early reviews are much more mixed: Nobody seems sure House Republicans have actually found a compromise that can pass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans are still very far from repealing Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The six-page document - drawn up by France's military and foreign intelligence services and seen by said it was able to reach its conclusion based on samples they had obtained from the impact strike on the ground, and a blood sample from a victim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French intelligence services have concluded that forces loyal to Syrian President Bashar al-Assad carried out a sarin nerve gas attack on April 4 in northern Syria and that Assad or his closest entourage ordered the strike, a declassified report showed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Donald Trump has signed twenty-six executive orders since going into office, and now his executive orders are getting makeovers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet makes fun of Trump's executive orders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP gives ground on border wall, deportation in spending talks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump administration said the Syrian strike was legal under the president's authority to defend US interests
The letter underscores tensions among Democrats over Trump's foreign policy and use of military force </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kaine, Schiff demand White House legally justify Syria strike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You cannot thicken this border without hurting people on both sides of it," Trudeau said. "Any two countries are going to have issues that will be irritants to the relationship. Having a good constructive working relationship allows us to work through those irritants.

Natural Resources Minister Jim Carr echoed Trudeau's sentiment, saying that the tariff hurts people in both countries, including American homebuyers, who will now pay more for wood.

The U.S. and Canada typically enjoy a friendly trading relationship, but things have soured in recent months.

Trump has been railing against Canada's decision to change its policy on pricing domestic milk to cover more dairy ingredients, leading to lower prices for products, including ultra-filtered milk. Trump has called the move "a disgrace" that hurts U.S. producers in dairy states like Wisconsin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian PM responds to lumber tariffs imposed by the US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cyber spies target German party think-tanks ahead of election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Intel Chair says US is in a new Cold War with Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former Marine general and Acting Deputy Commissioner of Customs and Border Protection Randolph "Tex" Alles is the pick for the position, law enforcement and government sources tell ABC News.

2 Secret Service agents let go over White House fence jumper incident in March, agency says
Secret Service limits sidewalk access south of White House
Selecting an outsider would be a big shift for the insular agency, which has long promoted its leaders through the ranks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New US Secret Service director to be named </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KILMEADE: Now, Kellyanne, it seems like youre doing immigration reform little by little. Lets bolster the border. Lets get rid of the criminals. Next thing you know, you could end up at comprehensive, only did it phase by phase. Could that same approach be with taxes, when  when most Democrats and Republicans agree the corporate rate should be lower and find out different things that can be done that they agree on and then build up? Or are you looking to do everything at once? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kellyanne Conway still seems out of the White House loop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Macron's digital campaign manager says attempted hacks were unsuccessful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French presidential candidate Macron targeted by hackers, cyber firm says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The attack is significant for reasons beyond the saddening and unprecedented death toll. First, the attack occurred in the northern stronghold of Atta Mohammad Noor, the governor and warlord of Balkh province. Mazar-i-Sharif had been among the most secure cities of the country. The base, which I have visited several times, is on the citys outskirts. Noor has many political opponents, raising questions about possible collusion with the Taliban attack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Afghan Taliban claimed responsibility for a deadly attack on the 209th Afghan Army Corps base near the historic city of Mazar-i-Sharif that has killed at least 140 Afghan soldiers and wounded scores of others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> H.R. 1695s supporters insist that it would increase accountability by giving Congress more of a voice in the selection process. But in practice, making the appointment one more contentious political contest would create a Register whos only really accountable to the lobbyists and special interests that help her get selected and confirmed. Indeed, proponents of the bill have touted it as a measure that will better enable the Copyright Office to serve the interests of the creative industries.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Registrar of Copyrights bill, big media seeks its own in-house lobbyist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Friday, he will sign an order related to his administration's "America First" energy policy, Reuters added. 
Last month, the president signed a wide-ranging executive order to start the process of rolling back former President Barack Obama's aggressive climate change agenda, promising the measure would create jobs in the fossil fuel industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump is planning to sign executive orders this week on energy and the environment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The president is expected to sign on Wednesday an order regarding the 1906 Antiquities Act that gives presidents the ability to make areas of land and water federal and to designate them as national monuments.

On Friday, he will sign an order related to his administration's "America First" energy policy, Reuters added. 
Last month, the president signed a wide-ranging executive order to start the process of rolling back former President Barack Obama's aggressive climate change agenda, promising the measure would create jobs in the fossil fuel industry.
My administration is putting an end to the war on coal, Trump said at the time, using a term coined by the industry and its supporters to describe government regulations harmful to their industry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump is planning to sign executive orders this week on energy and the environment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French election: Le Pen, Macron ahead in early results </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "El Clasico" is sometimes being called a mini World Cup because of the rivarly of two teams. Fights, Fouls and Red cards are common in this match. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you get elected and you get good people and those good people bring you the facts."
 
The Florida Republican said that "reality begins to assert itself" at that point.
 
"And you have to react to that," he said.
 
"You're now the president. You're no longer a candidate, you're not a pundit, you have to actually make decisions that have real impact and consequence, and I think that's what you're seeing here."
 
Rubio said he thinks the president is now "dealing with the reality of being president of the United States."
 
"I think he's dealing with the reality of our options oftentimes in foreign policy are not a choice between a good one and a bad one," Rubio said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rubio defends Trump: 'This whole flip-flop thing is a political thing' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Senate Judiciary Committee Chairman Chuck Grassley (R-Iowa) said this week that another opening could come as soon as this summer, and there have been rumors that Justice Anthony Kennedy, often a swing voter on the court, could retire soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump eyeing second Supreme Court seat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> France voted on Sunday in the first round of a bitterly fought presidential election that could define the future of the European Union, and is sure to be seen as a gauge of the anti-establishment anger that has brought upsets in Western politics.

Over 50,000 police and 7,000 soldiers backed by rapid response units patrolled streets three days after a suspected Islamist gunman shot dead a policeman and wounded two others in the heart of the capital, Paris.

Voters will decide whether to back a pro-EU centrist newcomer, a scandal-ridden veteran conservative who wants to slash public expenditure, a far-left eurosceptic admirer of Fidel Castro, or a far-right nationalist who, as France's first woman president, would shut borders and ditch the euro.

The outcome will show whether the populist tide that saw Britain vote to leave the EU and Donald Trump elected president of the United States is still rising, or starting to ebb.

But it also provides a choice between radically different recipes for reviving a listless economy that lags its neighbors, and where almost a quarter of under-25s have no job.

A high level of indecision added to the nervousness.

Hanan Fanidi, a 33-year-old financial project manager, was still unsure as she arrived at a polling station in Paris's 18th arrondissement.

"I don't believe in anyone, actually. I haven't arrived at any candidate in particular who could advance things," she said. "I'm very, very pessimistic."

Despite fears that broad disillusionment with politics could keep voters away, the early turnout, in fair weather nationwide, was marginally up on the last election, in 2012.

Emmanuel Macron, 39, a centrist ex-banker who set up his party just a year ago, is the opinion polls' favorite to win the first round and then beat far-right National Front leader Marine Le Pen in the two-person runoff on May 7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The University of Notre Dame's Center for Ethics and Culture and the Religious Freedom Institute just held a day-long symposium on the persecution of Christians world-wide. Government officials, business leaders, academics, human-rights and religious leaders gathered at the National Press Club to discuss how Christians respond to persecution and promote religious freedom for all. One individual was noticeably missing: The U.S. Ambassador at Large for International Religious Freedom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump, global religious freedom needs US ambassador to lead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 13:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The suspicious car was flagged as stolen and had fake number plates, a ministry official told Reuters, adding that a decision was made to evacuate the polling station, while bomb disposal experts were called to examine the vehicle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polling station evacuated in eastern France due to suspicious vehicle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 12:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ring of steel around London Marathon as police launch biggest security operation in 36-year-history amid fears of terror attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Latest polls suggest the results are too close to call, meaning France could end up with a choice between candidates from the far-left and far-right, or a far-right stalwart facing off against a political novice. With such a fractured field, no one is expected to win a majority in Sunday's first round </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
