<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7749</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 13:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bin kein Sys-Admin, aber wollte die nur kurz sagen: Hut ab, tolle Deutschkenntnisse! Das ist bei Weitem mehr, als ein Anfnger-Deutsch :) Dies Kann dir auch bei der Arbeitsplatzsuche helfen, spiegelt nmlich einen gewissen Grad an Bereitschaft wieder usw. Viel Glck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 14:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seit Jahren nur hier: https://www.designbyhumans.com/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 16:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes a lot of sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 15:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you guys expect similar hardware requirements than the Rift? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Damit wre das auch geklrt, wir lagen alle falsch UND richtig! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 17:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 14:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besttigt meine Theory, dass meine Familie sich das einfach ausgedacht hat :p Meine Oma hat aber auch immer "Eingebrocktes" gesagt und sowas . . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 14:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wenn man etwas darber nachdenkt, dann ist es schon komisch das es so viele verschiedene Versionen fr den Zustand "Tr ist nicht geschlossen, aber auch nicht vollstndig offen" gibt, oder? Man knnte ja meinen die Tr hat zwei wichtige Zustnde, aber der 3. ist viel wichtiger fr mich (zumindest semantisch). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 14:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vielleicht hat meine Familie deine Version einfach umgendert :D Ich mit wirklich mit der Redewendung "Tr anmachen" aufgewachsen und habe erst spter gemerkt, dass das einige Menschen verwirrt. Ist das ein Ost-West Ding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wer kennt die Redewendung "Die Tr anmachen" ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 14:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiel mir letztens in nem Gesprch mit einem Kumpel auf, dass das gar nicht so verbreitet ist. Die Tr anmachen bedeutet (in meinem Kopf), sie nicht vollstndig zu schlieen, einen kleinen Spalt offen zu lassen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 15:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now it makes sense, thanks for explaining :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 13:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all thank you very much! I have 2 SSDs with enough Storage for me (around 200 GB), so I guess I don't need the Seagate 1 TB :D Any point in going with 16 GB RAM? I was always using Nvidia Video Cards in the past, how is Radeon received in the community in general?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1200 Gaming PC + VR Future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 10:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **What will you be doing with this PC? Be as specific as possible, and include specific games or programs you will be using.**

I want to 60 FPS 1080p modern games (GTA V etc.) and be ready for the Oculus Rift later this year.

**What is your maximum budget before rebates/shipping/taxes?** 

1200 

**When do you plan on building/buying the PC? Note: beyond a week or two from today means any build you receive will be out of date when you want to buy.** 

Between Now and June

**What, exactly, do you need included in the budget? (Tower/OS/monitor/keyboard/mouse/etc)** 

Everything except Monitor,Mouse, Keyboard and SSD

**Which country (and state/province) will you be purchasing the parts in? If you're in US, do you have access to a Microcenter location?** 

Germany

**If reusing any parts (including monitor(s)/keyboard/mouse/etc), what parts will you be reusing? Brands and models are appreciated.** 

Both SSDs are Samsung

**Will you be overclocking? If yes, are you interested in overclocking right away, or down the line? CPU and/or GPU?** 

I have no idea about this, appreciate any input about this.

**Are there any specific features or items you want/need in the build? (ex: SSD, large amount of storage or a RAID setup, CUDA or OpenCL support, etc)**

Nope, just the earlier mentioned 60 FPS on 1080p is important to me.

**Do you have any specific case preferences (Size like ITX/microATX/mid-tower/full-tower, styles, colors, window or not, LED lighting, etc), or a particular color theme preference for the components?**

Subtle and or simple design if possible.

**Do you need a copy of Windows included in the budget? If you do need one included, do you have a preference?**

I have Windows 10 running on my SSD ar the moment and would like to take this with me in the new system.

**Extra info or particulars:**

I like my Gaming PC fast and quiet.

Regarding the Oculus Rift thing, here would be the requirements [LINK](https://www.reddit.com/r/oculus/wiki/requirements)

Thank you very much guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got an additional Beta Code </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 14:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Guys,

Here is my additional CBT 2 Code I don't need:

12?5-33FB-D923-4BA8-?6B0

The ? are letters A-Z, good luck.

EDIT: It's gone, see ya all on thursday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 14:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically all from Schubert :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 00:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah would love to :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 11:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 10:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel stupid now, I thought the long loading times back to base should feel immersive, I accepted the waiting as a game mechanic :p  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 17:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was looking for this, thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 17:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice observation, but what are the obstacles in your theory? No sound clues or shadows are there. An Empty grid does not really help us and I highly doubt that there is a mystery secret with an easy bruteforce solution/random trying. Maybe a layer above or is there a similar field we could put on top? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 00:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, 
First of all, I dont understand the argument you guys have, we are all fans of this wonderful little piece of art, which we all enjoyed in our own way. If you want to focus your attention to the backstory, thats awesome and its not like the subreddit is flooded with posts, but the way you write comes of as pretentious (bordering arrogance). Take a day to beat the mountain and then tell us your thoughts, would def like to read more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 18:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally with you, good that you explained further! I loved the environment and sometimes I was actually sad, that I "had to leave" to progress, the Autumn Forest for example. In the end I just wished for more, more time on the island, more puzzles to solve :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 17:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the "problem" here is, that we as players are used to get a prize or a kind of reward after completing something. We have to actively re-learn this part of our behaviour to enjoy games like The Witness (at least that's how I see it). Appreciate the way to the end of the game, the struggle of understanding rule sets and Overcoming challenges. Its Konfuzius in virtual form : "The journey is the reward". BTW OP on topic of "The Challenge", i'm in the same boat as you are, I couldn't get myself to grind   complete it yet, it's just not important for my enjoyment of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 17:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hint: Think about the rules you have learned on the way. Whats the rules for the Colored Dots?

There can't be two different colors in one "area".
You don't have to group the colors together!

If you cant solve it, here is a solution [http://imgur.com/Yv5ZHK0](/spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 04:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one puzzle in the symmetry area, where you had to change perspective for the first time to the rock right of it. Drove me nearly insane, was just not thinking out of the box :p Cursed at JB after like 3 hours, still love the game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 18:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FF15 is doch nochnetmal draussn . . .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 20:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Witness. Mein Kopf tut weh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 18:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deutschlnder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 15:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gibts eigentlich auch was Organisiertes auf Discord? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 10:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crazy Idea: Make a FF-like Tower, where we have to beat waves/floors of enemies. Every 10 or so there can be a boss floor and rewards increase with the amount of floors cleared! Would also love to see more horizontal crafting, you have such a nice crafting system, but lots of mats and crafts are used once and then you go further. I like to gather them again to maybe give my amor a special chance of something :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 10:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome idea, thanks! Didn't even think about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 14:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome to hear that development is continuing, I really love the game you put out there! Is this the right space for some suggestions? I'm playing on PC and I find the map a bit lackluster, I would love to see some more information on the actual map, like contains of the different biomes ("I need that special item, but forgot where I saw it") and names of NPCs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 10:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ja, denn dann habe ich endlich Zeit Crashlands zu zocken, welches gestern Launch hatte! Freue mich schon seit einigen Wochen drauf und die paar Stunden gestern waren groartig :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 19:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worked for me, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 20:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Tabletop Simulator](http://store.steampowered.com/app/286160) ist gerade im Sale mit 50%, aber nicht mehr lange! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 16:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Das Leben der Anderen* is quite good in my opinion. I love Werner Herzog, but he doesn't produce in Germany for a long time anymore, worth watching everything from him none the less, especially the stuff with Kinski (*Mein liebster Feind* etc). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 23:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tilo Jung - Find seine interviews interessant, glaube der knnte ein interessanter Gast fr Bohnjour sein. Hat auch mal in nem interview ber ihn gesagt, dass er die Bohnen guckt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 19:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to remember, this video is not meant for *us*, it's for our parents generation and the general tv audience. They have to give the TV watchers some anchors to understand. But totally with you, esports should stand on its own :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 17:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Found it online.](https://society6.com/product/force-awakens-movie-poster_print#1=45)


Hope thats the real Amien Juuog, but it seems so! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 15:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100 Punkte fr den Kandidaten bunglebum!

Aber zur Erklrung: Ich kenne das Subreddit hier noch nicht so lange und habe oft das Gefhl, dass ich die handvoll in-jokes zwischen Mods und 2-3 leuten net verstehe. Das hindert natrlich am posten und kommentieren, aber ich wrde genauso auch nicht verlangen, dass sich hier alles nach meiner Vorstellung von einem subreddit verhlt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 14:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ein Teil dieser Antwort . . .  Ach Schei drauf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 16:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kurze Frage: Kennt einer die Marke von Ralph's Hoodie in dieser Episode? Der schwarze, den glaube ich auch Eddie hat. Find den extrem stylisch :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 19:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH, when I was a kid it was a male neighbour or relative in the costume and that was more than enough :) With 4 years it shouldnt be too hard to convince them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 15:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Binding of Isaac: Afterbirth. Hab noch soviele Unlocks und dabei sind schon locker 300+ Stunden aufm Konto, ich liebe es.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 02:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neon Genesis Evangelion geht immer ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 17:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hab mich nie wirklich fr Flipper interessiert, aber Colins Begeisterung ist einfach ansteckend, werde einschalten :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 21:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mir fehlte nur noch "Wir haben 20k Leute gefragt, nennen sie . . ." :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 15:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wie sind wir da noch nicht drauf gekommen :D? los gehts, das hat wirklich Potential! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 16:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Es wurde der name "The Fappening" dafr gekhrt, aber frag mich nicht woher ich das wei :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 10:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you guys ever do a Isaac Bingo here in the Subreddit? I think that would be super fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 19:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wer jetzt Interesse bekommen hat an dem Spiel, dem kann ich den YT Kanal von [Northernlion](https://www.youtube.com/user/Northernlion) empfehlen. Er ist nicht der weltbeste Isaac Spieler, aber dennoch sehr informativ und unterhaltsam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 16:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excatly what I was looking for, thanks so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 22:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh, gute Idee! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 14:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich fand dich z.B. beim Pokemon AP richtig super! Also auch gerne mehr non-fitness content :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 19:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like MONDO, very high quality imo :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 00:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup, cya arena win ;_; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 16:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was a good show overall, interesting topics and good insights. The only thing I cant understand: why is destiny playing games while being on the show, imo thats so disrespectful. But I'm glad the show is back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Richard Lewis - Hello Kotakuinaction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 19:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 18:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> got chills, hyped! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 14:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find ich vllig OK, denn wir wissen Gregott liefert immer Qualitt ab! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 13:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 16:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Siedler 2 is top! Auch geil wre Dungeon Keeper 1/2, knnte man auch schn mit War for the Overworld verbinden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 17:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel stupid, thanks :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 17:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy Shit . . . . I wasnt aware of this, how do you do this :)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 16:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about soundproof booths for future events? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 21:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any idea to tie in Evil Morty in your theory? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 18:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If its not solely about PR, why didn't you do something like this months ago? The timing seems rushed  . . . .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 16:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you (ESL) be up to initiate a independent research about the effects of PEDs in eSports? I would be very interest to see what substances have an effect on the performance of eSports players.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 14:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the nut is obviously a hidden-rare item on the timed nodes . . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 12:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your definition of "content" seems pretty arbitrary but whatever man, just have fun in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
