<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4963</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do Anapanasati mostly but I can't tell if it's working or not. All I know is the longer I do a single session the harder it is to concentrate towards the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's that bot when we actually need it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Better Focus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find myself, both in sitting meditation and in life, succumbing to day dreaming quite often. When I realize that I'm day dreaming and I return to my task, it may take less than a minute for me to start day dreaming again and have to realize it again. Any tips on how to curb this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the longest time I wanted to be in a relationship. Finally I ended up dating this girl and it was great. Then eventually school got tough and I didn't have time for the relationship anymore so we broke up. Afterwards I realized how great being single is. I feel so much more productive and contributive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use Tao Te Ching +, the default Legge translation I find to be extremely awkward, however you can change it to the John McDonald translation and it reads a lot nicer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you explain the teachings of Hui Neng then? He did tell us to take refuge in the Three Treasures and to strive towards Bodhisattvahood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The former will bring forth the latter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You go on talking all day about Zen Masters and yet you haven't read a single word of theirs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slug themed death metal = best death metal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not anymore, since the third EP it's been a full band. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend has an S6 with damaged antenna bands so he uses his On5 as a mobile hotspot and he's never really complained about it not working. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the marimbas on Feedback Loop and Holomovement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) I don't know  
2) I don't know  
3) I don't know  
  
Were you actually expecting something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it's a bit of a waste of time to say what isn't Zen, don't you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I posted to r/circlejerk and got a bunch of free karma, good job guys! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Don't Get Why Everyone Is Getting Downvoted??? Now Give Me Karma! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! How can I determine if my phone has a locked bootloader or not? I've seen mixed answers on whether or not mine does (Galaxy Note 4 Verizon, N910V). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this yield less risks than rooting? Also does this work on phones with locked bootloaders? I'm sorry I'm clueless with this kind of stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you have a custom ROM without being rooted though?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you suggest upgrading then? I haven't had too many problems with my Note 4 so far besides occasional slowdown and battery life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Is The Moto Z Play With Doing Multiple Things At Once? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't necessarily mean the split screen feature. With my Galaxy Note 4 I get slowdown and lag when, for example, I'm updating apps through the Play store and I try to do other things while this is going on. Does the Moto Z Play experience slowdown in situations like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like when the monk asked Joshu "Does the dog have buddha nature?" and Joshu replied "Mu (N/A)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the Pali Canon correct but in Mahayana it becomes more affirmed that there is no Self nature in anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those "supernatural" things you listed aren't actually supernatural at all but are more based in logic.  
  
You may be familiar with the Buddhist notion of Anatman, that there is no Self nature in anything. So when we die, we're not actually dying, because there was nothing alive in the first place. You just go on thinking another body that isn't you is you like you're doing right now.  
  
Nirvana is just then the realization of this. The realization that nothing can be called "you" and you truly experience this state of no-Self, the way things actually are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Come to Note 4!" is the new "Come to Brazil!" in the smartphone world lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Is Sigur Rs "Nostalgic"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many people (including myself) seem to describe Sigur Rs as nostalgic. Even when I first discovered them they sounded like something that I heard long ago and am just finding again. Where does this come from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Does the King of Death have fixed dates?"  
  
"Mu."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gautama is usually doing either the Earth Touching mudra or a teaching mudra. Sometimes you'll see him doing the dhyani mudra (like the one in the picture) but most of the time he would not be holding an alms bowl if in this pose. If he's in the other poses mentioned then he may be holding an alms bowl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah so it's definitely Amitabha since Padmasambhava is an incarnation of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like it would be the other way around. Two toed sloths are cute, three toed sloths are creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Motorola said that the mods will work with all new Moto flagships for at least 4 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cosmic mudra indicates that it is very likely to be Amitabha. If this is a Pure Land temple then it's definitely Amitabha.  
  
EDIT: this actually looks like some sort of Vajrayana temple. In that case the possibilities of who this statue represents becomes a lot more broad then just Amitabha or Shakyamuni. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 05:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe thinking there's a dream to be woken up from is deterring the grasshoppers ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a marketing scheme. Technically you can send unlimited MMS but each one uses your data, so it'll be your data limit preventing you from sending more MMS messages, not your MMS limit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one said anything about Fox wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking  
"What do we want?"  
"There is nothing to want nor anyone to want it!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to be getting overly defensive... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both The Diamond Sutra and the Heart Sutra are short. If it's 20 pages it's probably the full thing, whereas the Heart Sutra should be a couple pages at most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is to understand that Samsara can be experienced differently. You can be a Deva in constant pleasure or an Asura in constant war and yet you'll still be in Samsara. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't the Buddha like yell at him for it though? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely forgot I have this! Thanks lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Does my Phone Keep Getting Woken Up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My battery usage chart shows that my phone keeps getting woken up when the screen is off. In the usage list, it only lists screen, Android System, and Android OS. Any idea what this could be? I have a Galaxy Note 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I might be starting to get it now, thanks everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are going to come regardless, the idea is to be fine with them when they do, and I don't think animals have the mental capacity to be adverse to it (for example I've never seen a dog complain that it is sick) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if they never go looking for the ox in the first place, then where's the dukkha? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
