<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9885</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved sing street too, as you say really heartwarming and fun film, and the music is great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take your point but don't think it couldn't have been resolved any other way. It's clear when the dying woman tries to get into the bunker that something is going on - alien or otherwise, so he's partially vindicated at that point. 
And as for the Michelle's story arc, I wasn't necessarily saying that the film should have just ended when she escaped, just that it didn't need the cg. I like that the ending is clearly an alien invasion, but it's too long and for me didn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] teriyaki tofu and vegetables, mushroom rice, egg rolls, wilted spinach with sesame and miso soup, with green tea I made at a cooking class in Kyoto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 11:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah exactly felt very disjointed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes exactly this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know, but I just felt it would've been a better film with less flashy ending - didn't feel necessary  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 cloverfield lane, was a great psychological thriller up until the last 15/20 mins - really didn't need all the cgi alien stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 19:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! They were a bit of an experiment, pastry is standard shortcrust 2:1 flour to butter and filling was a mish mash of veg I had around, squash, butter beans, carrots, mushrooms, peas, celery, and red lentils to thicken, added to a creamy curry sauce of onion, garlic, coriander powder, cumin powder, garam masala, stock, passata and creme fraiche. The key I think was letting the filling cool totally and then leaving the filled pies in muffin tins to rest in the fridge for 30 mins before cooking   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
