<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh...it doesn't matter, atleast their doing their bests to translate :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manga translations.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chapter 70 was a out a month ago and chapter 71 2 weeks ago (Atleast on rawsen) why isn't it translated yet? Are the translators busy or? Did they stop? 

Also a few chapters more and then it's finally gonna be after-anime material! yay (if you put the LN aside, i mean after-anime manga material).

^-^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no need, bell is gaining up on them he is half way maybe 3/4 on the way to lvl 4, after that 2 levels more and he's on their levels, it took them years and he did it in a few months lol. OP skill ftw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH RIGHT i read somewhere she can only get stronger by eating those magic stones nvm ty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL sorry dude, i mean this is REDDIT right? lol i'll just read the LN when i have the time, (lolsorry) 

Also why the fuk cant wiene join the familia? Is it like that it isn't possible for a xenos to join a familia? (I'm still asking questions LOLOL) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Back again with da questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1: will bell have that wiene (saw on the wiki lol) join the hestia familia? 
2: wouldn't it be awesome if bell tamed a monster, like a familliar (a dragon maybe?) 
3: did crozzo and lilli officially join the hestia familia? (I haven't read the LN's yet, who cares about spoilers xd)



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn, got dat sista pussy doe (in Highschool DxD he had children also with ravel lol) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His skill wouldn't be considered a "cheat" doe lol. He is born with it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, ottar is lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox mask = sunao, why do you think the fox mask attacks kazuya when doing stuff with woman and also one of the chapters you see kotetsu speaking to sunao (the katana is kotetsu)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions (again) (lol) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1: will anyone stand a chance against bell when he reaches everyone else (lvl 6-6+)
2: why did the author actually start sword oratoria, i mean by that what brought him to start that? Couldn't he have focused more on the danmachi LN and Manga? (I mean i started reading sword oratoria manga, i like it and i'll probably try the LN aswell but still, why?)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1: Will the manga (Danmachi one) continue after bell kills that level boss monster? (18th floor one, like in the anime)
2: why isn't the author just revealing the past of bell..who are his parents...and what happened to them...
3: also, is the manga monthly released?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theory oh hell yes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could it be that bell and aiz are brother and sister? In one of the episodes and manga bell said "Mother" when he was lying down when waking up on aiz's lap (his mother could look like aiz) but this isn't the only proof it, aiz's dad had white hair (hint?) and her mom had the same color as her's. If that's the case, if bell thought aiz was his mother when waking up that means aiz looks like his mother right? 
(Is it maybe hinted in the LN?) (anyone who reads the LN please tell meh). 
(This theory has been on my mind for a long time now lol). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Book depository all the way, i always get my manga/LN there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah shit forgot. Who cares let him take all dem bitches, kukuri, sunao, kiriha, I MEAN ALL dem bitches xd


Still crossing mah fingers for dat english release, somehow we need to advertise the tsugumomo anime so that people check the manga out, the problem is that alot of people say "it's not interesting" yeah the start is all explaining and stuff, they should read everything not only the first 10 chapters am i right? People never learn lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn i really don't get it that it has to get edited or censored...nobody cares about censoring stuff tbh lol also i'll start to import too if it doesn't come over.. BTW is yesasia the best site to order? (Raw japanese manga)


(I also use book depository for my english stuff got all my manga from there, great site). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 09:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the anime is going to be effective (so the publishers are going to notice that it's starting to get a even bigger fanbase) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about english release? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 09:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way to support the author to make them have a english release (easiest way to ask lol)

i mean does it get released once it reaches a certain japanese sales number? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL SAME, but sadly i think he cant switch them, actually he can.. but when using ascension he's probably going to use kiriha and kyouka (threesome huehuehue)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT IF HE DOES ASCENSION WITH ALL HIS TSUGUMOMO'S (i mean like the 18 tsugumomo's + kiriha and kyouka, like he goes beserk and unleashes incredible power to defeat his possessed mom) holy shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ascension between kazuya and kyouka </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If kazuya and kyouka did ascension, wouldn't kazuya be able to use like sonic boom like attacks? I mean move/run at the speed of sound and use his fists to make sonic booms? (It would because kyouka is a sound type) (still a flute but isn't my theory cool? lol

It would be OP doe. Good luck deflecting a sonic boom fist and outrunning/deflecting a person who moves at the speed of sound lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read alot of manga's and hands down tsugumomo is my fav right now. AW yis

Question 1: Please TELL ME (PLEASE) is kiriha going go be revived? (I SHIP EM HARD).
Question 2: Will tsugumomo get a english release? i'm certain they'll get alot of sales, i mean alot (the community is quite large).
Question 3: also, (this was in the manga) it's said that tsugumomo and humans can have children? So if kiriha returns and IF there's gonna be a happy ending at the end could they have kids? (It's possible between tsugumomo and humans, right?)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
