<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7582</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who haven't read it,
[The proposed 29th amendment]
(https://petemurphy.wordpress.com/more-good-stuff/29th-amendment-to-the-constitution-of-the-united-states/)  
  
I don't really see how any of this is a violation of that amendment though, especially since it's not an actual law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Berkeley cancels conservative firebrand Ann Coulters speech over fears of more violent protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I say public figure, I mean elected official, not celebrity.
Politicians forgoe some of their privacy as public officials. Celebrities do as a consequence of fame, but not as a requirement for their job or position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but to be fair, Trump is a public figure. And that's a different ballgame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damn Reddit is doing nothing but making this situation worse for these kids with a witch hunt. This seriously needs to end. Let youtube sort out what to do with their channel (they're obviously aware), and let the courts sort out the kids.  
If vigilantes are harassing the family, that's uncalled for an horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wut....  
Sorry, I'm not a youtuber and don't follow all of this stuff that seems to blow up every few months.  
Where is this video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next up:  
  
No, guys, I swear, I'm not racist. I have black friends.  
Uh, their names? Uhhh. Well, it's been a while since I saw them. I'm trying to remember.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Takeaways From The Georgia 6 Special Election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the real answer. Yeah, there may be a first popular meme, image, or cartoon, but it was hilarious how many employees tried to make a name for themselves by creating another version of some technology that hadn't been new in 10 years. Good on them for their motivation to succeed, but not every smart and/or well educated person has an innovative idea that will change the world. (and if I knew what makes something game-changing, apart from a good idea+(luck+motivation)+innovative enough, I'd be sipping on a gin   tonic in a hammock in Maldives instead of typing this message.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't even close to his first. In the bile that is the liveleak community, this guy is a veteran. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if you know someone who is registered, call them. Go to their house, drag them out kicking and screaming, and make them vote.  
Then buy them dinner if you had to be a dick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First place? You never had first place. You never had your car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do we want to talk about how EVERY SINGLE T_D thread where Michelle Obama is mentioned has innumerable comments about how she's really a man/trans?  
Trump supporters, especially those who continue to support him through all of what we've learned in thee past 4 months, are truly sick, horrible people. There is no forgiving them at this point. Be a conservative, that's fine. I've got tons of conservative  beliefs to go with my liberal beliefs. This is different. These people and this president are different, and they deserve no forgiveness for their words or hatred now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Spicer one. Great job on these. They're spot on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Safe bet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were playing your VEEP clip's audio on the biggest morning radio show in Dallas the day after you released it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty common in the U.S. too.  
[Here](http://i.imgur.com/RjIB0Zo.jpg) is Donald Trump eating KFC on his private jet during the 2016 Presidential campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Patients may qualify for medical cannabis if they have a terminal illness or if they suffer from cancer...

[Well then...](http://southparkstudios.mtvnimages.com/images/shows/south-park/clip-thumbnails/season-14/1403/south-park-s14e03c04-microwaving-your-balls-16x9.jpg?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Man Who First Fueled Donald Trump's Political Paranoia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lots of places have just one Obamacare insurer. What if that falls to zero? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN treats politics like sports  and its making us all dumber </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. We didn't. This is a bullshit article.  
It'd be great if we could, but we can't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't find a Youtube video link, but yeah,  
[here](http://deadstate.org/woman-interrupts-alex-jones-tirade-you-actually-have-liquor-on-your-breath/) isthe video you're thinking of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow, peddling bullshit to rubes (knowingly) makes him so much worse than if he's insane.  
But either way, whichever way you slice it, what he preaches is still bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That should help his credibility with his crowd.  
Nevermind, they don't believe anything that fucks with their worldview. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When every last dollar counts, yeah, they might parade fake ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every comment section about this has comments from the right side of the argument saying she hit him first. Is there a video of that somewhere? Cus I'm not seeing the evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, because Hillary was a raging success, and no way someone from one of the far ends of the political spectrum [insert Trump] could ever beat the establishment in a fair race [Bush, Rubio]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's not say that our politicians have swagger, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vineyard Vines is definitely the starter gear for the casual white supremacist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are what is wrong with political discourse online. You knowingly spread misinformation, then turn into a troll when called out on it. Trump happened because of people like you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still haven't answered the questions.  
How did you get the title so wrong?  
If it doesn't matter, why did you describe the race of the men at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title is incorrect. And yeah, it matters.  
Why did you write "black male" when he clearly said "white male?"  
If it doesn't matter, why did you write "_____ male" at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shit. Delete your post. You're spreading misinformation at this point.  
How did you fuck the title up so badly if it wasn't intentional? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not yet... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> La la la la la la la la </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He never said anything about black male suicides at all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  or he's just spewing a bunch of bullshit that will pass with his base.

who the fuck is his base, and what in the name of all that fucks is wrong with their brains? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see this as a bad thing in the long run. It'd be nice to live in a world where there are homes or parks where there are currently malls, strip malls, outdoor shopping centers, etc. It definitely could free up a lot of space for people to live in affordably without having to run to the burbs. Or hell, do live in the burbs. Wherever you want to live. Shit's coming to your doorstep now anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Has anyone seen my keys?"  
-- Wolf Blitzer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Focused on Trumps Successes, Many Supporters Are Unfazed by His Reversals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 12:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huh. TIL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, Wait.  
I thought My Little Pony was a cartoon from the 80s that some small group of people turned into a sexual fetish.  
Are you telling me that My Little Pony was so re-energized by the sex industry that a full blown cartoon reboot was created?  
Wow. So, um, go porn (or something)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wish this "uh huh" button worked on my slightly younger 30 year old sister. It doesn't even register with her. She just trudges on, telling me about her friends, her dog, or her job. Over the past 5 years or so I've started trying to see how long she can speak without me making a single sound. 4-8 minutes is pretty normal, but we've hit 11-13 minutes several times, and 16 minutes is her current record.  
She'll usually ask something long the lines of "how are things with you" at the end, but after about 20 seconds of talking, she's on again with a relatable "yeah that happened to me too, lemme tel you about it for 5 minutes" story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL: [Chip Sealing](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=92BKj2-Tbzk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I someone posted something like this in /r/The_Donald, they'd be banned immediately, yet here you are in our free speech zone.  
Go back to your safe space, snowflake. They love your bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald is LOVING his new toys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treason is the correct word. We keep dancing around it, but in the end, that is what we're dealing with. Treason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most were. I know I was. I was probably 50% Reddit, 30% Digg 20% Fark back in 2007-8ish. But damn did Digg fuck up. They really weren't total shit at one time, but when they fucked it up, they really fucked it up. Did you know that site still exists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a lot of poor Republican assholes. They vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I member.  
Member before the Digg users came over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blaming boomers as a group for this sort of stuff is just as lame as blaming millenials for whatever shit they get blamed for.  
  
What do millenials get blamed for? Being lazy and entitled? Sorry we expected what we were promised growing up, that if we studied and worked hard we'd have a chance at that ole American dream like our parents/grandparents did. You know, decent paying jobs like boomers had when they got out of college, reasonable student loan debt, a chance to buy a house and save for retirement. Not having to have both spouses working just to make ends meet. Yeah, those damn millenials.  
  
No, it's totally legitimate to blame the boomers. You know why? BECAUSE FOR THE LAST 50 YEARS THEY WERE THE ONES VOTING AND CREATING THE SOCIETY WE LIVE IN TODAY.  The millenials inherited this mess and they're pissed, and they have only the boomers and Gen Xers (to a lesser extent) to blame. It's not like the millienials were alive or voting when it got fucked. That's a TOTALLY false equivalence comparing boomers to millenials. There's nothing you can blame millenials for. They're too young to have caused any institutionalized catastrophies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firing Comey would do nothing but make Trump look bad in this investigation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've missed this meme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Havasu Falls/Supai is the Lake Louise/Banff of 2017 in this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typical babyboomer move. They get all the benefits of what we pay into social security, but cut it so we won't have any when we reach retirement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this statue as a bobblehead thanks to a Reddit post. You can get it on Amazon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't imply anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so weight aside, his bodyfat is definitely over 30%. [He's fat.](http://imgur.com/a/uLZhu)  
If you don't think he's fat, you might be fat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold her pussy - Trump  
  
FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just plain silly.  
Like titty whistle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump supporters were there too. Wait for the biker in the "Make America Great Again" hat and buddies...  
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uKt9Vz9vFCU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, what you're telling me, is that Steve Bannon isn't just a nationalist, he's an anarchist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really is.  
And, following up on our theme, the the worst combination of two words I've ever heard: soppy gooch  
Thank you guys like guys named zach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's not even a *chance* Trump ever, *ever* speaks under oath or in any real public forum about the Russia campaign/administration problems, wiretapping allegations, or his violation of the Emoluments Clause. Not a chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in a fraternity in college. Why am I not surprised that a guy named Zach would have the word choad in his username?  
I'm not hating on it. I just think it's really funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
