<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4276</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most Americans unwilling to give up internet privacy rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, i like how you think. It makes me consider things myself which i wouldnt have thought. Yes, i understand ( tounge in cheek)  or im trying to get my head around why would they visit us. A world which i can only guess from outsiders is full of war and violence and negativity. You bring up some very good points, about the threat we could pose to them... eventually. What im speculating here if that an advanced civilisation/ species/ being was indeed to take an interest in us, would they have to take any action? Again im speculating here, but would they not be capable of observing us, in ways that we cannot comprehend? Just like we observe bacteria under a  under a microscope, been ever so busy. 

We are assuming,  not wrongly with our human logic that we  humans are advanced and are capable of causing destruction to other outside species. However maybe going back to your comment on the human capability to self destruct and create chaos is by far an unintelligent way of living in the universe. Maybe alien life forms have tackled selflishness and evil. Concepts to us humans which are indeed self destructive. Maybe these aliens have learnt a lesson, way back in the past, that we as humans  are going to be learning very soon. Maybe along the way these aliens have been busy creating a new way of being, a way of living without evil.

Who knows !! truely speculation of course :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A look at how the climate is continuing to produce concerning data. This article contains links and information about the research. Interesting reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have successfully tested a new drug that considerably weakens the recollection of a negative experience in humans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. had 2nd warmest year to date and 9th warmest March on record. 5 billion-dollar disasters in first 3 months of 2017 set new record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. had 2nd warmest year to date and 9th warmest March on record. 5 billion-dollar disasters in first 3 months of 2017 set new record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. had 2nd warmest year to date and 9th warmest March on record 5 billion-dollar disasters in first 3 months of 2017 set new record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. had 2nd warmest year to date and 9th warmest March on record. 5 billion-dollar disasters in first 3 months of 2017 set new record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Q Poll: 66% Concerned Climate Change Will Impact Them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, thankyou for your explanation. You went into great detail, and i enjoyed your logic of thinking. Yes you raise some valid points regarding distance and probability etc. However im going to ask (and please dont think im picking an argument here) is that we are seeing aliens from the perspective of a thinking human mind. We are going by the logic that aliens need to operate like humans. They have to think like us, and see things the way we do. Can you really believe that another life form, think, and conceptualise like us. One that is possibly far far more advanced than us. Who have evolved way ahead of us? When we see an ant on the floor scurrying around, from what we know they have no sense of the complexity of the world. 

Now lets even say a chimpanzee who  from my understanding are quite intelligent from what we know. Are they aware of the achievements of space travel, the internet ? They dont marvel at are achievements ( not that im aware) Now imaging another life form which could be  way more advanced than us, with an entirely different way of being. A way of being we can not understand. Who are we as humans are to think that are thinking and knowledge ( so far ) has to be a measure of all knowledge across the universe and even far beyond. Who are we to say they dont see us like ants sculling around not even able to comprehend another life entirely?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Psychologists from the university of Georgia have found people with personality disorders are more likely to marry or make friends with people who are dysfunctional in a similar way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A look at how Australia will be impacted due to climate change. The article highlights how low level island people will be affected by extreme weather, and how they may cope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disaster alley: Australia could be set to receive new wave of climate refugees. US defence expert warns people fleeing low-lying Pacific islands a precursor to climate-exacerbated water insecurities that could trigger wider conflict </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. coal companies ask Trump to stick with Paris climate deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tasked with Saving the World, Jared Kushner Is Destined to Fail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study of the DNA in ancient skeletal remains adds to the evidence that indigenous groups living today in southern Alaska and the western coast of British Columbia are descendants of the first humans to make their home in northwest North America more than 10,000 years ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, now we are on the topic. In your opinion, why are people in general ( so adverse ) to the fact that aliens can visit Earth (Aliens which could be potentially far far advanced than us ) People are called conspiracy theorists crazy etc, when they believe these beings visiting Earth and having the capability to do this. 

However, hundreds of millions of dollars are spent searching for extraterrestrial life and we celebrate  this achievement and our technology,  like we are so advanced and special. Where  is the logic in this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jared Kushner Meets With Iraqi Leader on Future of ISIS Battle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Annual spending on robotics in mainland China is forecast to continue its rapid expansion and exceed US$59 billion by 2020, as demand ramps up in the countrys manufacturing industry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Risky' surge in consumer debt fuelled by interest-free credit cards, warns Bank of England </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds more than 20 percent of patients are misdiagnosed. Mayo Clinic researchers highlight the value of getting a second opinion for serious medical issues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will re submit with a working link.Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California and Scotland join forces to fight climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cyborgs at work: employees getting implanted with microchips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Innovation in AI could see governments introduce human quotas, study says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 10:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A look at how social media particularly Instagram feeds young peoples egos. This article displays some of the tactics used  by youngsters to help them achieve confidence online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young people will not beat around the bush as to why they use social media sites. They use these platforms to boast of their daily tidings, carefully craft their public image, and feed their egos in this interconnected digital age. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Noam Chomsky: Why Donald Trump is pushing the doomsday clock to the brink of midnight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stress a common seizure trigger in epilepsy, UC study affirms. Other studies have followed populations who have collectively experienced stressful events, such as the effects of war, trauma or natural disaster. All of which found increased seizure risk during such a time of stress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Large businesses push back against Trumps climate change, immigration policies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study of the relationship between climate change and clashes among the Classic Maya explicitly links temperature increases with growing conflicts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Android apps share data between them without your permission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA chief admits climate change is real  but the real issue is how much we contribute to it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you think this is so. Would you say there is a pattern? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No necessarily, was hoping could get more information regarding psychological issues and history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your response. Well thought out. Have you delved into this subject a bit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arctic researcher says White House is deleting her citations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research has shown that the US burden of neurological disease is nearly $800 billion/year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coordinated Action Needed to Face Sea-Level Rise, Experts Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With rates of sea-level rise along parts of the nations Eastern seaboard increasing three to four times faster than the global average, experts are working to mitigate the effects by identifying threats, organizing collaboration among governments and organizations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The West will pursue clean energy despite Trumps assault on climate science. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study has found that, on average, stand up comedians are two times more likely to die younger than their thespian counterparts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study http://thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(15)01026-0/abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drive-by headlocks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Care to elaborate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A nationwide study that shows just 9 of 25 state gun laws are effective in reducing firearm deaths, suggests that if three laws implemented in some states were adopted nationwide, they could reduce gun deaths by more than 80 percent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People tend to unconsciously imitate others' prudent, impatient or lazy attitudes, according to a study. The study results show that participants are bound to a "false-consensus" bias, i.e. they believe without evidence that the attitudes of others resemble their own. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study http://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/2158244017697164 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China accuses Trump of 'selfishness' over climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study has found migraine attacks double the risk of developing generalized anxiety disorders in men. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the outset, Lamar Smith, who chairs the committee, made his views clear: the alarmist theories of climatologists had no hard proof, he claimed. 

And anyone who even tried to predict what would happen to the Earths climate by 2100 was not credible.



One commentator suggested the "insane" hearing was a form of gaslighting, with the "cavalcade of falsehoods" designed to make people question their mental health.

Just one renowned climate scientist, Professor Michael Mann, appeared at the hearing, flanked by three academics described as being very much in the minority on the issue.

But one of them, Dr Roger Pielke, a climate science policy writer at Colorado University, clearly disappointed some committee members when he said climate science had consistently shown there was a fundamental risk since the 1980s.

He even advocated imposing a carbon tax on petrol to raise billions for climate-related projects.

That suggestion prompted a telling response from one Republican committee member, Randy Weber, who described it as utter blasphemy.


If every time you publish something you are worried about having to respond to endless FOIA [Freedom of Information Act] requests and receiving thousands of emails and being called to testify, obviously thats very stifling. 

The intention is to cause scientists to retreat. Its meant to send a chilling signal to the entire research community.

That is: if you, too, publish and speak out on the threat of human-caused climate change, we're going to come after you.

He said Republicans had been going after scientists simply because you don't like their publications of their research  not because the science is bad, but because you find the research inconvenient to the special interests who fund your campaigns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican sceptics call climate change hearing that massively backfires as expert witness calls for carbon tax </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US environmental groups file suit to block new coal mining on public lands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DOE Official Urges Staff Not to Talk About Climate to Avoid a Visceral Reaction From Sec. Perry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers discover link between watching light entertainment TV and voting for populist politicians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not baiting. Why dont you reread my comment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, any more information apart from that?  Because this phrase seems very common on this sub, which is very often i can imagine  used to discredit  articles, without explaining or giving any intelligent explanation. This phrase iv noticed appears very early when an article is posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-military and security firms oppose Home Sec in WhatsApp crypto row </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 11:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy advocates plan to fight Congress' repeal of Internet privacy rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK debt charity says demand for help hits record high </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study 

http://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/features/abn-abn0000258.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A consortium of psychologists and psychiatrists has developed a new, evidence-based alternative to the mental health field's long-established diagnostic tools for the classification, treatment, and research of mental disorders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study shows that an exaggerated emotional response from the brain to non-threatening and non-emotional cues predicts the emergence of the first signs of psychotic symptoms in late adolescence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China, EU rally for climate action as Trump backs away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, what in your view is the most import habit/s a person can do to prevent the onset of Alzheimers as much as possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You mean this, still an interesting read, with the main article

As robots and other computer-assisted technologies take over tasks previously performed by labor, there is increasing concern about the future of jobs and wages. We analyze the effect of the increase in industrial robot usage between 1990 and 2007 on US local labor markets. Using a model in which robots compete against human labor in the production of different tasks, we show that robots may reduce employment and wages, and that the local labor market effects of robots can be estimated by regressing the change in employment and wages on the exposure to robots in each local labor marketdefined from the national penetration of robots into each industry and the local distribution of employment across industries. Using this approach, we estimate large and robust negative effects of robots on employment and wages across commuting zones. We bolster this evidence by showing that the commuting zones most exposed to robots in the post-1990 era do not exhibit any differential trends before 1990. The impact of robots is distinct from the impact of imports from China and Mexico, the decline of routine jobs, offshoring, other types of IT capital, and the total capital stock (in fact, exposure to robots is only weakly correlated with these other variables). According to our estimates, one more robot per thousand workers reduces the employment to population ratio by about 0.18-0.34 percentage points and wages by 0.25-0.5 percent.

https://www.nber.org/papers/w23285 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, but you missed the hundreds of words before and after the 17 word part you have displayed from the 1000 plus worded article. Including the findings from the report. Let people read the article maybe . It is interesting.  Including this part

"The industry most affected by automation is manufacturing. For every robot per thousand workers, up to six workers lost their jobs and wages fell by as much as three-fourths of a percent, according to a new paper by the economists, Daron Acemoglu of M.I.T. and Pascual Restrepo of Boston University. It appears to be the first study to quantify large, direct, negative effects of robots.

The paper is all the more significant because the researchers, whose work is highly regarded in their field, had been more sanguine about the effect of technology on jobs. In a paper last year, they said it was likely that increased automation would create new, better jobs, so employment and wages would eventually return to their previous levels. Just as cranes replaced dockworkers but created related jobs for engineers and financiers, the theory goes, new technology has created new jobs for software developers and data analysts.

But that paper was a conceptual exercise. The new one uses real-world data  and suggests a more pessimistic future. The researchers said they were surprised to see very little employment increase in other occupations to offset the job losses in manufacturing. That increase could still happen, they said, but for now there are large numbers of people out of work, with no clear path forward  especially blue-collar men without college degrees." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which gives an analysis of the affects of robots and technology in the workplace . Various views are accounted for including up to date research on this interesting topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For every robot per thousand workers, up to six workers lost their jobs and wages fell by as much as three-fourths of a percent, according to a new paper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For every robot per thousand workers, up to six workers lost their jobs and wages fell by as much as three-fourths of a percent, according to a new paper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Public Media Cut to Curb Critical Voice, Democrat Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about if the Python was on a motorbike? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Home Office accused of blocking UK public's scrutiny of Snoopers' Charter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mercury rises 4 - 6 degrees above normal across parts of India. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mercury rises 4 - 6 degrees above normal across parts of India </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadly heat stress is projected to affect hundreds of millions more people each year under relatively little additional climate warming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dem states pledge climate action in face of Trump roll-back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Confirmation bias is a type of cognitive bias that involves favouring information that confirms previously existing beliefs or biases. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some things that psychologists know, but most people don't? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which describes how big oil are edging Trump to stay in the Paris climate deal, despite many years of covering up climate change to its consumers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exxon Urges Trump To Stay In Paris Climate Agreement. Investigations into the companys history of supposedly hiding climate research found Exxon had allegedly played fast and loose with information concerning global warming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ExxonMobil officials told President Donald Trump Tuesday that staying in the Paris climate agreement would reduce climate change and give a boost to natural gas production. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exxon Urges Trump To Stay In Paris Climate Agreement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High concentrations of the stress hormone, Cortisol, in the body affect important DNA processes and increase the risk of long-term psychological consequences. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Mobile phones are 'possibly carcinogenic' according to World Health Organisation experts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Major TV networks spent just 50 minutes on climate change  combined  last year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-military and security firms oppose Home Sec in WhatsApp crypto row </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do climate deniers celebrate. By demanding more harm to the environment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More than 16,000 staff in the public sector and its agencies have been empower by Section 4 of the Investigatory Powers Act to snoop on peoples internet connection records.

And thats before the estimated 4,000 staff at security agency MI5, the 5,500 at GCHQ and 2,500 at MI6 are taken into account.

Thats according to the responses from a series of almost 100 Freedom of Information (FOI) requests made in a bid to find out exactly who has the power to snoop on ordinary peoples web browsing histories under the Act.

GCHQ, the Home Office, MI6, the National Crime Agency, the Ministry of Justice, all three armed forces and Police Service of Scotland all failed to respond to the FOI requests  so the total could be much higher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 16,000 staff in the public sector empowered to examine your web browsing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humans become heat stressed when the body absorbs more heat than is tolerable. If core body temperature rises just a few degrees above 37, deadly heatstroke can result. By using its cooling system  sweating  the human body can maintain a safe temperature even if air temperatures rise above 37. This mechanism works better in a drier atmosphere (which is why steam rooms feel hotter than saunas  even at the same air temperature). The heat index is a measure that combines this humidity effect with air temperature to provide a feels like temperature. A heat index in excess of about 40.6 is considered dangerous to human health.


Study http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/03/21/1617526114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadly heat stress is projected to affect hundreds of millions more people each year under relatively little additional climate warming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mental health problems rife among teenagers but teachers lack skills to help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 11:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Anti-Climate Crusade Can Still Be Stopped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 16,000 staff in the public sector empowered to examine your web browsing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The researchers carried out two new genome-wide studies and combined the results with six previous studies in a 'meta-analysis' -- involving in total 12,496 cases of glioma and 18,190 people without.

The size of the study meant it was able to detect 13 previously undiscovered genetic changes that increased the risk of glioma. These were found to affect a variety of cell functions, including nerve cell division, DNA repair, cell cycle control, protein production and inflammation.

Scientists at The Institute of Cancer Research (ICR) and their colleagues found that different sets of genes influence a person's risk of developing the two subtypes of glioma - glioblastoma and non-glioblastoma.

Study http://www.nature.com/ng/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ng.3823.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Largest ever brain cancer study reveals new secrets to inherited risk. One of the genetic changes increases risk by as much as a third and the others by at least 15 per cent each. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh i agree. And i respect your profession, more so than you can imagine.  Every person has bias and every media outlet report so called facts and opinions which cater for an audience. As you rightly mention. However would you not say, in this day and age with the emergence of so called 'fake news' it very important to present both sides, facts of the story/ topic before  honest scepticism should be established?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right i totally understand. However as you know as a journalist, when a counter argument comes through the one saying it needs to back that argument up. Newsrooms across the nation show this. Imagine a debate on tv between two people. One says a claim with his or her own stats to back it up while the other argues " not true ' without any stats. How does this look? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any information which relates to the article which shows these stats are wrong then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you read the stats in the article it is. As far as i can see the analysis in the article  is right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The people one dates share many similarities  both physically and personality-wise according to a study. It looked at the characteristics of people in more than 1,000 past and present heterosexual relationships. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Half in US Are Now Concerned Global Warming Believers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which shows the decline in coverage of climate related news across the country s networks. It highlights coverage network by network, despite a number of climate related events which happened across the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last Year, America's Major TV Networks Spent Just 50 Minutes on Climate Change. Combined. That's Is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barely half of Americans, believes climate change is both real and a major threat: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 13:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top US coal boss Robert Murray: Trump 'can't bring mining jobs back' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 13:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study 

http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms14611 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the links, and comments, fascinating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medications which reinforce the effect of natural brain opioids could be an improved way to reduce anxiety compared to receptor-binding opioid drugs like morphine, which have major side effects, says new research from the University of Sydney. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump Administration Is Silent Hours After Russia Arrests Hundreds Of Protesters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probe to be launched into alleged civil rights abuses in implementing Trump's immigration orders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A short but interesting article centred around a lesser known drug gang from Mexico which is stating its claim north of the border. The article contains facts and links which some may find wothwhile clicking on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the Little-Known Mexican Cartel Operating in California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankyou. By the way, i like your links. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thankyou. I will take a look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What job do you do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, thanks for getting back to me. If you come across something that would be great. I do find this topic  you mention of some interest. Thanks again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robots to take over 'nearly half' of UK manufacturing jobs by 2030 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, its very interesting and you touch on the topic how shallow people have become regarding politics. Also do you have a link to the conference paper or a link which highlights any relevant studies you mention please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Treasury Secretary Mnuchin says AI taking US jobs is '50-100 years away' -- but it's already beginning to happen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 13:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A low socioeconomic status is so damaging to health, it reduces life expectancy by 2.1 years. That's worse than obesity or high blood pressure and a consortium of global researchers are calling for it to be treated like any other major health risk factor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research has found that specific patterns of activity on brain scans may help clinicians identify whether psychotherapy or antidepressant medication is more likely to help individual patients recover from depression. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study sheds light on why people who attend spiritual retreats report greater psychological well-being, after finding that such retreats may increase levels of "feel-good" hormones in the brain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Violence breaks out at pro trump rally in California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Middle-aged white Americans without college degrees are dying at higher and higher rates, with drugs, alcohol, and suicide driving a dramatic increase in mortality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL 5.5 million American jobs were lost due to slower economic growth during the 2008 financial crisis than what was predicted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Businesses will defy Trump in low-carbon transition, say climate experts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, however we are dying everyday if we like it or not, leading right up to death. Do you mean the case of if you get a disease, or you have severe pain just before death? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study shows that the very religious and atheists are the groups who do not fear death as much as much as those in-between. The team found 100 relevant articles, published between 1961 and 2014, containing information about 26,000 people worldwide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump mixed-up the 2 most powerful leaders of the European Union </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millions of UK workers at risk of being replaced by robots, study says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millions of UK workers at risk of being replaced by robots, study says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millions of UK workers at risk of being replaced by robots, study says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Without Naming Trump, UN Acknowledges Retreat on Climate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Zealand's Kaikoura earthquake was the most complex yet observed according to scientists. Research has revealed at least 12 separate faults breaking during the quake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7,000 huge gas bubbles have formed under Siberia, and could explode at any moment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7,000 huge gas bubbles have formed under Siberia, and could explode at any moment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps pick for Secretary of Agriculture didnt mention climate once during his hearing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Irrational exuberance is when investors are so confident that the price of an asset will keep going up they lose sight of its underlying value. They overlook deteriorating economic fundamentals in the pursuit of ever-higher returns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conformity is not a universal indicator of intelligence in children, study says. Because innovation is part of the American culture, adults in the United States may be less likely to associate childrens conformity with intelligence than adults from other populations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arctic sea ice appears to have reached its annual maximum extent on March 7. This is the lowest maximum in the 38-year satellite record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exxon Ordered to Recover 'Wayne Tracker' Emails It Claims Are Lost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China: Authority blames climate change for record high sea levels. The administration said at a press briefing on Wednesday that marine disasters caused 60 deaths and direct economic losses of 5 billion yuan (US$725.95 million) in 2016. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New poll indicates that base supporters are harbouring doubts about Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exxon lost 1 year of Tillerson's 'Wayne Tracker' emails, N.Y. Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to a new study consumers who experience a loss of control are more likely to buy products that are more functional in nature, such as screwdrivers and dish detergent, because these are typically associated with problem solving, which may enhance people's sense of control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No embarrassment, quite the opposite.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your going by the premise that people are able to ride it out though. I think for the average person seeing those investments fade very much away triggers off negative feelings of what ifs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right but your going by what you think you would do everyone else should do. Good for you . Now what im trying to say is that people dont always go long, and dont always want to wait 30 years for investments to grow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right so your seeing your money decreasing. Now to think that stocks dont go into the red and people dont lose money on their stock while this is happening is nothing sort of make believe and panic selling doesnt exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Market psychology tells us that people dont know how much they can afford though, even when they think they are working wonders on the stock market. The same bullish attitude creates greed and bubbles. And when a bear market comes about people freak. Stocks going by the subject history matter ( 2008 crash) showed us that people and a hell of alot, dont do what you do. If people were that wise with money and know how money works  why people are in to historic debt at the moment? 

And yes investing in one company is madness. However when a crash happens and your spreaded over several companies and there flying off a cliff with your money, well thats a different story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right lets use the example you gave

"If I invest 10K tomorrow, and the next day that stock crashes to 10% of its previous value then the worth of my stock goes from 10K to 1K. Now I've already spent that 10K, from the moment it is invested it is gone, and even after the crash the amount I've spent is the same. "

Now what would happen if that very same stock you bought decreased by another 20% and then 6 months later by another 15% where would that leave you? and how would you feel about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, if you have the money to ride it out that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm right,  your going by the theory that people can hold on to stock which turns into negative value and crashes last a few months. You know this isnt the case.  Crashes and downturns dont always last for months. Hence the massive sell offs, where people can not hold onto their negative value stocks. We have plenty of evidence of this through history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Panic selling yes. Now , how do you know what individual people have as assets and money they can hold onto during a crash , and a depreciation of just one stock value alone to fall in double digits,  which can last years? Can you really tell me that the average person in America has disposable income and no debt, to be able to watch such a downturn?  Fair play to you to be able to ride out this kind of storm if you can. However market psychology shows us that people dont always operate this way. There has been a financial crash very frequently.   Market  go up and so they should come down. They will bubble and then they will pop. And the cycle goes on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When stocks go down so does their worth. And they decrease into negative territory. Now unless you have money in the bank which you can afford to lose while these shares go down and you can keep investing when they go down  thats fine. History tells you that the average person doesn't, hence the sell offs which lead to crashes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Zealand parrots provide the latest support for a popular theory of crowd behaviour. Scientists report that the parrots can spread positive emotion,  or at least behaviour that could indicate their state of mind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, i wonder how many people other than the riches man of a country can hold onto stock when it decreases significantly when they have a  huge downturn ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study has found that attractive people are more likely to get divorced. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reminder from history how markets can crash surprisingly, wiping out huge sums of money. This particular days trade lead to the financial crises and in turn led to austerity and hardship for millions across the globe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On 29 September 2008 from one single day $1.2 trillion had been wiped off from the United States stock market. It was the worst single day drop for two decades. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL On 29 September 2008 from one single day $1.2 trillion had been wiped off from the United States stock market. It was the worst single day drop for two decades. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study highlights how rising temperatures in the Canadian Arctic are causing the last remnants of the ice sheet that once covered much of North America to disappear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldman building robo-adviser to give investment advice to the masses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teens suing U.S. over climate change seek Exxon's 'Wayne Tracker' emails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young survivors have social difficulties years after cancer diagnosis a new study has found. The American Cancer Society (ACS) estimate that more than 60,000 young adults in the United States receive a cancer diagnosis each year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Natural Gas Power Plants Emit up to 120 Times More Methane Than Previously Estimated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inflation in the UK hit its highest level in more than 3 years as Brexit continues to bite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A detailed account how temperatures have risen across the globe and the consequences and impacts of these trends across the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Natural Gas Power Plants Emit up to 120 Times More Methane Than Previously Estimated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The record-breaking heat that made 2016 the hottest year ever recorded has continued into 2017, pushing the world into truly uncharted territory, according to the World Meteorological Organisation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you liked it. Iv just read your source. I like a quote, taken from the book 

It's no accident, I think, that tennis uses the language of life. Advantage, service, fault, break, love, the basic elements of tennis are those of everyday existence, because every match is a life in miniature. Even the structure of tennis, the way the pieces fit inside one another like Russian nesting dolls, mimics the structure of our days. Points become games become sets become tournaments, and it's all so tightly connected that any point can become the turning point. It reminds me of the way seconds become minutes become hours, and any hour can be our finest. Or darkest. It's our choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which shows the desperate situation in Mexico and how the government is viewed by families of the missing as a government of  not much more than apathy and lacking in concern for the state of the situation.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexican parents, not authorities, led search for drug-war mass grave. After a six-months plus investigation led by the families, government investigators in the Gulf state of Veracruz said on Tuesday they had found more than 250 skulls in shallow graves in a field </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The psychology class served as a control group. The two history courses incorporated instruction explicitly designed to cultivate critical thinking skills. For example, students in the history courses were taught how to identify logical fallacies - statements that violate logical arguments, such as non sequiturs.

At the beginning of the semester, students in all three courses took a baseline assessment of their beliefs in pseudoscientific claims. The assessment used a scale from 1 ("I don't believe at all.") to 7 ("I strongly believe.").

Some of the topics in the assessment, such as belief in Atlantis, were later addressed in the "historical frauds" course. Other topics, such as the belief that 9/11 was an "inside job," were never addressed in the course. This allowed the researchers to determine the extent to which changes in student beliefs stemmed from specific facts discussed in class, versus changes in a student's critical thinking skills.

At the end of the semester, students took the pseudoscience assessment again.

The control group students did not change their beliefs - but students in both history courses had lower beliefs in pseudoscience by the end of the semester.

Students in the history course for honors students decreased the most in their pseudoscientific beliefs; on average, student beliefs dropped an entire point on the belief scale for topics covered in class, and by 0.5 points on topics not covered in class. There were similar, but less pronounced, changes in the non-honors course.

"The change we see in these students is important, because beliefs are notoriously hard to change," says McLaughlin. "And seeing students apply critical thinking skills to areas not covered in class is particularly significant and heartening."

"It's also important to note that these results stem from taking only one class," McGill says. "Consistent efforts to teach critical thinking across multiple classes may well have more pronounced effects.

"This drives home the importance of teaching critical thinking, and the essential role that humanities can play in that process," McGill says. "This is something that NC State is actively promoting as part of a universitywide focus on critical thinking development." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all thanks for the interesting read. You do write well. Im sorry to hear what happened to you and your wife. It seems more than harsh what happened. All due to the fact that luck wasnt on your side. If i can ask, how has it changed your attitude towards relationships and trust in general? Well done for getting your contract. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Andre Agassi, one of the greatest players in modern tennis, has confessed to using the highly addictive illegal drug crystal methamphetamine while a player. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankyou for the information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, thanks for the insight. So you discovered locus of control. Did any books or research help you in particular? Care to share if they did. And thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A recent study by North Carolina State University researchers finds that teaching critical thinking skills in a humanities course significantly reduces student beliefs in "pseudoscience" that is unsupported by facts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Self reflection, what did you do to make this work for you? Any techniques? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone ever experienced a midlife crisis, or even witnessed one? How did it play out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP rep concerned about EPA chiefs climate comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican environmental groups want to temper Trump on climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which shows the trial and tribulations Andre Aggasi went through during his illustrious career. An open and refreshing article into a talented mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andre Agassi: One day your entire way of life ends. Its a kind of death." Every day is Groundhog Day and whats the point? I declined in different ways. In some cases it was lack of work. In others it was the self-inflicted damage of drugs. I found many ways to hurt myself'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to the Met Office, the average spring temperature has risen from 7.1 degrees between 1961 and 1990 to 8.1 degrees between 2006 and 2015. Scientists blame the rise on carbon pollution from vehicles, factories, farms and homes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feelings that others are dismissive or blame parents commonly cited as reasons for not accessing help for children and young people with mental health concerns, according to a new study. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your right, i linked the wrong article. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 12:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Statistics gleaned from national Government data reveals how 23 per cent of city youngsters are classed as poor, more than 4,000 children.

Worcester's rate is the second highest in Worcestershire, with only the Wyre Forest faring worse at 26 per cent.

It comes after a child poverty action group hit out over the rising tide of low paid workers, saying it is plunging too many families into problems.

Some city leaders are blaming it on the rise in poorly paid jobs, zero hours contracts and the benefits crackdown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany to Introduce Voice Recognition Software to Flush Out Bogus Immigrants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shock as figures reveal almost one in four Worcester children in poverty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK child poverty hits highest level since 2008 financial crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump administration's 'anti-scientific statements' alarm ex-energy secretary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New evidence suggests that one of the core functions of serotonin may be to facilitate our adaptation to changes in the world around us - which, in turn, may indirectly impact mood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NHS services face 'impossible' budget crisis, health trusts warn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 12:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Fears About Climate Change Hit Record High, Poll Finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
