<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4054</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there!  I had a really similar experience my freshman year of college.  I was isolated in a dorm, and for some reason every single girl hated me, took every chance they could to bully   harass me.  It got to the point where I was afraid to leave my room to go to the bathroom.

I spent endless hours on the phone with my parents   boyfriend.

I attempted suicide for the first time in my life that 1st semester.

If I could go back in time and give myself advice, I should have dropped out completely and sought psychological help.

Instead, I pushed through that first year (I did manage to switch dorms) and ultimately transferred to a new university much closer to home.

Is transferring an option for you or maybe taking a year off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  Tattoo envy is the highest compliment I can give! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Srs I hate that the red side is matte.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good Bye Horses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta be the K   A or possibly Somerset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gaaahhhhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll say this much: it's a uniform color.  Surprised the roots aren't more yellow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #ClairolShimmerLights4Lyfe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the kind of post that makes me want to scrub off my "work" face have some fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually love the eye makeup, including the mascara. Kinda looks like a tree line against a sunset? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I want that Kindle Case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Nanny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Srs I've been on a Twin Peaks kick   this pic reminds me of a gold BOB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The little baby bat
Screamed out in fright
"Turn on the dark, I'm afraid of the light!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His rationale is that we would pay tens of thousands of dollars for me to miscarry, and cause me to spiral down further.  I get his fear; it's not a sure thing, especially at my age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to read   reply to everyone because this has been really meaningful to me.  I really feel better and less along.  I have a friend that is active in the Big Brother program.  Maybe it's time I talked to him
about it.

And the grief counseling...that's such a good idea.  I feel like no one in my life allows me to grieve over these unborn children.  Hence why I dwell on it.  Thank you for mentioning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to run away to the west coast of Florida.  I know everyone makes fun of Florida, but I love the gulf coast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I'm a Star Wars girl :)

I definitely would benefit from purging.  We have a house and it's just filled with stuff.  Not on like a hoarder level but getting rid of clothes, shoes, bags, makeup would probably be helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm afraid of any psychedelics, I'm worried I'll be pulling snakes out of my eyes that aren't there.  I've heard the come down from MDMA is awful, which scares me too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Husband and I both want to move, but we feel obligated to take care of our families.  It just sucks.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!!!  Yeah I'm in an east coast city where everyone is all about their handstand/Instgram game which is the opposite reason I got into yoga. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
