<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3861</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure it isn't unless I missed something when I searched the sub to see if anyone had already done this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL it took the Catholic Church until 1992 to recognise that Galileo was right about the Earth going around the sun. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.nytimes.com/1992/10/31/world/after-350-years-vatican-says-galileo-was-right-it-moves.html

My friend brought it up to me and I honestly didn't believe it because it seemed to outrageous to be an actual thing. Looked it up. Found this from when it happened. Honestly, this alone is enough to totally discredit the church. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I think it's just part of who she is, she would never want to leave politics, it's what she does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck. I took it last year and got a 5, I know quite a few people who did. I hope you do well. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, flag of the United States if it were colonised by the EU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A northwest passage at last? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flag of death and despair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flag of a union between France and Libya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Conservatives see lead cut to 17 points - Panelbase poll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump cheerleads for the torturers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippines says Trump recognized 'great job' Duterte is doing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thai junta leader says Trump told him ties 'closer than ever' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why was there the Civil War? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, had Andrew Jackson been a little later, you wouldn't have had the Civil War. He was a very tough person, but he had a big heart. And he was really angry that -- he saw what was happening with regard to the Civil War. He said, There's no reason for this. People don't realize, you know, the Civil War  if you think about it, why? People don't ask that question, but why was there the Civil War? Why could that one not have been worked out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winners and Losers of the Spending Deal (Spoiler Alert: Trump Lost) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard about this. I never really liked her, but lately I've come to realise that she's one of the only sane normal Republicans left. If another Republican comes after her, they will almost undoubtedly be worse. It has to be a democrat. The district is heavily Hispanic, but mostly Cuban, and they don't particularly swing democrat like other Hispanic demographics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He quite clearly doesn't know what he's talking about on issues like healthcare. He probably genuinely didn't know what was in the proposal because he hasn't read it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reince Priebus: Weve Looked at Changing Libel Laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Spicer facts' and weird handshakes: 100 days of Trump in memes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help Wanted: The Trump Administration (Still) Has Some Openings To Fill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservationists alarmed by Trump Interior nominee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish you good luck.

As far as you can tell, is the strike working? Do you think it will apply enough pressure to get the government to back down on the pension reform and the anti-labour laws? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmakers worry Trump immigration orders weaken protections for sex crime, domestic violence victims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I've ever seen anything like it. This isn't just rare, it's one of a kind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Obama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much of the Republican Party in the south still supports efforts to segregate schools and keep white affluent students in better conditions than black students. This case has made it more clear than ever. This is just more to show that racial equality really hasn't yet been achieved, and modern civil rights activists need to be vigilant to try to counter legalised segregation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Tax Plan Would Shift Trillions From U.S. Coffers to the Richest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Trump may never get his wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three dozen House Democrats urge Senate to reject Trump's pick for Army secretary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's important to remember that California has the GDP of a large country, so it's not quite the same scenario as in smaller states.

That said, this being done by the federal government would absolutely be preferable, but with the current administration, that's not happening any time soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I know there are actually places worse than Kansas. It was a joke, meant to poke fun at Kansas for being generally bad compared to the rest of the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. California has the economy to sustain universal healthcare. Hopefully they can get this to work smoothly and serve as an example to the rest of the country that single payer works, since a multitude of other countries doesn't seem to be enough to convince some people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god, what could be worse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN/ORC Poll: At 100 days, Trump approval rating shows no sign of growth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's 'big' tax plan has few details, no cost estimate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump starts review of federal 'overreach' in education </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Latest Obamacare Repeal Plan Exacerbates the Political Problems of the First </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Efforts To 'Drain The Swamp' Lagging Behind His Campaign Rhetoric </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China launches 1st domestically-made aircraft carrier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he'll struggle to find something racist to say about William H. Orrick III. He'll have to try something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. judge blocks Trump order threatening funds for 'sanctuary' cities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confederate monument furor could signal GOP's fate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French election: Le Pen says, 'I am not the candidate of the National Front' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malcolm Turnbull to hold first meeting with President Donald Trump in New York </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Political Press Favors the Rich and Famous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 12:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grow a fricking spine and tell him no, you're not going to "compromise". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
