<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9880</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 14:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, being a girl doesn't mean that you have to be scared and I get that just because you're a girl, you don't want to alter your life etc... Maybe you can take care of yourself. 
But maybe acting sensibly and accepting help, doing what the police suggested, could protect someone else in the future who might fall victim to this guy. Maybe now he will leave you alone, and target someone who is an easier victim.

Girl power is great, but sometimes there's more to these things than your own pride.

EDIT: I am female, and I may have typed this a little more angrily sounding than I meant too. My bad x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 14:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when your dad married Rita, there was no family present? (who were a bit surprised? Keeping it all the family and everything.)

I still think that your dad is the dodgy one, otherwise it doesn't really make sense.

Plus I'm confused about the timeline and age discrepancies. Unless I'm just being thicko. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 13:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, cool! I thought I missing a cosmic secret for a second! ;p  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 13:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have a link to paradise pines please? 
I've read the one the op is talking about, but I need more!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 00:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was truly amazing. Bravo.
I'm sure Dan knows that you've done your best by him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 23:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 01:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I'm going to look up op and see :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 01:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but there wasn't really much to give an impression of anything other worldly though. Creepy maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 09:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this a first part?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 08:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. She was quick killing a dog and two adults in the space of a clothes change! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 08:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the only other female mentioned so far is your mum who died in a car crash. So, maybe your mum didn't die. But that would mean that she has been possibly hidden away for over 10 years.

Edit: my comment on part one is still relevant. Yes!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 08:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly my thoughts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 00:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are really that attractive, why feel up other people's boyfriends? That's just rude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 16:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are literally two outcomes to this...

A) Rita is killing teenaged boys as a sick justice for her brother dying (or maybe she killed her brother as well) and the teeth are a memento. She works late because she still has ten boys alive somewhere. In this case your brother is next, and you and papa are both in danger. 

B) your dad killed these boys and hid the folder. This means that Rita has finally tracked down the murderer and that's why she is so weird and cold towards you. 

Either way, you need to call the police right now. Not calling the police is the dumbest thing ever, you are potentially putting your own life at risk and a potential murderer is getting the chance to keep that evidence hidden.

Please engage your brain, there is no good reason not to call the police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 12:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, if the dog is pretty old.. It's probably going to want a new body soon. I'd be really careful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 03:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alena turning like that just came out of nowhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 03:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does sound an awful lot like there were experiments being conducted underground, what with all of the locked doors. Although, it could have been that the blast opened up a passageway into the home of these creatures.. Being that this wasn't strictly nazi territory at the time the experiments would have started. (I don't think, forgive me history lessons were many years ago).

The latter kind of makes more sense, on account of the soldier thinking it was just a standard bunker to hide inside.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 02:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, bad idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 19:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What started all of this? What is wrong with your family, and will it happen to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 18:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your survival skills aren't the best are they? All these stories about the deep web, and you tell the nut cases that you're calling the cops... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 15:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a size five! I'll have you know that my feet are perfectly average size thank you.

But I'm sorry about the dog :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 15:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's way ominous, just for a virus. It makes it sound like he must have done something really serious. Unless the creator of the virus just likes to screw with epileptics lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 11:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, did you find the dog? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 11:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realistically though, thousands of people must download the same files. Why would anyone specifically target you? 
You can't undo what you've done seems very odd considering all you've done is commit copyright theft... Unless this is some new government initiative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 06:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the pictures are the same for me, is that my app messing up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 06:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dark lord finally made himself known, the first true apostles were contacted via memes. Praise him!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 00:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I didn't say it was. I just said that the baby was an innocent that didn't deserve to die. 
(And what if the woman didn't know he was a rapist or a cheat anyway, she says it's her fault for being with him.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 00:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, why would you pretend to be infected like that? Bad idea central! Jack got over it really quickly though lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 00:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 18:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, taibh is the younger brother? Does he suffer the same illness? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 18:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's possibly true as well. I think I just got caught up on not 'giving it a chance to live'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 18:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that, but at least you know that it wasn't 'real'. If that makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 12:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These kind of people are the worst. Seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 12:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that sucks. But you should definitely go back to Disney land, it's apparently really good and you shouldn't let your life be controlled by the actions of other people. 
I'm sorry that you went through that op. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 09:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, why was the dad so against making scarecrows? At first I thought he knew something about what might happen, in some form. But apparently not. The spiders controlling the scarecrows is a crazy thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 03:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't you go home at all, to see if Jane left without you? I don't understand where she would have gone. And this Is set in the future, so how do we know about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 03:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know of any weird animal diseases that could this much concern?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 03:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if the woman didn't know? You killed an innocent baby. Tbh, you should have just killed him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 03:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She aborted the rapists baby, that was inside another lady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 03:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow. 9 months? He literally had a tumour baby. Poor guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 02:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lavender smells so bad though. I'd rather be lonely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 02:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, Mrs greaves for the chop and she didn't even do anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 02:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judging by the fact it's trying to lure you away, and it's not coming too close to the cabin.. The dream catcher might be what is keeping it away. A local might have hung it up as they knew someone was staying there at the time? 

Dream catchers are usually good, but if they include bones it's usually a bad sign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 02:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of pleased, but kind of not. Stories like this make me question what is right and what isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 02:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you are in charge of security... But when shtf you wait in your car? Im not sure if you work security or not, it wasn't very clear. But you should probably call the police, or look in through a window maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 02:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I might if someone was creeping outside my window at night haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 02:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Peter :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 20:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest loudly telling this apparition to leave. Sometimes it works. I feel like you unknowingly allowed this thing to latch onto you, and it wants to feed from your grief.
Keep us updated op, best of luck and I'm very sorry for your loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 20:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure that the house just doesn't have new owners? If so, they probably think that you're the creepy one haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 16:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved this! Id like to believe that he wasn't crazy. 

(Ps, which is the 5th dimension? Is the 4th time?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 16:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that... This is one of my worst fears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 16:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kinda don't get it.. But I kinda hope you get a bit of crap from her for beating kids lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 14:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should pay some tweaker to burn that place that down to the ground lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 01:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second this. Mediators are great people to have around, it's so much fairer to have an unbiased third person involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 01:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad has carers come in to help us look after him, believe me, we understand just how hard it is to get good ones and keep them! It's awful. My dad can't walk and suffers pain all the time, but you wouldn't believe how badly some of these people can be. It's such an awful shame that your inlaws are doing this to you. I hope it all works out.

And honestly, this does belong in this sub. Things like this have made me toss and turn all night irl. Social services (English cps) wanted to take one of my sisters away once because her autism made her run away from home once to find my mum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 22:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that you told him that this isn't relevant to a cv. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 21:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well. At least you didn't die... I don't know how you lived with that image for this long though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 11:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, she must have been the one that you saw on your solo camping trip. Maybe she tried to have a normal life with you, but realised that she would have to go home... Hence the deep thought about 'the future'. She might still visit? 

Sorry for your loss op. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 09:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always choose tails, weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 01:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I hit a deer, I would seriously be bawling my eyes out omg. I don't get how some people don't get bothered by it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 01:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um. Is this being told from the point of view of like, one of those weird birds? How does a baby grow twice the size of an adult and you don't question it? And sure, babies die all the time... But usually you report it, or get sad! Lawd help you with this one op. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 23:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda ruins the mood with the little extra at the end. Authors are supposed to stay in character aren't they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 09:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have called the popo, and all the poor kitties!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 09:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have thought so too.. But he says that it's the yick that does the hollowing, because he's worried that it will do the same to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 09:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But tipped them off to what? Lots of people have car crashes, they don't all get recruited. I'm just curious as to what was different about you. Did they know about your Ryder already? 
I just feel like there are parts missing to what you're telling us, some things just don't quite fit together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 02:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 02:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you think it was living in a can of coke in the first place? IT probably needed a new host :/ 
Good luck op... Maybe try staying up, waiting for it to go hunting and then run like the wind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 02:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not finding answers, you are special because of the Ryder. But how did the organisation know that was inside you after your crash? And the sudden change in your Ryder hasn't been explained, and probably won't be because he is now just part of you and doesn't seem to talk anymore. :( I've read all the parts so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 02:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sam has a Ryder too, the wife of Osiris. Otherwise known as Isis, and we don't know yet if Sam came back from her coma as herself or Isis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 18:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, what made Ryder go from screaming about killing the child in your first case to a relatively eloquent talker? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
