<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4640</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 06:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cool. And very typical of Apple. They don't bother to even send a reply. Treating their developers like shit for years now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 07:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually not ironic, because that's exactly what the "Stop a Douchebag" movement is trying to improve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 07:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obvious solution: Kill all the snails! We could start by pouring poison into the oceans, maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 07:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never read something this stupid before. You think wsxcderfvbgtyh talked about the existence of the rock we call earth? Of course he meant the life on the planet. Not the planet itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 07:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG, so the range extender isn't actually for extending the range. Who would want to buy something like that then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 06:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joking or not, but interestingly, this is exactly how the [BMW i3 Range Extender](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BMW_i3#Range_extender_option) works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 03:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even find it that way. Maybe your website is pretty new, and nothing has linked to it yet? Especially not with that text? Anyway, I think this question would probably better in r/webdev or similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 03:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even cops actually don't have the authority to do this in this case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 06:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for posting, this indeed looks interesting. Wanted to buy it, but the page says I have to wait some hours until it is available. D'oh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 10:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like some over-the-top polished puzzle game with story. I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 11:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  suck comparisons


Hope you meant 'such' comparisons. Hope my post doesn't suck that much. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JavaScript vs C++: Creating the same 3D game in both </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 09:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 14:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why you usually wrap them in leather. Simple but effective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 13:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Richtig. Die WKO vertritt eigentlich nur mehr sich selbst, aber kaum noch die Unternehmer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 13:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a completely different question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 06:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the time when CNN was news channel. And a good one. What happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 14:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That happened in 2012. Not everyone had phones capable of recording HD video back then, especially with such bad lighting.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ygritte from Game of Thrones - how strong is she really? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 08:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, and we need people serving us cookies and tea while we watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 11:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I understand, they use bot steam accounts to do the transfer of the digital items between people and the website. Once the bot has the item, the website has it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 13:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the usual candidates like Bullet won't work for you? You should be able to model a humanoid using a few primitives and connect them using joints in nearly any physics engine out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PostCollapse gameplay (alpha) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 13:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 08:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being not from the U.S., I'm not sure how the law works there exactly, but shouldn't those people be denoted? So that a prosecutor can start working and see if a crime happened and those people can be punished? Wouldn't that be more effective than creating all those ranting videos about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 13:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But there is no need to be an asshole. Some people prefer not to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 18:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you would say all the games on Steam are not successful?


(My engine is named CopperCube, btw. 99 euro, 3D. Some would say it's in competition to Unity, but it works nevertheless.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 05:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right. Fortunately for OP, people bitching about the price of $20 are likely not his customers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 04:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who is making his money with a commercial game engine, I want to say that you could not be more wrong. Let pawbyte charge as much money for his engine as he wants. Saying a game engine must be free today because there are two engines which are perceived to be free is strange. His engine has unique features, so he should be able to create a business model around it as he thinks would work.

 
It's like saying that there are many successful free-to-play games, so you are not allowed to create a non-free game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 08:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe some people are interested in this? Just use the Up/Down vote mechanism. I think it was made just for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 09:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **PostCollapse**  
New this week: You can now water your own planted plants with a watering can. And fill it up in rivers.  
[Screenshot - Watering Can](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CkFwCQ2WYAAlBuw.jpg:large)  
[Screenshot - Generic Gameplay](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CfAcRC6UMAASL-v.jpg:large)  
[PostCollapse](http://www.postcollapse-game.com/) is a post apocalyptic survival simulator game running directly in the browser. Hunt, farm, fish, gather stuff from the collapsed civilization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 06:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CryEngine has been [put on GitHub](https://github.com/CRYTEK-CRYENGINE/CRYENGINE) and is open source as well, now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 04:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, good to know. Thanks for fixing this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 14:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would require an updated version of the game engine toolset, which the user would have to upgrade to. But there is no way to make it work with an existing version. That's also the whole point I was trying to make with the Android SDK, btw: Why updating something which works  flawlessly for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Android SDK Manager is now blatantly lying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 09:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Get Your Apartment Off the Grid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 05:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 11:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Hope there are no people walking past your back yard. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 10:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the feedback so far, especially from r/web_design. If you are missing something, or have an idea what we could add in a future release, just let me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RocketCake 1.2 released (free responsive web designer) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 10:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CopperLicht 1.12 released (open source WebGL library) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 08:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 04:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For my projects, I'm using Anim8or. It's small, fast and simple to use. Good enough for creating simple low poly 3d models. And it's free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 05:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Numbers found on the web vary, but they have a market share of abround 89% for desktop systems. That's more than enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
