<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6186</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Through hate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Maul survived his 'death' at the end of Episode 1.  My head canon is that he stayed alive through sheer hatred.

He's actually become a much better character in the Clone Wars and Rebels then he ever was in the movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They seem to be building towards a final conflict between him and Obi-Wan at the end of this season.  I'm guessing they are preparing to finally kill him, but I like Maul so much now, I don't want to see him go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars: Rebels - Maul pleads with Ezra to join him. I can't express how happy I am how these shows have turned Darth Maul into a fantastic character from basically a blank slate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeff looks like he's dying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 06:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone ruin this for me and tell me the ape was trying to kill him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neato, that's actually super close.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best airsoft fields near Atlanta? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of getting into Airsoft.  I know there are plenty of indoor arenas all over the place, but I was wondering if there were any huge fields around where there's a bit more space for open play.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.... IS BULLSHIT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They plan to wrap it up in 2-3 seasons I think I heard, but momentum has been faltering for AT for a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, nerf guns eh?  I've heard about LARPs using those... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is some Jimmy McGill shit right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is Simunition? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Airsoft abides by an honor system, so unless you're a huge dick, it's never really an issue when people are hit.  They just call it out.

Airsoft is also more realistic I guess?  I know there are some paintball guns that look real, but airsoft really has cornered that market. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this miniseries is good.  I'd really like AT to end on a high note instead of just fading into the background.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of like how The Witcher was big for Poland...  Big enough to gift Obama Witcher 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's apparently huge over there...  I'm not sure, but I remember seeing photos of like a STALKER parade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, forgive my ignorance.  I'm not in the software development industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such is life in the Zone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'd be a great trick to pull on people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got back into them because the mod release of Call of Chernobyl.

It really breathes new life into the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every year, a group of S.T.A.L.K.E.R. (video game) fans in the Ukraine gear up and LARP the game with airsoft guns and costumes. The result is probably the closest you'll get to being in post-apocalypse fiction... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They could hypothetically take their code to another studio and just replace the assets right?

Or does MS own the code too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes me wonder...

Have organizations ever considered donating game consoles to Nursing Homes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the player in the video says that...  But he's fully in character through the video, so it's hard to see what the real event is about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 01:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to find any English info about the meetup, but it has been around at least since 2008.  I found an article about it with some amazing photography:

http://englishrussia.com/2008/05/29/the-real-stalker/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it wrong to think that they're both pretty bad people?  Kim is right, Chuck made him that way...  If anything, it's established that Chuck resented how people liked and doted on Jimmy despite being a scamp, and that led him to pushing back against Jimmy's wishes to follow his brother into law.

Chuck is also right about how Jimmy is going to get people hurt, as he already did in Episode 2.  One of these days, the way Jimmy shrugs off corruption is going to fuck up everything...  His career, his relationship with Kim, and his friendships. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OWR makes them feel so good though.  Is Arsenal really worth it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this would have been my dream game if it wasn't a grindy-destiny like...

I wish they just tried to make a AAA Day Z clone with heavy focus on Survival gameplay.  Or a STALKER clone...

This game reminds me of a fantastic comic I read through high school and college called DMZ.  It was set in a demilitarized zone of Manhatten during America's second civil war, and I got some serious vibes of that comic from this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't see Azazel on the list of checkboxes when you start.  Is it a mod? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such is life in the zone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's Azazel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get a few stutters here and there, but mostly it has been smooth.  I think the stutters is the game spawning content across the small maps.  You just need to give it a sec and it'll even out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I installed a HD Skins pack for the character models...  But I can't find it ATM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one problem I have is that it's pretty crashy.  Only once or twice every couple of hours though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you play Arsenal with OWR installed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This mod seems more focused on the small, individual experiences.  I've had moments where I'm shopping for weapons while Duty is invading Freedom's base.  Neither shoot at me, seeing as how I'm in good standing with both of them.  You can enlist people with you who will follow a basic set of commands and travel between areas.  They die pretty quick though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone else been playing S.T.A.L.K.E.R. Call of Chernobyl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call of Chernobyl is a mod for S.T.A.L.K.E.R Call of Pripyat: http://www.moddb.com/mods/call-of-chernobyl

After reading about CoC being the top mod of the year in 2016 for ModDB, I reinstalled Call of Pripyat to see what all of the fuss was about.  I was surprised to find a fun, immersive, and engaging time sink of a game that randomly spawns you in the Zone with whichever alliance you want, and then lets you off the leash.  

You basically decide how you want to live your life in the zone from that point...  I personally have been taking on assassination contracts from whomever will pay.  There's not much depth to it, and the story (if you wish to follow it) is light, but there's something about just wandering the Zone which really scratches an itch I've been missing that only the Stalker games seem to satisfy...  You get these moments of emergent story that can only happen with how the AI behaves and how you interact with its systems.

I've installed a couple other Quality of Life mods too, and it makes the game a lot better.  First off: http://www.moddb.com/mods/call-of-chernobyl/addons/original-weapon-renewal-3 

This mod reskins and changes all the weapons in the game, and it makes gunplay a lot more fun.  I haven't tried the Arsenal Addon yet, seeing as how I think it conflicts with OWR.

Seriously, if you've been missing STALKER like I have, this mod is worth checking out...  It combines all the areas from the three games into one, traversable open world separated by loading screens.  It makes me really wish for STALKER 2... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were these Chicago Improvisors the One Shot Crew?

They do a podcast called One Shot where they play different tabletop games, and they also do a podcast called Campaign that's based around the Star Wars FFG series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 20:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting how Xcom 2 is his top choice when Giant Bomb had Xcom 2 in one of their most 'Disappointing Games of 2016' list...

I guess the game is still divisive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 09:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't the Daily Show make fun of this last time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe that's why it was an Xbox One player then...  I doubt the data mining scene is as big on the console side of things than the PC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seriously gave me shivers.

This is incredibly awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 22:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares?  Who honestly cares if Screen Junkies or Collider liked it more than they should of?  Everyone and their mother loved the film Nightcrawler, but I hated it.  That's the nature of subjectivity and criticism.  Go after the studios, the film makers, and whoever else you want...  But attacking the people who have a different opinion than you seems mean spirited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 22:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so this is getting ridiculous...

I didn't like Rogue One that much either, but there seems to be a lot of venom coming from RLM that their attributing to 'rabid fanboys' and 'paid reviewers.'  Mike, Jay, Rich...  Seriously, not everyone who liked the movie is being paid off.  Saying things like 'Star Wars fans aren't true fans..." or whatever they were trying to imply in earlier videos is elitist and really immature.  I know this is 'satire' but they're sending a very clear message with it, and with the amount of content they're putting out, they're trying to make it seem like there's a fight that just isn't...  There...

And it's not even like Rogue One was horrible enough to justify all this.  They all kind of agreed it was ok, but now that they've been challenged it seems like they're jumping into the batch that say Rogue One was completely awful.  It's like the backlash is warping their opinions a bit.

In my opinion, the one video was enough.  I agreed with most of their points on the movie, and it doesn't bother me that others liked it more, but to get this worked up about it is just childish and bitter.  I've would have liked an ACTUAL podcast discussing other films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to attempt to run a game of this tomorrow with some friends.

Hope it goes well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this one about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah...  I started D D with 5E, so I never knew the struggle of 4E.  Now that 5th is out, why do people still flock to Pathfinder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hearing good things about Dungeon World. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always hear people either play D D or Pathfinder...  What makes Pathfinder different? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite tabletop RPG that isn't D D? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I've argued about this, but the 'Holocaust' in a historical sense was distinctly the deaths of the 6 million jews, gypsies and homosexuals.  The Russian deaths were grouped into the general war crimes statistic of 'civilian deaths,' even though the Russian Civilian death count surpasses every other nation who participated in the war.

I think the reasoning of this is because the Russian death count is hard to measure...  There's no way of knowing how many of those were deaths by their own government.  I think that the 10 million or so Russian Civilians should be grouped in with the Jewish losses of the Holocaust, and they should bring the number up to the 16-20 million mark.  

Hitler's 'living space' plan was in part based around anti-semitism, so those people died as a result of the anti-jewish rhetoric of the Third Reich just as the Jewish populace of places like Germany and Poland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being this upset about someone elses opinon must be exhausting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you buy the Sprawl?  Or is it a PDF thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [KekRaptor] Battlefield 1 Fans Outraged Over Christmas Truce (Seeing how Verdun does this every Christmas, it really says something about BF1's player base.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 20:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 18:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, it's on the Criterion Collection... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That shit was better than TFA, and I loved that movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Day After - This scene always unsettled me... How the people were vaporized to skeletons and how the mushroom clouds almost look like monsters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 08:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember seeing this scene on Comedy Central when I was like 13, and laughing so hard my mom thought something was wrong with me...  I don't think I ever laughed as hard as I did at a movie then this scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 20:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting way to convey the connections...  Kind of erratic, but it fit after a few seconds after getting used to it.  I forgot Tarantino wrote the first draft of Natural Born Killers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HE JUST LEFT

WITH LIGHTS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 16:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably treasure chests... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 16:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a better quality trailer with no links that pop up in front of the action 2/3's of the way through? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 06:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the reason why human drivers are going to be gone in about ten years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 06:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I GOT ENEMIES I GOT I GOT ENEMIES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 05:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought the Ultimate Edition on sale.  I'm wondering how much content I'm getting with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 01:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your work has that Pixar look to it.  I'd apply as a storyboard artist! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 16:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought we addressed the reasoning for the plans...  The Death Star is a HUGE base.  You can't just say, "That tiny exhaust port over there!' and know what people are talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 22:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, can someone ELI5 why the UN is such a useless entity?  If I could vote the UN more power, I totally would.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if she cares?  I mean, yeah she gets a paycheck, but I bet after the response from Arrival and Nocturnal Animals, Adams could sit squarely in the indie circles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 16:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They probably should say it...  Josh Trank got exiled from Hollywood for talking shit.  If enough people were brave enough to say something, then maybe the studios would listen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you quoting SoA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 05:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'll run it in the United States, but I really want to focus a campaign on a road trip.  My hook would be that my group is a bunch of rebels and punks who steal a car and decide to run away across the country in a beat up, POS 80s car.  They'd run into car troubles, pick up shady drifters, find weird sci-fi occurrences out on the road, hide from cops, and all sorts of shenanigans.  I like the idea of my kids going from place to place rather than being stuck at school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I would if I could.  That frosted white hair is amazing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you see it already? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just started reading it.  It seems really fleshed out for an Alpha!

I heard its mechanics are based on Dungeon World.  Is that true?

I also wish the PDF had a chapter select area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 07:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> basically westworld </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Westworld experience... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 07:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good flapper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manchurian Candidate (1962) - The Assassination Scene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 21:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 05:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I HOPE THAT OUR FEW REMAINING FRIENDS

GIVE UP ON TRYING TO SAVE US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 00:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good idea...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I did like it, like I like some other fan productions, but that doesn't mean it doesn't have large problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely disagree about Tarkin.  And Jay is totally right, if that shit looks distracting to some people now, imagine how it'll look 30 years from now.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Rogue One is the greatest Star Wars fan film ever made."

That perfectly describes it with all its negative and positive connotations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best part of these is always Jeff beaming in from the digital ionosphere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A good ref sheet for new players on what the skills, dice, and symbols are. I'm including this in their character sheets. Found on the back of the beginner game! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 03:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 18:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Marlon Brando. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looked REALLY bad... And I know it's popular to rag on CGI, but this felt nearly as bad as the prequel's overuse of them. I thought we established with Superman Returns that, no matter how good technology is at the time, CGI use of an actor's face is destined to look bad years from now...

[Tarkin and Leia really took me out of the film. I really don't see why they couldn't have recasted Peter Cushing's character with someone else, like they did with Mon Mothma. Hell, Charles Dance (Tywin Lannister) would have been PERFECT as Tarkin, but they instead choose to go with this shitty Shrek tier CGI that is gonna make people laugh at this film years from now. If it looks bad NOW, it isn't going to look good later. Plus, I for one believe that using a dead actor's face without their living permission is a really low way to go... Disney should know better.
Overall, I found Rogue One to be a competent film, but held back by some really dumb choices and pacing problems...](#spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 19:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matthew Vaughn at his best.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has the game been patched to a working state yet?

I want to eventually play this, but I figure I'll do it when it has been fixed and has some significant DLC or Mod support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 17:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they didn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Heh, Deadspin is taking the piss out of the New Yorker Review...](http://theconcourse.deadspin.com/how-the-fuck-high-was-this-new-yorker-guy-when-he-wrote-1790058128?utm_campaign=socialflow_io9_facebook utm_source=io9_facebook utm_medium=socialflow) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone's been listening to Crimetown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't the reason he's using spyglasses because he doesn't want to be bothered filming?  You need permission to film inside businesses, and I doubt he gets those for every Goodwill he goes to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading a comment on reddit years ago that went like, "We are so tired of him." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]Russians of Reddit, what is your reaction to the U.S. election hacking allegations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad the election is over so she can focus more on the issues and politics of this new administration.  I love watching Full Frontal, but at times she seemed to lean to hard into her pro-Hillary bias.  I am reminded of the ONE instance where Bernie shut down Hillary during a primary debate, when Bernie didn't let Hillary interrupt him, and Bee skewed it in such a way to make it look like Bernie was talking down to her.  Stuff like that was incredibly frustrating, because I do believe that Samantha Bee's show is fantastic and she's one of the best female comedians working today.

I also think ALL of these parody shows need to scale back on the 'man-on-the-street' interviews that they continually do to point out the stupidity of the Trump Supporter at the rally believing everything the man says.  It has such a mocking, arrogant tone at times, despite the opportunities for genuine comedy out of these responses.  The focus should be more on the man and his actions, not the people.  Grouping all Trump supporters into the people who go to rallies and yell OBAMA IS A MUSLIM is not representative of his base, and the people who don't believe the more extreme shite that spews out Trump's mouth feel as if these shows are targeting them as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a fyn fact! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did it feel to like a M. Night movie?

Did you feel filthy afterwards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so weird seeing Fassbender and Cotillard in this.  They are in their prime of their acting career, and they have to know what a risk video game movies are.  Christ, they were in Macbeth only a year ago together, and that was something comparable yet wholly different from this in terms of tone.  

That scene of the buggy chase was actually pretty intense though, and the shots set in Spain look fantastically rich.  I'm super curious to see if this will be the video game movie to break the cycle.  It would be hilarious, seeing as how the Assassin's Creed franchise is associated with a yearly release cycle reminiscent of a product over art.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 16:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sudden unrelated racism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "TruthArbiter" 

lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear this game is getting better with every DLC.  I could seriously see myself buying a gold edition for 20 bucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how you force a society that's half against renewable energy to start using renewable energy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does Ace Combat follow an over arching story?  Could I jump into 7 with no context? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 10:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing this whole scene here didn't happen in real life though, correct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 21:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WE DID IT BABY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> G-G-G-G-GHOOOSTS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 17:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was his joke about killing Ted Cruz? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 06:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I am too tired for revolution...  And we've walked fucking miles." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 06:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The earth is dying.  Prepare." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 06:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Lonesome Dove right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 06:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, this question gets asked every post on here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the south and we've never seen anything like this.  Georgia has had a month+ drought that just ended today, and the northern part of the state has been getting wildfires left and right.

This FEELS like Global Warming...  It's Global Warming right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 21:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am nowhere near 50K, I think I'm more around 12K, but I still wanna keep writing into December. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut up, they have big ass omelets.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 18:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't it turn out to be both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 07:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "HE SAYS WHAT WE'RE ALL THINKING."

Is Cave Johnson Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 05:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain Iranian film to me?  It seems like these are issues the regime would look down upon, but it feels like Iranian expression is as open as the best American filmmakers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 03:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4chan accidentally memed a man into the white house, so I'm wondering if they've had any self-reflection at all in the separation between the online world and the real one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Groundhog Day - Phil and the homeless man... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 17:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 22:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm particular to the Mongols one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eurogamer - Fallout 4 one year on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 00:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think so.  I think they do general repairs during September because every shrine I went to was under construction.  There was no one around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they show this trilogy tonight.  I'd love to see it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took this back in September when I visited Japan.  I remember being curious about how the bodies were buried in this type of graveyard, because space looks very tight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 22:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seemed like they adjusted framerate at certain moments where what was happening on the screen was ahead or behind the music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 06:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ever visit Japan, seriously take some time out to go to Osaka.  If you were to compare it to the US, it's like Atlanta while Tokyo is like New York.

It's a bit sketchier than Tokyo, with the open prostitution district and the charming motorcycle gangs roaming around, but it's an awesome city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 06:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how Jeff is so DTF with anime bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I get it.  Your name is KindaConfusedIGuess, so these posts are a part of it.  You're in character!  Pretty good troll bub.  I almost believed GamerGaters were STILL pissed about Nintendo, Zoe Quinn, or whatever they care about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like you set your browser to fuccboi and started typing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime someone says the phrase, 'SJW' I completely tune out of what they say.  It completely negates everything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you all feel about Vice's Waypoint? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 04:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not often we see a new games media site with significant support appear.  Vice is a huge media company, and it seems that in its slowly building empire, it wants to divert resources into specific journalistic areas.  That's all great and all, but we're in the middle of this 'death of traditional games media' phase.  Many people now get their games information from Twitch streamers, youtube reviewers, or by general word of mouth.  In this transitional age of independent games journalism, continuous questions of integrity and streamer culture, can a site like Waypoint truly thrive?  Or is it doomed?

It has very prominent names behind it, like Giant Bomb vets Austin Walker and Patrick Klepek, but is that enough to raise the site to the heights of say a Polygon, Gamespot or IGN?  And are those names even relevant anymore?

I'd love to hear what you all think.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 03:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They sure made The Comedy Cellar look a lot bigger and brighter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 03:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You WALK to work?!"

People seem blown away that I walk an hour to work and back instead of sitting an hour in traffic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, he laid waste to dollar store Biff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul Ryan, Mccain, and I'm hoping not Romney...

All cowards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 18:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they say premiere, do they mean a trailer or the actual game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 18:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Republicans proved this election they are collective bitches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SEO Plays can be pretty funny too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Car Boys, Monster Factory and SEO plays are their only videos I watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 00:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This video is really sad with the context of the last few weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 20:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 10:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious how people on here feel about Elusive Contracts?

I personally love them and find myself on the edge of my seat with every attempt.  I don't even mind failure.  It's an immersive experience that the devs didn't have to put it, but still did.

On the other hand, it is very anti-consumer...  People who wanted to wait to buy the game when all 6 episodes released are SOL.  But...  I dunno, I'm just not that mad about it.  It's a weird, interesting idea within a format that makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
