<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8314</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am Filipino. I would use Lechon Kawalli as a fat bomb daily if I could.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 16:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you me? I had these sentiments exactly this morning. I broke into the 180s this week, but this was where I started several years ago when I got myself down to the 150s. It's bittersweet indeed, but at least on this WOE, I can celebrate my little victory with bacon and cheese and not feel like I'm being counterproductive. 

  I'm in for the long haul this time. My goal weight is just the beginning, not the end. We've got this!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 06:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [NSV] while out running errands, I hear DH laugh to himself. I ask what's up. He says "Your jeans are looking loose and keep sliding down. Keep up the good work!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 02:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, savings! I go to sbux, and I no longer get a pastry or cookies to go with my grande cold brew. I stopped buying frozen food entrees for the convenience and bought meat/veg/cheese in bulk and meal prep instead. Eggs are super cheap, and easily portable for an on the go snack or meal. Also, I get full so quickly I anecdotally seem to eat a lot less! Thanks, Keto!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 02:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also did a Costco run yesterday! Got the Cauli rice, a bag of super greens (spinach, kale and Swiss chard),  2-18 pks of eggs, and the box of Kerrygold butter! (3 blocks for 7.39 iirc.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LPT: Try throwing some baking soda into the water when you boil your next batch. Makes them way easier to peel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOWAD! Gallon of water a day. I don't even have to force it, I'm always thirsty! Plus you get those extra steps walking back and forth from the bathroom all day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
