<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9063</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This pink cabinet has seen some shit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 18:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 17:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You see how fat he is at the end? No chance he's running  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 04:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow wish the Canadian dollar wasn't so shit... 99$ for early enlister with prime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do I suck at hardline? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 04:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picked up hardline for 5$ while it was on sale and I seem to suck alot more than bf4. It seems like none of my teammates play the objective or listen to squad orders. I die alot more than in bf4. Has anyone else from 4 tried hardline and feels the same or is it just me. Glad I only picked it up for 5$ as I'm only really having fun in the campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 23:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Rooney should of been off way earlier, played terribly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 22:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imbrahimovic is 10 years older than messi...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 15:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A guy in my class was on the waitlist and started 3 weeks into classes once somebody dropped out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 02:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool that answers my question! Wasn't sure if refrigeration was required to work on ac units or not thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 00:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didnt necessarily mean working with refrigerant. As a g3 you can do anything a g2 can do under direct supervision. Do the same rules apply as a refrigeration apprentice? Can I trouble shoot or change parts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I work on ac units without my refrigeration licence? Ontario </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 15:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In school right now planning on getting my g3 obt3 and eventually g2 obt2. Wondering what il be doing in the summer though. I want to get into a refrigeration apprenticeship but il need time to pay off my current schooling. What will I be doing in the summer with a g2 licence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 14:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also this is a maschine sub, the studio is a much better unit, but nobody on here is going to recommended the touch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 02:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably it, plus the 100%xp weekend. Didn't even realize it was up for 5$ Ive had it for a year  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 00:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this... To bad it was after I did the molecular level mission.. I even tried talking to danse and was able to get through a few dialogue points but then he'd revert back to "check your fire we've got hostiles". To bad I didn't see that before as I think I'm pretty much screwed.. Oh well. This is only my first playthrough so I guess there's always next time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 23:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PS4] Can't connect to any server, put in massive queue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 23:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else experiencing problems joining any servers? None of them are full but even trying to join a 22/64 server I get put in a massive queue of like 40 people? Maybe they are having server problems today? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 20:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hdmi splitter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 00:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol no worries, you just said you'd be back in a few, just wondering what happened  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 23:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 23:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can still use any mpc with fl  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 22:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize that kratom is a leaf that can be smoked right...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 22:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you located? I'm in Canada so I use a canada based vendor called Terrabotanicals. They have by far the best prices and quality kratom, my bags are always a little heavier. Before that I was using kratora just because they came in a nice bag, 8/10 quality and was cheap. But they were us based and I suffered on the shipping. I would recommend both https://www.terrabotanical.ca and http://www.kratora.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 22:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my point.... You rated dagga 2/10, why would you continuing using it if it doesn't work. I do the same with something that gives me effects that I like and subsides my cravings  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 18:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly the strains are alot similar to weed. Certain ones have different properties, but kratom is kratom. I like maeng da and borneo white. Maeng da is supposed to be made from the highest quality leaves taken from many plants, so it's powerful and high quality. Some strains are more stimulating and others are more sedating. There's tons of info over at /r/kratom as I could go on all day but this really isn't the proper sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 13:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not use something that works if you're going to do that then? I use kratom when I'm quitting. Keeps me satisfied  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 02:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bruh I can almost guarentee king krule has a live drummer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 00:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big ups on camel crusher, gonna check that out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 00:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally rule number 1... First time on any subreddit you should take the time to read the rules. No one's gonna listen here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 00:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you looking for specific ones? Just did a google and probably 10+ came up... If you stop by ottawa there's a couple good ones that's where I'm currently living  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 15:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respect, usually reddit disagreements turn hostile quick. Glad to see some people on here are reasonable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 06:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All that article shows is him defending himself. It doesn't actually show any numbers or sources. I'm sorry but you're not changing my opinion with just that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 04:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao the ama he tried to do is hilarious https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/45m1hl/i_am_3x_grammy_awardwinning/ 

On a real note fuck him, I had a hard time watching this knowing what happened. He has good advice but i can't stand the guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 02:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did not read the full comment...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 01:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if it's a free download their isn't any legal issues he'll run into. removing the download will solve all problems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 21:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it's illegal, no nobody's going to come after you for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My buddy got a personal happy birthday video from the boys in Barrie! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 06:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 16:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea there's really no point in having over 4 or 5 kits you're never going to use them all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 07:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try running maschine in 32 bit (or 64 bit if you usually run it in 32). I've heard of lots of people having problems with vsts in maschine though. None of my ozone vsts work in maschine 64 and 32 bit. I usually just bounce to FL for using those vsts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 22:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big sinkhole downtown </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 22:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a massive sinkhole in downtown Ottawa yesterday...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 00:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you make him sign a contract? If not you're fucked... I treat my music the same as my drugs, money always comes first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 04:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem bro!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 04:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't think so, all usb carries 5v and 1 amp. Can't get any more out of it regardless of what it's plugged into </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 21:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup same, don't know what it is about that shade of green that annoys the crap outta me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 17:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I have the option to go with the railroad, minutemen or just do it myself too but I wanted to start the brotherhood before finishing the main quest. I guess it doesn't really matter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The molecular level brotherhood of steal bug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 17:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So earlier on in the game I tried to do the fire support quest where you have to help Danse with ghouls. After killing all the ghouls (searched the surrounding area for a while) and trying to talk to him the only response he gave me was "check your fire, we've got hostiles". After some research I found this was a common glitch but couldn't find a ps4 fix. I just left it for then. 

Now I'm trying to complete the molecular level quest by going to the brotherhood of steel because I haven't even met them yet. This requires you to go to the Cambridge police station and help them just like before. This time I was able to talk to him and answer like 3 questions before mid sentence he yells "check your fire, we've got hostiles" all over again. Does anyone know a fix for consoles to this glitch. This is my first playthrough and I don't want to do it without ever meeting the brotherhood. 

Thanks to anyone who replies.


*LOL spelt brotherhood of steel wrong in title by accident, sorry on mobile  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 04:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ordered the cheapest one I could find from China off eBay. Cost like 5 bucks and has 5 ports. I gotta use one to plug into the wall so it has enough power but hasn't failed me in a year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 20:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feeding them generic 3-1-2 fertilizer from home depot in regular cheap soil with perlite. First grow ever, bought regular seeds and ended up with two females! Been lst since around week 2-3. They are coming along nicely if I do say so myself. Burnt one of them slightly on the last feeding and had to flush them yesterday. Gonna wait a couple weeks before switching to flowering nutes as I want them to get bigger. Any tips would be greatly appreciated!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 01:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks that worked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 01:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other is already built </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 01:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only need 1  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 00:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to get 10 power for the radio transmitter at the castle but I can't place more than 1 generator. I have enough materials and I already made one so its not like I need a perk for it. Anyone else had this problem before? Playing on ps4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 21:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you have the legit instrumental it needs to be a really high quality version of both the instrumental and the original song or it won't work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 20:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lord finesse, mf doom, Mac Miller, havoc, Erick arc Elliot, kanye west, RZA, large professor, Dre.....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeech Beats - Buttered Popcorn [Hip-Hop Instrumental] (2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 19:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 18:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new hitman game isn't necessarily open world but the levels are massive. They're doing a periodic release so you can just buy the first episode and see if you like it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 18:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ocarina of time. Probably beat it 5 or 6 times, I do one playthrough a year usually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 00:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because it's not really funny or creepy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 23:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get some lock nuts, they have a nylon interior to prevent loosening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 23:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea figured this out pretty quick. Super annoying when you're trying to resample and you forgot all your samples are in stereo and they just cut out. Now everything I do is in mono  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 22:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the biggest complaints fl since the original release. I'm finding it really hard to believe you haven't seen any other threads on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 22:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I didn't purchase the full game right off the bat. I've only purchased sapienza and Paris an and I don't think il be buying Marrakesh after hearing about it. Il save the 12 dollars and maybe get the next one. Depending on the reviews </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 21:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still innocent until proven guilty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 21:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one's saying it proves anything, he's still innocent until proven guilty. Its just a reaaaallly strange coincidence. This guy literally said "you'll see in the next few months" 

Edit: damn I rechecked that link and I see what you mean. Mad people are saying that this means it's true which is bullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 19:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda crazy how he only got charged with aggravated assault and not attempted murder. He's already out on a $5000 bail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 19:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need more info on Freddie dawg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 18:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that guy is Austrian too... This really doesn't look good  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 17:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup that's the reason I don't take that. Still have a whole bottle left. Plus I like to drink so that's a definite no-no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 17:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gets alot quicker once you're used to all the controls on maschine. You can do everything from the hardware (assuming you have mk2 or studio) which really cuts down on the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 17:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duplicate the pattern and delete the snare in one. Then just go pattern 1  pattern 2  pattern 1

You can do pretty much anything in maschine, just maybe not in the same way as you would in another daw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 17:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't use ableton so I'm not sure how to explain this but check your polyphony settings and set it to legato. You should be able to adjust the time it takes to slide. Then again I don't use ableton and I'm at school right now il try to find the settings for ableton.

Edit:  https://www.reddit.com/r/ableton/comments/2v6oke/how_do_you_glideslide_808s_in_ableton/coex2jv simple google search yielded many explanations 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 02:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take this how you want but personally I think you need to cut down on the sidechaining  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sp 404 tips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 02:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have any tips for making beats fully on the sp? I have the og and I use the resample method (if that makes sense?) where I end up having my full beat on one pad in the end. Problem is all my beats I've made so far come out very boom bap kinda style, that would have someone rapping over it. I want to progress into more intricate lofi beats that are more melodic and can be listened to without a rapper. How do you make your beats? Right now I'm using drum breaks because I find it hard to lay down my drums. Just any tips would be appreciated, if this type of post isn't allowed in this sub I have no problem with removing it. 
Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 22:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gud said in his ama he has spent a long time (years) refining his sound by layering tons of different synth sounds from different synths  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 22:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is yung guds signature synth. Spend 13 years playing around with layering different presets and you'll get there. This same exact question is asked probably twice a year and it belongs in the how do I make this is sound thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 20:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I don't know what this guys talking about. Tons of the best rappers also produce alot of there stuff. Ex. Mac Miller, j cole...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 20:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maschine comes with premade projects already. Look under projects  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 20:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol everyones giving you advice you're just not taking it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 14:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man, if you are looking for more help and guidance on moderation check out /r/petioles!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 05:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have to do anything, I've just read from a few different forums and lots of people say that the extra 6 hours doesn't give anymore growth and it's better to just save on the energy bill but everyone's different. I just feel like any plant would benefit from atleast a bit of dark time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 02:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool! Autoflowers are so interesting definitely gonna have to play around with my first couple grows and see what they like!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you guys switch light cycles for flowering? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 02:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys first time grower here. I'm growing 2 northern lights autos right now and they are around 32 days in. I started them out on 24/0 because I didn't have a timer with a ground in it but switched to 18/6 after 2 weeks. Around a week ago (day 25-28) they showed signs of being females. A week later now they have lots of hairs and are smelling nice. I'm continuing with my veg nutes untill they stop growing vertically but I've had a hard time finding info on weither it's a good idea to change the light cycle to 12/12 or not? What is your guys recommendation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 16:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a difference between buying actual likes and advertising. Advertising requires people to actual click the link and physically listen to it. When you buy likes it's just a bot and they usually get removed after a month or so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 14:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't purchased Marrakesh yet and I probably won't. Just gonna wait for the next one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 04:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If youre ever in the Ottawa area hit me up, there's a couple  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 04:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn really appreciate this brother!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's your submission? Oh wait......  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude thanks so much, I was missing out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 17:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Depends what you want to do
2. Lol you can make any type of beat with audacity if you want
3. It's just as hard as learning any other daw, actually probably easier seeing as it's not a full daw
4. Personal thoughts are I never use it, I just bounce my stems 
5. They are very different programs and should be used together for maximum potential 

Most of these answers have been discussed many times, you could have gotten them yourself doing a bit of research.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 17:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be that guy man, you could of taken less time to check the sidebar then creating this post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 16:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to sampling and hit fade out. It will create a zero cross point for you without changing the sound of the kick,  usually. Some times it may lower the volume by a bit depending on the sample  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 16:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When this happens use the fade out setting in sampling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 15:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup today is day 8 for me and I cannot believe that I would of smoked atleast 60 bowls by now if I was continuing my habits  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 14:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Head over to goodwill bro! I've picked up multiple turntables and a couple cassette decks for 10 bucks each  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 13:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a cassette player. It will have audio out cables </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 05:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I appreciate you trying to help to man!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 05:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought so, guess I just got unlucky. They're built by Yamaha so they really are quality units. There is a local guitar tech who told me he'd look into replacing the inputs for me so I'm not completely out of luck. Don't think il be going back to Steinberg after this though. Looking at the focusrite 4i4 for my next one if I can't get it repaired.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 04:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shit thanks my dude I appreciate it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 04:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man this guys post history is cancerous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 04:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of them... Ive sampled a few video games too using an hdmi audio splitter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 04:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> links down really dont wanna miss out on this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 04:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that is hella tight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 04:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a save button for a reason...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 03:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your first answer completly contradicts it's self

1. When the agency contacts you about a job, they usually give you a very high level explanation. 

If they give you a very high level explanation then why would they only tell you it's a laundry detergent commercial and that's it? 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 03:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup coffee is great in the morning. I'd never have a coffee past 2 or 3 cause that might keep me up. Even then, some l theanine, Valerian and melatonin with a nice run before bed and I sleep like a baby.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 23:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ended up just scrubbing it down with a soft brush and diluted dish soap and baking soda. Then rinsed it out with a couple spray bottles of water. Let it dry and I'm gonna test it out soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to clean coils on a portable ac? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 21:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I'm a hvac student currently in second semester but we haven't gotten to refrigeration yet so try and bear with me. I picked up a 10 year old portable ac that wasn't working fully for really cheap just kind of as a project. The girl said it haven't been serviced ever and that it would run for about an hour only and only cool at average temps. I figured it probably just needs a really good cleaning. Fan runs great and everything. Only thing is the coils are literally welded into the tank of freon and I have no way of detaching them for easy cleaning. What is the best way to clean them without fully removing the coils?
https://imgur.com/a/wyp5u </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 17:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got off the phone with Steinberg. The guy is saying it's a hardware issue. They only have a year long warranty and I bought it 13 months ago so I'm pretty much screwed. Yamaha is the company that repairs them and it costs around the same price as I new one to repair so it looks like I'm upgrading my interface.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 17:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got off the phone with Steinberg. The guy is saying it's a hardware issue. They only have a year long warranty and I bought it 13 months ago so I'm pretty much screwed. Yamaha is the company that repairs them and it costs around the same price as I new one to repair so it looks like I'm upgrading my interface.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 17:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 17:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay thanks!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't talk to Preston about anything other than the castle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 16:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys this is my first time playing fallout so be nice. I'm on my first playthrough and I'm at the point where Preston wants to retake the castle. I keep telling him to wait because I have alot of quests stacked and want to level up more before attempting. Only thing is most of my quest require me to report to Preston at the end and he won't talk to me about anything other than the castle. I've also read about glitches where you can't talk to Preston after completing this mission so now I'm a bit worried about doing it. What do you guys recommend I do or has anyone else had this problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 15:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude I've really been in a slump lately with everything not just beats. This is really helping with my motivation. You have no idea how much I appreciate this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 08:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not easier to do either. Do whatever works best for your work flow. Every beat is different for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 07:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spotify isn't going to get you new listeners. Spotify us for people who already have a fan base and people searching for them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 07:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a load of bullcrap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 06:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the processor ram won't really help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 06:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a sample. You can try phase cancelling out the beat but you'll need a high quality instrumental </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 04:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to do that for the meantime but my laptop only has one audio jack. Not sure if it's in and out or just out. 

Edit: I know my equipment (sp 404 and turntables) work because I can plug then into other speakers and they work fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 04:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That happened to me before sapienza released, didn't know that was patched. Good to know  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
