<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5756</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 15:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was that kindergartner who said she wanted to be a teacher when she grew up. Great teachers inspired me, and I envisioned myself as Miss Honey from Matilda. Being the teacher's pet and helper only confirmed how much I loved helping others.

My mom was a daycare provider, so teaching kindergarten came naturally to me, but I've taught K-5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 00:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband usually cooks for both of us and his doctor has him on a low cholesterol diet, therefore I too am on a low cholesterol diet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 17:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been drinking more soda lately, so that may be part of the problem.  I have also been avoiding meat and eating more fish as part of a lower cholesterol diet.

My eczema right now shows up as small dry patches on my legs, but I haven't noticed anything on my face.  Is it possible that my eczema is somehow connected to me having more pimples on my face? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 17:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an appointment with a dermatologist, but the soonest appointment I could make was in January so I have to figure out what to do until then.

My pimples themselves can be itchy, so I worry that if I'm not regularly cleaning that they will only get worse.  Do you recommend that I cut out certain parts of my routine?

I don't feel more stressed, but my diet has changed.  My husband just found out he has high cholesterol so we've been sticking to foods with low cholesterol, but I'm not sure if that would affect my face at all.  I have been drinking more soda lately and am trying to cut that out starting this week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 06:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had eczema all of my life.  Although I haven't had flare-ups in a long time, I used to get it on my eyelids.  This means I am especially sensitive to products.

After reading some posts here, I think I have oily but dehydrated sensitive skin.  I have never had this much acne before, and I have had some of the same pimples on my face for the past few months - they just seem to spread to other areas instead of clearing up.  I tried using the Retin-A Micro my doctor gave me a few years ago, but that doesn't seem to help either.  Nothing seems to work and I'm tired of having skin that is itchy and hurting all the time.

My current skincare routine:

Morning:
- Aveeno ultra-calming foaming cleanser
- Aveeno ultra-calming daily moisturizer with spf 15

I currently wear Bare Minerals liquid foundation and concealer during the day while I am at work, but am also open to suggestions for other make-up brands.

Night:
- Aveeno ultra-calming makeup removing wipes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Acne] Help! My acne keeps getting worse and I don't know what to do! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 06:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 20:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Platform: PC

Region: Southwest US

Name: Art3mis#1626

Rank: 41-44

Heroes: Lucio, Ana, D.Va, Zarya, Winston

Looking for: Semi-serious casual, and decent competitive players (I've been burned by too many bad teams as support when I solo queue) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone resigned to teaching at a crappy, unorganized charter school for 7 years I'm happy to say that I'm starting my first district job this year! I just signed the contract and got my ID yesterday. Only downside is I'll be teaching 3rd instead of Kinder like I really wanted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 15:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get a lot of love as Lucio either, and I'm normally on fire for 75% of my Lucio games so I know it's not me. People don't understand that Lucio only heals within his LOS and can only boost that so much. It's a different kind of healing than people are used to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 15:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will become a surrogate parent to many of your students this year, so you need to stay patient and consistent. Expect students to be dependent on you, but encourage independence. Their joy and love is infectious. After their initial shyness wears off, your days will be full of fun - teaching Kindergarten is like a marathon and you need to pace yourself or you will burn out.  I taught Kindergarten for three years and loved it.  If you have any questions or need any tips/resources, I'd be happy to share even more with you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 06:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing PC FPS (CS:GO, TF2, LFD2, Overwatch) for 6 years and it is a crapshoot.  Sometimes I play random servers, but for the most part I play in servers where I know they are cool with me.  I get to know the guys and have lots of fun.  Even on servers I've vetted there are trolls, but I have learned to shit talk with the best of them.  The mods tend to help out a lot in that area too.  Of the games I've played, Left for Dead 2 was the worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please critique my resume! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 21:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teacher Resume - Please Review! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 21:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Are you OK?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 17:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed a strange phenomena at work lately. When I'm feeling really down, most of my co-workers leave me alone. But on my better days, more people come up to me and ask if I'm OK. I can't figure out why this is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
