<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3285</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 16, and here because I'm Catholic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, man. If you ever need to talk, message me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't get passed 1 day and relapsed 5 times. Now I'm on my 16th day. It just takes some conditioning, you got this man! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the seven mortal sins is lust dude. I would assume that masturbating to naked women on the internet or in your thoughts falls under that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I see. You confused me when you said "religion encourages extremism" which is not always the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol okay, friend. Look up the cosmological argument and come talk to me when you learn that atheism is impossible and a deity/deities are necessary. Plus, not masturbating is not extremism, it's self-improvement. It's addictive behavior that does nothing to really benefit you besides give you a slight decrease in the chance of acquiring prostate cancer. Meanwhile, the benefits I've experienced from not masturbating have been nothing short of phenomenal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or... you could just be not masturbating for religious reasons like I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relationship Advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A relationship is the congregation of 2 people who express affection towards each other. With that being said, there are too many people who are searching for someone to "complete them" or "make them whole". You can't make a relationship with one person and then someone who is half broken. The relationship isn't whole, if the people in it aren't. 

Fix yourself. Make yourself the best you can be, and never stop working for perfection. Do everything in your power to become the best and most fulfilled you can. Not only will your relationship with others improve, but your relationship with yourself will improve as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look man, causing yourself harm and possible death is not going to help. There's nothing more pathetic than not only masturbating but then killing/cutting yourself. Just ignore it, and get back on the horse. You didn't lose any progress, you're still breaking the conditioning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that way too. You got this man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem man. You got this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to fap 2-3 times a day. I was depressed and honestly a loser. The best way to stop is to immediately engage in other activities as soon as you get the urge to masturbate. I will either immediately start helping my mom with something or start working out. That way you know that you're at least not going to fap for the length of whatever activity your engaged in. When that's done, move on to the next thing.

I'm 16 and on my 14th day BTW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people recommend weening off PMO by doubling your streak until you no longer get the urge. I was wondering if that's the correct thing to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Should I Quit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My current streak is 14 days, which has been my longest thus far. My last streak was 7 days. I'm not sure if I should  relapse now and then increment my way to success or to just go cold-turkey. What do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man, you too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point. We've only been dating for a few weeks now. It's probably best to wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I Tell My GF About NoFap? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend is incredibly supportive and really cares about me. More so than any other girlfriend I've had. I'm wondering if I should tell her that I'm combatting my masturbation addiction. What do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats man! Keep it up :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean man. I've had to delete almost all my social media apps to get rid of the temptation. It sucked, but it was worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
