<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7451</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forget Conway--Trump's tweet clearly demonstrated a conflict of interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not afraid to represent us.  They're representing the people they really view as their constituents: their campaign donors.  

If you're poor/middle-class of any race, you are not the person they care about representing.  They'll only appeal to your biases to get themselves elected.  

Then they'll pay off the people who really matter to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My impression is that the GOP-controlled Congress either is scared of Trump or complicit in his obvious interest in looting the nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Every opportunity people in the US get to show Trump that the Presidency isn't his family's cash register strengthens the nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appreciate your perspective.  Thanks!  However, I posted it as it was written in the article.

In any event, some might say that *fighting* vs. *"accepting ...and dealing"* is a matter of semantics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submission statement: I found this to be a fascinating study of the practicalities of military logistics, as neatly summarized by this comment (from the article): 

*We dont talk about climate change, Capt. Dean VanderLey told visiting journalists in a tour of the base before the election. We talk about sea-level rise. You can measure it.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's Still Fighting Climate Change? The U.S. Military </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave it to the US military to be practical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's Still Fighting Climate Change? The US military. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submission statement: I found this to be a great study of the challenges facing the U.S. government today--in particular, its focus on the real power that Congress has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to stop an autocracy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot to quote in this article.

*But the US Congress is a tiger that we pretend is made of paper. It is, at this point, taken for granted that congressional Republicans will protect their co-partisan at any cost. It is, at this point, expected that they will confirm Trumps unqualified nominees, ignore his obvious conflicts of interest, overlook his dangerous comments, and rationalize his worst behavior.*

*That expectation  and the cowardice it permits  is the real danger to American democracy.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 05:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way in all those stars that intelligent life doesn't exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How big is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He forgot to add *so-called*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silencing Elizabeth Warren backfires on Senate GOP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically we can't believe *anything* this administration says. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 11:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CIA!  Not some made-up gobbledygook.  Fascinating.

[How Mars lost its atmosphere and became a cold, dry world](https://arstechnica.com/science/2015/11/how-mars-lost-its-atmosphere-and-became-a-cold-dry-world/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warren finds voice, support after formally silenced at Sessions nomination debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 11:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Road rage driver runs over man twice then is held at gunpoint by victim's passenger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's really amazing to me is that, after I finished each one, I had no idea what had happened in the book I'd just read, but it didn't matter because I loved them all anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The GOP is so out of touch with normal Americans.  It's just astonishing.

Both parties, really, but the GOP's the one in charge now.  And facts like this: *even in a GOP Senate where DeVos rained nearly $1 million* just make the whole situation almost unbelievable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly.  We'll keep you in mind!  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So weird.  Mavs in particular you'd think Cuban would be all over helping out their sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your response! If it happens again I will try the battery calibration trick.

Unfortunately mine is an 8.9, which Amazon doesn't sell anymore.  So I'm kind of out of luck if the problem is the device.

I'm thinking maybe one or two of the apps which kept running in the background drained it.  (I'm suspicious about one in particular.)

Weird that it didn't happen with an earlier version of the OS.  But I updated to 5.+ because I wanted to run Google Play on it.

If this 8.9 continues to have the problem, though, I guess maybe once and for all I'll switch over to my Samsung Tab S2.  It's actually been pretty great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My biggest hope is that we'll bring in some good people and (not necessarily related) that the team finally will support us.  No guarantee either of those things will happen.  But. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We could, but the numbers of responses we'd get almost certainly wouldn't come close to even a significant fraction of the number of users.  It would be next to impossible to ascribe any meaning to the nonresponses (as valid arguments would exist on both sides as to what silence meant).  

So I don't see how we could read a vote as meaning much of anything, except as to what the people who voted thought.  And we're seeing that here (believe me the mods are paying attention to this thread).

Problem is we're in a semi-public forum.  The nature of these forums is that people should be allowed to participate, as long as they follow our rules.  So it's hard to justify not wanting to let others know that the sub exists on the sole ground that an increase in numbers may lead to junk posts.

Need to realize, too--I've been a mod of this sub since it had just a few hundred subbies.  And a number of those subbies are still around.  In my/their views, a lot of the content that we get now--and which we routinely remove--consists of exactly the kinds of junk posts that everyone's worried about.

So we *already* get that stuff, and the mods *already* are griefed for enforcing rules against it.  

There's no obviously good outcome for this situation.  So we're thinking we might as well look on the bright side, hopefully bring in some articulate users who have something worthwhile to contribute (because we have, after all, gotten a *lot* of users like that over the years as the sub has grown).  And we'll keep removing posts that violate our rules (along with subbies' help in identifying them).

As /u/superkerfuz says, if ultimately it seems like it's not worth the effort, we can change our minds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As usual, SK, an articulate explanation of exactly what I think of it.  I don't know how you do that.  Thanks, bud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard to say.  Quantity kind of includes everybody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've been discussing it, yep.  As the sub has grown to this point, we have seen a significant change in the quality of posts--only some of it for the worse.  So we're pretty sure we'd continue to have to work against the relatively contentless posts.  

That said, it's not entirely clear that our subby count would go up that much.  The number of subs involved is pretty high--much higher, say, than the number of defaults, and much closer to the numbers represented in /r/all.  Also, the subs chosen seem to be based on some sort of rate of growth system; as this sub tends to grow after successful seasons, it's possible that others would surpass us and we'd get bumped off the list.

If our inclusion presents significant problems, we'll reconsider it.  But in light of the Cowboys' worldwide popularity and brand recognition, it doesn't seem right to decline.  

Also, it's all of the mods' opinions--and probably everyone in our sub's--that the Cowboys are missing great opportunities by continually choosing not to work with us.  One possibility is that as a result of increased exposure, the Cowboys finally will stop comparing us to Facebook and start trying to support us, the way so many other teams do their subs.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Words matter: Trump's loose talk about Muslims gets weaponized in court against travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the White House gets rattled by people making fun of it, what is it going to do when it faces a real crisis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 11:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi--did you ever find a solution to this problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the purpose to evenly distribute the many different classes of population?  If not, what is the purpose?  I understand the purpose may be to minimize the risk of gerrymandering, but in what way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll keep you in mind.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize foreign emoluments, and not the numerous other acts/statements he's made which indicate clearly his willingness to disregard the stability of the United States, are the basis of this call.  

But 2 weeks in, whether due to treason, incompetence, disinterest in representing this nation as a statesman, or sheer weakness of character, it's obvious that Donald Trump is not fit to be President.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Announcement: /r/cowboys has been selected as one of the subreddits to be featured in Reddit's new "logged-out algorithm", intended to replace the default subreddits as a kind of /r/all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More info is available [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/modnews/comments/5sghb1/introducing_popular).  One result is that we expect the sub to grow significantly over the next few months.  The Dallas Cowboys are one of the most recognized brands in the world.  (And are, of course, the greatest NFL team ever, with the best fanbase of all time.)

We love every one of you guys; you have made us what we are.  Still, as mods, we couldn't be more excited about the opportunity to meet new fans, to consider and discuss all the exciting new challenges the team faces.  We remain convinced that we have the most knowledgeable and devoted Cowboys fans on the net.  

We look forward to the change.  Let's all welcome our new subbies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is insane and needs to be impeached. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of when the Packers let Favre go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any team that adds him will get better.  He is a great player. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't.  But I will.  Thank you for the suggestion!

I finally gave up on the 3rd-generation device, got a 4th-generation one, and the various Google files installed just fine on the updated fireOS (version 5.whatever).

I guess too I could try resetting the device to factory default; that might work.

Or maybe I could find the 5.x version of the OS as a side load somewhere!  Might not be easy to find that though.

A real shame Amazon didn't support the 8.9 better/more.  A nice device.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House turmoil rankles Washington more than Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read an article months ago suggesting that Obama should have appointed Garland anyway, on the theory that the Senate waived its obligation to advise and consent.  As usual the Dems showed they weren't willing to go as far as the GOP in risking a Constitutional crisis.  But there was a fair chance that argument would have won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My opinion: Trump needs to be impeached, as he's a threat to the stability of our government. Seems as though his every public statement calls his loyalty into question.

Shame on the GOP-controlled Congress for its complicity in Trump's attacks on the legitimacy of our intelligence services, our judiciary, and the rights and privileges of our citizens. It's clear most of them are too terrified of Trump's supporters and too greedy in the pursuit of their own agendas to challenge this would-be tyrant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 14:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My opinion: Trump needs to be impeached, as he's a threat to the stability of our government.  Seems as though his every public statement calls his loyalty into question.  

Shame on the GOP-controlled Congress for its complicity in Trump's attacks on the legitimacy of our intelligence services, our judiciary, and the rights and privileges of our citizens.  It's clear most of them are too terrified of Trump's supporters and too greedy in the pursuit of their own agendas to challenge this would-be tyrant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's most bone-chilling tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 14:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 14:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ultimately a filibuster will fail, but I'm all for the Dems obstructing as much as they possibly can, particularly in this instance, as how the GOP handled Garland definitely seemed to me to be improper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 14:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally no.  Supreme Court Justices only have to recuse themselves from cases in which they have (or may be perceived to have) conflicts of interest.  But Gorsuch doesn't seem to have any conflict of interest in deciding whether Trump's immigration ban is Constitutional (compare to whether Gorsuch would be allowed to determine whether *his appointment* is Constitutional (or if he actually was on a Bench in a lower court considering the Constitutionality of the order)--then he'd have to recuse).

Think of it this way: if appointed Judges had to recuse themselves any time a case involved the office of the person who appointed him/her, there'd be no court capable of determining any suit against a governor in the many states in which the highest courts' judges are appointed.

[Here's an article](http://blog.constitutioncenter.org/2016/05/when-do-supreme-court-justices-recuse-themselves-from-cases/) briefly discussing when SCOTUS Justices have to recuse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump May Be the First Test Case for His Own Supreme Court Nominee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 11:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and almost certainly.  Trump has no idea how to govern and President Bannon wants to be in charge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Concur.  This is just more of the same old--people tying aging players to Jerry.  As remarkable and beloved as DWare is, he's a 34-year old linebacker coming off back surgery.  Still, if he's willing to sign a team-friendly deal, even part-time he'd be an upgrade over almost everyone on the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Constitutional crisis? What happens if Trump decides to ignore a judge's ruling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take it somewhere else--see what they say.

As an example, I have a 2006 Prius with 77k miles on it--its brakes/rotors *never* have been replaced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He really does.  It's obvious already he's unfit for office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A brief history of all the things so-called President Donald Trump has called 'so-called' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man parks truck on top of car to defend family in road rage incident, police say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right!  I deleted all my misinformation.  Thanks for helping me avoid giving out bad info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> South Koreans, man.  If it weren't for [Train to Busan](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pyWuHv2-Abk) and maybe [The Host](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lKZ55OiHl9w) I'd think it's a pretty cool place to live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: deleted everything I said because /u/beedlee and /u/nter are right.  Spora deletes shadow volumes, and it's so new there doesn't appear to be a solution for it yet.

[Info about Spora here](https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/spora-ransomware-works-offline-has-the-most-sophisticated-payment-site-as-of-yet/).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh.  So for travel.  Like a fuel-efficient RV! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 03:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally upvoted it because my sense is that the more Trump sees *President Bannon* the more likely he'll finally melt down and we can get rid of both of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious--when would you use a Prius bed?  Am I missing some really cool social movement? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.  Unfortunately I have a 3d-generation; it uses 4.5.5.

I followed the instructions [here](http://blog.the-ebook-reader.com/2016/07/02/how-to-install-google-play-on-fire-tablets-the-super-easy-way-no-pc-or-root/) and have older APKs on my device.  

But when I try to run the Play Store icon, I get the message "error retrieving information from server (RH-01)".  A search for that suggests a corrupted installation, but I downloaded APKs from a different source, too, and still get the error.  So I'm stumped! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portland woman gets python stuck in her gauge piercing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 14:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 11:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  It was a case out of Minnesota, from what I recall.  Long before Citizens United.  Involved a fusion issue.  A third-party had challenged its right to be named as a candidate for more than one party.  

Though Citizens United certainly solidified the positions of entrenched interests.

Ah--[Timmons v Twin Cities Area New Party, No. 95-1608](http://www.nytimes.com/1997/04/29/us/supreme-court-rules-against-fusion-tickets-by-minor-parties.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the very least before the impeachment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  recreational marijuana use.

They shouldn't call it recreational.  From what I've seen, based on the abuse bodies endure in the NFL, it's medicinal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few years ago--I forget the case--the Conservative-led Supreme Court decided a case that in effect kept us as a 2-party system.

There are many who agree with you.  But U.S. citizens are a widely diverse group, even if our political parties don't reflect it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep [since Goldwater](http://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2014/10/barry-goldwater-lasting-legacy-112210).  That's when the GOP realized it needed a long-term strategy.  Dems need their own Goldwater moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know how to install Google Play on a fire hdx 8.9? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried instructions from a lot of different sites and haven't gotten it working yet.  Got the files installed for a 3rd-generation device via [this site](http://blog.the-ebook-reader.com/2016/07/02/how-to-install-google-play-on-fire-tablets-the-super-easy-way-no-pc-or-root/), but then I get an error once I log into my Google Play account.

There must be a way, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's also absurd is how slow the Democrats have been to realize this, and the apparent lack of energy with which they've either defended against it or attacked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odd thing about the Cowboys is that, notwithstanding their improvement at drafting, they've shown no skill at trading at all.  And of course it's difficult to trade in the NFL anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd tell you that you're wrong, and at the very least there are many forms of heaven, including how I feel when (a) I'm hugged by my children; (b) I look into my wife's eyes; (c) I get a game-winning hit in softball; (d) I pet a cat that's purring in my lap while I read a good book; (e) I wrestle with a puppy; (f) I listen to the rain on certain days in the fall; (g) I snuggle under blankets on a cold night; (h) I realize that I've done the right thing on my job; (i) (I could go on).
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously.  The only thing that's going to defeat the imbeciles currently running our country is courtesy, common sense, courage, and neighborliness--i.e., the values we used to consider American. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 11:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is a narcissistic demagogue whose only strength is that he was born into money.  But it's the GOP-controlled Congress I blame; they're the ones defending what he's doing.  Clearly they're more concerned about enacting their own agenda than protecting the character and laws of the nation.  It's a disgrace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a cap issue.  A post June 1 release would free up [$14M](http://overthecap.com/salary-cap/dallas-cowboys/).  In contrast, if they trade him, they free up only [$10M](http://cowboyswire.usatoday.com/2016/11/15/dallas-cowboys-total-2017-salary-cap-impact-if-cowboys-trade-tony-romo-in-offseason/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wherever Romo ends up, he'll make the team better.

Based on the numbers seems a release is what'll happen too.  Though I'd love if he'd stay with the Cowboys, I just don't see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems that our leaders have lost their way.  The GOP seems only to want to increase its power, at risk of all that's held us together traditionally.  Trump's conduct so far is fraught with signs of incompetence at best and corruption at worst.  We need someone desperately to save us from these would-be tyrants.

You have my support, /u/kn0thing.  As does every American who wants us undivided, together, as one people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiger kills man after he allegedly scales 10 ft wall and drops into the zoo enclosure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was a really sweet guy.  He had this weird metal contraption that he would put on the back of his hand, and he would use it to massage my scalp.  It would vibrate so much I could feel it in my elbows.  It must've been manufactured in the 1950s.  

I told him once, "Oh, you don't have to do that".  Typical guy reaction, right, to anything unusual?  He said, "I do it for my arthritis".

He said he had so many great, great, great, grandchildren he'd never recognize them.  I chose not to point out that his vision only seemed to extend about 5 feet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heck I would do that now with any older folks looking for fishing buddies.  And I wouldn't even want to catch a fish!  Older people are so awesome; they have so many amazing stories that otherwise get lost to time.

I had a 96 year old barber a few years ago.  Whenever I'd go to his shop he'd be dozing in his chair with the door locked.  He used to say he had more customers in Heaven than he did on earth.  I think really by then I was his only customer.  He finally passed a few years ago, at the amazing age of 103.

I miss him.  But my first thought upon hearing of his death was this: *his customers have been waiting for him.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrific insight.  Thank you.  I try to maintain a neutral stance, typically, as my view is the real political divide isn't between the left and right, but the top and bottom.  I'm no fan of Clinton or the GOP to tell the truth.  And I definitely understand the frustrations of the forgotten classes.

But this guy Trump seems either like a lunatic or corrupt beyond belief, if the allegations about his business interests in the affected nations are correct.  

In either event, I've yet to see anything remotely suggesting that he's qualified or of serious enough mind to be President.

I keep thinking it's a matter of time before the GOP finally respects our nation enough to impeach the guy.  Seems obvious they're so giddy about enacting their agenda they're willing to work with him as long as possible, no matter what harm he does.  And maybe they fear his base.

But at some point they need to remember the significance of their offices and the oaths they've made.  They need to act in the interest of the United States and get this nut out of office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What in the world is it going to take for the GOP finally to rid us of this lunatic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you invite as a mod someone you couldn't trust? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except when they don't.  It's pretty clear to all of the mods in /r/cowboys, for example, that our top mod account was hijacked months ago, and they've done nothing.  It's so bad that another account involved in it has messaged me to mock us about it.  From what we can tell, all the admins did was check ips.  So all the work we do is at risk, and there's not a thing we can do about it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 13:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but you're the creator.  If your account was hacked, you'd want the legitimate mods to act.  Particularly if the admins didn't help you.

Plus, any fear in that regard would incentivise you to consider who you'd invite to be a mod.  Hard to see how that would hurt a sub.

Maybe a safeguard could be built in--verified account plus a code emailed to the original email address at creation could solve identity verification challenges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 12:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is that their decisions as to whether accounts have been hacked, except possibly in egregious cases, seem to be based solely on IP addresses.  Which are incredibly easy to fake via spoofing software which is readily available even on the most rudimentary hacker websites.  They're as ubiquitous as wardialers.

FYI mods *can* contact admins directly.  Doesn't mean they respond. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 12:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To borrow his formula: GOP needs to grow a pair and impeach this corrupt Narcissistic nutjob.  Cowards! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mods should have some form of power to remove mods above them if all other mods agree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 06:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would help in situations where entire mod teams have lost faith in mods above them, due to hacks or other issues, when admins feel they don't have enough evidence to act.

I understand why admins might want to protect the integrity of, say, a founding mod's access to the sub, or even the access of higher-ranking mods, but unusual circumstances sometimes arise, and it's not clear to me why admins should be the *only* ones with that power.

Under certain circumstances, it would be helpful for lower-ranking mods to have the ability to act to protect the integrity of subs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so insane--a repudiation of U.S. history.  With the exception of Native Americans, *all of us* are descendants of immigrants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy Pearce's [filmography](http://www.metacritic.com/person/guy-pearce).

(Used this site because it has links to trailers for all his movies.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 06:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A terrific actor.  May he rest in peace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 05:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just Texas though.  It's everywhere.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 05:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No matter what you think or what the laws say, the U.S. generally does not protect whistleblowers.  So even though you're almost certainly right, it doesn't matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what I was going to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree with this--in fact, I just this minute wrote a message to the mods saying something similar.  Bravo to the users who've been kind and patient.

This is not a small sub, and it speaks highly of everyone that users within a day of each other were so impressed they wanted to praise you guys.

Cheers, and thank you all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gotten attacked a lot of times for suggesting that.  But otherwise unless posters specifically referred to the names in the posts, there wouldn't be a functional way to ban the links.

Personally I don't understand why subbies keep linking to the stuff.  Who cares what those guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Astonishingly, Sony refuses a refund because my son earned 2 trophies and played 4%.  Whatever 4% of Minecraft means.  I originally had installed the game on the vita via my master account, and he played it for approximately an hour.  But that was enough for Sony to refuse to help.

I could challenge it via my credit card and win.  But then I'd risk Sony shutting down my main account.

Just really a brutal policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That worked!  I never saw preferences, but on the vita I was able to link the vita to the master account and buy the game for the sub account.  Thank you!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> !  I'll try that this evening!  If that works, eureka!  You're brilliant!

Well you may be brilliant anyway.  But thank you!  I'll check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! But unfortunately that address does not lead to permissions.  Account tab takes me to a page with 6 additional options--of which "manage my account" seems the appropriate option.  That takes me to https://account.sonyentertainmentnetwork.com/liquid/home/index!display.action, which, after sign-in, has an additional "account" tab with (finally!) a sub account tab.  But that sub account tab does not have permissions, either.  Instead it offers parental controls: Sign-In ID (E-mail Address) , Chat/Message Block, Content Restriction On, User-Generated Media Block,  Monthly Spending Limit.

Each sub account has its own email address.  I reset the Vita to clear my master account, reformatted the memory card to clear it, and entered one of the email addresses for a sub account.  Then, when I went to buy the game, it wouldn't let me.  [Here's a link where I describe that problem](https://www.reddit.com/r/vita/comments/5qf1s4/how_do_i_buy_a_game_for_a_sub_account_to_play_on).

As an aside, I have 2 copies of the game in my master account (was accident, and apparently I can't return them).  But based on what another user told me, it sounds like the sub accounts can't access those copies?  If that is supposed to be possible, I'd be content for the moment just allowing them to play those.  But I can't figure out how to do that either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay but how do I get the game onto them?  (I posted elsewhere about that problem.)

Also, what does adhoc mean in respect to vitas?

And would I need to get 2 copies of the game or just one?

Sorry about all the questions.  I'm just trying to figure this out.

Also, I'm kind of worried about registering both vitas to my master account; my children are *young*, so I'm being a parent.  But if that's the only way to get the game onto them I'll do it.

Just...there *must* be a way to get games onto vitas registered to sub accounts; it's just that no one seems to know how.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for all this info!

They are young children.  So I kind of appreciate the control.  I could imagine that by the time they reach any appreciable distance into the teen years they would prefer master accounts, but technology changes so quickly that by then I'm guessing changing accounts won't be such an issue.  

Master accounts don't allow for the kinds of protections small kids need right?

Next, thanks for clarifying how wallets are supposed to work.  Problem is, even though I've put money into their wallets from the master account, I can't buy the game via the sub account, as I get the indicated message.  

Do you have any suggestions how I might be able to do that?  Or what I might be doing wrong that's preventing me from it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said it before, but I think Martin is the best OL the Cowboys ever have had--better than Rayfield Wright, and he was *incredible*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope--no offensive lineman ever has been named MVP.  Heck, only 3 non RB/QBs [ever have been named MVP](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/National_Football_League_Most_Valuable_Player_Award).  Well, 4 if you include the PFWA's award.  And none in 30 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have 2 copies of the game in my master account, but as I mention in a different thread, I'm trying to figure out now how to configure the vitas via the sub accounts so they can access them (can't even figure out how to buy a game using a sub account).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of that great episode in Corner Gas (all of them were great but) where Brent keeps trying to make a joke about Amelia Earhart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 12:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you anyway!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 12:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem pretty knowledgeable, so if you wouldn't mind, I have a followup question: how do my kids access the games I bought in my master account?

Right now the vita doesn't show up as one of my devices in the web site.  I wonder if somehow linking the vita to my master account would allow them to play those games as well as buy games--but based on what you've said it sounds like I *don't* want to link the vita to my master account.

These seem like really basic, fundamental questions, so I'm amazed the info doesn't seem to be available online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 11:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As for memory card--does the vita have 2?  Or just the one that I bought as an extra?  I reformatted that one, based on my understanding that a reformat would clear the link to the master. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 11:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the screen after I try to buy the game, where it gives me that message quoted above, it won't let me sign in with the sub account.

I don't even see how to do it on the web site!  /u/tonygfilms suggests that I'll need to add permissions, but I don't see where I can do that either.

I'd think this shouldn't be so perplexing, but sheesh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 11:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds logical, but in the account section I don't see any place to do that.  I check under sub accounts (seems like the obvious place), wallet, account details--well, every tab, and I just don't see where to do it.

The vita doesn't show up as a device.  I wonder if maybe when I do the initial setup I should do it with the master account--but when I tried that originally I couldn't figure out how to sign in again with the sub account.

I did a search playstation permissions sub account and got [this page](http://manuals.playstation.net/document/en/ps4/settings/subaccount.html) (account management).  That's the one I've been looking at--but nothing about permissions.  Chat, user-generated media, content restriction, monthly spending limit--those are the only options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or else he'll say all the people who signed the petition are the same ones who cast the imaginary illegal votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were a *great* help!  You led me to that other link! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I buy a game for a sub account to play on a ps vita? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to buy a game for my 2 children to use via their sub accounts on their separate ps vitas.  I am trying to set up the first vita for this, and I am mystified at how to do it.

I restore the vita to factory settings, then on the first login use the sub account info.  Then I get a screen saying: *To use Playstation Network with this account, you must provide additional information.  Complete the initial setup and then link your account with the Playstation Vita system*.  

I have no idea how to do this.  It seems as though, when I've tried (no clue if I was doing the right thing), I keep making it so that the Vita only will recognize my master account, not the sub account.

When I haven't tried, though, when I go to buy a game, I am told that I can't access the Playstation network, and I can't log in using the sub account info--even though at setup I was able to sign in using the sub account info!

I haven't been able to find anywhere online how to solve this.

I am very confused.  I really would appreciate someone explaining what the heck I need to do, so my kids can play this game together.

Thank you in advance!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 04:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so confusing and I can't find info online about it.

I restored the vita to factory settings, then set it up with the sub account.  I have no idea what to do next.  You know what--I will ask the question to the sub at large.  I don't want to bug you.  Thank you though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 04:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to impose, but now I have *another* question.  I am trying to figure out how to buy the game for the vita so my son can play it in his sub account, but I can't figure out how!  I've signed into the vita with his sub info; but when I try to buy the game it says I have to sign into the playstation network.

Do I have to set him up an individual playstation network account?  I thought that's what the sub account was.  I can sign in using my master account, but I'm afraid I'll be buying the game for the master account (which I don't want to do).

I'm sorry to be such a dunce about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 03:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much!  You've just made 2 children very happy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 03:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's arguable.  That's *exactly* the role of the media in a free society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can my children play Minecraft together on vitas if they each have one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If so, how would I configure them so they could?  I've set up sub accounts, and if necessary I'm prepared to buy Minecraft for each.  But how would I set up the devices?

Thank you for any help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> these staffers were actually fired

Definitely a lie.  Or colossally stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just so astonishingly cynical, even for politicians.  No foreign Ambassadors, now no senior leadership in the State Department.  Is this what Trump meant by draining the swamp?  Getting rid of anyone who knew what they were doing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems obvious--none of the 3-5 million illegal votes which don't exist were cast for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So maybe you're right--Putin *couldn't* have done a better job.

At some point the GOP's going to have to impeach this guy, right?  He's so obviously out of his depth.  My guess is they're just waiting for the right excuse.  They don't even need to wait for him to sign all their legislation--Pence would do that.  They just need something so bad that they'll be able to use it to face down his supporters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heck, short of military action, Putin couldn't have done a better job crippling our federal government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 12:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice!  I wonder if I dreamed this.  Hm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 12:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ritual is one of the keys to life.  Reality is that few people *like* going to work--even if they enjoy what they do.  But ritual/habit lets us get started in that direction anyway.

Another observation: many people would rather do nothing.  But in the same way that the courageous act in spite of fear, not in the absence of it, the industrious act in spite of "laziness" (or a tendency to relax). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 12:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep.  Idea is that Congress is the one which needs to change the statutory definition.  Courts merely interpret/apply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 11:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything I needed to know about Reddit's political will I learned a few years back, when there was going to be this huge protest against the TSA at Christmas.  When Christmas arrived...not a peep.

What can we expect, though, from a site whose users skew 14-25?  They're basically teenagers, and like teenagers everywhere, they think they know everything--and will change the world simply by saying so.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember too of course that the GOP has mastered the gerrymander, to the extent it regularly increases its hold over governorships and state legislators.  When it comes to political strategy, cow is out of the barn and the Dems still haven't put on their boots.  

Net neutrality matters to redditors.  It doesn't matter to Joe Six Pack in Kansas, who's bought into Trump and the GOP.

Any change that's going to happen won't be soon, and it won't occur at all unless the Dems have their own [Goldwater moment](http://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2014/10/barry-goldwater-lasting-legacy-112210). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep this is one of the great moments in the series, along with [Walder Frey's death](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fw72ejliSYU), the scene where [Arya snuffs out the candle](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2luuPo5e65E), and *any* scene with [Jaqen H'gha](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y31RoHC15pM).  

But Peter Dinklage is simply an incredible actor.  The frustration, grief, and anger--just incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing!  Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cowboys' defense has a lot of guys like this.  Even the ones who play best miss a lot of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NFL mock draft roundup: Cowboys may select 'long' DE, 'electric' WR, more in Round 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this is my guess.  I suspect that most people in the US don't understand the extent to which local media funding and staffing has been devastated by the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could copy/paste whichever section of our code is necessary, but based on what you're saying I'm not sure our specific code is the issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep!  Problem solved!  Thank you so much!  And thank you again to u/elnuno who got me started in the right direction!  Cheers to both you guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi!  Thank you--I had to go afk.  I'm guessing that /u/ffsnipe has the right solution--right now I'm checking to see how to change the navtop setting, and when I do I'll report to him.  But it looks to me as though you two have solved the problem.  Thank you!

Edit: luckily RES has that great search engine!  Found it easily! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh.  It's actually something about Reddit Enhancement Suite that causes this, as, after your comment, I disabled the only relevant add-on et voila!  The problem was solved!  Of course if I report the problem in the RES sub, they'll blame CSS.  So it goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cowboys do this kind of limited edition a lot, as can be seen on [ebay](http://www.ebay.com/sch/i.html?_from=R40 _trksid=p2050601.m570.l1313.TR0.TRC0.H0.Xdallas+cowboys+limited+edition+football.TRS0 _nkw=dallas+cowboys+limited+edition+football _sacat=0).

Speaking from a production perspective, 20k isn't exactly a limited edition, except in the sense that *everything* is produced in a limited number.  Calling it "limited" is purely a marketing ploy to drive up interest.

Which apparently hasn't exactly worked, as the ball's for sale for [42 bucks](http://www.ebay.com/itm/DALLAS-COWBOYS-Champions-Ball-Football-NFL-Limited-Edition-HOLDS-AIR-/252703394777?hash=item3ad64bcbd9:g:xwsAAOSwubRXFpXr).  With the added benefit that it "HOLDS AIR".

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no way in heck Roethlisberger will retire. That he won't commit simply means he's tired and wants some time to recover from a disappointing end to a long season.  This is just a reporter trying to generate some buzz from nothing.

And we don't need to link every possible QB opening to Romo.  Offseason is too long for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could use advice: a glitch occurs in Firefox but not Chrome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a mod of /r/cowboys.  Whenever I view /r/cowboys in firefox, [this](http://imgur.com/zVEiRci) happens.  As you can see, our banner at the top overlays my reddit user info, and I can't access my user info.  

This problem does not occur in Chrome, so it seems that the difference must lie in how Firefox handles css.  

I would appreciate any suggestions on how to fix this problem in Firefox--while an obvious workaround is to use Chrome, we do still have a lot of users who access the sub via Firefox.

Thank you for any suggestions!

Edit: you guys were awesome!  Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the agreement would set aside $56.5 million for recipients of 900,000 criminal summonses

I.e., about $60 each. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe.  But pretty sure I didn't read about it on reddit.  I seem to remember jumping down there myself once.  Hm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaping Dragon question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading *way* back about loot existing somewhere down below the Gaping Dragon's ledge.  And if you jumped at just the right spot you could get it.  Does anyone remember this?  I don't remember if it was true or not.  At this point I probably don't even have the patience to find out.  But does anyone remember reading about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9LBasxQ9Nyc) is the most retarded thing I've ever heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another thing to realize is that you may be seeing the child through the mother's eyes.  That's one of many reasons why this movie is so disturbing; by making the mother's ambivalence toward the child so palatable, it almost justifies her treatment of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much for running the table. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like either team but I don't mind that the Packers are getting blown out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd broaden it to say anyone who abuses anyone.  We mess each other up so badly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something with artichokes--I dunno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure.  Help/contact us/prime or something else.  I think [this  link](https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/help/customer/contact-us?ie=UTF8 nodeId=471044 ref_=hp_gt_comp_cu ) works for amazon.co.uk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White was a great player, and both would change a defense.  But from what I remember, Bob Lilly and Deacon Jones both were better than White.

In any event, Taylor and Alan Page remain [the only NFL defensive players ever to win MVP](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/National_Football_League_Most_Valuable_Player_Award).

Regardless (after all it's all unprovable), check out some of [these all-time greatest lists!](http://www.nfl.com/photoessays/0ap3000000648967)  A lot of great players have played in the NFL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  JJ Watt will probably go down as the best pass rusher and even the best defensive player of all time. 

He's got a ways to go before he catches [Lawrence Taylor](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/players/T/TaylLa00.htm).  Taylor's the only guy on defense I've ever seen who reminded me of Jim Brown--a man among children.  But Watt's certainly headed in the same direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Toyota product line is marked by exceptional engineering and build quality.

Testify.  I have a 2006 with barely 70k miles on it.  Never once had a problem--though the *regular* (not hybrid) battery did get replaced a while back.  But it still runs *great*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pfft.  If Jerry hadn't wanted all the credit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job bud!  Excellent post!  A lot of insight and a lot to think about.  Well done.

Biggest problem we all have is that none of us can read the future.  All we have is the past.  And we've all seen how excellent Romo has been, and how often his teams have let him down.  It's hard not to want a guy like that to succeed.  No easy answer to this situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention Jerry.  Who is, we must admit, a tool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 00:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seemed like this year a *lot* the Cowboys fell into the habit of run on first, pass on second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 00:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Landry did that back in the day with Morton and Staubach.  Of course they were both young.  But it was every bit as excruciating as Prescott/Romo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/watchmemikey mentions letting them fight it out in the preseason.  I like that idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to see this too.  If Tony beats out Dak this summer, there'd be no problem in sitting Dak.  And if Tony got hurt, no problem in sending Dak in.  Except for the salary imbalance, this could be a good outcome.  But my guess is that the Cowboys will release him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Cowboys fans should take away more than disappointment from shocking, heartbreaking finish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dak's at the end too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garrett's postgame press conference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys defense laments costly breakdowns, early and late </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crosbys kick sends Packers past Cowboys in NFC Divisional playoffs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garrett and Cowboys fight, but they were their own worst enemies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get what you're saying.  It was such a magical year none of us wanted it to stop.  And there's no guarantee it'll happen again.

But comfort yourself.  Game wasn't stolen from them like in 2014.  They left it all on the field.  Offense and defense played their guts out, like they had all year.  Not the defense's fault it lacked playmakers.  

But comfort yourself.  Next year the Cowboys still will have all their great talent on offense.  If Dak could learn/do this in one year, imagine what he'll be able to learn after an off-season of study.

Also next year hopefully Tapper and Smith can play.  Maybe Lawrence finally will show something.  Sure, the Cowboys will be drafting low, but they got some great talent all across the draft this year.  So they finally may be able to add some guys who'll take them over the hump.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved that clutch catch--he went exactly where he was supposed to go for the first down.  And then sat down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 03:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and the spike.  But that first half hurt.  Cowboys played as well as they could.  Honestly I've felt worse after losses.  The future looks really *bright*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 03:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what it was like in the 60s.  Landry kept getting the Cowboys to the verge and couldn't get past it.  For 11 years he kept trying, kept hearing that the Cowboys *couldn't win the big one*.  Imagine how fans felt after Super Bowl V.  Totally outplayed the Colts and made enough mistakes to choke a goat.

The Cowboys adjusted at halftime today but spotting the Packers an 18-point lead was tough.  Like that game in the 90s when the Cowboys gave the 49ers a 3-TD lead.

With luck, this is just the start.  Cowboys draft defense next year, and they'll be even better.  Just like when they lost their first playoff game under Johnson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 03:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate 'em all so I'm rooting for nobody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 03:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sentiment exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 03:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We really do have a lot to look forward to.  Hopefully the Cowboys will focus on the defense in the draft.  That 3d and 20-whatever killed us.  Sigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 02:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys.  I'm a mod of /r/cowboys.  It was a great game.  Congrats.  Enjoy it.  Good luck the rest of the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 02:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a great game, great comeback, and a tough loss.  We have a lot to look forward to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys out to finish what they started </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 17:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess what we'll need is a player who's also a Redditor.  Sigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 19:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Focus of the telescope is on the moon.  Causes the background to appear to move as the moon passes in front of it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 19:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Kent!  We really appreciate your supporting our sub and making yourself available for this AMA.  Your work is terrific, and we're fans, as I think you can see from the enthusiastic response here.  I have 2 questions.

(1) How'd you get in this line of work, and how'd you come to work for the Cowboys?  
  
(2)  We've had a lot of trouble getting the Cowboys interested in supporting the sub with AMAs.   What do you think we could do, other than making this a great experience for you, to make the sub more visible to the players and management, to get them interested in doing this, too?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what I was going to say.  Amazing post /u/brexbre.  Great way to commemorate a magical season.  
  
Edit:done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least [a remake](https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1598858095/system-shock?ref=user_menu) is coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys' Dak Prescott Can Handle Any Kind of Pressure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On This the N.F.L. Agrees: The Cowboys Offensive Line Is No. 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see that, but the story was such a twist the rest of the way and...I don't remember now.  I'll have to watch it again.  But it just didn't seem to...ha!  follow from the rest of the movie.

But I don't really need movies (or anything, really) to be perfect to enjoy it.  I can like things for what they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or different expectations, you know?  It doesn't particularly follow genre rules.  A lot of what happens is in the background.

I dunno.  As usual with art I feel kind of bad for people who don't appreciate it, because all it means is they're missing ways to enrich their lives.  I kind of think the more you can value in, the better your life can be.

And sure this applies to me, too, when I don't get stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STDs I could see it, sure.  But that's not even a subtext.

Instead, like you suggest, seems like something else is going on in it.  I went away from this movie after the first time thinking of--not STDs chasing them; but that it was death, and they only became aware of it upon sexual awakening.  I don't mean puberty, or even the act, but the change that happens to the mind when sex approaches for the first time.

I saw this movie really about memory, the passage of time, regret, and the relentlessness with which our own mortality approaches.

Swimming pool scene was pretty bad, and this movie wasn't perfect, by any means.  But almost none are.  Heck, there are people who criticize The Exorcist.

What I liked about this: its originality.  And also the sense of timelessness.  Like...exactly when did this story happen?  Had a very Donnie Darko-ish kind of dream-time to me.

Weird things going on in it, nothing to do with the monster.  The mom, drinking.  The phones on the walls.  The e-reader, unlike anything we've ever seen before.  Yet the kids are watching Killers From Space on a cathode TV.  And the girl using that e-reader to read The Idiot--hardly mass market paperback fare.  

Anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even with whatever issues it has, it's the best horror movie in years.  

Hard to create an entirely new kind of monster.  Remarkable, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 14:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome!  One thing's for certain: the Cowboys never will move.

And here's something else: yeah, sure, Jerry generally is an annoying owner.  But ever since he hired Garrett he's stepped back from football operations and he's letting competent people run them, who seem to have values that almost all of us can respect.  So if you'd like to root for guys you might actually admire in RL this may be the team.

Though Jerry still does say goofy stuff.  And he likes to take credit for *everything*.  But if that doesn't bother Garrett it won't bother me.

Also, I became a fan amidst the Staubach/Morton controversy, and I clearly remember when they drafted Dorsett.  So I remember the feeling back then.  This team is pretty exciting.  A lot like those teams.

It's a good time to come back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 04:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess if Psycho can be a horror movie, so can Green Room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 01:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While to some extent it depends on how you define it, and whether you allow for exceptions, generally, several have laws requiring it.  [Here's a map](https://www.thisisnetneutrality.org/).  U.S. (for the moment), Canada, Iceland, Norway, Finland, Israel, the Netherlands, Switzerland, India, Japan.  Those all are nations in which English is pretty common and which have laws requiring it.

Many other nations are considering codification of it--which could mean a variety of things, ranging from that they already practice it to that they don't have laws precluding its practice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have come really to enjoy seeing Collins chugging around after QBs.  If he can get to them in the pocket they're toast.  But if they manage to break outside forget it.  He's like the Little Engine that Could, squat sturdy body chugging, relentless in his pursuit.  But slow, slow.  I love him!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
