<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3307</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 21:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it!!! Something I'll have to try soon. I love the colors! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 04:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like being the submissive one with both males and females. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 01:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, congrats on being stable. I'd like to think I'm stable, but my Dr. doesn't think so. He says my case is very complex, whatever that means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 21:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you find a new psychiatrist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it weird for my Dr. to call me every day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 03:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My psychiatrist calls me every day of the work week. We talk about my life and my feelings, etc. I guess you could say he's also my counselor. Is anyone else having or have had this experience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm confused about not being confused. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 03:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the title explains it all. I am currently crushing hard on this girl (32) (me 32f). I'm not confused about whether I want to be with her or not, but why I'm not. I know it doesn't make a ton of sense, but I needed to get it off my chest. 

P.S. I have a backstory that ~~goes with this~~ is in the comments below in case anyone wants to hear it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't stop buying games that get little to no game play in my home. Help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 01:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 04:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on 500 mg. Hmm.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 05:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is nasty, but I assume it's better than original flavor if there is such a thing.

It helps with my depression. I only take 1.25 mg because it knocks me out and makes me feel groggy the next day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 08:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is my collection](http://i.imgur.com/NDB3qq5). I love the OMG That's Bright collection! So pretty!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish I could cry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 05:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel so numb inside. I actually feel really good, I just have no emotions. I wish I could have a good cry but I can't get myself to cry. I think sometimes people need to cry to let all the feelings out.

Edit: Do others feel numb but aren't feeling depressed at the time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 22:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on the highest dose (according to my Dr.), 500 mg. It has really helped even my mood. I'm not so good at taking my meds all the time (I"m also on Paxil 40mg, and 26 mg of Abilify. This combination seems to work for me. 

The only thing is when I forget to take it, I go through withdrawals after two days but that could be due to one of the other drugs.

Let me know how it goes for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 05:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know what to reply to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 20:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was very proud of myself. It was my first DIY project. The bottom is a little crooked but overall it turned out great. Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 20:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
