<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4368</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao no I don't think so. I would imagine it would be a circle and the cockpit would be the little line.

Edit: kind of like the Power On symbol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should have a Wing for every letter of the alphabet. Q-Wing would be interesting..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact this dude has so many subs while some really good channels continue to go unnoticed gives a glimpse at how culturally and morally  devoid we are as human beings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what Socrates might did thought about the youth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bust my ass making short films and no one subs to my YouTube. This guy beats his kids and everyone loves him. I hate this planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they both made it on to Family Guy though. In different ways... But... Silver lining... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally. Now we can stop hearing about him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue koopa shell would have stopped him dead in his tracks just saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Joker took my report card!" "Ok you lying little shit..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've never had your paper graded by another student? We did it all the time! "Grade your neighbor's paper..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea...  That happens a lot at school, actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Goldberg's are the real life equilvilent to Bojack Horseman's "Horsing Around" except replace the horse with a busty, blonde middle aged woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That there aren't enough cassette tapes left in the world to do my suicide boxed set. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like an odd question... If you don't mind me asking, why would you like to know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
