<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5161</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The thing inside my roof </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each night it gets worse. 

Night time is the favourite part of the day for me. The world is finally going to sleep, and all the stress and demand of this modern society shuts down for just a few hours. 
I feel like I can finally be at peace with myself and the world, even just for a few hours.

So this is the time when I feel calmest. As if I can finally shut my brain off for a little bit and let tomorrows worries be exactly that; tomorrows worries.

But lately it has been different. I keep having this overwhelming feeling of unease take over. 
No matter how hard I try, it will not go away. I cannot control it. Its as if it lives in the form of a black cloud that forced itself down my throat and I swallowed it whole.

12.30am every.single.night (well morning) without a doubt. I creeps upon me. 
And BAM! It hits me in the face. 

I can't breath. I can't move. I am paralysed for what feels like an eternity, but is really only 30 seconds at most. 

Fear. Absolute fear that something terrible is going to happen. 
Something so awful, I cannot even begin to describe. 

It all started when I started hearing noises at night. Nothing major. Nothing too threatening.
Just an occasional bang on the gate or side of the house. 
I generally would not worry as the dogs wouldn't bark, which means that they weren't alarmed by these noises so I would pass it off as the wind.

But then it started to get louder, more frightening. By this stage the dogs would be awoken by these noises also, and would growl and bark in a way that made me feel extremely uneasy. Frightened even.
They're only small dogs, but they can and will cause harm if they feel threatened.

It was now becoming more frequent. I felt that if I left my window open I would be left more vulnerable. It was as if someone was going to tear down my security screen, force open the window, and come inside. I do not know where this fear came from, but I was overwhelmed by it almost every night. 

I became too scared to leave my blinds open, even the slightest bit, incase someone did actually attempt anything. They would be able to see straight into my bedroom, and have a perfect sight of me in bed. 

I thought that this was the worst that could happen and eventually started telling myself I'd read too many creepypastas, and that it was all inside my head. 

But then the creaking in the roof started. It sounded as if someone was directly above me, and was about to fall straight through the roof, and land on top of me. 

The first night I heard it, I didn't sleep until 4am. I thought I was just going crazy. It was unlike any noise I had heard before, and I was certain it was not the house creaking or settling. It was too loud and heavy for any wildlife we have around the area and we also have no holes in our roof.

I was almost asleep after I talked myself into finally attempting to close my eyes. 
I remember thinking to myself 'finally I can get some sleep'. The second this thought went through my head, I heard it yet again.
I was terrified. 

This is now happening multiple times a night. The banging, the dogs growling and barking, the 'thing' inside the roof. The feeling as if someone is watching me outside my window....

And now I'm seeing things.

[+] (https://www.facebook.com/thestephrobinson/?ref=aymt_homepage_panel)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
