<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7923</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The combo works so well together! The first (and only other time) I had it was at SPOT dessert bar in NYC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the recipe. There are three components: the Thai tea creme brulee (recipe almost the same as Hot Thai Kitchen [changed water and sugar amounts]), a black sesame paste, and coconut and pandan caviar and jellies.  
 nbsp;  
**Thai Tea Creme Brulee:** *4 or 5 small ramekin servings*  
240 g heavy cream  
50 g water  
120 g evaporated mteilk  
40 g Thai tea leaves  
80 g sweetened condensed milk  
4 large egg yolks (~72 g)  
12.5 g granulated sugar  
pinch salt  
a few grams sugar to brulee  
 nbsp;  
1. Oven to 325 F.  
2. In a pot on medium heat, bring whipping cream, water, and evaporated to a boil. Turn off heat, add Thai tea leaves and stir, and let steep for 5 minutes.  
3. In a bowl, whisk sugar, salt, and egg yolks until smooth. Whisk in condensed milk.   
4. Using a fine strainer, slowly add the Thai tea mixture over the yolk/ condensed milk. Whisk constantly.  
5. Strain again and then add into ramekins. It is better to err on the side of shallow vs filling up to the top. Quickly get rid of big bubbles by torching the tops.   
6. Put ramekins onto a sheet pan and then add hot water to fill the pan to about half the height of the ramekin.  
7. Bake for 40-45 minutes. Tap the sides of the ramekins and if it jiggles a lot, it definitely isn't done. But if it only jiggles a little like jello, it is probably fine.  
8. Let cool a little at room temp, then transfer to the fridge. You want them to be completely chilled before bruleeing.  
9. I use a round cutter to take the custard out of the ramekin but that doesn't matter. Add a few grams to the top and spread evenly. Torch slowly until it bubbles and browns a bit.  
 nbsp;  
**Black Sesame Paste:**  
15 g black sesame seeds  
2 g sugar  
40 g heavy cream  
1-5ish g water  
 nbsp;  
1. Grind the seeds to fine pieces with a food processor. Add to a pot with cream and sugar.  
2. Stirring constantly, reduce the mixture down until little cream remains and it is a thick consistency.  
3. Add in water a few g at a time and stir until you like the consistency. FYI, attempting to sieve at this point will release lots of oil. If you processed them well enough, the texture should be fine without needing to sieve.  
 nbsp;  
**Coconut or Pandan Caviar/ Jellies:**  
a small cup of oil, refrigerated  
*Coconut*  
50 g coconut milk  
50 g water  
1 g agar (or whatever setting agent you have)  
10 g sugar  
*Pandan*  
1 g pandan paste  
100 g water  
10 g sugar  
1 g agar  
 nbsp;  
1. Put the oil in the fridge immediately. Or freezer. You want it really really cold.  
2. Add water, sugar, and either coconut milk or pandan paste into a small microwaveable bowl and stir well. I added some white food coloring to the coconut as well. Add the agar powder, stir, and heat up until the agar dissolves. Microwaving for a minute works fine.  
3. Let cool slightly and then transfer 1/3 of the mixture into something that makes droplets. I have a syringe, but you can really use anything that has a nozzle.  
4. Slowly drop the agar mixture droplets into the cup of cold oil. They should start to fall down and resemble a lava lamp and settle on the bottom.  
5. Take the oil + caviar (gel spheres) and strain [I use a fine mesh tea strainer].  Rinse with some water for about 20 seconds to get rid of the oil.  
6. With the other 2/3 of the mixture, pour out onto some cling wrap lining a small pan or container. Let cool (fridge speeds this up) and then you can slice into cubes once it solidifies.  
 nbsp;  
This flavor combo tastes so good together. Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Thai tea creme brulee is based on Hot Thai Kitchen's recipe. I made up the recipe for the paste and caviar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, I'll post the recipe a bit later tonight. Not sure if anyone will ask for it, but since it's tasty, I want to post the recipe for quick access in the future :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was inspired to make this after visiting Garden Creamery in SF where I got Thai tea, coconut pandan, and black sesame ice creams. They worked so well together! If you're in SF ever, go get ice cream there. SO GOOD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Thai Tea Creme Brulee, Black Sesame Paste, Coconut and Pandan Caviar/Jellies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow this is so good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh, it's called a multiple color coupler I think. A coupler on its own is just the white thing that will hold onto your tip. regardless, I don't use either :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also have an actual coupler, but it's difficult the get the last bit of batter. And when you aren't starting out with a lot, that last amount counts! haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically treat a bag with two batters like a single one(I put two bags into a third). The little swirl thing you do when you pipe each macaron so they don't get a little nub, just swirl a little more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 09:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha. my friend said the exact same thing :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohgawd. Raspberry macaroni would taste weird :p.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmkay, here's the recipe. It's the French method because I'm 1. lazy and don't like having to do the extra step of making a simple syrup and 2. am stingy and can make a meringue with a small amount of egg whites. With this being said, you can do everything the exact same from one time to the next and end up with hollows. RIP.   
 nbsp;   
**Macaron Shells**  
For about 10 1.5 inch macarons:  
46 g almond flour (sift, no big almond pieces)  
42 g powdered sugar    
35 g egg whites (room temp)  
25 g granulated sugar  
 nbsp;  
1. Oven to 325F. Measure out and sift your powdered sugar and almond flour. Whisk together and set aside.  
2. Make your meringue. I speed warm up my egg whites by putting them in a small container and then putting that container in a bowl with hot water. Takes about 5 min to bring up the temp and doesn't cook them.  
Beat/ whisk your egg whites until frothy and start to incorporate the granulated sugar a bit a time. Beat until stiff peaks.  
3. Macaronage. Look up on Youtube if you're unfamiliar on how to do so.   
For this batter you want to split the batter in two as soon as the ingredients are incorporated. Fold about half your dry ingredients into the meringue until just incorporated and then add the rest and continue folding until just incorporated. Split the batter into two and add food gel food coloring. Individually, fold until you get a lava like consistency. Fold by scraping along the edge of the bowl to deflate the meringue a bit and then scooping the batter. Repeat. You should be able to pick up the spatula and have the batter fall down in a ribbon. The ribbon should incorporate back into the main blob after about 10ish seconds. If it doesn't fall correctly, I do a few more folds. Put each batter into its own piping bag with no tip. Then put these two bags into a singular bag with a tip (so a bag with a tip containing two bags of different color macaron batters).   
4. Pipe out your macarons. I treat this like any normal bag of macaron batter. When you squeeze from the top, both colors will incorporate into the tip and then when you lift up, exaggerate the swirl you do at the end (you normally do a little one to avoid those little bumps). I use a silpat (would highly recommend). Rap the baking sheet against the table a few times.  Pop any air bubbles with a toothpick and swirl the toothpick around a bit to have that hole close up.     
5. I hate waiting for the shells to dry, so I cheat and dry the shells using the oven heat. I do this by opening the oven and holding the tray in the oven, rotating it every 10 seconds or so for about a minute. My hands usually get hot at that point. I take them out for about a minute. Then back in again, rotating, for another 30 seconds. This quickly dries out the shells and makes a skin without having to wait 30 minutes at room temp (especially if it's humid!) :p.   
You want to be able to touch the shell and have it not be sticky. Make sure it doesn't shine and you're probably good to go.   
6. Bake for 10 minutes at 325 and drop to 300 for another 5-10 minutes.  
 nbsp;  
**Raspberry Ganache**    
25 g raspberry puree      
70 g white chocolate      
 nbsp;  
1. So normally I also add a bit of cream, but was lazy (recurring theme) and didn't. It still turned out fine.  
2. Put the white chocolate over a double boiler and mostly melt. Take off double boiler when there are a few unmelted pieces remaining.  
3. Puree raspberries and then sieve out the seeds. Heat in a small saucepan until it warms up a little.  
4. Add the raspberry puree to the white chocolate and fold together until incorporated.  
5. Transfer to a piping bag and chill it in the fridge or freezer for a short while to firm up before piping onto the macaron shells.    
6. After piping, let the macarons rest in an airtight container in the fridge overnight for optimal chewiness!   
Gluck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a simple raspberry ganache. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will post soon when I get home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww. Have you had macarons from well known places? I've bought some pretty bad macarons before from places that try to do too many things. I am also not a huge fan of buttercreams and sometimes that's all a shop will offer. Very disappointing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should check out the s'more macarons from Baker's Royale. They're beyond stunning! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can check out my other macarons. I have recipes for those. The ganache is basically just 70g white chocolate and 25 g raspberry puree. Sometimes I use some cream as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I post them! But usually not till later in the night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just need to keep trying! I've made a gazillion crappy batches. Lately they've been better. But yeah, at one point I wanted to give up and I didn't think it was worth... but somehow things got better and now I get to think of ways to make them look pretty :). Also, coupling failed experiments in lab with failed baking wasn't fun lol. But now only experiments in lab are failing. Woo. #thelittlethingsinlife </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't made raspberry macarons in a while and I figured why not. I ended up doing swirls because I couldn't think of anything else. haha. BUT, in the process of taking this pic I became inspired for future macarons, so look out for those :D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yeah :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty swirls :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Raspberry Macarons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Recipe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol well I suck at drawing dogs haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol which part </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You haven't? You need to change that!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol to be 100% honest I was trying to make a design, but I can't make microfoam with my crappy handheld electric frother to save my life, so it poured out in a blob. Had to work with what I had haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never had. Should try it out! Though, I really only drink it when I go back home for Christmas :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And mmkay, here's there recipe. I reduced the granulated sugar from what I normally do and I think this has helped out with my shells.  
 nbsp;  
**Macaron Shells**  
For about 10 1.5 inch macarons:  
46 g almond flour (sift, no big almond pieces)  
42 g powdered sugar  
5 g Abuelita chocolate tablet (ground in a processor and sifted)  
35 g egg whites (room temp)  
25 g granulated sugar  
 nbsp;  
1. Oven to 325F. Measure out and sift your powdered sugar, almond flour, and sifted chocolate powder. Whisk together and set aside.  
2. Make your meringue. Beat/ whisk your egg whites until frothy and start to incorporate the granulated sugar a bit a time. Beat until stiff peaks. Didn't add any food coloring to this recipe, but you could always do that shortly before reaching stiff peaks.  
3. Macaronage. Look up on Youtube if you're unfamiliar on how to do so.   
Basically, fold about half your dry ingredients into the meringue until just incorporated and then add the rest and continue folding until you get a lava like consistency. Fold by scraping along the edge of the bowl to deflate the meringue a bit and then scooping the batter. Repeat. You should be able to pick up the spatula and have the batter fall down in a ribbon. The ribbon should incorporate back into the main blob after about 10 seconds. If it doesn't fall correctly, I do a few more folds. Put into a piping bag.  
4. Pipe out your macarons. I use a silpat (would highly recommend). Rap the baking sheet against the table a few times.  Pop any air bubbles with a toothpick and swirl the toothpick around a bit to have that hole close up. I added some ground up chocolate powder on top.    
5. I hate waiting for the shells to dry, so I cheat and dry the shells using the oven heat. I do this by opening the oven and holding the tray in the oven, rotating it every 10 seconds or so for about a minute. My hands usually get hot at that point. I take them out for about a minute. Then back in again, rotating, for another 30 seconds. This quickly dries out the shells and makes a skin without having to wait 30 minutes :p.   
You want to be able to touch the shell and have it not be sticky. For any macaron you sprinkle things on top, you want to make sure the shell has had adequate time to dry on the top as well, and not just sides. Make sure it doesn't shine and you're probably good to go.   
6. Bake for 10 minutes at 325 and drop to 300 for another 5-10 minutes. [NOTE, I actually forgot to drop the temp down to 300 immediately after putting in the oven, so maybe this might work fine.]    
 nbsp;  
**Abuelita Mexican Chocolate Ganache**   
3/8 of an Abuelita tablet (33.75 g)     
50 g heavy cream  
70 g white chocolate      
 nbsp;  
1. Add cream and 3/8 of a tablet and heat over low. Stir and incorporate chocolate into the cream.  
2. Reduce down to about 30 ml cream and then take off heat to cool slightly.  
3. Put white chocolate over double boiler and mostly melt. Take off double boiler when there are a few unmelted pieces remaining.  
4. Add slightly cooled cream to the white chocolate and fold together until incorporated. If the cream is too hot, the chocolate will seize so be careful!    
5. Transfer to a piping bag and chill it in the fridge or freezer for a short while to firm up before piping onto the macaron shells.    
6. After piping, let the macarons rest in an airtight container in the fridge overnight for optimal chewiness!   
Gluck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Doggies :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These were the first chocolate macarons I've made :p. I usually don't like normal chocolate. Mexican hot chooclate is a whole different story though :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 07:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abuelita Mexican hot chocolate is awesome. So why not make macarons with it :D. The ground up powder is in the shell and the ganache. And then I tried a latte esque thing with the hot chocolate. Microfoam is tough to make without an expresso machine :'(.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Abuelita Hot Chocolate Macarons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 07:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I still am not consistent with them and I've made them tons of times. As a first try, you absolutely killed it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Great job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 07:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you take a pic of final product? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 07:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many marshmallows recently! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 07:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks so good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always try to see if I can squeeze in a correction without sounding like a jackass lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha yes. I got home from lab at 8:30 and was like, "If I start now, I should be done by 10" (since that's how long it normally takes me from start to clean up). NOPE. Didn't finish cleaning up until like 11:15 lolol. To be fair, there was a bit of trial and error and I contemplated a while trying to figure out proportions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
