<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4454</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they actually do have a date, imma be all, 

"bullshit this is fake" 

And then find out weeks later it's not an epic prank.



In all seriousness I think I read that it's because of a union thing. But im not sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of mania? That me spending all the rent money would make everyone happy. And we could totally figure out a way to deal with that later. 

During depression: 

I was like everyone secretly hates me, everything in my life is trash, and nothing good will ever happen for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second that you're protected by the Americans with disabilities act. Tho they could probably trump up some random charge. 

It's really annoying but they do need to be reminded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you want a girlfriend. I'd love a very thoughtful cake from you. I mean technically it's not cheating if it's not another boyfriend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I think St. Patrick's is a day of special dispensation. 

It's great. Especially because some Catholics I know either out of habit or maybe it's a local custom  also abstain from any drinking during the Lenten season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lenten observers how are you holding up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So today I actually remembered it was Friday. I thought it was yesterday but got reminded when my husband had to go to work. Lol. 

So we ate cream cheese pancakes for breakfast. But im at a loss for lunch and bored with tuna salad. 


How have all my keto Catholics and Lutherans doing? 

What you been eating for Friday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like you're 14 now.

Dawson's Creek reboot here you come </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk if I'm okay. I'm not planning the date or anything. 

The note hasn't been written. But idk. I'm just like massively disappointed in my life. I've very few friends. I eventually push them all away. 

Everything else in my life is trash. 

I just am trying to muster up something to live for. And I'm coming up empty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what I want to do. I know what I'm good at. But I don't have the ability to do it because of my circumstances. 

Like I'm an excellent bookkeeper and accountant. But I've been a sahm for the past 5 years so no one wants to hire me. Least of all in my field but at all in general. 

I suppose I can get my masters, if I can afford it. But I likely can't. 

So I'm stuck. 

And I hate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it isn't. Which is another reason I hate my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you. 

I hate that too. Like acknowledge my feelings. Even if they aren't "real". Acknowledge that I'm upset and let me feel that without feeling crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finding Meaning or Purpose (warning suicide thoughts) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been increasingly more suicidal lately. 

I always think of suicide. That's like baseline for me. I can go to Disney world and be having a great time and still think, this would be a good time to kill myself because I'll go out on a high note. 

Basically, it's rare that I'm not thinking about it. 

However, lately I'm moving forward in my thoughts. 

Where once it was just the idea. It's now moved to me having the idea, and knowing the method, and having the method handy. And like a true writer and planner researching ideas for what to say in the note. But no date yet.

I've told all this to my psychiatrist and he is not yet worried for me in that he hasn't suggested that I make my way to the emergency room. 


However, he did suggest that I try to find a way to stop feeling trapped by the obligations and commitments in my life. 

For example, I've a kid and a husband and while I'd love to travel the world and join a research group in Antarctica over the winter. I can't do that because of them. 

So I feel trapped by my life. And to me it seems the only way out is death. Currently I just pray for it. Hoping that I'll go to a doctor and they'll say "you have terminal cancer or something" but alas no. 

But I don't know how to not feel trapped. 

I made commitments I can't just cut out on them. And abandon them. 

So I'm stuck and miserable. 

For you who have found meaning and purpose in the midst of horrible circumstances, how did you do it. 

Any tips?

Thanks in advance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for your problems.

Have you attempted volunteer work to ease you into working more. Plus of you quit no sweat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When should I be concerned for my own safety? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a person has suicide ideation and bipolar 2

At what point do you think I should be worried for myself? 

When just thinking about it turns to thinking about it but also having picked a method?

Or when you have a method and you've started on the note?

Or when you've got a date and a method and a note? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a location recommendation I can do some research. I am free on Wednesday but I gotta say earlier is better for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well while my personal style is nothing but tshirts and jeans I do obsessively watch fashion tv. So I'm pretty good at that sort of thing. I'd love to be involved if you're interested in having me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd save my allowance and when I was 15 I'd use it all to buy Amazon and Google stock at it's low.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT is much rather be shot than the victim of an acid attack. 

Let's keep guns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's when Ruth bader Ginsberg exposes her chest to show an insanely detailed tat of a woman getting spit roasted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed that one. I'm soon going to see everything on Netflix due to insomnia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have kidnapped him and made him release season 3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone says that the group part is informative and I'm sure to eventually go. Idk if I've developed some social anxiety or something, but I kinda gotta work my way up to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. What's worse is from now on when people check my reddit history this will come up. I think I'll have to make an alt account and utilize that for when I inevitably need reddit to help me out if a jam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a series he's gotten. The whole film will be on him in a few years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm jerk but I'm not an idiot. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kinda hope to cut to this guy like 10 years from now and he's one of those Kirk Cameron super Christians. And he's got this tattooed on him for life.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This tattoo makes me want to kill all humans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an epic prank. Idk if I have the dedication to get a tattoo and then get all my Bros to cum on me to fool everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's supposed to help you work on things but idk she said I didn't have to do that. 

I'm pretty sure she'll broach the topic later. But for now I don't have to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean nothing. Everyone knows, if you're going to get a tattoo get one that shows what you love.

I choose bender. But I guess that's his bender.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do people really pm you that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even in a garage I'm not sure this would go over well. 

Idk if I'd even want to buy crack from this dude after seeing that. 

I'd be like, "you know what, I think I'm gonna go to rehab." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tons. Is that not normal? No wonder I can't get hired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an idiot. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I went to the first appointment DBT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well after realizing I was being one of those weirdo jerks that just flat out dismisses things based upon no actual experience and hearsay only, I sucked it up and went.

It wasn't so bad. I'm still not fond of it, but at least she said I didn't have to commit to any group stuff for now. So that was good. 

I thought it would be rigid and like going to school or something and you gotta do this and that and no room for making me comfortable with the thing.

So I'm going to give it a decent chance to work. We shall see what happens.


Thanks to everyone who told me to try it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking for a friend as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you draw cum often? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was from a video on FB. I didn't know how to like capture it or whatever so I took screenshots. But it looked pretty legit. Also it's on his arm. Which is super nice for extra trashyness. It'll be amazing at the water park.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was told a rule, 

If you meet 1 person and they're an asshole, it's just bad luck.
If everyone you meet is an asshole, you're the actual asshole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously to get lots and lots of job offers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eris? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. I'd need to see this artist. 1. To smack him for doing this. 2. To get some work done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great tattoo work but a totally WTF idea. He'll really enjoy it when he's a grandfather. Xpost - trashy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone actually got this tattooed on them. Nice quality work but trashy AF. NSFW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how you feel. I'm here for you.

Like I literally have had people say that I hate my son because I wish he didn't have autism or complain about the utter difficulty that our lives (mine, my husband, and my son) now entail.

It sounds like autism. It wasn't until later that my son got better with other kids. But he does love playing with adults. 

He's nonverbal so it could be communication issues that make it hard for him to play with other children. Just like your son has hearing loss and that might make it hard for him to play with other children. 

Try talking with early intervention. And I hear that some people like and find enjoyment in support groups for parents if children with special needs. 
I have only gone to one or two. I didn't like it. 


I hope everything works out. 

If you wanna bother me. I'm available. 

Much love to you. You're doing some hard work. Also fuck anyone who makes you feel bad. They don't know what it's like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 07:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on mirena and asked my psych about this same thing. He said it's only relevant for oral contraceptives. 

I suppose if multiple other sources say otherwise, check again. Maybe with your gyn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where you live but a lot of pharmacies have prescription clubs that reduce the fee for some meds.

Mine did a few like Prozac and some other common ones. 

They cost me about 3$ per 30 days.

I'm not sure what your financial situation is so I can't say. Also try and see if you qualify for Medicaid. I believe there may also be a buy in program but I'm not sure because I only know of one from NYC which is much different than other places.

Anyway. Good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 11:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless it was the hardest jump in the world, there's a good chance it wasn't anything that caused it. I've had numerous friends who were in car accidents or fell down stairs while pregnant. And they didn't lose their kids. 

Sometimes it's just the luck of the draw.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 10:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knowing it's not just me is helpful. at least I'm not the only weirdo, or whatever. 

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry about that. I'm sure you can rework things with your friends. Everyone has had a terrible GF/BF who made them choose friends or them. 

I'm sure they'll understand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a much calmer person than I. I'd have backed over him in my car. Lol. 

What a jerk. 

If you want to sit on a machine and do reps with no added weight other than the initial bar you're allowed. I used to do that all the time when I'd throw out my arm. It helped to move it but I couldn't do weight. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think my grandfather. Died 2 years ago or 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they said they're pretending I'm dead. I was even specifically told not to come to my grandfather's funeral. 

Which considering he raised me from the age of 7. Is basically like being told, you can't come to your dad's funeral.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm so depressed and lonely </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one friend and he lives in Scotland. I mean I have my husband, but that's it.

I'm only moderately close with my brother. I'm completely cut off from the rest of my family. I guess maybe because they're all narcissistic jerks. But it's possible my then undiagnosed bipolar disorder had a play in the rift.

I'm fairly certain that it's the reason why I lose friends like people lose keys.

I just wish someone liked me. You gotta spread your crazy out you know. You can't just unload it all on one friend. 

 Idk maybe this is just a vent. Or idk maybe I should be asking advice. But idk what that question would even be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's mainly the regulated breathing combined by attempting to empty one's mind. Which isn't a thing I'm comfortable with doing. But since I've been told by my friend that I'm being self destructive. And I really don't want to piss him off. I've decided to go and at the very least get the materials to have my pastor look over them for anything that would be concerning. 

Ultimately it's adiaphora and it's a matter of Christian liberty. Like I technically have no problem with yoga for exercise. Some people do. I have no problem with foul language. Some people do. 

It's just I don't want to give the impression that I'm cosigning certain things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While it's a matter of Christian liberty, and many don't. Even many other Lutheran's like myself. 

I'm not terribly fond of engaging in practices that are at their core based upon eastern religious beliefs.

I also don't pray with people that aren't of my denomination. 

I am concerned that may be a problem. But I'm going to see rather than just dismissing it from the start.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 10:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really appreciate you taking the time to write all this. I know you didn't have to so it's very appreciated. 


Thanks for telling me your experience. 


It sounds like it was very helpful to you. I guess I'll give it a shot. I'm not thrilled with it. I don't really have time for it either. But I'll do what I can.

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. It's usually the opposite in the states. 

I wish it wasn't because fresh mushrooms taste amazing IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk where you shop but at my supermarket precut frozen stirfry mix is like 1-2$ for a 14-16oz bag. Which is significantly cheaper than the fresh option </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? What do you mean? This is weird?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bi polar? Or something else?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is great, but there's other options. 

It's not like it's DBT or nothing at all. 

I didn't even hear of that til now. So there are definitely other types of therapy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I don't want to go. If given the opportunity to grow to accept the idea, I'd be more willing to be open minded.

And to be fair even if I were open minded about it. There's some stuff I don't like or want to engage in for personal reason or religious reasons. 

I don't do meditation. I don't like it. It's something I won't do. I've got like a zero tolerance wiggle room for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For regular normal talk therapy he's actually pretty good. I'm normally very closed off to outsiders but with him I immediately felt affinity with him to tell him about me cutting that one time. I'd normally have not said anything at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not basing in on AA. I actually had a good time at AA when I eventually went because I wanted to go and not because everyone was trying to force me to go. 

When I went because I wanted to, I shrugged off any bad things that happened because I wanted the help that was offered.

I just know myself. I know how I'm going to feel because of the forcefulness. 


I don't have a problem with talk therapy. I do have a problem with meditation. Signing contracts for things I don't want to do. A bunch of random rules.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. 

I can tell you now unless some miracle like Jesus rising from the dead happens in the first 2 or 3 sessions, I'm not going to like it. 

And literally anything that I don't like that happens in the first 3 weeks, will probably mean me quitting. 

I've quit jobs over things I didn't like happening in the first few weeks. And I like money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's both. 

I specifically chose him because he did both and I didn't want to go see two people. 

Because I hate that. 

And with this DBT crap, I'm going to not only apparently have to see a therapist and a psychiatrist but also a group. 

I not only don't have money for all that. I do that have time for all that. Or patience. And I don't want to have to explain things  3 different times to 3 different people or groups. 

It's more annoying than anything else for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will say this. I have an appointment. But my whole goal is to get him to stop harping on about it. 

So not really gonna be motivated to do much more than the bare minimum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want someone to talk to. I've literally got no one that I can just be myself with. 

90% of my distress comes from feeling like I've got no one to turn to when I'm upset, confused, or otherwise burdened. 

When it's you against the entire world, suicide and other bad ideas seem to be a good idea.  It's like I'm the only person on earth and everyone is a chat bot. And then lo I found a human. But nope it turns out to be a robot who just wants me to sing karaoke and I hate karaoke. I don't know if that's a good description of how I feel. But that's how I feel in my everyday life. 

Sure I can talk about some things online because you don't know me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can work myself up to it eventually. I can slowly get used to the idea and read up on it and ask people about it and talk about my fears and apprehensions for why I don't want to go with my therapist for a few weeks until I've gotten to the point where, okay I'm gonna go. 

But it's like telling me, you need to go swimming and I'm telling you I'm afraid of water. Well forcing me to go when I don't want to go isn't going to make me  enthusiastic about going. In fact forcing me when I'm not read is a sure fire way to making sure I'll have a terrible time and hate water even more than I did in the first place. 

All I want is the ability and leeway to go when I want to go. Shoot, all the force towards it makes me want to go less than originally. 

If he had said, "look into this thing and we'll keep doing therapy" 

I'd have looked into it and probably come back the next week like okay here's my questions. But instead he's like you're gonna go because I'm going to stop doing anything but forcing this upon you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how this ends tho. 

I'll do it for 3 weeks to make everyone happy and then I'll quit because I don't like it and don't want to do it. And because I'll now harbor resentment to my psychiatrist for making me go I won't return to see him either. 

And eventually I will descend into me sleeping all day and showering when I absolutely must. (1x a week). 

I don't want to do that. I just want to grow into doing the thing I don't want to do. 

It's like when I had a drinking problem. Everyone told me go to AA. But I didn't want to. Well I went. It was a disaster. And then I refused to get any help whatsoever because I harbored resentment for the program because of people forced me to do something that I didn't want to do when I wasn't ready. 

If that's what he wants. Cool beans. But ultimately it's my money. I should get the service I want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I sent this letter to my psychiatrist because I don't want to do DBT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sent this letter to my psychiatrist because I don't want to do DBT. His response was basically, I'm not going to force you, but I'm not going to do anything but force DBT on you til you do.

Idk what to do.

The letter I sent is below. 



I know you're busy and have a life and things to do.

But I'm just feeling very depressed and sad and lonely and isolated.

I get that you're concerned for my well being and think DBT is the best thing for me.

But I don't want to do it. And because I don't want to do it and you seem hell bent on me doing it. Its like I feel pushed. And when I feel pushed it makes me feel boxed in and choiceless.

And I get that maybe it's the best thing for me. (And sorry for the message, I'm much better in writing than in conversation). Maybe it's the greatest thing that I'll ever experience, but I just don't know if right now is that time.

I wasn't even going to do talk therapy in the first place. But I figured that it would be a good place for me to discuss and possibly learn how to deal with the crippling disappointment that I feel in my daily life.

But it's like we can't talk about it. We can't discuss it. Because you don't want to do anything but this silly DBT thing. And I venture that no matter how great it is, it probably doesn't have a 100% success rate.

Why can't we just operate under the assumption that it doesn't work for me. At least until idk I'm willing to do group therapy, or interested in DBT. Or not so much of an anti newage skeptic person.

Why isn't that an option?

Rather than making me feel like here's yet another place where ivgreen is forced to do something that she doesn't want to do because of someone else?

My entire life is that. 24hrs a day 7 days a week. My life is nothing but me doing things I hate because someone else wants or needs me too. And I hate it. And I wish I was dead because of it.

And I know that Sisyphus was happy during his task, but I'm not him. I'm miserable doing all these things that I don't want to do. And now it's like here's this other thing.

But I know what I can do all on my own the way I want. So maybe that's why I think of suicide all the time. Who knows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I made and appointment with a DBT therapist. I don't want to go. I don't want to follow a bunch of stupid rules. And I don't want to do 4+ hours of therapy a week. 

Nevertheless I guess I'll do it at least until i've gone enough to justify me saying that it doesn't work and I dislike it. 

Tho tbf I probably just don't want to do anything that changes me. I probably do really want to kill myself and really do find cutting comforting and am scared that this program will change me in some way that I don't end up killing myself and I don't keep on cutting.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I didn't think so but could only say for sure what I knew to be true in my state.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is I'd literally rather go to jail than a group. I've done AA and that's cool but I only liked smoking cigarettes with the guys afterwards not the actual meetings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we fit. he's nice and kind and I like him.

I don't like 99% of people I encounter. So it was kismet. Now I gotta find someone else and I didn't even really want to do therapy on the first place. And now I have to see a person and a group. Which is worse than just therapy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah it's that he thinks DBT would be the most helpful and he doesn't do it. Idk why he's throwing me out like trash  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Therapist/Psychiatrist wants me to do DBT with someone else. But it feels like abandonment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I was at odds with the guy at times but he seems so nice and kind and I felt like I could actually trust him. 

But today he told me that he thinks that DBT would benefit me best and that I should go to therapy with someone who does that. But I don't want to go somewhere else.

And I definitely don't want to do DBT. With all its stupid rules and group. Like gross I don't want to do that.

Nevertheless now I'm all sad because why doesn't anyone ever stay. Everyone sends me away and no one ever really cares about me. It's all bullshit lies. Everyone leaves. 

No one really cares.
I just am so tired of meeting people, letting them in and then they go. 
And I'm tired of not being able to do what I want.

It makes me really just want to die. But then that probably wouldn't fix anything. I'd probably just be like rejected from hell and heaven cuz I'm trash. Or whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk about your state but they don't have to wear a vest where I live.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah definitely. It is hard with public meltdowns. It's weird how little I give a shit about what other people think now. 

I used to care very much about appearances. 

Now I'm like, yep that's my son who decided to take his shoes off in Denny's, what of it. 

It's weird tho randomly mentioning to people before they come over, that my son's probably going to touch them randomly to get to know them and also he is probably going to strip naked at some point so you may see a naked child at some point during the Superbowl party so you know just tell me and I'll handle it. 

But knowing why my son wasn't talking. Or why he only wanted to eat pasta and cereal. Or why he refused to eat away from the house. Was good. Because then you can develop strategies to deal with it. 

It does get better. And I'm not sure if that's just a things improve thing or a you stop caring so much thing. 

On one hand the more independent I see him get with his schooling and therapies does help me to be less worrisome about his future which weighs heavily on me. And also I have changed a bunch of my expectations of the parenting experience. 

I've definitely replaced West point graduate with him passing a community college certificate program in anything he's interested in. 

And I gotta say, it's probably for the best that he had autism. I'd probably have been a massive jerk like my parents with a bunch of overly insane ambitions for him. I've had a lot of time to work on my parenting skills and expectations for others and myself since then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first it is. It take a lot more money, time, resources and more to deal with. 

For one, I didn't expect to be changing diapers 9 years later when I first had my son. It wasn't something I had planned on. And if someone had told me that I'd be caring for my kid for basically my entire life well into my elderly years (as is extremely likely) I don't think I'd have had a child. 

Now that I've gotten to know him and parent him and be friends with him. It's much different. When you are standing on the starting line, it's daunting. Like eating an entire elephant. 

You're gonna sit there and be like "fuck me what did I get myself into". 

It's normal to be scared. 

Now tho, I'd kill the person that tried to take him away from me. I'd work my hardest to destroy anyone who harmed him. He's my world. But that first day, month, year. It was frightening. 

And letting other parents know that it's normal and okay to be scared, and upset is good. 

I spent years pushing that fear and sadness away til I ended up a drunk. Because everyone made me feel like shit if I even mentioned a fraction of how I really felt. 

I reckon it's how parents feel when they have a daughter and wanted that daughter to be a ballerina and she's into trucks. Not on the same level, but there's some disappointment there because you had a plan and it didn't work out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It takes a while.

There was a point where I just wanted to die. I still do half the time. 

I drank myself towards oblivion for 2 years.

I tried hard to make everything work. To be happy and the person people wanted me to be.

People think that a kid with a disability just is overnight accepted. It isn't.

There's a large amount of me that hates everyone and everything because *MY Son* has autism.

I did everything right. I ate all the proper foods, avoided everything I was supposed to, did everything right. But alas I have a kid with autism and my ex friend who drank and did drugs while pregnant with both her children has normal kids.

Sometimes I hate God. Sometimes I fear I hate my son. Sometimes I hate my husband. And sometimes, I probably actually hate my son. A lot of the time I hate myself.

From 2012 to 2014 I drank while my son was at school and after he'd gone to bed. All the while wishing I could just leave and live in a trailer on a reservation drinking myself to death like I'd been told my father had done.


Even now, I constantly think about suicide. Every day, no matter how great or bad the day is. It often seems like the only way out of Autism. But then I remember that he needs me and I don't.


To get to the point where I wasn't just faking happiness and functionality, it took a lot of therapy.


It's going to be a while. He may need to talk to someone. He might never be able to deal. Some people take it harder. Typically men. Like they fucked up somehow. That's how I feel. Like I did something wrong and this is my fault. I logically know it isn't. I logically know that things don't work like that. But the brain is tricky. 

It allows you to know a logical thing but also know an illogical thing and still despite your brain yelling that it's not logical to think that you created this situation, to follow that illogical thought to the point of destroying yourself, knowing also that destroying yourself won't logically fix it and still working towards the idea that it will. 

Give him time. 

I seemed fine at first. I was the perfect autism mom for the first year or so. Exemplary. But eventually all that faking took a toll. 

If he's not taking it well at the start let him. It's best for everyone. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Familiarity helps. But ultimately we just always have 4 people on hand to help hold my son down. 

One on the legs, one on the body, and one on each arm. Plus they have a board. 

It's not great at facilitating happy feelings but ultimately it's not that bad. 

However I did take him with me once to get my own blood drawn and I think he remembered that for the next time and was less anxious. 

Maybe you can get some blood work done at the same time. And he can see how well you do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 09:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I went back and reread and it did sound like I was being a massive jerk. 

Lol. I need a  Clarity checker more so than a spell checker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant with accepting your children. I too have mental health issues. But I'm definitely a much better parent than the people that raised me. 

Idk what their problem was. I hope it was just untreated mental health issues, as opposed to just some people being evil without redemption.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you have mental health issues, you should be fine.

I've found that the love bears all things.

I literally love my son so much, I think if he became a zombie, I'd likely go all weird and feed people to him like in the Santa Clarita Diet. 

Lol. 

Good luck! Four months is probably the worst part of parenting in my opinion. The novelty has worn off and they still aren't fun enough yet. And in my case he was still a night owl so I was like tired and annoyed. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reflections on the 7th Anniversary of My sons Autism Diagnosis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today is the 7th anniversary of my son being diagnosed with Autism. I'm rereading some of the posts from that day, and it's almost like someone died. I guess technically the child that I dreamt of having (the one that would go to west point, and yale, and become a five star general) did die that day. And while it took a few years, eventually I accepted the child that I have. He's really smart, he can't talk, but he has his own distinct voice.

It wasn't what I planned, and that hard to get past even 7 years later. But, the journey with him, is one that is overwhelmingly positive. We both love science museums, books, and futurama. Plus he introduced me to Rick and Morty (My new favorite show). And ultimately we just mesh. Whether he be a future astronaut, cashier, scientist, or fry cook, he's my Corbin and that's ultimately all that matters.

"All the adversity I've had in my life, all my troubles and obstacles, have strengthened me... You may not realize it when it happens, but a kick in the teeth may be the best thing in the world for you. " Walt Disney </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my what an in appropriate reaction to help. 

Shit, take it or leave it you were just trying to help. 

The problem lies with them not you. 

Thanks for being such a kind person. Things like that make me go, "well fuck them and everyone else in the future".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rube. Well at least they'll get their comeuppance when they get that rejection letter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk what the fuck I was thinking. Probably typing on my phone. Grrr I'm an idiot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol definitely just doing this in my house thus far. Maybe if i magically acquire an ability to catch the beat, i'll take a class outside. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was pretty good, tho my self-esteem is taking a hit. That stereotype about black people having rhythm seems to have missed me. I'm a hot mess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't like them don't say anything. Otherwise, letting them no is the nicest thing you can do. I wouldn't tell them because I'm a thirsty jerk. But you don't want to be a thirsty hater like me. Be nice, tell them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i think you're right. There's like this hypomania / mania type part of me that wants to destroy myself. 

So i'll basically do anything I can to get to that point. be it ruining my marriage by sexting with random guys, or spending the rent money on video games and a thousand bottles of shampoo cuz it was a really good deal. Or being obsessed with drinking. 

Today i tried learning some salsa. so that seemed like a good outlet. and it was fun and didn't involve me hurting myself or anyone else with my actions. 

Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. 

I hope you also stay tough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> trying hard to not make terrible choices while in hypomania [tw selfharm] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in a temporary moment of clarity (basically i was talking with someone about their heroin addicted son and realized sometimes you have to 'snitch' on people to get them help that they clearly need) I realized that my psych and therapist as well as my husband might be right about the self harm thing. 

I guess I'm in like a hypomania state right now. Cuz I have tons of energy, I'm very focused on my goals, and I have some weird self destructive plans. 

Like I tend to super over spend and make tons of terrible choices. I get super angry, super quickly. And I become terribly obsessed with doing things like either drugs or cutting. 

so today I'm trying to work my safety plan. But I really really really really just want to cut. Like i'm not even upset, it's just like this thing i'm obsessing with right now. tho i do feel extremely lonely. but idk.

I tried the meditation, talking to people, and a few other things. I'm just idk nearing the end of my list and i really don't want to bother my psych. i'm always bothering him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are most motivation quotes things that I read in the AA big book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't know what i'd most benefit from. I'd love suggestions. i'd considered committing myself. but i'm not even sure if thats a good idea. like would that even be a good plan for me. maybe i can discuss it at my next session.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also thanks for saying you're concerned. It's nice of you to say. Tho i strongly doubt you are, you don't even know me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC he has both a PhD in psychology and a MD in internal medicine and psychiatry. 

  I mean spending an hour or more each week talking in detail about why you feel the way you do, in a way that's not geared at "fixing" it with medication

at the first session that we had he said the goal was to utilize both medication and talk therapy to address my issues and help me to live my best life. 

I mean, I'm not necessarily sure he's the best dude out there. Mainly because i'd much rather talk about other shit rather than the cutting. and he's kinda forcing me to deal with that first cuz he said something about the hierachy of needs and that saftey is one of the basic ones and cutting isn't safe. 

I'll research a few other people. Tho i'll likely end up not doing anythign because it took a lot to trust one person. And i'm sure i'll just sleep on it until it gets so bad i can't function before i do anything about it again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well he's a psychiatrist and psychologist. so he does my therapy and my meds. i found that easier than dealing with 2 people. 

and i filled out the ridiculous safety plan thing he wanted me to make. tho i didn't know what to put down for the stupid "whats one thing I've got to live for".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I'll give you that I'm probably irrational. I really don't like not getting my way. And he may be interested in my safety. Tho I do not know for sure. He might just be in it for the paycheck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even really want to be a wife and mother. But if I gotta live up to the responsibilities I took on and promises I made
 I should at least be able to do 1 thing I want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand the keeping others alive. But isn't it my body? Shouldn't I be allowed to remove this body from the world if I deem it necessary. Or cut it if I deem it necessary to me getting things done. 

Til now I was sitting around laying around and wishing I were dead. At least now I can bear living enough to do things that make me productive. The house is clean, I'm baking, I'm doing extra shit that I don't have to. 

I'm super mom and super wife. 

I found a way to do that. And if cutting a few times a week makes that happen, I don't see how anyone has the right to stop me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does he have my best intentions in mind? Or is he just doing his job that he gets paid for. 

And I'm not entirely sure that my husband did it because he cares. 

I can't read intentions but it seems like it was just to dick me over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO it doesn't foster trust. 

If I can't trust my husband to not snitch then I can't trust him. If I can't trust him, then marriage is pointless. Trust is paramount in marriage. Now I can't trust him. 

And as for the doctor, now I can't trust him. I told him no, and he did it anyway. 

I don't forgive violations of my trust. So now, instead of being honest about cutting. I'm just gonna lie and say I'm good. 

Just like when I went to a doctor to help me stop drinking and when I kept failing to stay sober, she threatened to get my child taken away from me. 

So from that point on, I was only as honest as necessary. It was all surface stuff from then on. Nothing really big that might have helped me deeply. Yeah I was less stressed but the deep shit that I really needed help with, like the fact that I never ever stop thinking about suicide. 

I'll be having a great day and I'll think, "what a great day, I should probably kill myself and go out on a high note." 

But I couldn't tell her that because I feared that I couldn't trust her. 

Now I know I can't trust this guy. So now it's pointless to tell him anything more than surface stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you think he's a good one? Why? 

It's been very upsetting for me. His actions have made me very angry with him. And additionally my husband. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he did come to one appointment. But when he asked about calling my husband, I said no but he said he'd do it either with me there or after I left because he was concerned and had a duty to do so. 

But IMO it's bullshit because me saying no don't call him should have been enough to make it like he couldn't have called. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do i have to find a new one? can i just be like, i'm not going to see anyone else, take more meds, or anything, just going home and done with this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TW SelfHarm Bipolar 2, Problem with Psychiatrist whom also runs my therapy sessions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i found this psych who was really nice and he seemed to click all the boxes that i needed clicked in what i look for. He was a similarish christian denom and political philosophy, he seemed attentive and intellectual and very nice. Someone I can easily talk to and relate to. 

Anyways, at first i'd been diagnosed as PTSD and Depression. He switched me from prozac to effexor. however, after about a week I got all happy and stuff. And i did make some weird choices like spending all the rent and bill payments (ie car payments etc) on random and not necessary things. Well, he said thats part of being bipolar and thought i was maybe bipolar. So he subscribed lithium. 

I was none to thrilled. anyway i got back into cutting but before i cut i called him up and was like look, i want to cut and my bff thought it was a good idea for me to call you. 

Anyways he called my husband to get him to check in on me and stuff. and then he said to try some breathing exercises and i was technically supposed to go into the hospital if i actually didn't think i was able to keep myself from cutting. 

I didn't do that shit. I just cut myself anyway, but not until later because i was good until i heard some frustrating news from my brother about my shit family. 

So i cut a little tiny bit. and that was that. and a few pricks with a pin and stuff. whatevers. 

So when i went to the appointment today he asked if i cut, i said yeah because i'm a fucking adult and it happened but i was over it. 

Anyway he decided to call my husband to let him know to lock up all the sharp objects and medications and stuff. And i feel like thats a mad violation of privacy. 

Like 1, i'm an adult. and 2, it fucked up.

then my husband like a fucking buster was like, oh let me tell you about her pricking herself with a pin. snitches on me. Anyway i don't even want to be married to him any more. 

Am i being rediculous. 

also i dont want to go back to the guy. But i worry if i refuse he'll like have me committed or something. 

any advice is appreciated. 

thanks in advance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r[ough draft of my sketch](http://imgur.com/d8kzWRe). i got a little busy.

its supposed to be a woman looking at her phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks I think i did the beard backwards. I did like the white block and then tried to put in the black but that's good advice for the main colour as the solid colour and hten adding in the light colour like i was trying to do. I knew it looked wrong but i couldn't figure what i was doing wrong. 

and that's smart with the really dark background and then the other shades. I think that was bothering me but i was having such a shit time at figuring out what i wanted to do. Everything kept getting washed out but i couldn't figure out what was the problem and now i realize that it's the background being so light. thanks! you give good tips. 

I love criticism because it really helps me to get better and sometimes someone else sees a problem that you couldn't pull out on your own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I rather felt like crying so I figured I'd do robin williams. 

[My interpretation](http://imgur.com/xBhb2yy)

[The reference photo.](http://imgur.com/OXxn401) 


I had some trouble with this. so any critique is welcome. 

 [](/help)

- [](/critique)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 11:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a random cartoon I made https://imgur.com/8w2A6c9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 11:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally photos from the past. I'm so tired of these historians saying there weren't pictures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still feeling ill. so not very detailed. hopefully i feel better tomorrow. so i can knock it up another notch. http://imgur.com/qnUW1dp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> quick sketch. http://imgur.com/eImp19Z </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> quick sketch. http://imgur.com/eImp19Z </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [MY version](http://imgur.com/fX6VvLU) and the[ reference picture](http://imgur.com/aiRQ1X3) for lipstick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it says prescriptions count toward the maximum but not the deductible. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks i typed in deductible and oopm and didn't get anything that explains anything. I'll check for the evidence of coverage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you meet your OOP limit but not your deductible do you still have to meet your deductible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to make things easier lets say that I paid a bunch of money for some prescriptions. MY OOP max is 800. My deductible is 500. But I didn't pay more than 200 towards my deductible. The prescriptions cost me about 600 but don't count toward the deductible.  

Will i still have to pay the remaining 300 for the deductible or would I be exempt from that? or will i still pay it but get a check for the balance i paid toward the prescriptions? 

Thanks in advance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 05:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just made some shape pattern thing in illustrator. I was feeling pretty I'll today. 

Random shapes https://imgur.com/gallery/DAuaY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 04:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [First picture I made this year](http://imgur.com/cOXzVV2). I totally had a lot of shit going on today. So I'm going to just post this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I decided to do [Obergruppenfuher Smith](http://imgur.com/JF05bKJ) from Amazon's Man in the High Castle. Warning: Nazi symbol and it's also not complete. The day got really hectic. But i figured i'd share what i had done and then finish it for friday. Also not really spoilerish but maybe a little.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're the only thing [keeping the galactic federation from destroying us](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S-Bxe1VS3jQ feature=youtu.be). A necessary evil. LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alt theme: Damask Patterns. [there's 999 haunts but we have room for 1 more.](http://imgur.com/rf7yqRj) 

I'm thinking of putting a zombie face in front of it, but I'm still working on that and I just kinda wanted to get this out by itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, you're great. What tutorials are you using?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Garak ain't no one to mess wit'!](http://imgur.com/RGrVivz) Here he is wishing you "Peace amongst worlds" 

Also any other Trekkies out there?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 04:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember Him!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
