<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3726</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for taking the time to answer this! It's so helpful. There are three I'm still a little confused about. If I were looking to practice my verbs with Verbe Du jour - where would I cover the duolingo catagories called *pluperfect*, *past conditional*, and *past subjunctive*? Perhaps there is no direct equivalent for these?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's those damn supermarkets are the trick I think! I'm not near one, so usually I'm buying wine either at the posh wine shop or the corner shop across the road. To be very honest I'm not confident around wine at all, and that's probably because I don't *love* it. In fact if I'm buying wine I'm more often than not thinking about using it for cooking! I leave the wine for drinking to my partner, who knows much more about it than me. If I knew more I'd be better at identifying these 'mid' quality wines that are well suited to cooking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually wasn't aware there was such a thing as 'cooking wine'! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are on different food budgets!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the half bottles of wine you can buy are a fantastic idea. I get them when I can. Generally they are only sold here in the really big supermarkets, and I rarely visit them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  bottles I haven't managed to finish

We're in different realities! Thanks for the comment though :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wine in cooking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everybody
I have a question to you all about using wine in cooking. 
For a while now (at least this is true here in the UK) the orthodoxy that has been drummed into us is: *only cook with wine that you would drink*. Now, I enjoy using wine in cooking and do so often - especially now when it's cold outside. But the thing is - the wine we drink is *expensive* - honestly, at between 8 to 10 a bottle, it makes for really very extravagant stock! In addition, if for example I'm using red wine as a marinade for meat, I'm probably going to chuck a splash of red wine vinegar in there, and this feels terribly wasteful when using a really good bottle of wine. Does anyone else have this problem with wine in cooking? What do you do? Do you always stick to the wine rules? Anyone else dread the humiliation of entering a wine shop and telling them you're looking for 'something to cook with'? The looks I've gotten in the past! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verb help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi - first time poster here - hope this question is within the rules! I am learning French on duolingo and have completed my 'tree' so to speak. I find now that my stumbling block (that never seems to get improve) is the verb tenses. I had a search through this sub and found a link to a brilliant site, www.verbedujour.com, which is a basic learning tool focusing exclusively on verbs. For the moment, I only want to focus on the tenses covered in duolingo. My problem is the various tenses appear to have quite different  names depending where you look. The names given on duolingo are: 

*Past imperfect*

*Compound past*

*Infinitive*

*Pluperfect*

*Gerund*

*Future*

*Imperative*

*Conditional*

*Past conditional*

*Past subjunctive*

The names for the verb tenses in Verbe Du Jour are:

*Prsent*

*Futur*

*Imparfait*

*Pass simple*

*Conditionnel*

*Subjunctif prsent*

*Subjunctif imparfait*

*Participe pass*

*Impratif*

*Participe prsent*

*Axiliaire*

Can anyone match these terms up for me?  Or, can someone tell me which tenses from Verbe Du Jour I should practice in order to cover those included in Duolingo? Some are obvious, but others I'm finding quite confusing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you have any recommendations on american humanist filmmakers?

I'm not really sure what you mean by 'humanist' film makers, but these two spring to mind:

Sean Durkin *Martha Marcy May Marlene* (2011)

Abel Ferrara *Bad Lieutenant* (1992)

why does the europeans seem to be more interested in humans, rather than plot?

Well, the vast majority of all films have a plot and very few films are not interested in the human aspect of their narratives. Having said that, a couple of the film makers you mention (Tarr and Costa) would be considered by some to be deeply pretentious. Whether you agree with that or not, you're moving into a style of film that is so far removed from what we think of as 'American' film making, I don't really see the problem in simply admitting that you don't particularly like American films. Generally speaking, I prefer European cinema to films from the US - it's just a matter of personal preference. There are a few directors in America who exist very much on the fringes of the industry you might be interested in. Check out Todd Solondz (just IMO *Palindromes* (2004) is one of his best), and the non-Hollywood films of Gus Van Sant (specifically his trilogy *Elephant*, *Last Days*, and *Paranoid Park*). 

P.S. If you consider a move towards American film as a process of 'de-snobbing' yourself, you *are* a snob! :-)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the time and thought that's gone into your interpretation - it's very interesting. To my mind, however, you're imbuing this movie with depth it does not possess!! Chazelle has chosen *Rebel Without A Cause* because it's one of the few iconic films from what can conceivably be thought of as 'old Hollywood' that is *set in L.A.*. Chazelle is attempting to discover a sort of 'cultural heritage' to ground the theme of Los Angeles in his film. Ironically, *Rebel Without A Cause* was also one of the first movies to attempt a gritty, realist portrayal of L.A. street life, far away from the fantasy land of Hollywood *La La Land* celebrates. In this way *Rebel* is the predecessor of films like *Boyz N The Hood*, having very little in common with the Hollywood musical *La La Land* is so nostalgic for. When Stone and Gosling have their romantic night at the Planetarium, are they not just like the businessman who crosses the scene at the very end of *Rebel Without A Cause* - completely oblivious to the problems in the streets around him? It's just one of the *many* inconsistencies that kept me confused throughout this movie!

Hollywood has no culture. Hollywood is a mirror - a cypher for culture from *elsewhere*. That's why films about Hollywood have tended to be cynical or even dystopian - *Sunset Boulevard, The Day Of The Locust, The Player* etc - or else they've taken the fantasy route and buried themselves safely in a glorious past - *Singin' In The Rain* or even 2011's *The Arist*. *La La Land* makes the bold move of setting itself in contemporary Hollywood while maintaining an upbeat, positive *Singin In The Rain* demeanour. This is pretty original - I can't think of another example. For me, however, the experiment fails. Chazelle fails to really pin down a coherent version of Hollywood, drawing a colourful screen over Hollywood's well documented dark side (industry parties where *nobody* is snorting coke??), turning a blind eye to the violence and deprivation just over the fence (did anyone notice a single pair of saggers??), leaving us with.... well - what? Memories? Memories of movies - the vast majority of which were not set in L.A. - not written or directed or acted by people from L.A. - and in fact could have been filmed *anywhere* with the appropriate technical facilities. To add to the confusion, Chazelle proceeds to throw contemporary Jazz into the mix, thereby adding a whole other cultural element of LA that has little to do with Hollywood  - aayyeesh! It's a cultural melting pot indeed - but a confusing and stressful one - and *not* one that contains any resemblance to the cultural melting pot that is contemporary Los Angeles!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 11:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Yi Yi* - *Fanny Och Alexander* (the original TV version) - *The Double Life Of Veronique*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 11:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I consider La La Land unintentionally existential.

I know exactly what you mean. Halfway through the film I thought *WTF am I doing here?*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 11:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lesley Manville?? That's awesome - good on her!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Susan is very shallow.

I did question the casting of Amy Adams in this regard. I think Adams is one of the best of our current crop of Hollywood A-listers - and she seems to be getting better and better with each role - I really rate her very highly. But in this film.... I wonder. Thing is, I *can't not like* her. Of course, if Ford had cast an *un*likable actress the film wouldn't have worked at all. But casting someone as thoroughly likeable as Adams.... I like her so much I think I was *always* on Susan's side!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really interesting observations - thanks. 

Do you think the narrative would have been strengthened by just a *little bit* more information on Susan and Edwards split, and maybe on the impact the nature of the split and the termination had on Edward?

Do you think the ending would have been strengthened by *some* indication, however subtle, that the events of the film had inspired Susan to move on from her crisis? This could be the possibility that she will leave her husband - or even the opposite; a determination to continue with her life as it was before and to once more bury all thoughts of Edward. Or perhaps there might simply have been more of an indication of the choices facing Susan now - a question - what is she going to do now? The final close up of Susan's eye was a stylish ending, but there was a blankness to it I found dissatisfying. It emphasised the idea that Susan has been duped - the ending becomes Edward's in a way, and I think I would rather it belonged to Susan, as it was her character I felt invested in. 

In retrospect, after thinking about this film quite a lot, my biggest criticism of it would be a feeling that Ford is seperating different 'types' of creativity into 'authentic' and 'superficial'. The 'authentic' creativity would be exemplified by Edward's novel - the 'superficial' by slick and commercial contemporary art. He's romanticising the former I fear. I wonder if this could be the opinion of a man who has spent a lifetime in fashion, and perhaps indulges fantasies that taking a 'deeper' path - maybe becoming a film maker for example - would prove to be more fulfilling. There's something rather immature about this attitude, no? As if the literary world is any less beholden to superficial trends and commercial cynicism than the world of contemporary art. I don't buy it! 

(I liked this movie a lot - if I didn't I wouldn't be thinking about it so much!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saw Nocturnal Animals. I was pretty impressed with this film and engaged throughout - but I found it confusing. I felt like Ford had something to say, but I'm not sure what. Anyone care to tackle any of these questions? (**WARNING: Spoilers**); 

For starters, who do you think was the protagonist in this film? Who was the hero of the piece? Edward, or Susan (or both or neither). 

Does Ford *like* contemporary art, or view it as garbage? Was there something more authentic or worthwhile in the creative act of writing a novel in comparison to a creating a piece like the dancing ladies installation of the opening sequence? 

Is there a connection to be drawn between the various 'murders' in the narrative i.e. the murders in the novel and the termination of Susan and Edward's child (or even - at a stretch - the 'murder' of their love)?

Was Jake Gylenhaal's fictional character's (was his name Tony?) ending a triumph or a tragedy? Had he evolved into a 'stronger' man - or did his death indicate the terrible cost of such a transformation? 

:-)

Ps - anyone think this is worth making an actual post about? I can't find much discussion of Nocturnal Animals on the rest of the sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  culinary masturbation

Thanks for including this image in a post about oyster cream. Won't get this out my head for a day or two. :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be down hearted. If we can conquer pork today, tomorrow the world is ours! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 11:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Ayyeessh - this is *long* - sorry!)

Hi I've been following this thread and although I'm not on your side (sorry!) I think it's cool that you are arguing LLL's corner without getting angry about it, as many do when discussing this film. I also thought Birdman was far from perfect so we can be friends about that later (!). 

For me, however, the positive points you make about LLL's structure and writing  - groundwork for characters being laid before they appear; thematic motifs returning throughout; environment used as a symbol of the central characters inner life - are really just observations on some very basic narrative devices. These are things movies are *supposed* to do - they are very basic starting points! I think that those of us who didn't rate the film very highly are looking for more, dare I say 'deeper' content. I would stress here that this only applies to LLL because of its rapturous reception by many critics, audiences, and awards ceremonies. If LLL were just another fun movie these discussions wouldn't be happening. 

As for the music being memorable, yes I think it *is* a significant point. I remember very well music from the last 20 years! Even if we don't compare LLL to 'the greats' like Singin In The Rain, I remember (in all seriousness) much of the music in, for example, the Southpark movie. Southpark was, in my opinion, an excellent movie musical, and I could sing you bits and pieces of the score right now. I also have a vague recollection of some of the songs in The Muppets (2011). Particularly in the case of Southpark, I would also argue that the songs functioned far better in terms of story telling than those in LLL, often occurring when a character or situation was going through some kind of transition - they moved the story on basically, and were not simply incidental comments on the narrative as I felt they were in LLL (with the exception possibly of Emma Stone's audition song which was transitional). Comparing both film's opening songs, which in the tradition of musicals are intended to establish a sense of location, I would argue Southpark's 'Mountain Town' functions far better than 'Another Day Of Sun', quite brilliantly introducing the town and setting the scene for the action to come, while at the same time introducing the major characters. Frankly, I had *no idea* what on earth the performers in 'Another Day Of Sun' were singing about (I couldn't make out the lyrics!) and for me the song established absolutely zero!

At the end of the day, there is not that much to say about LLL, and this is the problem. This is nothing to do with it being a 'popular' movie. Even when we avoid comparisons to art house films such as Cemetery Of Splendour, LLL doesn't stand up well. To take Southpark as an example again, this silly and often peurile animated musical had, in fact, quite a serious political subtext which attacked the hypocrisy of political correctness and left leaning liberalism (this is something people rarely comment on - for all its subversion, Southpark has a conservative heart). Take, as another example, the massively popular crowd-pleasing comedy Bridesmaids. This bawdy movie contains a deeply subversive feminist subtext - I could deconstruct it for days! These popular, unchallenging, entertaining mainstream films are, none the less, *about* something! What is LLL *about*?!

My own theory is that LLL was intended simply as a loving homage to Los Angeles, using a template provided by Scorsese's New York New York - a loving homage to New York (I would go so far as to suggest Chazelle *wants* us to make the comparison - I mean *New York New York* - *L.A L.A* - it's in the title!). My ultimate criticism would be, therefore, that I left the cinema without a real feeling of L.A. I wasn't inspired by Chazelle's vision of the city - I didn't feel I knew anything unique about its spirit or its character. From a foreign perspective (I'm not from the US) the choice of jazz and theatre based song to celebrate the spirit of L.A. seemed to make far less sense than Scorsese's use of this music to celebrate New York, a city the rest of the world associates with this kind of music. I suspect Hollywood's embracing and promoting of LLL as a 'great movie' has to do with a sense of loyalty and nostalgia for their home town. A film about L.A. that's simply a shiny happy celebration - that's a rare thing, and after 20 years of PT Anderson cleverly dismantling Hollywood and presenting it to the world as a kind of heart of global darkness, Hollywood is going to grab it with both hands and celebrate this rare note of positivity, perhaps turning a blind eye to the real qualities of the movie itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And by who? This sub? 

Probably

So-called film buffs? 

Yes

Critics? 

Them too

The general public? 

Yup

Film scholars?

Definitely

:-)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gah! They're firing at me now! Good..bye..... cruel..... world... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Brood_Star was right in his comment above - you are barking up the wrong tree here my friend. While I admire your attempt to lift *La La Land* onto some serious level of discussion, the fact is it's just not appropriate material for serious debate. People like bright shiny colours and happy songs. That's about it. But listen - your original comment has, at the time of my writing, 19 upvotes. *La La Land* only got 35. You're more than half way to winning! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooh - downvoted to oblivion for dropping a truth bomb. You shall be rewarded in the afterlife my son.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know this - wow. Isn't it amazing this actress gave what was possibly the performance of her life just a few years ago in Amour? I will never forget her in that film - genuinely (I'm not just saying this) one of the best film performances I've seen. I forgot Riva was acting. It was miraculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was a brilliant actor - and classy as hell. I'm so impressed by his performances, it's hard to explain - he didn't draw a lot of attention to himself (if that makes any sense for an actor!), but quietly commited everything to character and story. He had a fascinating and unique presence - he could be kind of wicked when he wanted, or disdainful and cold, but underneath the surface you sensed a warm and tender heart. Anyone who could portray the vulnerability of the elephant man, and through all that make-up - that's amazing! His skill as a story teller was beyond compare - for me his narration in Dogville very nearly steals the show. When you think about how much he gave to that film with just his voice! He's an integral part of Dogville, and effortlessly achieves exactly the right tone - wry, knowing, ironic, but never giving too much away. A huge talent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   the most irksome thing is when people refuse to believe someone can not enjoy the same commercial cinema that they do.

I have the opposite problem sometimes. I can't believe people *can* enjoy some commercial cinema. It upsets me to an unreasonable degree I think. I don't know why it's so important to me - but it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I very much prefer art house to mainstream cinema these days - but there are always exceptions. The exceptions get fewer and fewer sadly - don't know if I'm changing or cinema is changing or both. But I can still appreciate a good mainstream movie. David O Russel is great IMO - love his run of movies from *The Fighter* to *American Hustle*. Love a lot of Pixar movies too, and there have been a few others. Good writing, solid craftsmanship and a level of emotional authenticity still exists in mainstream cinema for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did she? I didn't know that. It's great the oscars would give her a bit of recognition- she's *possibly* our greatest living screen actor. Definately in the running anyway! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True enough - good point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Emmanuelle Riva didn't win for *that* performance in *Amour*, I doubt Huppert, or any other French actor come to that, has a hope in hell!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the spirit of *fun* - Does anyone else occasionally experience periods when the whole world completely adores a movie you thought was an utterly worthless piece of garbage? Or if not utterly worthless, at least one that you really *really* don't see what the fuss is about? This has happened to me quite a few times. I won't name the current film that inspired this post (because I don't want this to become about that film), but my most recent periods of complete bewilderment and dismay have been caused by the enormous success of:

*Birdman* (2014)

*12 Years A Slave* (2013)

*The Artist* (2011)

*Tinker Tailor Soldier Spy* (2011)

What would your list be? When have you felt radically out of step with popular and critical opinion? What movies have made you seriously doubt your ability to tell good films from bad?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First one that springs to mind? The final scene of *La Dolce Vita* when all the party guests are walking down to the beach. Fellini's camera follows their backs mostly - the wind whips through their hair and flutters scarves - the camera gets close - moves back - it's a beautiful ballet of gliding movement, and completely magical. This has made me think also of the hat shop scene from Varda's *Cleo From 5 To 7* - a similarly magical little piece of sudden enchantment. I love it when that happens! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is *Rita Sue And Bob Too* (1987) obscure? It's a *very* British sex comedy set in the working class estates of Bradford. I love it - it's brazen, funny, energetic, and rough as hell. It also accurately portrays a period from my childhood I have never seen in any other film - teenage girls with big 80s hair, plastic shoes and knee length pastel cardigans. This is a celebration of a uniquely British attitude to sex - clumsy, giggly, unsophisticated - the very opposite to that regularly displayed by our French neighbours. Unusually however, the sexual content in *Rita Sue And Bob Too* displays none of the depressing 'wink wink' *Carry On* style of sexual comedy people associate with Britain. It's open and celebratory. This is rare for the UK.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I make carbonara practically every week and I have had this happen too. It may sound weird, but I've formed the impression that when I've overcooked the pasta a bit this dryness can tend to happen. Do not ask me why this might be. Apart from this you just need to up the liquid a bit. You'd be surprised how much liquid you can add to a carbonara without it turning soupy. Do you use vermouth? I always splash some dry vermouth into my bacon and let it bubble down a bit. I also add a large-ish ladle of pasta water to this mix, as well as not draining the pasta all that well. I use one egg per person - and in my house 160g of pasta is one serving (yes - I know). Don't add too much cheese to the eggs. As another commenter has mentioned (and been immediately shot down for) a dash of double (heavy) cream is a lovely addition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ignore these fools - if I happen to have cream to hand I always add a splash to my eggs for carbonara. Adding cream to anything **is never wrong**.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the kind of fascinating fact I want to remember but never do!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks - yeh I guess it was the rabbit maybe. I take your note about buttermilk being used mainly for fried chicken etc. I guess I was excited to use it because I found it at the market! I also take your point about braising - although I have had great results marinating rabbit and other game in cooked wine before braising. In retrospect the buttermilk thing doesn't quite feel right before a braise though - you're right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raw buttermilk as marinade fail. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Guys - my usual random kitchen question after a bit of a cooking fail! I'll make it short - purchased some *raw buttermilk* from the farmer's market. Despite it tasting absolutely horrible (like milk that should have been used two weeks ago) I persevered and used it to marinate a wild rabbit someone gave me (around 18 hours). My thinking was this would make for nice tender rabbit (I eat rabbit quite a lot and know it can be a bit tough). Anyway, short story shorter, this turned out to be the toughest rabbit I've ever eaten. It could be this was simply a tough old animal that would never be pleasant to eat. It could be that I messed up the cooking - but as I said I kind of know what I'm doing with rabbit (braised it low and slow in stock for 3 hours and rested for 30 minutes). Is there any chance this could have been something to do with the buttermilk? Does the marinating idea only work for specific meats?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey - not really to the point of this post (sorry) but *Tropical Malady* is my favourite film of his too (love the way we all go out of our way to not have to write out the guy's name!). What an intensely beautiful dream of a film - sweetly romantic and feverishly ritualistic in turn. I also loved *Syndromes*. I disagree with those who don't like the photography in *his* (!) films. He captures light like no other. *Syndromes* was like a poem written in light.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting explanation - thanks. My problem with Innaritu's idea there is that to me his films strongly communicate to an audience there is a great deal of literal meaning (a *message*) there to be followed and absorbed by the audience. There were so many ideas on everything from social media to post-modernism in *Birdman* it was bewildering - but it all *meant* something - and something *big*. So, if Tarkovsky includes a random firey comet in a film I take it for a poetic symbol of something intangible - as something I just go with and *feel*. With Innaritu my instinct is to look for *what it means*. If you're always telling the audience your movie is an allegory - don't make the allegory illusive. Gah! - illusive allegory is a *pet hate* of mine!! But, as I said, I did not connect with this film. 

*Uncle Boonmee* - we're now approaching a film experience that has little in common with the way regular audiences watch regular movies! The unpronounceable Thai (I will google it later!) makes films that are close to a meditative experience. You just have to sit with them - and yes that may well include getting a little bored here and there. It's a totally different ball game! Thanks for your interesting comment :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes you just don't connect with a film artist. It's frustrating (believe me - I *know*) when it's somebody that seems to be universlly adored. Kubrick is, IMO, a difficult artist. Not because his films are particularly clever (although of course they are often very clever), but because his ego is so apparent in his work. His presence can be stifling.

He is admired, I think, for his intellectual rigour, his audacity, and his extraordinary single mindedness. Kubrick pandered to *no-one* - not Hollywood, not his producers, not his actors, not even his audience. He pleased himself, and there is something inspiring about such an uncompromising artist. Basically he has massive balls. 

The work itself is often thrillingly dramatic. Kubrick had a great flair for composition, knowing when and where to push an audiences buttons to maximum effect. *The Shining* is a good example of this flair for drama, which at times borders on the theatrical. The theatricality is tempered by his direction of actors, which was punishing - he ground actors into submission by making them repeat a scene so many times they abandoned their ego. The technique worked - there is a style of 'Kubrickian performance', dry, measured, and assured, that is quite distinctive. Of course this combative approach (rather than collaborative) is another sign of the man's overwhelming ego. (There are exceptions in the case of the odd actor Kubrick seemed to genuinely admire - Peter Sellers and Jack Nicholson for example). 

He is also greatly admired for technical innovation, to which he was never so beholden that he allowed it overwhelm his story telling. The steady-cam in *The Shining* for example is used as a wonderful story-telling tool - never simply for the admiration of the technology itself. 

The downside of Kubrick is his extreme control can feel claustrophobic - it can easily turn the viewer off. In addition it meant that his portfolio was highly hit and miss. He did get things wrong, and such was his overwhelming command that his mistakes translate directly onto the screen. The result is that when he is good he is very very good, but when he is bad he is *rotten*. There are all kinds of reasons for not connecting with Kubrick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
