<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1166</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your worst experience with roadrage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have all waited for you to finish all 7 gens. Bravo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/patientdogs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calling all breaststrokers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have a question for all the breaststrokers out there, what is your technique to reduce drag? I've heard that trying to keep your head down helps out but I always accidentally breathe in water lol... Anyway to help that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a heckin' s N O O Z E G I R L E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> be his F R I E N D B O Y E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, what you said makes sense, I too believe she has poor judgement. I'll talk to her Monday :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure he didn't go to a cemetery  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Advice] My coach insults us during practice and during events. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we have a new coach this year and she seems to be the opposite of anything good in this life. To start the season she picked who she liked and didn't and moved them to the "fast" lanes and had them swimming more events than the rest of us. I don't know exactly why but to top that off, she always says we need to be like them and during a set she decided we weren't doing good enough and called us all retarded and how we need to be like the "fast" lane. I have a problem with how she treats us and what brought me to my breaking point was on Saturday, I got invited to an invitational and she decided to put me in the 200yd free and just a little background, I am a breaststroker and sprinter only... and I HAVE NEVER SWAM THE 200!!! So after my event she comes up to me saying that i should've done better and she was mad at me for getting last. That's what threw me off the edge because I know I tried my best and for her to say that really upsets me... Should I confront her or just let it be since season is almost over with anyway?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried doing that in a race and I felt like it slowed me down... I like to think that im kicking like a frog and keep my legs below the water. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
