<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9314</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RE: If There Is No God, Murder Isn't Wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RE: If There Is No God, Murder Isn't Wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yours is a nicer imagining than most.

In a nutshell the 'new' atheist ideas are that there is no evidence for the existence of gods, and that the activities of religions tend to be of net harm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Christians don't view the world in the same sceptical way that atheists tend to. To us contradictions in scripture are evidence against the claim that it is divinely created or inspired. 

You are fairly unusual in embracing contradictions though. It's really common for Christians to be unaware of them, or just to hold contradictory ideas without feeling a need to reconcile them. They become evasive when asked about them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to be honest, I rarely trust those to be accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Christian god is purportedly omni-benevolent.

Here are the original lyrics anyway, including its endorsement of the class system:

1.
All things bright and beautiful,
All creatures great and small,
All things wise and wonderful,
The Lord God made them all.

2.
Each little flower that opens,
Each little bird that sings,
He made their glowing colours,
He made their tiny wings.

All things bright ...

3.
The rich man in his castle,
The poor man at his gate,
God made them high and lowly,
And ordered their estate.

All things bright ...

4.
The purple headed mountain,
The river running by,
The sunset and the morning,
That brightens up the sky;

All things bright ...

5.
The cold wind in the winter,
The pleasant summer sun,
The ripe fruits in the garden,
He made them every one:

All things bright ...

6.
The tall trees in the greenwood,
The meadows where we play,
The rushes by the water,
We gather every day;

All things bright ...

7.
He gave us eyes to see them,
And lips that we might tell,
How great is God Almighty,
Who has made all things well.

All things bright ...

(Amen)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corbyn really over-uses the oratory technique of repetition. 

I suspect he learned it on a speech-writing course and for some reason forgets everything else it covered. I'm sure he thinks it's effective but it just seems awkward when not actually giving a speech.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been on a Prevent course and I thought it seemed to be almost awkwardly avoiding mentioning Islamiscism. 

It was all about the far right, and used clips from *This Is England* for examples.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 13:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite server shut down a few years ago. 

Does anyone remember the SAS Sniper clan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but of course its to the tune of a famous Christian hymn, and it illustrates the inconsistency of the Christian god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying it more despicable to.steal from a church than a school, say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised that he apparently hasn't performed it on cadavers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll go, a head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Searching for that turns up plenty of creepy stuff.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that if you take an analogue watch, and point the hour hand at the sun, then the mid-point between that and the 12 on the dial is South, when in the Northern hemisphere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh right. is there a new 12-sided Pound coin coming out? I didn't know that.

It's good to know as otherwise I'd be puzzled by it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think counting by number of dead is not a meaningful way. It's better to count the number of shooters.  That's more directly affected by gun availability.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> European countries have varying gun laws, but as a whole guns are much less common than in the US it seems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What new 12 sided Pound coin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://c1.staticflickr.com/9/8215/8274218167_7aae144bd9_b.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The part about him not having met May, and Downing Street denying it is odd. Surely if they met they would know the occasion?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't say it was Nazi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh well that's totally different then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/EIyixC9NsLI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a grave offence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah that's helpful. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lower of these, i think.

https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/mar/24/woman-hijab-westminster-bridge-attack-victim-photo-misappropriated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I wonder how many individuals have been involved in these sex-abuse gangs? We should expect 2-5% of them to be non-Muslim, though the sample might not be large enough for significance if not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not sure that it is preferable that it be the national origin, rather than the religion. 

I wonder though, have any Pakistani Christians or Hindus been involved in this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remainers tend to be good people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remainers don't have the motive to remove foreigners from London </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There must be some statistical significance to these  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't sound like it was planned to be a Big-Brother type show, and C4 say they will show programmes about it later, so I don't see what is the story.

I'm totally bored of reality TV anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's the point. It's not the fault of multiculturalism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it would have been better if he was caught alive. Prison seems more of a deterrent in these cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. An incident like this  needs at least two people planning it for it to be counted as part of a terror campaign.

I gather seven others have been arrested, but I'd imagine if they were plotting with him they would have attacked people as well, in a coordinated way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy was in his late 40s I believe,  so not the usual disaffected youth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it was expected either to be a Muslim or an overexcited Brexiter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is some suggestion that Muslim suicide attackers are often suffering from depression and are commiting suicide in a way which they think is religiously and socially acceptable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Wormy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They could try for a bit longer than an hour though, don't you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like it, but it isn't as good as full EU membership, as we wouldn't have any say in the policies which which we would have to comply.

I think the point is that the reason many people voted Leave was to get rid of immigrants, but that won't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You work for the govt and wonder if messing up suits you to it? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder why people remove the catalytic converter? Would it add performance? (seems unlikely) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is actually a longer version where the owner looks around and asks if the puke came from her dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did that a lot. He had special lenses made too.

https://youtu.be/fb7Meqaz7Aw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solved! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have activated my love-blob.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Railway line Blue cable box thing, top left </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cave of Mirrors Cube. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 09:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article doesn't say what the risky part of the ritual is.  I wonder why?

I understand that the mohel cuts the skin then removes the forskin with his mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Oh no you didn't!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like people have come around to smash up my home and I am not allowed to do or say anything about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey come on, I just asked a non-strawmanny question, you should answer it.

Should the SNP try to follow its manifesto? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mandatory adoption of the Euro will make it pretty much impossible I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think the SNP should try to follow its manifesto?

If not, why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does that make a difference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 09:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's too late. I already sang it to Thr Imperial March. Now that us stuck in my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Expensive though. I wonder if the vehicle is a rare model, or some such? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That lingerie fits her like a glove. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll remember that, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two reactions that I recall were one woman who felt that the effect of reduced risk on all the children today is worse in total than the injury or loss of a few was in the past. Of course she had no data to support that view. Another woman became angry at me for stating that their policy would hurt children.  She preferred to attack me than address the point.

Safety regulation is not very sexy,  and sometimes it seems silly, but it is one of the factors contributing to longer lifespans of people in the developed world.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks dangerous. It doesn't seem to be a stuntperson either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ford Escort Barn Find. It reached a good price. There has to be something weird about this.. (rehosted at mod request) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was arguing with a bunch of twits on FB who wanted to bring back all the dangerous playground equipment of the past. 

They didn't like it when I said they wanted to hurt children.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Hiroshima bomb seems to have caused rain soon after detonation. I guess a pressure wave like that can condense water vapour. It fell as poisonous black water, contaminated with strotium 90. Lots of burn victims drank it and died.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More pics here:

http://www.ebay.co.uk/itm/Ford-MK1-Escort-van-barn-find-/272589663200?_trksid=p2047675.l2557 nma=true si=CymrewdPKnyJzdjrV8iXLw84ZWo%253D orig_cvip=true rt=nc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ford MK1 Escort van barn find - there must be something weird about this one. It's a wreck but bid up to 4033 as I post this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that narrows it down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would it look like without that blue tint? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He was straight-jacketed into campaigning for Remain by the vast majority of Labour MPs. Did as best he could to campaign for Leave at the same time.

Indeed. He seems piss-weak.

Tory Brexit may be shit, but it looks like the most obvious route back into power for Labour.

The other way is to elect a leader and develop polices and ways of presenting them which appeal to the majority of voters in the swingable seats. There are presumably quite a few of these seats so there is probably more than one approach that might work. Blair and the rest figured out one way.

And then the country can be put right again.

He's doing so badly in opposition that I dread to think what he would be like in power. I guess we will never know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corbyn wants Brexit because he doesn't like the EU.

That seems reasonably likely. I wonder though why he couldn't find it in himself to campaign to Leave in the referendum? That runs counter to the Corbynite notion that he is very consistent and principled.

He also wants the Tories to make a pig's ear of it.

That seems very short-sighted, and disloyal to the country. Wishing the Tories would look bad is understandable, but wishing they would hurt Labour supporters is not understandable to me.

He also wants to recover the working class vote that New Labour abandoned.

I expect he does see it that way. Some would say that New Labour successfully recovered the working class vote that Old Labour abandoned in the 80s, and is abandoning again.

The United Kingdom might not survive the medium-future. Its lose lose lose.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slimy Piece of Worm-Ridden Filth - Life Inside Jabba the Hutt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your core point, that you want to make? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's not Labour's fault that it was mathematically impossible for them to have won.

You are basically arguing that no opposition should ever resist what the government is doing.

Nobody is saying that Corbyn didn't face a challenge. I am saying that he made no attempt to rise to it when any decent MP would have done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a free vote would have been so easy. It would have left Corbyn and all the PLP with their reputations intact.

Instead he said 'oh I suppose it is then' when a journalist asked him if he was having a 3-line whip. He's dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went there last year. Actually the Nazis didn't use the Reichstag building much, following a fire there in 1933. The Nazi 'parliament' was based in [The Kroll Opera house](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kroll_Opera_House), which has been destroyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you being deliberately obtuse? There are pro-remain and pro single market Tory MPs. Even without any coherent action from Corbyn May is unable to command full loyalty, with some high-profile dissenters in her own ranks.

At the very least Corbyn could have made May's zombie-walk uncertain of reaching the cliff. He would only need to persuade about 5% of the Tories not to support leaving the Single Market, and there are well over that many who have stated that is their view.

I guess that is out of Corbyn's reach, but I don't think it would be out of the reach of a competent and sufficiently-principled Labour leader. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems a good resource:

http://www.skeptical-voter.org/wiki/index.php?title=Tim_Farron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put it down to 'Tory Rebels' if you like, but May could have easily put them in place with a little help from Labour, which she obviously didn't get.

You illustrate the point about Corbyn having some power, if he chose or knew how to wield it.  
Do you suppose he even offered any conditional help to Hammond? Corbyn is probably in favour of increased NI to pay for improved services. What concessions did he fail to secure for the people of this country? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There's only one other party he can do this with, the Tories.

He could do it with every other party in parliament, including the Tories (ukip would probably be fruitless, but that's about the only one you can say that of) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have an example of anything Corbyn did leading to the current government's defeat?

I'd hate to be missing any data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corbyn needs to strike some deals with other parties, and his own. That's his failing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course none of that is Corbyn's fault. It's his fault that he has waved it all through when he could intervene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the other commenter said, there are lots of jobs in social care and policy of various kinds. Consider local government and housing etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one is saying all study choices should be about jobs. The OP is arguing that vocational study should not be considered a poorer choice than academic study. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there are any actual courses with that title, lest we start mistaking comedy for reality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 PowerPoint to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy Jumps Into Oil Pool - not much of a plan to remove it afterwards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 13:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose he could have taken-up cluster-ballooning as a hobby and done it more safely, with permission.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cluster_ballooning

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God killed 2,821,364 while Satan killed 10, but he shared some of those 10 with God in their bet about Job. 

Edit: [Forgot link.](http://www.patheos.com/blogs/friendlyatheist/2013/07/25/how-many-people-did-god-slaughter-in-the-bible-steve-wells-has-written-a-book-documenting-every-kill/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a friend who said he didn't need freedom of speech because he wasn't planning on writing any controversial books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That land includes lovely Mediterranean coasts and islands, northern fjords, arctic tundra, forests, mountains and ski resorts and many of the greatest historic cities of the world. We are to lose over 80% of the land on which we are currently entitled to live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty significant. Today Scottish people have the right to live and work on 1.7 million square miles of land. That's to be reduced to about 313,000 square miles. Its a big material change in their rights, as is the proposed removal of the human rights protections afforded by the ECHR.

Those would be enough to change my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what would happen if they held one anyway, and then declared independence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get her to join reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. I hear good things about Blackpool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's grim. It takes a while to understand what's happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh dear is cool out of date now?  Should I be saying dank instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if you got up in the night to get a drink and saw Old Greg's face pressed against it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a bananana.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes a religious symbol is a political symbol too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that's how I read it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it would really matter if the 52% or some proportion of them were upset because it was reversed. What would they actually do about it? They might burn a few cars and smash a few windows at the worst. 

The 48% are pretty angry at this point too.

The other possibility of the UK disintegrating is much worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I basically think the whole thing has become so obscured that another vote on the actual options available would be the right thing to do, especially with the prospect of Scotland leaving the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boris campaigned on the promise that we would keep the single market.

http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/boris-johnson-eu-referendum-single-market-brexit-a7104846.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Leave campaign heavily promoted the idea that we could remain in the single market. So, while neither of us have figures, I don't agree that many or most Leave voters want a hard Brexit.

Hey, why don't we have them vote on it?

http://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/open-britain-video-single-market-nigel-farage-anna-soubry_uk_582ce0a0e4b09025ba310fce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU workplace headscarf ban is legal, says ECJ - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Ratzinger was doing more for the atheist movement, as everybody hated him and he was pretty tarnished with his paedophile protecting. I suspect he realised this and that's why he quit as pope.

The trouble with Bergoglio is that he keeps making PR-friendly remarks which are not then enacted as positive changes to church doctrine.

And he went out of his way to speak up in defense of the Charlie Hebdo murders. Don't forget that.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
[Plaid Cymru want a referendum. They have a long way to go however.](https://www.pressandjournal.co.uk/fp/news/politics/1194033/welsh-independence-must-explored-scotland-leaves-uk-says-plaid-cymru-leader/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do think at this point we are being rail-roaded down a route that very few people wanted when voting in the referendum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what argument?

Also Sturgeon gave the example of being left out of the conversation about the single-market. Apparently May told her it wasn't decided and then unilaterally announce we are leaving two hours later. That isn't good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She probably will be able to in a couple of years.

May could guarantee it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some are possible. For example they could guarantee the status of EU nationals in the UK, as Sturgeon offers in Scotland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't have to in order to be funny as a spoken joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> William Shakespeare went into a pub, and the barman said "Get out! You're bard!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One could just say "one's lighter" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a chance see Sturgeons press conference of today. She basically has been unable to get any reliable news or assurances from Westminster, and she has a mandate to do this and to represent the Scottish people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh chirpy chirpy chickens...! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. So they can leave the EU independently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be Sinky McBoatface. They none of them have the souls of poets, these people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are 44 cities in the USA with a higher population density than Greater London. London is not among the  ten most dense cities in the European Union, but I can't find longer list easily.

Basically London is a medium density city. There is a relatively large amount of scope for expansion, though I think the transport network would be a bottleneck to functionality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did notice that Sturgeon at no point says 'I don't know yet' to any questions, even when that would be a simpler answer. Instead she set out the possibilities. That seems a little more like familiar politic-speak. It avoids a don't-know sound-bite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she is in the politically novel situation of being dead right, and justified. So, she doesn't have to dissemble in her responses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submarines are technically boats

Yes but submarines aren't very floaty, are they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Sir Tom Courtenay, if you are wondering.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> London isn't even in the top 50 most densely-populated cities of the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a good chance it isn't. The red boxes are often preserved in those areas of London. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's called Tom. Coincidentally Tom and Margot are the names of notable characters in a 70s sitcom called *The Good Life*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no use crying over spilt milk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of them substantially pre-date the development of RADAR though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. It's the form used in the link posted by /u/shwag945.

Adding an S on the end is usually OK too in English, but it can erase some of the fun little irregularities if we are not careful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 11:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The plural of cannon, is cannon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 10:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just took it very personally. I sort of understand, she and the presenter were basically denying that gay people were attacked for being gay.

It was another example of the regular debates about the motives of Muslim who commit violent hate crimes. Is it because of the religious instruction to do so, or in this case just regular homophobia?

It is commonly missed that a person can have multiple motives for one action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 10:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Landlords still spend money.

They probably don't spend twice as much on those other things as non-landlords, even if they have income from rent equalling their other income. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 10:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are good atmospheric conditions for hearing thunder? Usually it's stormy when it thunders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 10:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would mean that 'no' votes wouldn't count. Still, I like the suggestion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 10:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a valid trigger I'd say.  I also think Scotland voting to leave the UK would be a material change justifying a new EU referendum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd imagine Westminster has legitimate power to do so with military force if it chooses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you replace the first comma with a full stop it makes more sense.

"If a referendum is held that's fine. It should be held." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 02:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't make Corbyn not an idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 02:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is repugnant. 

What a disgusting cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paramedic ambulances attend when there is serious risk to somebody.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also you don't want your gimp getting out and posting to your Facebook.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'd like to see quick and robust prosecution of people who issue threats of violence on social media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were being assholes to him. I don't think they realised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All that money spent on rent is not being spent on other things like food, clothes, consumer goods, recreation, holidays. So I'd imagine all those sectors are not doing as well as they might be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10-Yr-Old Prodigy Is Out to Prove Atheist Stephen Hawking Wrong: God Does Exist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes there is a book about it:

http://www.artisanalpencilsharpening.com/

https://www.amazon.com/How-Sharpen-Pencils-Theoretical-Contractors/dp/1612193269 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. But it is more important right now than the NHS, for example. It will have a bigger effect on the NHS than anything the tories are capable of doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask it what it's sinking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah thanks. If anyone is wondering, uneddit indicates /u/TimbuFTZB originally said:

ask it what it's sinking about

I'll borrow that, if he doesn't want it. 

Edit: he's changed it again. It was saying 'BLM is a hate group' when I first commented.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, but I think I'd be smug if I was him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. I don't know what Black Lives Matter has to do with squids. Care to enlighten me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Brian Cox Dead' wouldn't have the same ring to it.

Edit: I was thinking of Brian Glover. Don't mind me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brian Cox Live - This is encouraging - a science-show stadium tour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 13:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brian Cox Live - This is encouraging - a science-show stadium tour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 13:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 11:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah we kinda already know that lost of people don't have a balanced view about the EU.

For me the EU deal currently outweighs everything else, because it is the biggest danger to the future stability of the UK.  
It also affects pretty much everything higher on that list.

Thanks for the disheartening info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 11:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be good if the PLP would defect en-mass to the Lib-Dems at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 11:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Airplanes use a lot of fuel, which is burned up high where it does most damage to the atmosphere. The Hyperloop has the prospect of moving higher volumes than current flights allow, at much lesser environmental cost.

Also airports are not as convenient as railway or Hyperloop stations.

It could make shorthaul flights on that route redundant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 10:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is addy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 10:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's at a seminal moment in Western cultural history.

Is he not entertained? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I used to date a girl called Geraldine. She faded in the night like a poem I meant to write. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here for this comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one looks like it'll be damaged  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a reddit meme, you see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do wonder why buildings in brush fire risk areas don't have external fire suppression sprinklers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would there be a new photo in a year,  with nothing to see? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And don't forget to video it (with phone held horizontally ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose this is some obscure usage of the word 'real', of which I was previously unaware.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm intrigued.  What scaling problems are you thinking of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it works it'll be faster than any train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How effecient are these batteries?  Could they solve the intermittency problem of wind and solar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least our plastic pals will be fun to be with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. I'll join now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst thing about that is that he clearly hadn't considered the whip policy and only responded 'oh yeah' to a journalist who asked him if it would be a three-line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are the only party which seem to care about my views, as one of the 48% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but he should have laughed and quickly gone to pick them up and put them out, before coming back to the camera. That would have been amusing and normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that intention is significant. However I don't see any harm in feeding back to a person that a remark is not acceptable these days. Then the next time they do it they are doing it intentionally.

 I gently told somebody about using the word 'coloured' quite recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is the threshold for you? What kind of homophobic words or actions do you find acceptable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a nice photo.  It's suitable for framing, that.

It's time to stop stereotyping people with autism though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even given very different mortality rates surely that's incredibly high?

That's 22.11 per year, or one every 16 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I visited some caves in Beer, in thd West country which have graffiti from the Romans, through to the 1980s. It was pretty cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Medieval Steve did it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised the video is so shitty.  I don't want to see candles,  but the cave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dumping is having a poo here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an unspecified year, between the 26th and 31st of December..  

It needs a comma:  One year, after Christmas. . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what Kid Pix is and I am not googling it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, a big ass-camera? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't learn about 1984 today, but about the real Telescreen surveillance.

Anyway, its interesting how close the prediction is, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: George Orwell anticipated the CIA Smart TV surveillance, 69 years ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The way this decoration is cutlery* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 10:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you a fan of Jon Ronson? Does his work influence yours in any way (eg have you avoided any subjects he covered)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 10:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He made a follow up film about Jimmy Saville, who remained in contact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your belly-button runneth over mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But their job was to protect people, at least those on the planes. They didn't do their job properly. They didn't protect those people and consequently, those people were killed.

If they had done their job properly, they might not have been killed. This doesn't exonerate the hijackers.

I think if the pilots flying a plane didn't do their jobs properly, and subsequently the passengers were killed, you would acknowledge the fact.

Is it that you are touchy about accepting any responsibility for the US or anyone else other than the hijackers? I understand the sentiment, but not the logic. Nowadays airport security is tighter. That's a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
