<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4211</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you suggesting that Trump and much of his administration would be horrible at playing poker?  Because, if so, I agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right.  For anyone who needs [a refresher on Ollie North, here's a surprisingly accurate cartoon take from *American Dad*.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lFV1uT-ihDo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who even knows

Er, anyone who checks OP's history?

The linked article from *The Independent* really isn't that great.  It doesn't talk about Flynn's failure to disclose payments from Russia, so it's already behind the cutting edge of news from yesterday.  There's nothing actively wrong with the article; it's just kind of mediocre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo.  Sanctions are crippling Russia's economy.  So we should keep them up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It turned out that Americans made a horrible miscalculation in the second half of the 1900s.  Communism was never the enemy of the USA.  Instead, communism was the great **weakness** of the enemies of the USA.  Totalitarianism was the true enemy, and it still is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can [read the form here.](https://www.dropbox.com/s/ao33b0bfim14awi/Flynn%2C%20Michael%202-11-17.pdf?dl=0)  There is one and only one form.  It lists 30 sources of compensation, but Russian propaganda compensation is notably absent.

Electronic Signature - I certify that the statements I have made in this form are true, complete and correct to the best of my knowledge.

/s/ Flynn, Michael T [electronically signed on 02/11/2017 by Flynn, Michael T in Integrity.gov] 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  As late as a White House press conference on Monday, February 13th, Flynn was still very much the National Security Advisor: Trump was still [evaluating the Michael Flynn situation.](http://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-is-evaluating-the-situation-involving-michael-flynn-and-russian-calls/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A source close to Flynn told The Daily Beast on Saturday that his resignation from the White House last month interrupted efforts to file a complete and accurate disclosure form, and that the amendment was an effort to correct deficiencies that would have otherwise been sorted out.

He filed the first disclosure form on February 11th, but he resigned on February 13th.  So how did his resgination "interrupt" his disclosure?  Did his resignation travel back in time and disrupt the space-time continuum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, you know, the slightest shred of morality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why?  Why would Giuliani take it upon himself to do this?

I'm sorry to say that any time members of the Trump campaign take actions that could reasonably be interpreted as helping Russia or its allies, their motives are immediately suspect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Play that dead band's song" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tinkl**e**, sploo**s**h, s**p**loosh, dr**i**p, spl**o**osh, ti**n**kle, spl**a**sh, glu**g**-glug, tinkl**e** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If their evidence is strong enough to get Trump and Pence without Flynn's testimony, they wouldn't want to give Flynn immunity.  See also Ollie North. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... and a child refugee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^(I know, I was trying to play an April Fools' Day joke) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... now you're off to /r/CenturyClub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red on /r/thebutton, Red on /r/place, RED LOYALISTS UNITE! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I throw an obscure music video in here for Hold Music Part 3?  Unfortunately, it's less than four minutes long, but to my taste, it's by far the best the band has done.

[Teen Girl Scientist Monthly: Safari](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0eOmK5upihk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me try an analogy.

Company C has a job opening.  After reviewing resumes and interviewing applicants, there are two candidates remaining, Candidate A and Candidate B.  They seem equally suitable for the job.  So Company C decides to speak to the candidates' professional references, and it just so happens that they share a reference, Reference R.

Reference R knows some things about A and B that Company C doesn't.  Reference R knows a little negative information about A; even with that negative information, A will still be suitable, but not quite as attractive as Company C's current evaluation.

However, Reference R knows damning information about B.  B is actually a horrible candidate, and Company C would be better off hiring nobody than hiring B.

Reference R releases the little bit of negative information about Candidate A to Company C.  But Reference R does **not** tell Company C any of the negative information about Candidate B.  That's because Reference R has an ulterior motive of wanting Company C to fail.  So Company C hires Candidate B.

Note that everything that Reference R has said is the truth!  But it turns out that having more of the truth is sometimes both much worse than having less of the truth, and also much worse than having all of the truth.

To answer your other question, it is at least quite possible that Russia has information about Trump, or information gleaned from hacking the RNC, or both.  Russia has released none of this information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is crystal-clear that Wikileaks is a tool of Putin at this point, and has been for some years.  Selectively releasing information, selectively withholding information, and timing releases to help Trump are all nefarious activities, even when the information is true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe because most redditors aren't fans of participating in Russian propaganda operations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As /u/MindOfMetalAndWheels titled his helpful explainer video, ["Death to Pennies."](http://www.cgpgrey.com/blog/death-to-pennies.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What?!  Criminals like Flynn only get an immunity deal if their testimony is both necessary and sufficient for the conviction of bigger criminals.  Here is a complete list of the people whose conviction the FBI or Congress would trade for immunity for former National Security Advisor Flynn:

* President Donald Trump.

* Vice President Mike Pence.

That's it.  That's the whole list.  The translation of Trump's tweet is "Either my vice president is guilty as hell, I'm guilty as hell, or we're both guilty as hell." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Flynn Jr. also pushed Pizzagate on twitter, so his credibility is even more dubious than Nunes's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he could scare them by threatening to *support* them in the 2018 midterms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on the ebbs and flows of teams' strengths, you can usually closely replicate the assignment of berths in the 32-team World Cup by giving half the berths based on the strongest teams in the world, and half the berths based on the number of teams in each confederation.  That seems to be the right sort of idea, at least: balancing a desire to have strong teams with a desire to have geographic diversity.

Presumably we don't just want to take the strongest 48 teams to a 48-team World Cup.  That would probably mean taking **all** of CONMEBOL, or close to it.

I think CONMEBOL should have at least five and a half berths in a 32-team World Cup, and similarly, seven berths plus a play-in in a 48-team World Cup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could also mean that the article from TheHill is thirty-five minutes old, and things just don't happen that quickly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  All five CONMEBOL teams advanced to the last sixteen in the 2010 World Cup.  Five of six CONMEBOL teams advanced to the last sixteen in the 2014 World Cup, and the sixth finished with four points and a goal differential of 0.  In a 48-team World Cup, CONMEBOL could easily justify 7 slots plus the play-in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two cycles ago, Iran finished fourth in their qualifying group behind South Korea, Saudi Arabia, and heaven help us, North Korea.  That Saudi Arabia team went on to lose a playoff to Bahrain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't consider Trinidad and Tobago decent this cycle.  They somehow managed to concede a semifinal WCQ draw to Guatemala in Port of Spain, and neither their semifinal WCQ matches against the USA nor their hex matches so far inspire confidence.  Their only good result of those six matches is that 1-0 home win against Panama.

I think Panama could be decent this cycle, and I'd like to see more from them.

I definitely do **not** think Honduras is decent this cycle.  I think they're in the midst of a significant downswing.  8 points in the semifinal round?!

Jamaica was certainly decent and then some in the 2015 Gold Cup, but has looked shaky since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bestow upon you the Comment of the Day award.  Your comment can't be linked to for some reason, but I found it your history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The USA is in for a long war on ISIS.  Trump, not so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the hilarity of helping out Mexico paralleled the sadness of eliminating Panama.  Panama fans might not want to click on any of these links:

* [Highlights of the match.](https://youtu.be/1qpt23kBTpg)

* [Behind-the-scenes documentary about the mixed feelings of USA fans.](https://youtu.be/kLOovgFwjPQ)

* [Mexican announcer's reaction, with English subtitles, translation occasionally dubious.](https://youtu.be/vFREXbDG_Qc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hoped the "/s" would be implied by the phrases "oh-so-concerned" and "definitely for sure". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sloppy, sloppy Russian hackers.  Not even using VPNs to make the attacks look like they're coming from other countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Call Was Coming From Inside the White House" wins the Headline of the Day award.  "The call is coming from **inside the house!**" is an older meme, sir, [but it checks out.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rkcGm-pWwsQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure we'll be able to confirm your guess soon, because House Republicans are oh-so-concerned about leaks.  So they're definitely for sure going to come down hard on Ellis and Cohen-Watnick for leaking to Nunes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a friendly reminder that in the last two World Cups, there have been eleven CONMEBOL berths, and ten of those eleven advanced out of the group stage.  So on all of the given days, CONMEBOL has generally been superior on the field, not just on paper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because last cycle, when FIFA asked Mexico to play qualifiers, Mexico almost played themselves right out of the World Cup, and needed the USA to save them.  That was hilarious!

But yes, six spots is too few for CONMEBOL, six spots is too many for CONCACAF, and eight spots is waaayyy too many for AFC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, just at the moment, it would be Mexico in one group, Costa Rica in the second group, and USA in the third.  Costa Rica is better than the USA right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Expanded FIFA World Cup Means More Slots for Africa, Asia and Americas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Africa's nine spots are the least of my concerns.  There are generally at least a dozen or so decent teams in CAF.

CONCACAF getting six spots is scary.  There have never simultaneously been six decent CONCACAF teams at the same time.  Usually, there are three or four.

But if CONCACAF is scary, then AFC is a horror show.  Japan and South Korea are consistently decent, and Australia is often up there as well.  Iran and Saudi Arabia have their moments.  After that... ye gods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the end of the day the Russian influence was limited to releasing factual information, and perhaps publishing outlandish stories Americans were too stupid to decipher ( and those articles were very, very clearly false)

This sentence expresses unjustifiable certainty in your own knowledge of the limits of Russian influence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is his family also complicit? is his whole campaign team? are his donors? are there also republicans/democrats politicians compromised?

Specifically, is Vice President Pence complicit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is **absolutely the case** that nations that have suffered American interference, especially recent American interference, should be upset with the USA.

Similarly, Americans should be upset with Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who lived through 9/11, and then watched a Democratic president be the one to bring Osama Bin Laden to justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [OP delivered!](https://i.redditmedia.com/QmkE5nz1dmVva3_HIFFWAWMs1NX6pS0uNROFz5ATM1w.jpg?w=663 s=3e73216d1b47d6468d7f80c9382f8232) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The eGift Card that pizzaforyourcomment sent me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine that /u/evil420pimp is alluding to the Earth spending half of the year moving toward from the sun.  Of course, it spends the other half of the year moving away from the sun, ending up ever-so-slightly farther away, on average, each year.

I guess I'm saying that we can assume that there's a basic level of astronomical knowledge in... evil... 420... pimps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct, the red-tailed hawk is not an eagle.  The red-tailed hawk is in genus *Buteo*, which does not include any species of eagle.  The bald eagle is in genus *Haliaeetus*, one of the genera that includes species of eagles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are people under there.  They keep it up for a short time at the beginning of the game.  Those people don't see much for the duration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody's playin' the game    
But nobody's rules are the same

Never take a stranger's advice    
Never let a friend fool you twice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ was obviously the good guy all along.

I'm less certain that all of his followers are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genetic memory, maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PMed, thanks!

I first learned about the [connection between the bald eagle and the red-tailed hawk on NPR,](http://www.npr.org/templates/story/story.php?storyId=156187375) I think. I certainly came across it later [via John Oliver.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nObupsG0Lf4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [4:01.](https://youtu.be/Erp8IAUouus?t=241) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except the "eagle sound" is actually a [red-tailed hawk call.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3VJulGLXpJo)  Real bald eagles [sound like this.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9RArGl2vkGI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked the Clippy reference! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this case, the Senate is the saucer that allows you to drink the tea at all, even though the teacup has wandered off somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q38F6kGpB8Y </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~honors~~ dishonors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did somebody say Little Serow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That USA-Honduras Hamilton tifo again, in all its animated glory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Seth Abramson called it on Twitter](https://twitter.com/SethAbramson/status/846135383129772032) three days ago (via /u/alixsyd):

MEGA-THREAD: MI6 agent Chris STEELE, author of history's most explosive intel dossier, will soon testify against TRUMP. Read his story here.

(1) Between 6/20/16 and 12/13/16, former MI6 agent STEELE compiled an intel dossier establishing TRUMP and allies had committed treason.

(2) STEELE first worked for anti-Trump GOP operatives, but most of his research was done for free due to his concern for the intel on TRUMP.

(3) Between 6/1 and 11/18, parts of the dossier were variously held by anti-Trump GOPers, the MI6, FBI friends of Steele, and David Corn.

(4) During this time--largely pre-election--there is no evidence that any of the dossier's sources had been identified or in any way harmed.

(5) From 11/18 to 12/9, John MCCAIN was also aware of the dossier. During this period, none of the dossier's sources were blown or harmed.

(6) Between 11/18 and 12/9 MCCAIN acquired the dossier. The Guardian reports MCCAIN didn't share it--to avoid looking vengeful toward TRUMP.

(7) On 12/9, MCCAIN gave the dossier to COMEY. Presumably, COMEY thereafter shared it with other agents at the FBI.

(8) The NEW YORK FIELD OFFICE of the FBI is known to have illegally leaked confidential information to TRUMP advisers GIULIANI and PRINCE.

(9) GIULIANI and PRINCE--a TRUMP "shadow adviser" and brother to DEVOS--have admitted to having active FBI sources.

(10) Former TRUMP National Security Adviser Michael FLYNN was just found to have active (and paid) FBI sources also.

(11) Within seventeen days of the FBI having possession of Steele's dossier, the chief source behind the dossier had been murdered by PUTIN.

(12) On 12/26, the top aide and most trusted advisor of SECHIN, head of Russia's oil/gas company, was found murdered in the back of his car.

(13) The deceased man, former FSB agent Oleg EROVINKIN, was the trusted "go-between between SECHIN and PUTIN," also both former FSB agents.

(14) The dossier accused SECHIN of offering TRUMP, via PAGE, money from Russia's oil company ROSNEFT in exchange for lifting U.S. sanctions.

(15) The theory PUTIN helped elect TRUMP and offered money via SECHIN for lifting sanctions (allowing a ROSNEFT pipeline) is "#Russiagate."

(16) The death of SECHIN aide/STEELE source EROVINKIN was reported as a heart attack before an autopsy had occurred.

(17) By 12/29, outlets reporting EROVINKIN died in the back of his car via heart attack were withdrawing the claim.

(18) While news of the death wouldn't break widely until late January, it's reasonable to assume Steele had heard about it by early January.

(19) The reason for this is that former FSB and ROSNEFT man EROVINKIN was--as later became public--the chief source for the STEELE dossier.

(20) As there was no reason for STEELE to think on 12/26 the FSB had his dossier, there was no reason for him to think EROVINKIN was killed.

(21) On 1/10, BUZZFEED published the STEELE dossier. Steele was quickly outed as author by the WSJ, endangering him.

(22) The BUZZFEED publication also would've confirmed for STEELE that EROVINKIN had indeed been identified and thereafter murdered by PUTIN.

(23) On 1/12, STEELE and his family abandoned their home in Surrey with no indication of whether they'd ever return.

(24) By 1/12, British media had established Steele's strong reputation in the IC as former Russia-desk head for MI6.

(25) Meanwhile, U.S. media did little research on STEELE--and indulged claims by TRUMP that STEELE was a "failed spy" peddling "fake news."

(26) By 1/27, it had been leaked that EROVINKIN, a "go-between for PUTIN and SECHIN," was a primary dossier source.

(27) The news of EROVINKIN being linked to the dossier within a matter of days increased the credibility of the dossier for law enforcement.

(28) On 2/11 CBS said "it's gaining credibility among law enforcement--even for people who discounted it initially."

(29) On 2/27 reports placed Steele in Cambridge after 7 weeks without a sighting, though he remained away from home.

(30) On 3/1 it was revealed the FBI had enough confidence in the dossier that it offered to pay STEELE to expand it.

(31) On 3/2, SENATE DEMS contacted STEELE via friends and offered to help him testify before their Intel Committee.

(32) On 3/7, STEELE emerged from hiding and told the press, "I won't be making any further statements at this time."

(33) A reasonable speculation is that STEELE's emergence from hiding was prompted at least in part by U.S. assurances he'd be foregrounded.

(34) The more attention U.S. officials gave STEELE, and the more legitimacy their statements lent to his work, the safer he was from PUTIN.

(35) On 3/17 it was confirmed that a STEELE source, MILLIAN, met with former MANAFORT boss (DERIPASKA) in June 2016.

(36) DERIPASKA, a close ally of PUTIN, had paid MANAFORT $10 million annually from 2006 to 2009 to shill for Russia.

(37) MANAFORT, whose current tie to DERIPASKA/PUTIN is unknown, has now been found to have laundered his Russia pay.

(38) The MILLIAN/DERIPASKA meet further confirmed the dossier originated from sources in a position to know the movements of TRUMP advisers.

(39) On 3/20, the HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE met publicly with COMEY. The Dems cited STEELE's dossier repeatedly.

(40) Within 72 hours the Dems had indicated they intended to ask STEELE to testify. Citing his dossier was likely intended to keep him safe.

(41) The likely Dem theory: if the dossier's content is not just public but made public by Congress, PUTIN gains nothing in killing STEELE.

(42) On 3/23, Rep. Himes (D-CT) of the HOUSE INTEL COMMITTEE told CBS, "Well want to talk to Christopher Steele."

(43) Himes' statement confirmed the House as well as the Senate was interested in STEELE and had a new level of confidence he would testify.

(44) In the past (e.g. after the 2004 election) minority parties in Congressional committees have scheduled informal meetings for witnesses.

(45) So even when the GOP refuses to let STEELE formally testify, HOUSE AND SENATE DEMS can (and say they will) schedule informal testimony.

(46) The benefit of informal testimony is that Dems can televise the testimony so long as STEELE agrees to discuss no classified U.S. intel.

(47) So there's every reason to believe that (a) STEELE has strong sources, (b) PUTIN won't kill him, and (c) he will soon testify publicly.

(48) For all the lies told by TRUMP and ALLIES about both STEELE and his dossier, in fact virtually none of it has been disproven to date.

(49) E.g., PAGE has confessed to ROSNEFT meets; the ROSNEFT sale was as described; COHEN was a courier as described.

(50) In sum, the IC and Democrats increasingly think the STEELE dossier and #Russiagate theory are accurate. If so, TRUMP will be impeached. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's [all the fault of the USA that Mexico made it to the last World Cup.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vFREXbDG_Qc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like /u/TheApatheist forgot about [*cachirules*.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cachirules) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One point not made in the *Times* article is that the Trump-Russia collusion scandal, and the Republican Congress's ham-fisted attempts to address it and cover it up, are fuel for China's anti-democracy propaganda.  And China loves loves loves to preach about the "evils" of democracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, in this analogy, a filibuster is quad aces? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bwak-bwak-BWAK! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's unsurprising that the lawmaker is Walter Jones, who was [also the first House Republican to co-sponsor a bill calling for independent investigation of collusion between Trump and Russia, back in mid-February.](http://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/320087-hacking-investigation-bill-gets-first-republican-cosponsor) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SSSIIIIIIIIIIIIIIMMM, actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You beat me to that one, so here's: [Go Tell the World](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MfRflwe1WXA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [W]e have an energy cost problem.

Yes.  That's the only way Trump could bring back coal jobs: by somehow causing the costs of fracking to rise so much that coal would become price-competitive again.  Not going to happen: the petroleum and natural-gas industries in our country wouldn't stand for it, and Trump can't kill fracking in the rest of the world anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please permit me a tangent.

Dear Erik Wemple, author of this article:

The phrase *ad hominem* applies both to males and to females.  The word *hominem* is a Latin form of the word for "human".  It's not as if that phrase uses a Latin form of *vir*.

Sean Spicer was indulging in an *ad hominem* attack, but not in an *ad feminam* attack.  There was nothing particular chauvinistic about this sentence:
She is an idiot with no real sources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But actually, it's a great idea for the House Intelligence Committee to spend all of its time investigating Clinton.

Meanwhile, an independent commission can investigate collusion between Russia and Trump's transition team.   That includes such members of Trump's transition team as Nunes, who is still inexplicably chair of the selfsame House Intelligence Committee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on how the Trump-Russia investigation proceeds, a one-week delay could end up being almost totally meaningless... or it could mean the difference between Justice Gorsuch and the next president nominating someone else instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Kushner is going to testify, how soon till Steele testifies?  [Seth Abramson on Twitter](https://twitter.com/SethAbramson) via /u/alixsyd:

MEGA-THREAD: MI6 agent Chris STEELE, author of history's most explosive intel dossier, will soon testify against TRUMP. Read his story here.

(1) Between 6/20/16 and 12/13/16, former MI6 agent STEELE compiled an intel dossier establishing TRUMP and allies had committed treason.

(2) STEELE first worked for anti-Trump GOP operatives, but most of his research was done for free due to his concern for the intel on TRUMP.

(3) Between 6/1 and 11/18, parts of the dossier were variously held by anti-Trump GOPers, the MI6, FBI friends of Steele, and David Corn.

(4) During this time--largely pre-election--there is no evidence that any of the dossier's sources had been identified or in any way harmed.

(5) From 11/18 to 12/9, John MCCAIN was also aware of the dossier. During this period, none of the dossier's sources were blown or harmed.

(6) Between 11/18 and 12/9 MCCAIN acquired the dossier. The Guardian reports MCCAIN didn't share it--to avoid looking vengeful toward TRUMP.

(7) On 12/9, MCCAIN gave the dossier to COMEY. Presumably, COMEY thereafter shared it with other agents at the FBI.

(8) The NEW YORK FIELD OFFICE of the FBI is known to have illegally leaked confidential information to TRUMP advisers GIULIANI and PRINCE.

(9) GIULIANI and PRINCE--a TRUMP "shadow adviser" and brother to DEVOS--have admitted to having active FBI sources.

(10) Former TRUMP National Security Adviser Michael FLYNN was just found to have active (and paid) FBI sources also.

(11) Within seventeen days of the FBI having possession of Steele's dossier, the chief source behind the dossier had been murdered by PUTIN.

(12) On 12/26, the top aide and most trusted advisor of SECHIN, head of Russia's oil/gas company, was found murdered in the back of his car.

(13) The deceased man, former FSB agent Oleg EROVINKIN, was the trusted "go-between between SECHIN and PUTIN," also both former FSB agents.

(14) The dossier accused SECHIN of offering TRUMP, via PAGE, money from Russia's oil company ROSNEFT in exchange for lifting U.S. sanctions.

(15) The theory PUTIN helped elect TRUMP and offered money via SECHIN for lifting sanctions (allowing a ROSNEFT pipeline) is "#Russiagate."

(16) The death of SECHIN aide/STEELE source EROVINKIN was reported as a heart attack before an autopsy had occurred.

(17) By 12/29, outlets reporting EROVINKIN died in the back of his car via heart attack were withdrawing the claim.

(18) While news of the death wouldn't break widely until late January, it's reasonable to assume Steele had heard about it by early January.

(19) The reason for this is that former FSB and ROSNEFT man EROVINKIN was--as later became public--the chief source for the STEELE dossier.

(20) As there was no reason for STEELE to think on 12/26 the FSB had his dossier, there was no reason for him to think EROVINKIN was killed.

(21) On 1/10, BUZZFEED published the STEELE dossier. Steele was quickly outed as author by the WSJ, endangering him.

(22) The BUZZFEED publication also would've confirmed for STEELE that EROVINKIN had indeed been identified and thereafter murdered by PUTIN.

(23) On 1/12, STEELE and his family abandoned their home in Surrey with no indication of whether they'd ever return.

(24) By 1/12, British media had established Steele's strong reputation in the IC as former Russia-desk head for MI6.

(25) Meanwhile, U.S. media did little research on STEELE--and indulged claims by TRUMP that STEELE was a "failed spy" peddling "fake news."

(26) By 1/27, it had been leaked that EROVINKIN, a "go-between for PUTIN and SECHIN," was a primary dossier source.

(27) The news of EROVINKIN being linked to the dossier within a matter of days increased the credibility of the dossier for law enforcement.

(28) On 2/11 CBS said "it's gaining credibility among law enforcement--even for people who discounted it initially."

(29) On 2/27 reports placed Steele in Cambridge after 7 weeks without a sighting, though he remained away from home.

(30) On 3/1 it was revealed the FBI had enough confidence in the dossier that it offered to pay STEELE to expand it.

(31) On 3/2, SENATE DEMS contacted STEELE via friends and offered to help him testify before their Intel Committee.

(32) On 3/7, STEELE emerged from hiding and told the press, "I won't be making any further statements at this time."

(33) A reasonable speculation is that STEELE's emergence from hiding was prompted at least in part by U.S. assurances he'd be foregrounded.

(34) The more attention U.S. officials gave STEELE, and the more legitimacy their statements lent to his work, the safer he was from PUTIN.

(35) On 3/17 it was confirmed that a STEELE source, MILLIAN, met with former MANAFORT boss (DERIPASKA) in June 2016.

(36) DERIPASKA, a close ally of PUTIN, had paid MANAFORT $10 million annually from 2006 to 2009 to shill for Russia.

(37) MANAFORT, whose current tie to DERIPASKA/PUTIN is unknown, has now been found to have laundered his Russia pay.

(38) The MILLIAN/DERIPASKA meet further confirmed the dossier originated from sources in a position to know the movements of TRUMP advisers.

(39) On 3/20, the HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE met publicly with COMEY. The Dems cited STEELE's dossier repeatedly.

(40) Within 72 hours the Dems had indicated they intended to ask STEELE to testify. Citing his dossier was likely intended to keep him safe.

(41) The likely Dem theory: if the dossier's content is not just public but made public by Congress, PUTIN gains nothing in killing STEELE.

(42) On 3/23, Rep. Himes (D-CT) of the HOUSE INTEL COMMITTEE told CBS, "Well want to talk to Christopher Steele."

(43) Himes' statement confirmed the House as well as the Senate was interested in STEELE and had a new level of confidence he would testify.

(44) In the past (e.g. after the 2004 election) minority parties in Congressional committees have scheduled informal meetings for witnesses.

(45) So even when the GOP refuses to let STEELE formally testify, HOUSE AND SENATE DEMS can (and say they will) schedule informal testimony.

(46) The benefit of informal testimony is that Dems can televise the testimony so long as STEELE agrees to discuss no classified U.S. intel.

(47) So there's every reason to believe that (a) STEELE has strong sources, (b) PUTIN won't kill him, and (c) he will soon testify publicly.

(48) For all the lies told by TRUMP and ALLIES about both STEELE and his dossier, in fact virtually none of it has been disproven to date.

(49) E.g., PAGE has confessed to ROSNEFT meets; the ROSNEFT sale was as described; COHEN was a courier as described.

(50) In sum, the IC and Democrats increasingly think the STEELE dossier and #Russiagate theory are accurate. If so, TRUMP will be impeached. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, no Belize?  No Antarctica?

That's why it's only *relatively* uncontroversial.  Fortunately, the category at trytreats.com doesn't include any of these exceptions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suggestion: a relatively uncontroversial descriptor for everything south of the USA is "Latin America". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but my questions would be more like:

"Poison" is one of the great pop metal tunes from the eighties.  How did you compose those transitions that are practically symphonic in scope? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, really?  One *more* war in the Middle East with unclear goals and no exit plan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, Roger Stone, that's what westvirginia.forums.rivals.com says, but we all know that the most accurate reporting on matters of national security comes from /r/PittSports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep reminding myself that scumbags are exactly the sort of people whom we need to turn state's evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subject-verb disagreement is a threat to newspaper respectability says Strunk   White </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now it's 0-6 by Honduras    
Pinto's a des-pe-rate man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mattis has an ulterior motive too: the preservation of the Republic.

Fortunately, his "ulterior motive" is more like his "honorable duty to his country". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I think what Pence means is that after Trump's eventual demise, he intends to trudge the earth as a zombie.

I mean, even more than he does now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She technically has massive power, but does not assert it.  For example, no law can be passed without her assent, for example, but she always assents.  In addition to royal assent, she also has the powers of Queen's Consent, as well as royal prerogative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But not in the hex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to get into pro-Klinsmann or anti-Klinsmann, but here's a list of every four-goal game by the USA in the hex ever:

* USA 6-0 Honduras, 2017-March-24. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But congressional sources say that the offer by Manaforts lawyer, Reginald Brown, a former White House lawyer under President George W. Bush, was carefully hedged. There was no explicit promise to testify in public or address a broad range of questions that have been raised about Manaforts business and lobbying work over the years for figures closely associated with Russian President Vladimir Putin.

This is an interview, not testimony, Jason Maloni, Manaforts spokesman, told Yahoo News. A statement by Maloni says only that Manafort is willing to provide information about recent allegations about Russian interference in the election. It says nothing about recent accusations regarding disguised payments made to Manafort from the political party of the pro-Putin former president of Ukraine, Viktor Yanukovych, or his past work for Oleg Deripaska, a prominent pro-Putin oligarch  both of which have been cited by Democrats as evidence of close ties between the Trump campaign and the Kremlin.

Forget this.  Congress can just subpoena the bastard.  If he wants to plead the Fifth, let him; his silence would speak volumes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the keeper can't see the shot, he can't react to the shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice encroachment.  My favorite is the Albanian who is five steps in when the penalty is finally taken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely Nunes is on the House floor for the healthcare bill vote, not at the White House. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fascinated to see what comes of this.  It's probably either good news for Trump or really, really bad news for Trump.

Unlike Nunes, Comey does actually have it in his job description to brief the President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.  Something is up.  This is the first move that the Trump team has made that actually makes sense.

I hope they ask Carter Page about his [speech in Russia in December 2016,](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MEmg4DNVFSE) especially [the part where he admits talking to Rosneft.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MEmg4DNVFSE feature=youtu.be t=1620) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're saying we should start hitting F5 on /r/politics/new around 3:29? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump team clearly thinks this will help them.  Let's see if they're right.

Let's hope that someone presses him about [the meeting at the Mayflower Hotel.](https://twitter.com/SethAbramson/status/845089192438829056) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TV screen overlays are, as you may imagine, not definitive.

[The goal did not get disallowed.  It was given.  It turned out to be the game-winning goal.  The match was not replayed.](http://www.telegraph.co.uk/sport/football/competitions/bundesliga/10409186/Ghost-goal-match-between-Hoffenheim-and-Bayer-Leverkusen-will-not-be-replayed.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It did not get disallowed.  It was given.  It turned out to be the game-winning goal.  The match was not replayed.](http://www.telegraph.co.uk/sport/football/competitions/bundesliga/10409186/Ghost-goal-match-between-Hoffenheim-and-Bayer-Leverkusen-will-not-be-replayed.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked up "iodine clock".  Then I ask myself, "Where am I going to get sulfuric acid or a persulfate?"

Then I found a [version of the iodine clock reaction with more common household ingredients.](http://imaginationstationtoledo.org/educator/activities/iodine-clock-reaction) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The theory of plate tectonics was one of the most shocking recent discoveries in this history of science, enduring decades of ridicule until the evidence was overwhelming.  Do you think there are any revolutionary ideas in the 21st century, like plate tectonics in the 20th century, that could end up following a similar path -- in geology, or in science in general? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a really good question. I believe that the answer in the case of that redditor was influenceexplorer.com, but part of that website seems to be down at the moment.  An alternative may be opensecrets.org.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 11:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wayne Tracker is going to resonate in the history of aliases, just like Ron Mexico. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying that Obama is controlling my microwave, but in response to Trump's ultimatum, it just suddenly started making popcorn of its own volition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the president needs to know some intelligence, doesn't he already have people to give him, you know, intelligence briefings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> epublicans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something something Br'er Rabbit something something briar patch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, Mark Shanahan of *The Boston Globe*: I [beat you to the punch](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/61193d/trump_to_time_im_president_and_youre_not/dfawm15/) by a few hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/UnexpectedHamilton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just Yandex, Yahoo, and Google?  Really?  Not Baidu? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to /u/flounder19 for the tip.

Here's [the report of the then-confidential review in August 2016.](https://ethics.house.gov/sites/ethics.house.gov/files/OCE%20Report_0.pdf)

Here's [the press release by the Committee on Ethics today.](http://ethics.house.gov/press-release/statement-chairwoman-and-ranking-member-committee-ethics-regarding-representative)

Here's [an explanation of what the press release means.](https://secure.politico.com/story/2017/03/duncan-hunter-campaign-finance-investigation-236422) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> redditor (who has since deleted account) posts analysis of a Congressman's spending in April 2016. Ethics board secretly reviews spending in August 2016. Today, we learn that the Justice Department is pursuing a criminal investigation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would take a highly unlikely Constitutional Amendment, not just "laws".  Recall Article One, Section 6, Clause 1:

The Senators and Representatives shall receive a Compensation for their Services, to be ascertained by Law, and paid out of the Treasury of the United States. They shall in all Cases, except Treason, Felony and Breach of the Peace, be privileged from Arrest during their Attendance at the Session of their respective Houses, and in going to and returning from the same; and for any Speech or Debate in either House, they shall not be questioned in any other Place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I'd username-ping the redditor with the deleted account to let them know that they nailed it... except, you know, they deleted their account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, seriously, though, what does Carl Bernstein know about Nixon's treachery?

#

^(What's that you say?  *All the President's Men*?  He was?  Oh, okay.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, the Artist of the Deal can't even successfully negotiate with his own party in Congress?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Trump failure, and good news for America?

Break out the champagne! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NATURE OF THE ALLEGED VIOLATION: Representative Duncan D. Hunters congressional campaign committee, Duncan D. Hunter for Congress, reported expenditures that may not be legitimate and verifiable campaign expenditures attributable to bona fide campaign or political purposes. Rep. Hunter may have converted tens of thousands of dollars of campaign funds from his congressional campaign committee to personal use to pay for family travel, flights, utilities, health care, school uniforms and tuition, jewelry, groceries, and other goods, services, and expenses.

If Rep. Hunter converted funds from his congressional campaign committee for personal use, then he may have violated House rules, standards of conduct, and federal law.

RECOMMENDATION: The Board recommends that the Committee on Ethics further review the above allegations concerning Rep. Hunter because there is substantial reason to believe that Rep. Hunter converted campaign funds to personal use to pay expenses that were not legitimate and verifiable campaign expenditures attributable to bona fide campaign or political purposes.

VOTES IN THE AFFIRMATIVE: 5

VOTES IN THE NEGATIVE: 0 

ABSTENTIONS: 0

[Source.](https://ethics.house.gov/sites/ethics.house.gov/files/OCE%20Report_0.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any other year, this would rocket to the top story of /r/politics.  As it is, though, it's spitting in the ocean, unless Duncan Hunter's campaign finance violations are somehow connected to Trump.

(I'm not saying that it's impossible that they are.  Hunter was only the second member of Congress to endorse Trump, way back in February 2016, and Hunter was supposedly on the short list to become Trump's Secretary of Defense.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any other year, this would rocket to the top story of /r/politics.  As it is, though, it's spitting in the ocean, unless Duncan Hunter's campaign finance violations are somehow connected to Trump.

(I'm not saying that it's impossible that they are.  Hunter was only the second member of Congress to endorse Trump, way back in February 2016, and Hunter was supposedly on the short list to become Trump's Secretary of Defense.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like that episode of *The West Wing* in which the Bartlet administration tricks Congress into firing the special prosecutor and conducting a partisan investigation instead.

Except that this time, the presidential administration **doesn't** want Congress to call for a special prosecutor, but is making it even more obvious than that fictional administration that Congess **should**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh.  No, I don't use Bing either, at least not since I was last behind The Great Firewall of China. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, can we bet reddit gold?  (Spoiler alert: [I would win.](http://www.alexa.com/siteinfo/breitbart.com)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops, [actually it turns out that Breitbart.com is more popular in China than in Russia, and the fraction of Russian traffic is unknown, but small.](http://www.alexa.com/siteinfo/breitbart.com)

Of course, it isn't *proof* of treason.  I've known several Russian programmers, none of whom, to my knowledge, were agents of the Russian government (nor the Soviet government, way back when.)  But who is the Russian programmer who designed Breitbart's home page?  I'd love to hear the story from him or her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least so far, he's not using any of those tactics.  Rather:
If this nominee cannot earn 60 votes  a bar met by each of President Obamas nominees, and George Bushs last two nominees  the answer isnt to change the rules. Its to change the nominee.

And:

[...] was unable to sufficiently convince me that hed be an independent check [on Trump].

And:

[...] not a neutral legal mind but someone with a deep-seated conservative ideology.  He was groomed by the Federalist Society and has shown not one inch of difference between his views and theirs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pop quiz: where in the Constitution does it say that there are only 9 seats on the Supreme Court?

(Hint: It doesn't.  FDR threatened to increase the number of Supreme Court seats so he could pack the court.  There's fundamentally nothing stopping a unified president and Congress from putting as many people on the Supreme Court as they want.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask yourself this, then.  They're already using Google analytics.  Why also analytics from Yandex, a Russian search engine?  Why **not** also analytics from Baidu, a far more popular Chinese search engine?  Why **not** also analytics from Bing, a search engine that's actually in, you know, the USA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So here's a fun exercise.  Go to breitbart.com.  View the webpage source.  Find the line that says:
	meta name='yandex-verification' content='48776dffe0b99888' /

Ask yourself why Breitbart is using a **Russian search engine's** analytics.

(Thanks to /u/anon902503, who linked to [this tweet about it.](https://twitter.com/christogrozev/status/843985158499942400)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely Cummings will have lots of Republican support, because Republicans are oh-so-concerned about leaks.  Right?  ^Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smoke, meet fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chevy Chase, is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the single most effective evidence of climate change when convincing skeptics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But this was FISA surveillance, which is specifically for foreign agents suspected of espionage or terrorism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they should treasure their unique opportunity to hear a commencement speech from a former president who resigned in disgrace in the first few months of his term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care if Donald Trump is Ice Cube in disguise... today, for him, It Was **Not** a Good Day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I thought what was next to Nunes's name was . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sally Yates! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, but they were specifically under FISA surveillance, which is only for espionage and terrorism suspects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems as if you are saying something that may be particularly surprising for people who have just moved to Virginia from almost any other state:

#VIRGINIA HAS GUBERNATORIAL ELECTIONS IN 2017. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I have grave concerns too.  Like: 

* Why were members of the Trump transition team, and possibly Trump himself, communicating with people who were under surveillance as possible criminals?

* Why has Nunes not resigned from the Intelligence Committee, since he himself was a member of the Trump transition team? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For new arrivals in Virginia: when are the next elections in Virginia?  Will it surprise some people how quickly those elections are coming up?  What are the voter registration deadlines? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nunes actually literally said "The reports that I was able to see did not have anything to do with Russia or the Russian investigation." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, [he was a member of the executive committee for Trump's transition team.](http://www.latimes.com/politics/essential/la-pol-ca-essential-politics-updates-rep-devin-nunes-named-to-trump-s-1478893307-htmlstory.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, [he was a member of the executive committee for Trump's transition team.](http://www.latimes.com/politics/essential/la-pol-ca-essential-politics-updates-rep-devin-nunes-named-to-trump-s-1478893307-htmlstory.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specifically "hombres" seems unlikely, unless there is reason to believe that Trump has connections to the Mexican mafia, who appear to be the "bad hombres" to whom Trump was referring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shh!  *First* let Nunes obstruct, *then* tell him it's obstruction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredibly, this commentary piece, less than half an hour old, is already out of date: the latest revelations are now that House Intelligence Chairman Devin Nunes has claimed that personal communications of the Trump transition team, and possibly of Trump himself, have been picked up by investigators.  Nunes also claims that the communications are incidental collection, but not Russia-related.

The next-to-latest revelations discussed in this commentary piece are Manafort's work as a Russian asset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
