<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2044</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a load of them doing the rounds in London at the moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw Things We Lost years ago and remember loving it. I love the editing style and think it's a great way to create a kind of impressionism within stories, chopping back and forth and showing things in association rather than linearly. Very few films do it but it always works well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, only one is an original script </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When groups of men slip into that weird negative, primitive, cynical group-think thing where they assume that because you're there, you obviously don't mind and will join in the banter. I worked in an office once where it was customary for a manager to look out the window and say "look at that fat cunt" about whoever happened to be passing by, to which others would add more critical slurs. I used to drive home feeling so drained and uninspired.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I didn't either way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously, context is going to be a crucial variable here. Do you understand that? Does it make sense?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 150% of a *belief* seems a strange thing. I wonder how much percentage of belief certainty is worth?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're saying something obvious, you might be worried that you're not explaining it clearly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I generally enjoyed it, and admired its ambitions, but it had one major flaw. It didn't rise above its influences. Say for example an Edgar Wright film, even though you know its packed full of homages, the core of the film is oomphy and interesting enough to be a film in its own right. The homages are an after thought. Same with something like Kill Bill, or Carpenter's Assault on Precinct 13.   

But The Void will *only* be talked about in terms of its homages, it doesn't have the oomph or confidence in itself to rise above those comparisons and feel like a worthy project or story in its own right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's some Dettol in the jeep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some good points. Generally, in my experience, people seem to use that particular coping mechanism of diminishing personal accountability with something like "it was meant to be" when they (consciously or unconsciously) know that they were somehow responsible OR a freak event that is *positive* (where it feels nice to think it was destined). E.g. Anna gets rejected by her partner, because she lies all the time. Rather than take accountability for that (something which is perceived by her mind as painful), she says "oh well, it wasn't meant to be" and moves on, forever stubborn in her self-denial. Or, Anna picks the winning lottery numbers just as she's planning to save up for a new car, and says "it was meant to be". But if in a gusty gale, a slate slides off of Anna's roof and decapitates her cat, she probably won't say "it was meant to be", neither would her neighbors when consoling her. But yes I agree. 

As a complete aside but related to your comment on religion/Buddhism/dumb animals on a rock, recently I've been trying to live in the frame that free/conscious will is an illusion, that everything is a happening and some things just feel like doings, and it really does cause some massive shifts in perspective on things.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed this, although its one of those homage projects that seems so focused on its reference points that it never really becomes bigger than that, it doesn't become a thing of its own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, I appreciate its a coping mechanism. But it can also be unhealthy to imply *meaning*, as it encourages an external locus of control and diminishes personal accountability (even if there is none, the sense of personal accountability generally can be diminished by any belief system that promotes some sort of cosmic "meaning"). Something like "its just one of those things..." seems far more appropriate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is like a found-footage version of that fucked-up film Rubber.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing about this scene that I never see mentioned. She's making popcorn, and when I saw this at the cinema the screen also smelled like popcorn. So it was a clever way to build a little more immersion, because you could literally *smell* the scene.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a thread based on phrases people are sick of other people saying, its natural that some playful ranting is going to occur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peter Jackson's Dead Alive (Braindead in UK).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When sports personalities (or David Brent style managers) talk about giving something 110% or higher.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do say this sometimes if friends are bitching and whining about some situation where they're clearly not able to accept reality (e.g. a date that didn't go as well as hoped). Its usually a substitute for "shut up and deal with it".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or when someone says something obvious followed by *"if that makes sense"* as if to dampen their knowing righteousness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Also, "oh well, I guess it was meant to be". No it *wasn't* you fool, so rather than apathetically brush it aside why don't you reflect on your personal accountability in the situation so you can learn from it for the future? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "At the end of the daaaay, being honest, all said and done, truth be told, the long and short of if is ...[some half baked opinion based on ignorance]" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the french kid who can smell ridiculously well, and starts killing girls to capture their scent (also the inspiration for Scentless Apprentice by Nirvana).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He comes across like the annoying guy who gets shot as part of an action scene in the first act of a nineties thriller (but no one cares).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHOOAAA what the fuck? Flight of the Navigator is *still* a great movie. HOW FUCKING DARE YOU.   

Seriously though, the atmospheres in the film are so unique and cool, especially the whole section from walking his dog on that spooky walk, calling on his (now older) parents and then escaping in the ship. Once he's in the ship, things get a little cornier, but that section is only the last third of the film, and it gets cool again once they try to go back in time. I still think its a really interesting film. I think about what happens at the end - imagine if within a couple of years his parents got divorced or one died for whatever reason, David would know that in the parallel world where he went missing for 8 years, they stayed together and survived, so it would really fuck his head up knowing that his presence has a weird butterfly effect for the worse. DARYL is also still an awesome film, they're both just kind of exciting and fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Unbearable Lightness of Being (Milan Kundera)  
Perfume (Peter Suskind) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So rather than discussing the mechanics of its plot that you think about, you post a trailer instead for the karma eh?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repo Man, and Upstream Color.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2001 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe how quickly the film was turned around either, between the first two Batman films. Its so meticulous and perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the first two seasons, but whilst its fairly interesting here and there and has some nice character observation, I found it difficult to really feel engaged with the story. It just all feels a bit limp.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine too, sad times. Was after showing some friends a bunch of VR stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its nuts isn't it? Its like the cinematographer knew how to focus the camera to where your eye should be looking. I also loved the bits where the editing team managed to make the sound of people speaking synchronize with their mouth movements on screen. Also when Felicity Jones is talking, I like how the director made sure we can see her face rather than a close up of her shoe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine this is what prison wardens do after saying "LIGHTS OUT BITCHES!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rug really ties the room together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was watchable, but mainly out of curiosity for where the story went. I found the characters and the overall modern-teenager vibes excruciating. If they hadn't pandered to the audience demographic and kept it fairly sensible (e.g. Stranger Things vibes) it would have been much more fun and memorable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still haven't seen The Way Back and I should because I adore Peter Weir's films. I hope it has the same level of depth and subtlety as the others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Powerful? It felt extremely satirical, but maybe that's because I've seen this used as background music in probably 100 amateur edits by now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed it on first watch, and its admirable for bringing Desmond's story to the screen. But I don't think it does it with a true sense of integrity or cinematic depth. In hindsight it feels very Hollywood, emotionally manipulative, overly-polished and kind of bland because of that. I have no desire to rewatch it at all, there's nothing between the lines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently watched The Neverending Story and felt the impulse to visit the boards to see what trivia and thoughts fans have written over the years. Then felt that familiar sense of loss after finishing pretty much every movie I enjoyed that I want to explore further in some way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blimey thats pedantic. Im sure OP would be willing to change the word "driving" to "riding" on the flyer for this imaginary triple bill to keep you from losing your shit and throwing it at the screen in protest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, Eyes Wide Shut, Run Lola Run, Summer of Sam. I really dont think a more recent year compares. 1999 had BIG movies that are still talked about today, like Fight Club. Listing other years below with stuff like Spy, Rogue Nation or Hardcore Henry just seems a bit silly. Fucking *Spy*, seriously </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how the film is like a magic trick, with Caine directly referencing the audience. In a way, both Prestige and Inception are like meta-explorations of cinema as illusion (I realise how pretentious that sounds). Also, Im blown away by how quickly The Prestige was made, between the first two Batman films. Its one of the few films I feel is an improvement on the book, with substantial changes for the better. Its such an exquisite, meticulous film that feels like it should have taken years to make. Amazing it was released in such a low key way as well (although Ive been lucky to see all of Nolans films at the cinema since Memento).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 10:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. After the film Compliance came out a few years back I researched the pranknet scene and was shocked to find out how much these kinds of pranks/scams happen. The thing that freaks me out is that for every one that gets heard about there are probably a lot more than go unreported.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't eat beans... I get a rash if I eat beans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll add attention seeking troll to the blanket judgement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not literally made of cardboard. Google Cardboard was the original version, where you had a very simple cardboard VR set to try it out. The apps still come under the umbrella of "Google Cardboard" to mean VR, but the headsets have evolved into much better quality versions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't ever had that on an LG G4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to have no clue what the app does or why its good. Its a lot more than putting seats in front of you. How did you get to be so contrary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're all the same, the company that manufactures them sells out unbranded units so other resellers can rebrand them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! Hopefully she'll love it. I recommend the "Cedar Falls" rollercoaster free from Playstore as a way to introduce her to it - its a brilliantly detailed coaster (the best in my opinion) with a huge drop that makes everyone lurch and feel sick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes exactly that. There are free ones available, but the cmoar app is insanely detailed and realistic. Its really as if you're there. I load up something like Escape from New York and feel like I've gone to some late showing and been the only one to show up so have the theatre to myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it does! Also IPD and lens focus adjustment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're fine. They're the better end of low-end headphones, good enough bass and clarity. There is a version of the headset available without headphones to make it easier using your own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, because the lenses distort the light to make it exactly the same as if you were looking at a huge screen that was much further away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the picture is excellent. I use an LG G4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the focus and lenses make it so it doesn't appear inches from your face at all. What phone/headset did you use? I'm very impressed with it, and have watched a few full films with the cinema experience. It gives a much better immersion than TV, a different experience entirely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it works excellently - that's exactly the phone I have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a high-resolution phone with a gyro sensor, a BoboVR Z4 Google Cardboard VR headset for about $25 with built in headphones, and the Cmoar cinema app for $5. Upload 1080p films to your phone storage, watch them in your own private cinema. Its genuinely immersive, excellent picture quality, and fully captures the feeling and scale of being a the cinema. The seats even reflect the light of the film as you look around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they meant Diet Coke rather than normal Coke, because its less sugary. *Right?*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I daren't look up my playing time for GTA:O. I'm terrified to. I know if I start thinking about the foreign languages or other knowledge I could have learned I'll feel depressed as hell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IPD is misunderstood. Usually it means inter pupillary distance but of course here its inter LENS distance. If you have lenses directly in front of your eyes, your eyes will stare directly forwards, see the images, and the brain will merge them. If the lenses (bobo lenses, not eye lenses) are slightly closer, then the eye gaze will gave to converge slightly, before the brain merges the images. These two scenarios have different results on the sense of distance that is perceived. You need to focus the lenses differently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw The Accountant alone in a screen, and loved it. It was such a weirdly good experience being able to shout things out, or bark, because I could.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a weird coincidence. Yesterday (when you posted) I mentioned to mum (who has a bike set up in front of a tv) that she could probably get a VR app to cycle to.   

But, here's why I don't think it would work. With a straight road, you mention that people would want to just look around. Would they? I think the last thing people would want to do is wear a big thing strapped to their heads, fogging up, head itching from micro-perspiration in the hair with the straps, just so they can look around at polygon trees which would get boring fast. Then there's the issue of battery drain, whatsapp/text/calls interfering the flow. It just seems like finding a problem for a solution rather than the other way round. I really can't see how it would be better to deal with all that over watching something on TV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be extremely interested to know how a 1080p video file looks in cmoar cinema (or alternative) on a 4k phone. On my LG G4 it looks pretty damn good, but can see pixelation here and there. Something like The Lego Movie is nowhere near as sharp as on TV. If a 4K screen can approach that, I'd love to hear about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing I've noticed on my bobo is that a completely different feel can be found according to whether you have the IPD set narrow or wide. Both variables can be adjusted for focus. A wider IPD gives a wider FOV, but the two fields of vision have a smaller 3D overlap. Recently I've been much preferred the feel of narrower IPD, with more 3D and immersion. I don't notice any difference at all between my 2nd Bobo under different branding, compared to the first on release last year. The 2nd one is much better though with the perforated pvc padding rather than foam, and longer jack lead to plug into my LG G4 without using an extension.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 08:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, just saying sorry you had such a shit response here. This is where IMDB boards are sorely missed because you'd have had a good, detailed and on-point response there. If you ask a technical query like that here, people feel they have to respond because "alien", have nothing useful to contribute so take it out on you instead with junk negativity in the hope it will stir the hivemind and get upvotes. Ive seen a LOT of reasonable observations or queries get trashed by morons, OP gets justifably frustrated, more morons say "chill man, its just a film". This sub reallly isnt good for film discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 08:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes a post just has bad luck and attracts assholes, who seem to influence other assholes like in that conformity study by Asch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe anyone who has worked 39 loyal years for a company and lost his son in the process deserves a relaxing retirement. If you don't, then I can't say I give a shit that you're "pissed off so much" about it. *Now fuck off.*    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ man, when someone writes you "good luck" in a leaving card, do you call them up and berate them on the physics of determinism and fallacies of belief in fortune or lack of? Chill the fuck out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Tony Robbins seminars, worshiping their leader.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your bf and your mom are *very fucked up people*. You are not. You have that going for you, escape from these assholes with that intact, let them experience their own hell without someone like you to make it better.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish you a relaxing retirement Jerry, you surely deserve it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I called up Michael Mann's production company after that film, and asked to speak to him. They put me through to him, whilst he was on a sound stage for Ali. I asked him questions about it and he chatted, it was awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first one by Yeah Yeah Yeahs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagined this being Spud from Trainspotting, saying "i joost gat hitt bah fookin' PAJJIN!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper Moon is such a terrific film. Its like a Coen bros movie for its visual style, language patterns and overall creativity in writing. I can imagine George Clooney playing O Neals part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't think its conjecture. Pasted from a James Cameron interview "well yeah, we were going to shoot a scene where the Queen has a little Giger designer backpack, with a couple of straps around her arms. When she's on the ship, she unzips a compartment and takes out an egg, sort of splooges it into the corner of a room, then unzips another compartment to drink from a HR Giger branded water bottle before sharpening her tail then hiding. But Gale said we should cut it because of time, we already had to lose reel 4 and the backpack/waterbottle merchandise tie-in deal fell through so yeah, we had to lose it. But it definitely happened".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes no sense. Would *you* like a film that was middle-of-the-road as possible? If you would, then by definition like it that way. If you don't, then you're disproving your argument that a middle-of-the-road film would be universally liked. Its a poor argument to use a film being disliked as some argument that its doing something right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily. The queen had a little HR Giger designer backpack, with an egg in it, and she snuck on, planted the egg, then gone and done Bishop in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 12:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great list, and just what I'd have put. North   South is SO much fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I love Aliens for its structure, fun and classic set-pieces, but for cinematic atmosphere and depth, I actually prefer Alien 3. Its a *really* intriguing and original story, a far cry from what you'd expect from a threqual. That Fincher did as good a job as he did under the circumstances is absolutely extraordinary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. The funny thing is that it ends up almost convincing me its a shit film! Some of the points are pretty valid.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was absolutely brutal, and made me feel sick inside at the cinema. I can't think of a more horrifying concept in a film.    

In terms of logic though, it unravels slightly. Like the guy in the present suddenly starts losing limbs etc, but the very moment they alter him in the past, his whole destiny would change. Its unlikely he would end up in the exact same spot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great film! Some of the segments really got under my skin, especially the guy with the parking ticket and the wedding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why its perfect! It would make it so much more impactful and otherworldly. Predator was one of the first "grownup" actioners I'd ever seen, and I'm so thankful I was introduced to it around that time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 07:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres *plenty* of good aspects to Alien 3. The direction, atmosphere, set design, camerawork, originality, performances, themes and subtexts. The opening credit sequence is brilliant. The thing that isnt so great is the dodgy CGI. I really don't think Alien3 should be classed as a "bad film", most people just hate on it because its so different to Aliens and killed off Hicks/Newt so soon. But I admire its balls for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's it! I remember once having been stuck for a while, I went to get my haircut in town, and Iain (the kid with a 1gb harddrive because his dad was into IT) was there waiting too. I asked, and he explained this bit. I couldn't wait to get my haircut and rush home to continue with the *awesome* game. Sadly Iain died in his mid-twenties when a parachute failed to open properly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I laughed hard at some of that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Capturing The Friedmans must have frustrated them too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Die Hard 2, Point Break and Crimson Tide are a lot of fun. I guess CT isn't really action but it sort of feels like it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are absolutely right, excellent post. Not only that, many hypnotherapists market shockingly inaccurate things, and cannot leave their egotistical bubbles to even contemplate what their customer is actually looking for. They literally think the customer is there to say "wow, you're so knowledgeable and powerful, here, take my money".   

I used to be a hypnotherapist/hypnotist and also marketed adwords for other small businesses (I recognised the importance of marketing so naturally read up and got good at it). Once I marketed a special territorial deal for hypnotherapists, ready made with relevant keyword combinations etc. Wow - the dialogues I got into with hypnotherapists were amazing. They were incredibly ignorant, defensive, and massively obtuse. Some were just total assholes. I stopped it in the end and focused on other niches, they weren't worth the effort and I was happy to watch them crash and burn with a total lack of clients.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a study done which found responsiveness to increase when more specific instructions were used, and the subject rehearsed a few times. Basically, people respond differently *because of what they do in their heads*. You need decent, specific instructions and you need to do them, rather than be distracted by your own thoughts. Essentially you just need to imagine the right things, until you forget that you're imagining them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> old Amiga games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She looks like the cute girl you fancied at Blockbuster one time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Polly has a weirder, firmer jaw and more hostile, harder eyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I was going to suggest. I have one and used to take clips like this all the time, once I zoomed into Jupiter and saw a bright dot with four dots around it (Jupiter's moons). Incredible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Predator, Die Hard, Aliens, Robocop, Terminator.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I remember that ram module. Also Monkey Island, I got stuck for *months* before figuring out I had to throw poisoned flowers (or sausages, can't remember) to the dog to get past it. Then getting an A600 and having to load Kickstart 1.3 (or whatever it was) to play Supercars and North   South.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We mocked Iain for getting a 1gb drive but only 'cause jealousy. I think he used about 300mb. Its weird to also think than an amazing game like Syndicate back then was only about 3mb big, whereas now even an Adobe Reader update is over 100mb. I remember when my mum got a zipdrive for work, and everyone was "wow, you can fit *100 floppy discs* on *one zip drive!*"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 12:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I had an Amiga in the early 90s, a 270mb HD was a huge thing that clicked onto the side and cost about 150.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 11:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next up the director of CHiPS is rebooting Big Trouble in Little China with Jai Courtney and Amy Schumer. Just kidding (but I wouldn't be surprised).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 11:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would disagree on that. Gosling is good at what he does, but having more range? The difference between his subdued mode and slightly-more-expressive really isn't that great, with everything else (e.g Fracture, Only God Forgives) falling somewhere in between.   

McAvoy's range between say Atonement and Filth, or even *within* Split is pretty extraordinary. He seems to encapsulate his characters with his whole being. Psychopaths, everyman, comedy. I just can't see how you can say he hasn't shown that range when he clearly has.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 11:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen Split? Those performances were great, but I feel that Split is his showreel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 11:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rodriguez is far too eager to impress his audience and contemporaries (well, Tarantino) with a bunch of self-conscious gimmicky shit and cameos etc. He learned a bunch of useful filmmaking stuff from all the older films he watched except how to tell a good story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *...vaaallk!* (FTFY).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tamitami, what youve just said had a negative effect on my brain cells. At no point in your rambling, incoherent post were you even close to writing anything that could be considered a sentence worth reading. You should dunk your head in a sink of cold water and contemplate your sense of purpose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently hes going to reboot Escape From New York which I don't trust him with at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
