<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7195</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing too special, I was just proud of my latest Bohemia game where I decided to dismantle the HRE. Pretty much concerned myself with knocking out everyone exclusively in the HRE until 1700, and then I got a chance to contest a PU with France. I would've like to have been able to integrate them, but alas. 

It ended up being too late to remove the Ottomans, so I just nibbled off Spain, London, Tunis, and Italy for the remaining years. It's the most I've expanded in a game before, and started getting really boring towards the mid 1700s. Had no idea what achievement I could've gone for that I didn't already have, and ended up getting Market Control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They didn't want to elect me HRE so I made my own. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fever Dream! Really gripping and uniquely written. I rarely feel the level of ominous dread to the extent that I did during reading that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my first foray into Mitchell. A fantastic book. Reading Thousand Autumns presently, glad to hear more praise! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bakewell is great at presenting a clear depiction of the existentialist movement in that book. Stick with it! I just finished it a week or two ago and has spurred some real interest in reading the works of the philosophers she discussed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, I loved Atlantis Found when I was in high school. I thought Cussler was going to be one of my favorite authors. But damn me if he doesn't just regurgitate adventure plots every year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had heard a lot of praise for Locke Lamora, but I was similarly apathetic about a lot of it. I listened to it on my rides home from work, and it was enjoyable enough, but it doesn't seem to have had a lasting impact. The characters are all wise-cracking, witty delinquents and Lynch's dialogue was enjoyable, but by the end it just all felt like one of those 1st in a trilogy vapid summer blockbusters. I'm in the same boat whether or not I'll continue it at some point, but I was hoping more time would've been spent on lore and world-building then on finely crafted back-and-forth dialogue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Mariner's Revenge Song is just about the greatest modern sea chanty you'll ever hear. A rollicking 9 minute tale of retribution on the high seas. 

Otherwise, the rest of the Picaresque album uses traditional diction and themes of the genre, with the first two songs in the album personally the most catchy/relevant to your interests. The Crane Wife and The King is Dead are also two classic Decemberist album that I'd check out if you end up liking Picaresque.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything, haha. I find myself reading and rereading passages, trying to figure out what exactly he's trying to get at. What's the purpose of this specific point of the plot, or why is he spending time meandering around this subject for pages on end. I go into every novel knowing that he's writing some kind of satire, but there's no way for the reader to join in on the whole joke if you take it all at surface value. His works are incredibly rewarding, but they are a labor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An entertaining, playful modern retelling of the gothic picaresque/fairy tale that I read last year was Patrick DeWitt's "Undermajordomo Minor." Thomas Pynchon's books often have a lot of characters with qualities resembling those in picaresque novels, employing peculiar names and idiosyncrasies, but he's a difficult author sometimes, and you have to work for an understanding of his stuff. His "Crying of Lot 49," is a nice short introduction to his style, and "Inherent Vice" is a comical riff on detective novels that was recently made into a movie. Not a novel, but whenever I hear the word Picaresque, the Decemberists album of the same name comes to mind, and is amazing. Lyrical picaresque characters and antiquated plotlines woven into song.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> part 1: https://www.reddit.com/r/eu4/comments/63z3gr/couldnt_sleep_so_i_spent_3_hours_writing_a/

Due to adequate demand, I've returned with part two of my long-winded period drama, "Bohemia AAR". This one is a doozy, 36 images in length. My thoughts were to create an album for each ruler as I played them, but I'm not sure if that'll be able to be kept up. Mr. Jiri z Podebrad lasted for quite a while, but his successors might not. People might not like to read too many image descriptions either, so should I continue with this recreational project, I'll do my best with the pacing.

For the time being, I hope you enjoy reading my chronicle of the early history of Bohemia. I had a lot of fun creating the narrative for Jiri, so hopefully that comes across in the writing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Insomniac's Bohemian AAR Part TWO, The Reign of King Jiri, aka Electric Boogaloo, otherwise known as Battle Tendency, more commonly referred to as The Hussites Strike Back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could be right, it's been awhile since I took classes on the subject. From what I recall, Chiang spent a lot of his time hunting down the Red Army sympathizers (exhibit A: The Long March), It was the Red Army guerrilla warfare tactics against the Japanese and resource sharing with small, devastated villages of peasants near the Northern Manchuria occupied regions that garnered them a lot of support. Obviously, they couldn't fight effectively either with the Nationalist Army of China hunting them down. 

I don't mean to romanticize the Red Army, nor discredit the Nationalist army fully. I think Chiang didn't get criticized enough, especially by Americans due to us "siding" with him throughout the war. While he was in a precarious position, I think he was far too obsessed with wiping out the Red Army. This is all my own personal belief, though, and I can understand sentiment either way. It's just what I learned about the whole situation developed a certain bias against him and his tactics during the war. Thanks for bringing up the other side of the argument! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Chinese casualties were Chinese civilians and disarmed soldiers. Most did not have military training, so fighting was not an option for them. Nanking was their home. A cease-fire to evacuate the city was proposed, but Chiang Kai-Shek refused to surrender the city. It's important to recognize state of the nation of China was in disarray, that while Chiang technically ruled the country, he proved completely inept at fighting the Japanese invasion. Instead, he spent much of his resources eliminating the Red Army. 

Sorry I don't have any numbers for the Japanese invading army, but I figured that if the core of your question was why the Chinese didn't fight back, that is better answered by examining what was going on internally in China at this time. A lot of great history books have been written about this topic if you're looking to research, one that comes to mind is Edgar Snow's account of the Red Army in the Red Star Over China, which concerns itself with the political situation in China before the Japanese invasion. 

*edit: The film City of Life and Death by Lu Chuan was a great visualization of the Massacre itself, too. Touches on the disarmed soldiers, women, children, and International Ambassadors within the city during the occupation, and what they went through.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Stormlight Archives are the only Sanderson books I've read, and I've greatly enjoyed them. While there are only two publishing, the third is set to come out later this year I believe. The characters are really well written, and the pacing of his world building was really satisfying. I say this latter point because I'm incredibly frustrated with Rothfuss's Kingkiller Chronicles, as I feel like for a large portion of the books, so many facets of society are left unexplored. Sanderson introduces such a diverse array of characters and different perspectives that everything about his world comes together seamlessly in an engrossing way. 

I don't think you need to read any other of Sanderson's books first, like others have suggested, unless you want to appreciate the apparent shift in his writing skills. Some characters, however, have connections to his great literary universe, so perhaps reading other books will tune you into those cross-overs. All in all, though, a fantastic stand-alone series.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that work in college for a class I took on World War II era China. As an American whose country always condemns communism as some abject terror, it was extremely elucidating to see how the Red Army functioned. Snow produced a much needed exposure of Mao Zedong, Zhao Enlai, and other forerunners of the Communist China. Good on you for committing to this one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Edit, part 1: https://www.reddit.com/r/eu4/comments/63z3gr/couldnt_sleep_so_i_spent_3_hours_writing_a/

Due to adequate demand, I've returned with part two of my long-winded period drama, "Bohemia AAR". This one is a doozy, 36 images in length. My thoughts were to create an album for each ruler as I played them, but I'm not sure if that'll be able to be kept up. Mr. Jiri z Podebrad lasted for quite a while, but his successors might not. People might not like to read to many image descriptions, either, so should I continue with this recreational project, I'll do my best with the pacing. 

For the time being, I hope you enjoy reading my chronicle of the early history of Bohemia. I had a lot of fun creating the narrative for Jiri, so hopefully that comes across in the writing. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I found myself unable to sleep tonight, so I gathered some pictures from my recent Bohemia game (trying out the new free patch features), and attempted to actually role play a little bit. I put a little bit a time into it, reading up on wikipedia to throw in some historical grounding, and generally devising a sub-par storyline to go along with the events of my playthrough. I kind of wanted to take it slow with this run, and focus on goals from ruler to ruler. Figured if I ended up chronicling it, at least that'd be a good way to catalog each part. 

This being said, you might intuit that the first part here is fairly short since Bohemia begins in interregnum and then Jiri z Podebrad  pops up and overthrows your first king. Or at least, that's how I always play them because I feel strongly about that kind of thing (Habsburgs be damned). 

Anyway, thanks for reading whoever does. I'm just a simple man who likes to look at maps, so I apologize for any mistakes I made. It's also 3am. Goodnight, reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
