<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for all of your concern. My first part post got removed from nosleep because it was labeled as an intro and not an actual story. I will repost it tomorrow so all of you who want to follow me in this can. I'll edit it to include the series flair (I didn't know that was a thing since this is my first time to post on here) and mention that there is more to the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Wish My Roommate Was Here (Part 2) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1 Here] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/69ms9y/i_wish_my_roommate_was_here_part_1/?st=J2DM9JCT sh=e828831a)

Most of you are probably asking yourselves, "why the hell is this guy so frightened by his dad?" This is a fair question, one I will have to back up for. My mom was married to a man before she met my dad. They had apparently met in high school and married soon afterwards. They had my 3 older siblings together. My mom separated from him shortly after my older brother was born. I don't know all of the details, but supposedly he was abusive and an alcoholic. Anyways, after spending some time as a single parent, my mom met my dad through a mutual friend. Apparently, they hit it off pretty quickly. Before they got married, I was conceived. They married shortly after they learned of the pregnancy. I guess you could say I kinda drove them together. From what I've heard, there weren't really any issues or warning signs to be seen when they got together. My mom never had any idea what kind of man - or rather, monster - she was marrying.

I don't remember much from my childhood, but later in life my siblings reluctantly filled me in. I was my dad's first kid. I was born out of wedlock, to a woman that I would claim he never even really loved. Naturally, his anger at his situation was taken out on me. Like her first husband, my dad was an angry and violent alcoholic. Fights ensued almost daily at our house. Usually they were just shouting matches, but sometimes they turned physical. Sometimes, when things got really bad between him and my mom, he would hold me (as an infant, under the age of 3) hostage. He would lay down in bed holding me, the barrel of a pistol pressed against my temple. "Come to fucking bed woman, or I swear to God, I will reprint our bedroom before I pump another one in you," was just one of the many colorful phrases he liked to use. There were many incidents, as I have been told, from when I was little. However, to save time and space, I'll share the most distinct, most horrible memory I have of him.

I was 11 years old. I remember very distinctly, it was 3 days after my birthday. I came home from school one day, climbing off the bus. I see my dad's car in the driveway, which I find odd because he was usually at work. My older siblings had all left home (they were 18 or older), and on that particular day, my mom and little sister were at the hospital. My little sister was recovering from a very serious surgery. I walked in and find my dad on the couch, watching TV and drinking what was definitely not his first beer of the day. The floor in front of the couch was littered with crushed cans, the whole room was filled with the stench of beer. Before I could even say, "Hi Dad," he called out, "Get some fucking work clothes on. We have work to do." My dad was a mechanic for almost as long as he could remember. His actual job was as an aircraft painter for a private corporation, but he always did mechanic work on the side in our garage to make extra cash. I go upstairs and set my stuff down. I was used to his anger and, honestly, was usually just happy if he wasn't hitting me or throwing things at me. I change and run back downstairs, heading to the garage. "What took you so long?" He says, hunched under the hood of a car, beer in hand. "Sorry, sir," I reply.

We work silently on the car, him occasionally calling out the name of a tool and me retrieving it for him. It was a simple routine, one we'd repeated countless times from the time I was 8. After a couple hours or so, I attempt to break the silence. "So, did you get off work early today?" I inquire. From under the car, I hear a sort of angry snort. "The fuck did you just say?" He rolls out from under the car and I see his face twisted in an angry grimace. Fear washes over me like a tall wave knocking a swimmer off of their feet. He stands up, towering over me. He steps forwards me and I step backwards. "I..I..I..I just..." my voice breaks as I back into our stack toolbox. "Just what?" He yells. I find myself unable to speak, which appears to anger him even more. He takes the beer can sitting under the hood of the car and chunks it at me, sending a trail of beer flying through the air, nailing me right in the shoulder. I had closed my eyes and shielded my face when I saw him throw, and when I opened them back up I see him moving upon me. He seizes me by each of my arms and pulls me away from the toolbox. "I'll show you to ask fucking questions you have no business asking," he grunts as he walks me to the car.

He puts his hand square in between my shoulder blades and pushes my head and chest down on to the motor of the car forcefully. He uses the same hand to grab the hood and pull it down harshly, though not slamming it down as I had anticipated. With my arms spread out and the hood down on my back, he takes a smaller toolbox and drops it on the spot of the hood directly above me. I cannot even begin to explain how I feel at this point. My chest has tightened, my lungs feel as if they've both been pierced, my head is spinning, and my vocal chords seem to have seized. As much as I want to call out, scream, beg, or cry, I can't. I struggle, attempting to free myself, but the weight of the hood and the toolbox are simply too much for an 11 year old boy. It is at this second that the world itself changed for me. I feel my dad reach around my waist and begin removing my shorts. "You're just like your fucking whore mother so I'm going to treat you like her," he sinisterly whispers to me at the same time as my shorts and underwear are being dropped to my ankles. I hear his belt being removed and his zipper unzip. I feel a single tear push it's way out of my eye ad drip off of my cheek to the motor components underneath me. What came next was, well....

That part of the story is terribly difficult for me to even think about myself, let alone share with others. I'm sorry, I just can't do it. What I can say is that at that very moment, I died inside. And while I wish I could say this was only a single isolated incident, I cannot truthfully make that claim. Each time afterwards, I died a bit more.

[Part 3 Here] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/69tlet/i_wish_my_roommate_was_here_part_3/?st=J2F5PKF1 sh=25ea90c6) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's definitely more, it's just hard for me to talk about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
