<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4010</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[BUG]** Game crashes every half hour, it's just random. By now I've lost a couple of thousand minerals and a couple of guns because the game froze while I was swimming to my base. F*cking perfect. This only happened after the update and now I can barely play because of this. I don't get any error messages because everytime it crashes I have to get the task manager open to close Rust down, if I don't it just loads forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. I've recently started to level up medic class and just got to level 1, almost every time someone dies it's either run to them and revive in a 2 second span or not making it.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 10:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sounds like Miles Teller </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That didn't even answer my question... I did download them though and all of them stood still checking for updates for 6 hours with nothing happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 13:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would I need all of them? Looks like some of them are more up to date than others </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 13:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, nothing changes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 21:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Timezone is correct, but I never receive an update error. It just never stops checking for updates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 21:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has been going for about 5 hours straight now, no errors. I tried finding a solution some months ago and tried to manually install the last win7 update they gave out but it didn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows 7 won't install the last updates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 19:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just stuck on "checking for updates", and since I had to re-install windows on my pc any update have never been installed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 23:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree with almost everything you said, after watching the movie I wanted to know more about what happened to their characters and how this will/may tie in with the games in any way. Only thing I disagree with you is the death of Maria. I thought it was perfect the way it was shown. It showed the dedication of the members of the creed where they wouldn't let their emotion control the outcome of the events. It was either save Maria and maybe lose the apple/get killed in the process or kill the pope/saint guy.  But because he chose to try to save her she died right away which almost resulted in him getting killed.
The beginning was alright but could've been shortened a little bit. The ending was a little confusing to me with Sofia's change of heart. I was really sure they would make her join the assassins instead of her taking her fathers place since she didn't like what he was going to do with the apple.

Other than that I really liked the movie, the action was awesome and i believed in the characters motivations. Really hope that it gets a sequel and that the box office or critics ruins that chance cause this was a 7.5/8 from me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 22:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just seems like they would rather show what happened to obi wan through their animated series rather than make a full movie/s. Don't really have a good reason for it other than a gut feeling that they won't do a movie at all and choose to do this instead to satisfy the ones that want a movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope I'm not the only one not wanting Obi Wan to appear on rebels, guess it's too late now.. Since he's appearing the chances of an Obi Wan spin off is down to what, zero? thnx disney.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we please get a server stats window in the server browser? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 21:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like in BF3 or 4, every time you chose a server it would show the stats of each team and how far out in the match they are. Would really like to get that feature back 'cause I'm getting tired of joining nearly done matches and matches where my team has barely any progress while the enemy team have almost won...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 22:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think all of you are getting the point, I'm not looking for a solution for barely getting summoned. Rather getting someone to grind for loyce souls with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 17:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spider-man 3 could've been so, so great. I've re-watched all of the movies and my biggest problem with the 3rd is that it feels like 2 movies cramped into one. The scenes between Eddie Brock and Peter should've been drawn out into 2 movies where the 1st would show how peter takes his job and ruins his career and the 2nd would show eddies hatred toward peter and becoming venom. Same with Harry, they would fight and leave Harry scarred, fast forward to the next film with Harry's face being healed and etc..
Feels like Sony loves fucking this franchise up don't they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 15:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really dont wanna use an asthetics, just hoping to co op with someone who hasnt killed the boss yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 15:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on PC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone up for some good old fashion grinding? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 19:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at the last DLC (Ivory King) and I've killed every boss, and I've gotten to the point where the Ivory Knights don't respawn AT ALL in the Old Chaos. Yesterday I tried 20 times to kill the knights but they just didn't spawn. I've also been trying to be summoned but I've had some luck but I'm barely getting summoned. Was hoping anyone would be up for grinding loyce souls during the boss fights since the loyce knights despawn after a while.

My level is 175 and SM is 4.5 million. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 19:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's an update from the developers of clockwork? It's weird because I've only seen it the last couple of months </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 19:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has happened on two servers I've helped out on, both clockwork tho.. Haven't tried singleplayer but it's most likely working there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The playermodel get warped and glitchy each time you launch pac, only way to use it without getting glitched is spawning a camera or go in thirdperson. When you walk in any direction a set of floating t-pose arms follow you around while the playermodel stays still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This happens to the playermodel when you launch pac3 on my friends server, we have no idea why and need help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder how they're going to do that if all the cars costs about half a million each.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to get South Park the stick of truth for ps4 without Fractured but whole? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ps4 launched in 2013 while stick of truth came out in the end of 2014, I havent found anywhere where you can get it for ps4. Anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't add steam overlay to Origin games, only Origin itself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 23:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done everything correct according to all posts and articles I've found about this. You add Origin.exe as a non-steam-game, launch the game, and viola. Except I get the overlay in Origin launcher and none of the games, a friend of mine did the same thing but he gets the overlay in the games so I don't know what else to do. I've even disabled Origin in game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 02:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it ever be possible to stop or slow this process?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:Why do we age? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 01:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Managed to kill them, upgraded the red twin blade to +10 and used that instead of my Zweihander. Now I only need Elana and Sinh... If you want to help with those two (or one) I can add you on steam if you want? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think I'm gonna try kiting them now, not sure how that will go. I'll most likely have to upgrade another sword since I'm using a +10 Zweihander which may be too slow for this fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but I'm gonna continue to try doing it solo, don't have much human effigies left and the others that commented gave some tips :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I noticed that when I first tried with summons.. Figured that the two summons I had would keep two bosses busy while I killed one at at time but that didn't happen... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, I'll try doing solo for now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost 3 million at this point, I've done all the main game bosses except the ones in throne of want. Just started the dlc's :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help with Graverobber, Varg and Cerah :L </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been trying to kill them both with and without summons and each time they manage to pull some bullshit insta-kill on me. Either 2 hit kill with full health or getting a backstab animation from the front. The npc summons are the worst, they only take damage and don't do shit, they don't even hold one of the bosses away from me which makes it impossible for me to kill even one when the two other summons are just getting bashed by Mr.Backstab or Wannabe Havel...
I'm on PC so if anyone can that would be great... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The killing joke has nothing to do with their 'animated universe' that they've made. I just think that the way the characters are portrayed in the animated universe movies are much better than their live action counter part. Sure Batfleck was cool to watch but I think Jason O'Mara's version of batman is the best one yet, and tbh I think the same about the other characters as well. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 12:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the ones im talking about..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warner Bros should hire DC Animation team for their live action movies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 19:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a thought I've had for a while. Their Animated Universe so far has introduced a ton of characters without being too dark or feeling overcrowded. It didn't have the same setup as the MCU and it still worked, the first movie was basically a setup for the other movies and starting the Justice League. Why DC and Warner Brothers doesn't get this is just beyond me. Also this version of batman is definitely the best one in my mind.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 13:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks for the info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 13:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well my plan was to buy a ps4 pro then sell my regular one so I don't lose too much money :p But thank you guys for helping! ^^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wanna get a ps4 pro, can I transfer some or perhaps all of my data from my regular ps4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 03:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you have an online account for ps4 is it possible to transfer some data from one ps4 to another? Since it's all linked up to one account shouldn't it be possible? I've got a couple of destiny characters and some finished singleplayer games that I don't wanna lose progress on so if you can't then I guss there's no Pro for me :L </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 23:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could tolerate the boss more if you could just teleport directly to it after lighting all of the fires and not having to use a human effegie, but since you have to kills npcs and waste the effegie makes me just wanna skip it :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 23:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you add more details? Never done this with a char in fear of loosing all souls and existing specs. Do you respec your char at the beginning with the old ladies and do you get all the souls you've used if you do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tips for meleeing Darklurker? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 22:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried everything... I've upgraded atunements to have more spells, I've takes loads of magic resistant shit, got all kinds of magic, dark and fire resistant rings, got an upgraded rebel greatshield and a +10 Zweihander. I've tried every pyromancy spell I have and gotten the best one you can get (Chaos Storm) and they barely do any damage against it. (Why the fuck did the devs nerf pyromancy for this boss :() Hitting it with my sword goes all well and good until the thing splits in two and makes it impossible to even hit one of them without loosing half my health. Does anyone have any tips or ways I can kill it more effectively?

EDIT: I managed to kill it (Thank god..), I upgraded my Pyromancy to +10 which I had totally forgotten you could do. I had a light armor set so I could gain stamina easily and run around more when I needed to block the attacks. The armor and weapons I used was:


Head: [Dark Mask](http://darksouls.wikia.com/wiki/Dark_Mask_(Dark_Souls_II)

Torso: [Armor of Aurous +4](http://darksouls.wikia.com/wiki/Armor_of_Aurous)

Arms: [Dark Gauntlets](http://darksouls.wikia.com/wiki/Dark_Gauntlets_(Dark_Souls_II)

Legs: [Dark Leggings](http://darksouls.wikia.com/wiki/Dark_Leggings_(Dark_Souls_II)

Right hand: [Pyromancy flame +10](http://darksouls2.wiki.fextralife.com/Pyromancy+Flame)

Left hand: [Transgressor's Leather Shield](http://darksouls2.wiki.fextralife.com/Transgressor's+Leather+Shield) (Which I had imbued with Dark at [Steady Hand McDuff](http://darksouls.wikia.com/wiki/Steady_Hand_McDuff) at [The Lost Bastille](http://darksouls2.wiki.fextralife.com/Lost+Bastille), since Darklurker does almost only dark damage the shield had 100% dark resistance. Bought it for 8000 souls from [Chancellor Wellager](http://darksouls.wikia.com/wiki/Chancellor_Wellager) in [Drangleic Castle](http://darksouls2.wiki.fextralife.com/Drangleic+Castle).)

Ring 1: [Ring of Binding](http://darksouls2.wiki.fextralife.com/Ring+of+Binding) (So my health wasn't 50%)

Ring 2: [Cloranthy Ring +1](http://darksouls2.wiki.fextralife.com/Chloranthy+Ring)

Ring 3: [Dark Quartz Ring +1](http://darksouls2.wiki.fextralife.com/Dark+Quartz+Ring)

Ring 4: [Clear Bluestone Ring +1](http://darksouls2.wiki.fextralife.com/Clear+Bluestone+Ring) (Shortens spell casting time)

The Pyromancy spells I used was: [Great Combustion](http://darksouls2.wiki.fextralife.com/Great+Combustion),[Flame Swathe](http://darksouls2.wiki.fextralife.com/Flame+Swathe), [Firestorm](http://darksouls2.wiki.fextralife.com/Firestorm) and [Chaos Storm](http://darksouls2.wiki.fextralife.com/Chaos+Storm) which I got from the chest on the lava rocks in Iron Keep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
