<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8367</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and providing baselines for power level comparisons

Yeti </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone interested in reading more can find sources [here](https://books.google.de/books?id=0Ez4DAAAQBAJ printsec=frontcover source=gbs_ge_summary_r redir_esc=y#v=onepage q f=false) and [here](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22953323) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the first female doctor in Britain spent 56 years disguised as a man. It wasnt until after her death in 1865, that the doctors secret was finally discovered. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a really interesting line that they have randomly set. They don't nerf a whole bunch of cards and just rotate them out. Yet, they nerf molten giants and a bunch others. The community is definitively gonna be confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you kindly! Great answer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really nice video! Great to actually have someone talk to you standing up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a quote from the lead author:

 RG: Has climate change played a role in this?

 Barnard: Yes, in addition to the record sea surface temperatures which lead to highest number of hurricanes ever recorded, climate change influenced this extreme El Nio event, which are expected to become more frequent due to climate change. 

 This event coincided with a major drought in California, conditions predicted for the 21st century by most climate models. Higher sea levels also accompanied this El Nio event, including a recent acceleration along the US West coast, which exacerbated impacts.

edit: quote format </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You talking about the 1-1 sheep spell or is there another silence option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to the study here: http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms14365 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Latest El Nio caused unprecedented levels of erosion along the west coast of the US, 76% more than the typical winter. Climate change was found to be a factor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can be done (if anything) to prevent the Larsen C ice shelf in Antarctica from cracking and releasing the iceberg? What are the consequences of this being released? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odds are tough at the best of times. I also think you need an amazing amount of knowledge to know which is the better play odds wise. But I completely agree, nonetheless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snap is pricing its IPO at $14 to $16 per share, setting its valuation as high as $22 billion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The name of the spy was John Dee and this is the quote from the [wikipedia article](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Dee#20th_century)  I posted in an earlier comment:

 Ian Fleming took James Bond's code number, 007, from John Dee. Fleming was reading a memoir on the life of Dee at the time he set off to write Casino Royale (1953). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Dee#20th_century </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Queen Elizabeth I had a vast spy network and one of her spies signed his reports with "007." This was later used by Ian Fleming, writer of James Bond. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 11:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree completely. I still play the game and I still get a feeling of joy when I open the game. I do inevitably get disappointed after a few games. I guess that initial joy comes from vanilla + my time with handlock smashing patron.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the AMA. I hope this is within your purview. What is holding back quantum computing? Is there a particular aspect of it that, if overcome, could open up the technology? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Do you know the odds for vaginal intercourse?

Edit: Information as per comment below

1:1250 Risk to a female having sex with an HIV-positive male

1: 2500 Risk to a male having sex with an HIV-positive female </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this AMA! I'm curious as to the chance of HIV infection from sexual relations compared to drug injections? How does this affect your study? I have read that the chance to contract HIV sexually is very very low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study can be found [here](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/cdev.12719/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harsh parenting can lead to poor school outcomes by making teenagers seek immediate rewards and prioritize relationships with their friends over responsibilities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true haha and revenge. I take it back :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter Introduces 'Safe Search' And Other Tools Targeting Abuse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter rolls out new anti-abuse tools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
