<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject670</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize if you feel that was too personal; I assume it was a company policy so I assumed it wasn't. I was just curious to know which healthcare plan tripled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, why not wait until that legislation is drawn up before repealing it? Why not draw up that legislation 6 years ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tripled? What plan are you using?


Edit: I apologize if you feel this was too personal.   I don't need to know your plan, specifically. I was more just asking for which ones--in general--fell into the tripled category. [As far as I know,](http://www.politifact.com/wisconsin/statements/2016/dec/20/ron-johnson/testing-ron-johnson-claim-under-obamacare-premiums/) no plans have "tripled;" I was hoping to become better informed by asking about plans that have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why repeal the Affordable Care Act? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://obamacarefacts.com/benefitsofobamacare/

Why repeal it without a specific better plan to replace it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 07:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I guess I will have to completely redo my skills (and I am out of chromatic orbs). Thank you so much, I was starting to have trouble with tier 7 maps. This bit of information will no doubt help a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 06:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IC thank you. The wiki seemed to hint at something like that, but didn't state it. You would think it would... Maybe I was looking in the wrong place.

Does this work for all of my summons? Can I give my zombie's melee attacks things like Culling Strike Support? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vaal Summon Skeletons: What Gems work with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 04:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading some of the posts here led me to believe that Multistrike Support and Lesser Multiple Projectiles Support would affect the Skeletons if linked to Vaal Summon Skeletons. However, the gems do not highlight each other when linked.  Does anyone know if they work? They seem to. If they do work, how can I tell which gems work with my summons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you are what you eat, killing a mosquito is suicide. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 07:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else find it weird the IP addresses for The_Donald's mods originate in Russia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 23:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else find it weird the IP addresses for The_Donald's mods originate in Russia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 23:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ultimate revenge Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 23:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 05:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I think you've got it backwards.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E8OVmhpjPKI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 00:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Anyone smart enough to see what he's doing is just laughing.

So.... not Trump himself, then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calling racism 'racism' is a product of racism. It should be called "phenotypism." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 14:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the definitions of the terms "[democracy](http://www.dictionary.com/browse/democracy)" and "[republic](http://www.dictionary.com/browse/republic)" we are one and not the other, and the election was one and not the other.  To quote wiki:

*"The United States of America (USA), commonly referred to as the United States (U.S.) or America, is a federal republic"*[[1]](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 19:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright. My point has simply been that (if we are assuming "realism") fighting with a metal staff does not prepare one for fighting with a sword made out of light.

Now, in saying that, I think that the movie directors made it clear that Kylo, while proficient with lightsabers, was near death. Thus, he wasn't in fighting shape. And, while Rey (arguably) wasn't proficient with a lightsaber, she wasn't a combat novice nor was she impaired like Kylo.

Anyway, I agree with your assessment of how it would work in 5th edition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, since there are only the "simple" and "martial" proficiencies in 5th, I would agree with you that a lightsaber would only need special training if your DM was being a dick about it in 5th. However, in 3rd there was the additional "exotic" classification for weapons.

Anyway, I'm not sure what your preference in editions has to do with whether or not Rey's training with the staff is directly applicable to using a lightsaber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 14:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know jaywalking was punishable with violence. Nor did I know that rules were enforced when no one was around to enforce them. But, again, speaking just for myself, I like doing things the right way and don't like doing things the wrong way. No threats needed. Whether or not waiting when there is no need to wait is "the right thing" would depend on circumstance, to be sure.

Anyway, I am guessing from your use of the word "violence" with regard to the state, you are referring to the *[Gewaltmonopol des Staates](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Monopoly_on_violence)* philosophy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 13:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you say it's so for yourself, alright. But, you don't speak for us all. Personally, I've always liked helping others and working together because it made me feel good to be a good person. But, if you say the threat of violence is the only thing keeping you from lashing out, then to each their own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 12:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the threat of bloodshed is meant to make us override our laws and the Constitution, why bother having an election? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 12:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said that's not how it works. The fact we've never lived in a democracy, and have always lived in a republic, was the whole point of my post.

It was not a "democratic election," and was never meant to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 12:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason lightsabers required different training then a sword was explained in the 3e book:

* Because only the handgrip has any weight, unskilled users have difficulty judging the position of the blade. They are as likely to injure themselves as harm their opponents. The lightsabers true potential becomes apparent in the hands of a fully trained Jedi, who can defend and attack with the weapon, deflecting blaster bolts or striking opponents with the glowing blade.

Which always seemed like a good reason to me as to why you needed a different skill set to use a lightsaber then you did a sword. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 12:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was not a "democratic election" because the person with the most votes lost. But, we don't live in a democracy; we live in a republic. And, by the rules of that republic, the electors can vote for who they want to vote for.

Many were thrilled when they heard Trump won the "Electoral College." But, maybe they should have looked more closely as to what that meant. Regardless, if one starts complaining about the same rules they heralded before, then it makes them a hypocrite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 01:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet, my understanding is that the Sun Blade has the same weight as a normal sword. The reason lightsabers required additional training was explained in the 3e book:

* Because only the handgrip has any weight, unskilled users have difficulty judging the position of the blade. They are as likely to injure themselves as harm their opponents. The lightsabers true potential becomes apparent in the hands of a fully trained Jedi, who can defend and attack with the weapon, deflecting blaster bolts or striking opponents with the glowing blade.*

Which always seemed like a good reason to me as to why you needed a different skill set to use a lightsaber then you did a sword. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 01:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, certainly. But the question would still remain if normal sword proficiency would be enough to use one without penalty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 18:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was unaware they had lightsabers in 5e. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 18:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 3e the lightsaber counted as an exotic weapon which required a [class feature or separate feat](http://force.wikidot.com/exotic-weapon-proficiency-feat) for the exact reasons BryceMuldoon mentions. 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Star_Wars_Roleplaying_Game_(Wizards_of_the_Coast)#Saga_Edition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, Time Travel, *amiright?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Be a Sucker - 1947 Antipropaganda Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Don't Be a Sucker" Anti-Demagogue Video from 1947 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/False_equivalence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's one of the more common reasonable answers I've heard. The conservative judges are something he hasn't really waffled on yet.

I find it frustrating when other Trump supports seem to think he is not a typical politician, when making outlandish promises you don't intend to fulfill is the quintessential caricature of a typical politician.

But, yeah, his judge appointments are likely to be more conservative than Hillary's would have been. True. If that's your main issue than I guess you picked the right guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 03:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Charles Darwin was not an Atheist.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Religious_views_of_Charles_Darwin) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why vote for someone if you don't believe anything they say? Or, to put it another way, how do you know the stuff he said you liked was true and the stuff he said you didn't like was false?

Or doesn't it matter which part of what he said was true or false? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just didn't care. I'm not sure to what extent his supporters did either.

"Build a Wall!" sounded good. Most of the Trump supports I talked to see to care more about things sounding good than **being** good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The descriptor "indescribable" is a paradox. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 13:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 12:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you CAN have a long running non-partisan political forum. It might start neutral, but its going to lean more and more in one direction. 

Just like politics in real life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mission Accomplished </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 15:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do teach it as a theory, just like they teach the theory of gravity. No one calls it "the fact of gravity" do they?

Pence just doesn't seem to know what a "scientific theory" means. Maybe he should have payed better attention in school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 02:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yellow_journalism#Spanish.E2.80.93American_War </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook is the Yellow Journalism of this generation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 23:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Faithless_elector </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That sounds like fun.

We are in agreement. I look forward to see who the Republican Electorates, handpicked by the established state republicans, vote for on Dec 19th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops. That's not how elections work.

Right, I am glad you agree with me now

It doesn't work by the popular vote. [It works by having the Electoral College vote on Dec 19th.](https://www.archives.gov/federal-register/electoral-college/key-dates.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they did, Hillary would be our president by the popular vote.

The Electoral College votes on Dec 19th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about the real election on Dec 19th. https://www.archives.gov/federal-register/electoral-college/key-dates.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As do I.

So, we would both condone an uprising sparked by people not wishing to follow the rules of our election on Dec 19th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying we should abolish the electoral college, I am saying we should use it as it was intended to be used.

"It (the Electoral College) creates an important barrier that acts as a safeguard against the peoples own primitive instincts by creating as much distance between the people and the people in power themselves. ." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And exactly 0 instances of the Electoral College voting for the loser of the November election.

That isn't even close to being true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would not be the first time people didn't vote for who they where pledged to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And, how many rules are being changed because of it? So, why should we change the rules if the other supporters threaten the same? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And, how many rules are being changed because of it? So, why should we change the rules if the other supporters threaten the same? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The rules are the Electoral College votes Dec 19th.](https://www.archives.gov/federal-register/electoral-college/key-dates.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In 2000 a member of the United States Electoral College did not vote for the presidential candidate for whom they had pledged to vote. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The laws say no one wins until Dec 19th,](https://www.archives.gov/federal-register/electoral-college/key-dates.html) and [that the Electoral College  can vote for who they want to.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Faithless_elector) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one wins until Dec 19th. That's the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The threat of violence is meant to be an argument against us following the rules of our democracy? Why did we even have an election under that logic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Them protesting does not change the laws, and the laws say the Electoral College votes for who they want on Dec 19th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Read the laws yourself.](https://www.archives.gov/federal-register/electoral-college/key-dates.html)

No one is changing anything. The Electoral College has not voted yet, and them voting for him is the only way he wins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, they should vote for John Kasich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many times has Trump won the election?  Is the argument that just because it never happened it can't happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should vote for John Kasich then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you live in a populated state you're less of an American?

Alright. By that logic we should do what the Electoral College says, and they vote in a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did, and you should read the Constitution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The threat of violence is meant to be an argument against us following the rules of our democracy?  Why did we even have an election under that logic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under what facts does Trump win? Only if we use the Electoral College over the will of the people.

Are you saying the Electoral College shouldn't be the decider or aren't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the threat of a Republican uprising is enough to make us ignore the laws of our country, then we shouldn't have even had an election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, maybe I am wrong about the amount of more votes, but I am not wrong about **who** has more votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the threat of Trump supporters taking to the street is enough to ignore the laws of our country, then we shouldn't have even had an election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then the Electoral College has yet to vote and can vote for whoever they want on Dec 19th.

How many times do you need to be told this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was earlier Nov 12 before all of the votes had been counted (but after Trump won enough states), they're still counting votes in some places.

http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/11/opinion/clintons-substantial-popular-vote-win.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Go back on it?" The vote doesn't happen until Dec 19th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The will of the people is Hillary. 2 million more vote for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The threat of violence is meant to be a reason for us not to follow the laws of our country? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under what logic does Trump win? Only if we use the Electoral College over the will of the people. Are we saying the Electoral College shouldn't be the decider or aren't we? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under what logic does Trump win? Only if we use the Electoral College over the will of the people. Are you saying the Electoral College shouldn't be the decider or aren't you?

By the laws of this country, no one wins until Dec 19th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its what our laws say.

https://www.archives.gov/federal-register/electoral-college/key-dates.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The threat of violence is meant to be an argument against us following the rules of our democracy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't think Republicans are law abiding? You feel they would respond with violence if the outcome doesn't go their way? And that it meant to be a reason not to follow the rules of our democracy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, and our Democracy says the Electoral College can vote for who they want to vote for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuz everyone has been right about the election so far.

Under what logic does Trump win? Only if we use the Electoral College over the will of the people.

Are you saying the Electoral College shouldn't be the decider or aren't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 million more people voted for Clinton than voted for Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under what logic does Trump win? Only if we use the Electoral College over the will of the people.

Are you saying the Electoral College shouldn't be the decider or aren't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She conceded the Nov 11th vote, not the Dec 19th vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one wins "fair and square" until Dec 19th.  If we follow the rules of our election, then they can vote for whoever they want.

Under what logic does Trump win? Only if the Electoral College is the decider.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we follow the rules of our election, the Electoral College does not have to vote for Trump.

If we follow the will of the people, Hillary wins.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Hillary Clinton Still Win The Election? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Electoral College delegates are chosen beforehand by the party and can vote for Jeb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 17:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who will vote from the Electoral College on December 19th, and could they vote for Hillary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 04:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who will vote from the Electoral College on December 19th, and could they vote for Hillary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 04:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Who will vote from the Electoral College on December 19th, and could they vote for Hillary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 04:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This election proved to our generation the importance of voting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 23:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://fivethirtyeight.com/live-blog/2016-election-results-coverage/?ex_cid=extra_banner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I voted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 18:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non-hypocritical anti-immigration republicans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 02:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the guy. You said:

 He dropped them because there was nothing there.

In reference to "the charges" I was asking about, and than went on to say in the same post:

The FBI does not press charges anyhow.

I was confused before, but I became downright befuddled. What was the "them" you were talking about being dropped? I guess it was the "recommendation to press charges?"

Look, I already early voted for Clinton yesterday, so I understand you might be wasting your time talking to me. But, I think the distinction between "recommended charges" and "charges" is kinda a thin hair to slice with a guy asking a question about the whole thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 02:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was quoting the comment I was responding to.

Then you know "them" the part of the comment was "charges" and that it was a question, not a statement. I can't claim to understand the nuance of this, which is why I'm asking about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 02:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He dropped the charges he couldn't press? 0.o This is more confusing than I thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 02:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [What are you asking me for? I'm asking you.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sShMA85pv8M t=1m36s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 00:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comey was the guy that first dropped the email charges against Clinton, right? I'm just checking because people seem to be throwing him under the bus awfully fast.

**Edit:** I'm being told I should have said "recommend charges" when I asked my question for clarification on this issue. I am sorry, I didn't realize this was such a touchy issue.  I mean, I already early voted for Clinton yesterday. So, it's not like I even *CAN* have my mind changed (not that this would do it anyway); I just genuinely wanted to know what was going on with this Comey guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 02:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, I like seeing things from the other side. So, I would go to the Donald on occasion. But, (and maybe this is just me) there never seemed to be any good, well thought out, discussion going on. It just seemed to be a bunch of people enthusiastically shouting. Nothing wrong with that, but not something (I felt) would change minds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is on your search history you'd never want your loved ones seeing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 16:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 16:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The OP probably should have made this post as the last post on the old account THEN changed it.

Or just use this as a throwaway and make another one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 13:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 21:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, there is "satire against bigotry" here and there is "comedy against bigotry." But, there is no "violence against bigotry" here, because there is no "violence" here. Obviously... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 17:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except Terry didn't actually hurt anyone. This was staged.

So, there is no "violence against bigotry," there is "satire against bigotry." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 13:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 21:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've not given out gold in less increments than... what... 10? 50?  And, nothing in the game costs less than... what... 1,000?

Why do you want to introduce **pennies** into this economy? When was the last time you went out of your way to pick up a penny IRL?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 13:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 00:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already told you my mom is too old. But, if you think we have a chance you [should volunteer at PA too.](http://www.dos.pa.gov/VotingElections/OtherServicesEvents/PollWorkerTraining/Pages/default.aspx) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 00:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Miss USA didn't directly accuse Trump either.

But, Trump is saying volunteers like my mother don't have ethics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 00:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you are saying he is claiming my mother is "just following orders?" That sounds even worse.

My mother isn't a government stooge. She'd never listen to someone telling her to destroy democracy; that goes against everything she believes in. If she was younger I would urging her to sue Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say 'the government,' I said 'election officials.' And, he is most certainly hurting their reputation. 

My mother, for example, volunteered in PA. He is saying my mother is guilty of misconduct *before she even started.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't think it would matter if enough people did it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could individual citizens sue her for misconduct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: If You think hillary should go to jail, why aren't you suing her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 22:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 22:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In either case, it should be taken to court. If Trump feels strongly, then he should be able to back up the claim in a court of law. Otherwise, he should shut up and stop slandering people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The election officials should sue Trump for defamation, unless he can substantiate his accusation of a rigged election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The election officials should sue Trump for defamation, unless he can substantiate his accusation of a rigged election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> '2016' will become synonymous with 'batshit crazy.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SNL should sue Trump for defamation, unless he can substantiate his accusation of a rigged election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The election officials should sue Trump for defamation, unless he can substantiate his accusation of a rigged election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
