<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2574</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 19:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think Neverwhere is my personal favorite, followed up by some of his story arcs in Sandman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 19:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved it as well!  The book hit home on multiple fronts for me:

- the writing was wonderful. so many incredible turns of phrases, metaphors, the intelligence of the characters really shown through

- the machinations of accounting, empire running, and espionage was a surprisingly addicting and heady mix

- it's not a genre, but Heroic Accounting should be

- the overall narrative arc honestly had be guessing at every turn

[SPOILERS](#s "the ending honestly shocked me, but not in a bad way: it was internally consistent, and now I can't wait for the next") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 19:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To clarify a bit, I think this Tumblr is the home of the _tabletop_ version of Shadowrun, no? So not so much the devs of the recent Shadowrun CRPGs.  

Either way, that is super encouraging to read.  

It's always struck me as interesting that some of the original "neckbeards" (Greenwood, et al) were also some of the more socially progressive people of their time.  

In a way, the history of science-fiction and fantasy has been about pushing social/technogical norms and boundaries, so it's always super strange to me whenever GG folks or whoever else complain about "politics" in their books/games/movies.  

I mean, do you understand the genre you are participating in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 23:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a little late, but there is! It's not TKL tho:

http://www.amazon.com/Topre-Type-Heaven-104-key-Keyboard/dp/B00DGJALYW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 08:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't have it both ways.  Players have been demanding more transparency from game developers, wanting to see how games are made in greater detail, wanting to be part of the beta process, wanting to see the naturally iterative process of creation.

But that also means watching parts of the game change, sometimes for reasons you agree with, sometimes for reasons you don't.

Raking Blizzard over the coals because they attempted to communicate a change out seems, well, counter productive.  Sure, they might have avoided a lot of drama.  

But do we really want to go back to the old days of stonewall Blizzard who will only give "when it's done" responses? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 08:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean yes, he probably was trying to score free points.  I don't see anything wrong with that, tho that does bring up an interesting question:

Would the internet have gone batshit insane if he had prefaced his intitial response with "We were already planning to replace the pose, so this is good timing"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 08:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely less sharp than the retina, but only if I look closely.  My face is generally farther away from the monitor than from the laptop.

(And even on my MBP 15", I run at 1920x1200 instead of the default retina) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 17:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I copy emacs and have it bound to (re)indent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 17:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm lucky in that because I use emacs, it's also my window manager most of the time :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 16:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  An internal Sony poll concluded PS+ satisfaction was over 95% in 2012. Using that poll and this one as guidelines, consumer satisfaction in PlayStation Plus has fallen more than 70% in three and a half years.

This is not how polling works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 18:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is good for GamerGate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 18:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is good for GamerGate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have caps lock set to control, and command set to meta.

Also, because command is in the space right near my thumb, I've rebound some of my most used things to it.  For example:

```
Cmd-b: switch buffers with helm
```

```
Cmd-o: find-files with helm
```

```
Cmd-F: find files in project
```

```
Cmd-f: helm-occur in file
```

```
Cmd-e: git ls-files with helm
```

```
Cmd-s : save file
``` </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 16:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a CV1, and I don't really notice the screen door effect.  If you look closely, you can see some pixellation, but at least for me, no where close to any sort of actual screen door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 05:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that was me! fear makes all things possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few reaction videos of coworkers trying out the CV1 for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 04:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prior VR experience here is a mix: most have tried the original Kickstarter Rift (which I have), and a few have tried Gear VR and DK2.  

100% of them said that the CV1 experience was a whole other level, however.  The realism of the better visuals shouldn't be underestimated.  Comfort, also, was much improved. But it should be noted that none of the ones in the videos wear glasses.  The coworkers who do wear glasses found it quite the ordeal to get the glass frames behind the Rift -- both when putting it on, and when taking it off.

Highlights so far have been the dinosaur dreamdeck demo, Windlands, and Eve Valkyrie.  

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZyW8xpnhju8

EDIT: Figured out to use iMovie on the phone! Here's a Youtube version of the prior individual Twitter vids.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 04:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually quite enjoying Farlands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 04:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a CV1.  In temrs of headphones, I currently own a pair of ATH-M50s, a AKG 7xx, B O H6s, and a few IEMs (IE80, JVC FX850).

I'd rate the CV1's built-ins at a notch or so below the M50.  It's quite good considering it's packaged with the unit, and probably a smart thing to have.  I find it super convenient when showing people that I can just ask them to position the built in headphones correctly.  

The bass is definitely lacking, tho that's more due to the design of the headphones (foam on ears) than the quality of the parts.  It's present, and decent, but I wouldn't call it good.

But if you have a good pair of headphones (say, roughly, above $100-150), and you're not constantly showing others or moving the unit, I'd use those.  Especially if you have a separate amp, etc.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 04:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the CV1 from Kickstarter.  Can confirm iFixit was confused.  Moving the headest up and down just moves the sweet spot of the lens around -- Oculus' instructions are purely to make sure people are viewing the lens through the sweet spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 23:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, WTF Nintendo. WTF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 16:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but I don't expect Tracer to be overtly sexual in the same way that I don't expect Batman to suddenly slap his own ass, wink, and say "the night is young" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 04:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine if you have more than 200 results, you likely want to narrow it some more -- or at least, that's what I usually do when I get a huge number of results from incremental searches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 17:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   He sees the same amount of feedback from players as you do.

He sees at least as much feedback as players do, but I think it's silly to assume he doesn't have access to internal testing, reports from other channels, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 07:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Yeah, sure, convenient timing. It gets removed and then you just happen to have a replacement on hand.

Do you think Blizzard's artists and developers are just sitting around twiddling their thumbs just waiting for juicy forum posts to jump on in order to do some work?

They probably have potential poses or discarded poses or even just poses to be released in the future for all their characters.  I see no reason to doubt Jeff when he says that they already have a pose they love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 07:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, I think if you read the first comment through the lens of the 2nd, it makes much more sense.  It's just that Jeff had a specific context in his head that readers didn't have (that changing the post was something they were already considering)

I think in that light, the first comment is just Jeff trying to be nice and acknowledging the OP, especially if they've were thinking about changing it for some of the same reasons the OP gave (eg, creative issues with the character) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 07:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think what happened was that the OP's forum post was just an opportune time for Blizzard to make that pose change, and Jeff happened to see the thread, and decided "why not, we've had some of the same concerns, let's make it official, we've been thinking about this for a while now"

But the context wasn't there for people who wasn't Jeff, and so, well, the internet exploded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 19:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry about your wife, but great progress! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 17:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grace of Kings  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 02:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry, shoulda been more clear.  i've only introduced lifting to my routine since the start of 2016.  I've been trying to eat better for around a year now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm finally starting to wear Medium! 33M 6'0 SW: 225, CW: 184, GW: 165 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 20:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/ePV4ehr

On the left, I'm ~225.  On the right, ~184.  

At my highest a few years back (in 2012), I was ~240.  I gained most of my weight in college.  Freshmen year, I was 165.  By the junior year and through the rest of college, I was averaging around 200-215 depending on the year.  But after school, my weight ballooned to 240.

My driver's license is real old and actually still has my weight listed at 165 from when I was in college, haha.  So that's my goal: to get it so I match my license stats again.

I've mostly been eating at a deficit (no specific diet, smaller portions of chicken, veggies, whole grains).  Recently, starting in January, I started doing basic lifts, and I think that's really helped me get additional definition around my shoulders.

I haven't really set aside for cardio, but as the weather gets nicer, I've thought about running in the morning.

I've mostly been self directed so far, but am considering joining up with a gym for more directed training.  

I've been stuck in the 180-185 range for about a month now, and not entirely sure what I need to do to get past it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 19:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ehh, I think this article has good intentions, but is showing a startling lack of empathy:

1. An overblown sense of invincibility is a symptom, I think, of being in your early 20s in general, and not one specific to white college kids.

2. This is taking everything that the North Korean gov is saying what he did as face value, which does not seem very prudent

3. Regardless of why he did something, the punishment far far outweighs the crime, and we shouldn't let white privilege schadenfreude undermine the very real humanitarian considerations here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 07:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DADDIES

(Now how do I scrub my brain of that tweet, oh god) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 05:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's kind of a narrow view of the precedent and ramifications this ruling, if actually upheld in appeals (I don't thin it will) could have on media.

This link probably explains it a bit more eloquently than I could: http://www.capitalnewyork.com/article/media/2016/03/8594339/jury-awards-hulk-hogan-115-million-gawker-looks-appeal

(Seperately, I don't know if it's KiA brigades or what, but it's a little disheartening to see the understandable hatred of Gawker cause any divergence from unadulterated glee to be downvoted) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 01:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW I upvoted 

There's a very good chance Gawker gets this turned in appeals.  And it might even be for the best: the precedent this sets is not entirely comforting.

(Not because what Gawker did was right, but because of what it means for other stories that are published at other outlets) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 01:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one likes Gawker, but it's also important to consider the effect it may have on other companies, and that it will encourage other folks with weaker suits to potentially make cases. 

anyway, here's a good summary: 

http://www.capitalnewyork.com/article/media/2016/03/8594339/jury-awards-hulk-hogan-115-million-gawker-looks-appeal

About why it'll likely be overturned in appeals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 20:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still good for GamerGate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 19:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is good for GamerGate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Actual ethics? " Forbes investigates after 'contributor' asks PR for 300 to write online profile" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 19:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars Battlefront VR version exclusive to PlayStation VR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 22:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using a Filco Majestouch.  It's working great! I have the alt key configured as command, and the windows key configured as option.

(In emacs, i also have command as meta) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 00:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used https://github.com/antonj/Highlight-Indentation-for-Emacs !

From what I recall, it works well enough with Python  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 10:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's mine!

http://i.imgur.com/tvkC6RT.png

And here's the physical environment emacs is usually running in!

http://i.imgur.com/bNddJB7.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 22:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do the shift keys on these use costar style stabilizers, or cherry?

(I love the feel of costars much more than cherry, but it's getting harder to find these days) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 05:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nosek, who took part in the new investigation, said Thursday night that the bottom-line message of the original undertaking was not that 60 percent of studies were wrong "but that 40 percent were reproduced, and that's the starting point."

major lol

that's some serious spin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 14:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes plz! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 18:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I took breaks on weekends.  It was normally 30-45 minutes on the treadmill or elliptical on days I did cardio </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 17:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nation building isn't the primary focus, but The Traitor Baru Cormorant has elements of nation *running* and the more mundane aspects of administration, warfare, and civic works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 03:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks!

I stopped doing cardio, but i might start doing it again.  maybe move one day cardio one day lifting routine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 07:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Following up from a face progress post a made a few weeks, ago, I've been taking regular shots on my phone to keep a record of progress.  I hadn't really looked until today at the very first shot I took when I was ~230 and the shot I took just most recently ~187. 

I'm still not there muscle and tone wise, but things are starting to firm up! 

I originally focused on a pure cardio routine every day to try and lose weight, but have recently (for the past 4 weeks) been doing a dumbbell lifting regimen I found on Reddit.  And already, I feel like I'm beginning to see some additional definition.

My arms still feel pretty weak and flabby tho, it feels like most of the additional definition has gone to my chest, shoulders, and waist/stomach area </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M/33/6'0 [230  187, GW: 165] Body progress, didn't realize the difference until I compared directly. NSFW, shirtless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 07:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Struggles and Victories of the First Transgender Fighting Game Champion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 06:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 02:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this article is 1.5 years old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 04:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, unfortunately, I've been trying to get a black one and the Mystery Ranch shop has been sold out for a bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 06:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been hard to find good info on it, but this page has a nice video towards the bottom going over the pack's pockets and zippers:

http://item.rakuten.co.jp/moonloid/19760128/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 00:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SJWs, obv. They drove everyone away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Actual ethics, maybe? "The Intercept recently discovered a pattern of deception in the actions of a staff member." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 20:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 18:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh good point, i'd forgotten they came out with a wireless version </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 17:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking for a phone that I can use while commuting via Bluetooth, and one that I can plugin to an amp after I get to the office and am at a desk.

I've tried the Momentum 2 wireless, the PSB wireless, and the Sony MDR1R wireless.  If these don't work out, my next attempt may be the B O Beoplay H7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maybe finally a bluetooth headphone I'll keep -- Master   Dynamic MW60 [OC] [1581x1184] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 19:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 20:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa! Didn't realize Staked was out already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 16:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One delay is reasonable. It's a new team, new funding model, maybe new tech for some of them.  But __three__ delays? I can't reasonably use "programming is hard" as an excuse anymore.  That's just dysfunction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 16:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every programmer on the planet can give you a time frame if you force the issue.  Every programmer on the planet will be wrong the vast majority of the time.

(That said 1 delay is reasonable given the complexity of game dev. 3 delays? That sounds like dysfunction.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 21:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 21:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only really listened to the admittedly limited selection on Spotify (I'm much more familiar with cpop and jpop).  Do you have any faves or suggestions on albums I should seek out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 19:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW i've found my IEMs to be remarkably resilient.  i dropped my pair in ocean before at the beach and after a day of drying, they worked flawlessly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 18:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa, that's awesome!

Also whoa, 20 years ago is the 90s ;___;  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 05:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **David Eddings**' books all feature powerful wizards.  To start, try **The Belgariad**, **The Mallorean**, and then **Belgarath the Sorcerer**.

The **Alex Verus** novels by **Benedict Jacka** is one that was super interesting and fun for me.  It features a ton of powerful wizards, but the main character is a diviner.  Yes, that school of magic every laughs at and never picks in D D.  It's one of the few books that takes seriously the idea of practical divination, and it's pretty fascinating.

**Patrick Rothfuss**'s **Kingkiller Chronicles**

**Ursula Le Guin**'s **Earthsea** books.

**Vlad Taltos** books by **Steven Brust**

The **Iron Druid** series by **Kevin Hearne** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 05:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just read a synopsis online, sounds pretty derivative imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 05:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's mine!

https://www.goodreads.com/user/show/761189-david-zhou </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 19:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep, tho i guess some people may not call that suicide, so ymmv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 01:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said this before in some other threads, but suicide is almost always unfortunate, and people considering it deserve help, no matter who they are.

Good vibes to her family and friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 01:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's censorship, technically, but let's be real: this is a company moderating their comments and forums.  The actual ideas being expressed are not being censored from being publicly discussed in any meaningful way.  Users can very easily (and have) just comment on the respective KiA thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 19:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  he is not forcing them to not hire someone else and do what they want. Why is this a thread at all?

That's the joke.

GG supporters often say that Polygon/Kotaku/______ is trying to "censor" them when no one is stopping people from posting their own thoughts elsewhere, or when its only criticism of something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 21:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  largest profit makers for Roosh, estimated sales bringing him more than 45,000 dollars profit each month

Is there a source for this? 

(Out of curiousity, mostly, for how accurate that number is) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 05:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confirm that Day9 in person is as nice as he appears online.

Aside from trying to keep to a calorie deficit, I went to the gym three times a week for mostly cardio.  45min-1hr on the treadmill or elliptical.

This year, for 2016, I'm trying to go the rest of the way with more regular exercise plus some light strength training, and actual running. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 05:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My drivers license that I got in college still says 165lbs (lol), so my goal weight is to once again match my college weight!

Anyway, I say 3 years up there because that's about how old some of the photos are, but most of my weight loss has been in the last year.  I was ~230 at the beginning of 2015. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M/32/6'0" 240  192 (GW: 165) Face Progress. It's been ~3 years, so I didn't even notice until I put them side by side </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 05:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 05:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out Max Gladstone and his Craft Sequence. 

http://www.amazon.com/Three-Parts-Dead-Max-Gladstone/dp/B00D00VKYW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 16:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Whenever there is a moment in the film Rey is going to be in danger, all suspense is extinguished when she effortlessly navigates through any challenge or trial put in front of her.

I don't think you understand what "effortlessly" means.  Remember how she effortlessly triggered the fuses on Han's freighter and in turn effortlessly releases his rampaging cargo?

 she can use a lightsaber (extremely well)

In the first movie, in his first training session, Luke was able to _reflect blaster bolts_.  Also, her lightsaber usage and style was also very precisely designed to look like she was chopping -- very different than the swooping arcs that others use.  This was deliberately designed.

  has shown to have an incredible ability where she can overpower an established force user (Kylo Ren)

A force user that was shot with a bowcaster that was hyped the whole movie as very deadly and powerful, that had already been slashed by a lightsaber, and she _still_ initially got slammed into a tree and would have likely been killed or captured if not for Finn intervening.  Plus, Kylo Ren was held off by _Finn_, a force insensitive who had never used a Lightsaber in his life.  So obviously the movie is taking some liberties, or maybe Kylo Ren just isn't that strong.

Anyway, you think she's too perfect and powerful. I don't.  But more to the point, we've been shown time and time again through successful movies (like the original Star Wars or hell nearly every modern action movie), that you know what? People tend to like powerful main characters who might be "too competent".  There's nothing wrong with that, and its a curious coincidence that the particular complaint about "Mary Sues" only flares up now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intel, Vox Media, Re/code and Lady Gaga's Born This Way Foundation to Hack Online Harassment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 01:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 05:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "We love your passion for Rey"

I love that they act surprised that fans loved one of two main characters of a major Star Wars motion picture.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 17:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're only giving away a little under 7000 units.  If that amount of free units is enough to require subsidizing off the retail price, the Rift is in trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 16:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also just got the survey asking for shipping address they mentioned to fill out "before Feb 1", so looks like they're really on the ball so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "All Kickstarter backers who pledged for a Rift development kit will get a free Kickstarter Edition Oculus Rift" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 16:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 23:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Discworld** provides some good ones:

- The Color of Kitties
- Kitties! Kitties!
- Small Kitties
- Kitties at Arms
- The Last Kitty
- The Wee Free Kitties
- Night Kitties
- Interesting Kitties
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 02:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably -- and that idea is also explored in wuxia.  But I'm mainly saying that a lot of the elements of what we think of as a "superhero" is not at all unique to American comics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 20:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My suggestion for anything: read them in publication/release order.  

Many times I find that the author grows and matures just as much as the story does, and it's great to follow along.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 20:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not going to lie -- I like reading Mary Sues.  Sometimes after grimdark after grimdark, I just want to read some books where the protagonist kicks ass with no troubles.  

(Tho I should note that I'm using Mary Sue with the definition given in the OP: that of a maybe overpowered character.  The traditional Mary Sue of author insertion as invincible character is a separate matter and usually not all that pleasant to read)

(Also I realize defining Mary Sue as poorly done overpowered characters is a self-fulfilling proof) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 20:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chinese wuxia as a genre has incredible similarities with American superheroes: independent, strong willed, fantastic powers, a desire to act in a vigilante fashion when the normal balances aren't up to snuff, and above all, the sort of family and inter-group/clan/league drama that heroes are so famous for. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 23:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suicide is sad, and people considering it deserve help, no matter what kind person they are.  From his tweets, he sounded very troubled.  I'm sad that he apparently ended up going through with it.

I don't know much about Ian Murdock, but he sounds more troubled and in need of help than some kind of coherent racist in the linked tweets.

Anyway, this post's title is not only in utter bad taste, it also spells his name wrong.  A mod should hide and request a repost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 03:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rocket League: I've never had so much fun being so bad at a game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The big primary UGH that I have with the op-ed is the sentiment that "whiteness" as vehicle for universal appeal is a status quo that's worth being maintained.

The author attempted to clarify on Twitter:

"So in my piece, I define the "superhero" as being an American construct and one steeped in secular American values"

"And we all have our heroes. But the concept of a "superhero" seems uniquely American."

But that doesn't make it better. The very thing that the on-going diversification efforts in comics are trying to address is the idea that being "American" or possessing "American" values also means being white. That the author seems unable to acknowledge other racial and ethnic groups as being just as American as anything else speaks the ill-effects of "whiteness" as universal appeal.

America is incredibly diverse, and the on-going effort to make American comics reflect that diversity should only make comics feel more American, not less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 06:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Pace them out. Gemmell, for all that his books are fun, was a limited author in terms of characterisation/prose/narrative. You'll see a lot of the type of characters in Legend repeat, a lot of the events and morals come up in the same way again and again, and while there will be a few differences here and there, if you smash them together, they'll blur, for sure.

This is actually exactly the way I also think about David Eddings, but like Gemmell, I recommend both without reservation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 06:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the Paksenarrion books in a macro sense, in that I remember the overall arc of its narrative and characters fondly.

But I also remember really struggling to plod through some of the, ah, more mundane I-will-spend-five-chapters-talking-about-marching stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 04:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain to me why Keanu Reeves is shouldering a portion of the blame? I'm unclear on the timelines -- did they sell Lionsgate a "Keanu Reeves thriller" to secure funding, or did Lionsgate change the movie's script and focus after the fact, and Downie is blaming Reeves for not standing up to it?

(Personally I think Downie is overestimating the effect that Reeves could have had on the movie/studio. Maybe in the 90s when Reeves was at his height.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 11:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't even mind that much except that Lin and Elma are required for a bunch of missions, so I can't even use other party members regularly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 19:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game looks suuuper fun but ugh I just cannot stand giant bugs x_x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 18:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> London is actually incredibly cosmopolitan in terms of its racial make up.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 18:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that she probably isn't black, I think it's that her being black doesn't go against anything explicitly written, and it's a stage play so in the next few years you'll probably have blonds, redheads, asians, hell, even maybe males playing this character, so who cares? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 17:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> practical empire running is a pretty great description of what I really meant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 06:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha, i'll admit that it's not for everyone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 06:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently reading baru cormorant and I would love to see more novels tackling the finance/trade side of things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 06:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malazan. I've stopped and started Gardens of the Moon maybe 5 times now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 06:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The anger at this is so silly. It's a stage play.  In the next few years, you'll have people of all types playing the character.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 02:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not exactly rare in literature -- or within SF/Fantasy -- to create intentional social commentary.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 08:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are actually (at least) two confirmed witnesses, both working for DreamHack, both with no real incentive to lie about (1) a player attending their event (2) a person employed by the event as a host.  If anything, they should be incentivized to *downplay* the actions of their host.

Both of their statements reflect that not only did Richard Lewis initiate physical contact, "strangle" is also the  appropriate verb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 06:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of buy singular vs plural clarification, and kinda buy the desire to explicitly call out women ("she" vs "they') to help combat the idea that only men play MtG.

The style argument tho?  Yeah, the singular "they" has been accepted usage for decades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 06:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it did. the cops came. but i assume neither pressed charges, the injuries weren't severe, and so the cops left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 08:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jlaw okay.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 07:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arena (http://www.amazon.com/Arena-Magic-The-Gathering-No/dp/0061054240) was one of my early faves.  It really felt it captured the feeling of Magic.

I remember appreciating the Brother's War novels, and especially the characterizations of Urza, Mishra, and Tocasia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 21:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really great breakdown of "censorship" the word, and how its been used/applied by various groups.

Also, I laughed because _of course_ the words "elitism" and "ideologies" were used. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 22:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never understood the "unrealistic men" defense.  I mean, yes, sure, that may also true, but what is it supposed to prove? The point about sexualized women still stands.

"This coffee is brewed kinda shitty." "But the coffee place across the street also makes bad coffee." "Yeah, but this coffee is still shitty." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 22:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh.  When you intentionally tweet something out that's meant to provoke, it's pretty natural for the target of your provocation to act aggressive towards you.

What's not natural is for an industry person to escalate aggressive behavior into an actual physical altercation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 06:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read Uprooted last week on the kindle and loved it. Enough so that I actually ordered a physical copy with the Amazon black friday discount to have on my shelves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 16:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the big ironies about Youtubers is that they are often held up as being  more "authentic", or "real", but actually have less oversight than most other forms of reporting. There can are all sorts of deals flying around that aren't being disclosed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 16:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL WAT

I mean you might as well just add this to the petition

 But if we fail, then the whole world, our lives, our hobbies, including all that we have known and cared for, will sink into the abyss of a new dark age made more sinister, and more puritanical, by the lights of perverted social justice. Let us therefore brace ourselves to our duties, and so bear ourselves, that if gaming lasts for a thousand years, men will still say, this was their finest hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 09:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dresden as open world rpg

Power Mage as over the shoulder 3rd person shooter

Traveler's Gate as Guilty Gear-esque fighting game

China Mieville's New Crobuzon as setting for a Myst-like game, or a Dark Souls/Bloodborne like game..




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 13:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use emacs to write code daily, but I use other apps for other things -- I've never liked using emacs for other tasks, tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 18:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it -- makes it clear that reviews are really what the person who played it thinks, and not the site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finding Fuboy: one man spent four years and $35,000 to unmask his internet troll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 17:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we're on the anime train, also check out: GATE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 07:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That mushroom technique is super neat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 16:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Richard Lewis is precisely the same sort of trollish shock-baiting writer that Milo represents. He's been through a number of outlets in recent years, and each time his articles have courted controversy at the expense of accuracy, and notoriety at the expense of respect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 16:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The biggest current flag about Richard Lewis should be that Richard Lewis agreed to write for Breitbart.  Pickings might be slim in the esports journalism market, but if you're agreeing to write for that publication, any respect I have for you immediately drop to 0.  Breitbart stands for a lot of things, and from the two linked articles that Richard Lewis wrote above, it sadly seems like he fit right in to Breitbart's brand of sham journalism.

This is a "journalist" who, when approached on Twitter about using an uncredited photo, explodes over what he terms "faggot melodrama".  I made a tweet a bout it a few years back that gained some traction, and he acted like a man-child the entire way through. http://i.imgur.com/pdA30ty.jpg

Yeah, fuck that guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 16:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the 40 hours/week limit is much harder to pull off when you're self-employed.  In my experience from being a freelancer for a year and change, it becomes difficult to separate "work hours" and "not work hours". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 01:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Powder Mage trilogy by Brian McClellan.  

All the books written by David Eddings.  They feature gods, incredibly powerful magic, more gods, and incredibly powerful... stones

Iron Druid chronicles.  The main character has regular dealings with gods of various pantheons.  They also feature heavily in the narrative.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 22:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's an important distinction between censorship, the act you and the ACLU describe, and _censorship_ the abhorrent crime against freedom that many others label the decision to not use a bust of Lovecraft.

Technically it's censorship, but IMO it's not really _censorship_, no in the alarmist sense that so many promote as leading to some kind of 1984/Fahrenheit 451 society downfall scenario.  No one is removing Lovecraft from the shelves, no one is even calling for anything that impacts Lovecraft as an author.  This is purely about the symbol that the _World_ Fantasy Aware chooses to use to represent the honors it bestows on someone.

IMO, this is censorship at its most benign and helpful: a decision to remove and select a different thing that harms no one and helps foster inclusiveness.  

(There's plenty of other examples of benign censorship: a TV station deciding to delay or cancel episodes in the wake of a disaster, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 07:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said it before during the Hugo fiasco, but I'm immensely happy that many of the top fantasy/sf writers in the industry (including, thankfully, most of my favorites) have been vocal about their opinions on this, "social justice", and other related matters.  It's in stark contrast to the relative silence that pervaded the games industry during the height of gamergate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 06:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the middle of reading the third of the Power Mage novels and wow! What a ride it's been.  McClellan's world and narrative is one of the better executed I've read this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 06:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a great distillation of the confusion i've been feeling about people who oppose the move because of some perceived slight against the World Fantasy Awards,  or against the freedom to read Lovecraft.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Awards or Bust' by Steven Erikson, on the World Fantasy Awards replacing the bust of Lovecraft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 06:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 20:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't understand the apparently stubborn determination to hold the GamerGate panel, when there's ample evidence that it was born out of a direct reaction from the exact abusive parts of the internet that the harassment panel is trying to deal with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 20:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually precisely what downvoting is technically not supposed to be used for -- it's supposedly to be an indication of the quality of the post, not an indication of how much you agree with the post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 23:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if you're going to place priority on gaming performance, you're going to be happier with one with G-sync.

The one I have on work is primarily for non-gaming use, so I don't really need it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 06:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level of surprise that _of course_ Richard Lewis now writes for Breitbart: 0

The guy is an ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 22:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW Vox Media uses that term too.  It usually means that rather than a general purpose site, its a site targeted to a specific "vertical", eg a tech site or a gaming site </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 20:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And of course, Breitbart needs to say something: http://www.breitbart.com/tech/2015/11/11/vox-media-bans-staff-from-mansplaining/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
