<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the truck only needed a little pull, then yes, it's entirely feasible that even a small front wheel drive car could have helped him out. They just about managed it with two, which implies that the other car probably wouldn't have been able to on his own either. Ok so he didn't single-handedly pull out the truck, but he was the first guy in line to help, for which he deserves credit.  
Source: someone who has pulled, and been pulled, out the sand countless times. I'm grateful to everyone who's ever helped me out, which is why I help others out too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed Rodney, [san tropay, san tropay! It's very mal da mar!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jet29TQv2uA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it that Odd? There's a Tripoli street, and may other names of other places.  
This happens all around the world too. There are numerous "London Roads" in the UK. Scotland Yard isn't in Scotland, Oxford Street isn't in Oxford and China Town... well there's a butt load of those around the world.  
However, I do concede that I too thought it was odd, until I thought more about it.  
EDIT: Jumeirah Hills, Jumeirah Village Circle, Jumerira Village Triangle, Jumeirah Lakes Towers, Palm Jumeirah, Jumeirah Hills. None of these are in Jumeirah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I haven't even used my car today!  
  
Where did you leave it... On a pedestrian crossing by any chance ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had so many fines which were incorrect, but it's easier just to pay them. The process is too painful and was informed by the police traffic dept that you cannot leave the country whilst there is an open case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was told otherwise by the police. Hmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  macabre

Even native speakers are unlikely to use this word; you're very modest in your estimation of your English vocabulary. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Poignant](https://en.oxforddictionaries.com/definition/poignant) would be better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really... it's clearly a frame, he was joking about a big bezel, I continued the joke implying it was an old CRT (which it clearly isn't). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if you don't pay for your internet, you'll start seeing adverts appear on websites </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the joke...  
did you not notice him offering the guy even more, he actually haggled UPWARDS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's CRTs for ya. I miss [my old Iilama](http://media.bestofmicro.com/LCD-TFT-flatpanel-display,9-2-254342-13.jpg)...  
Actually... no, no I don't, just the degaussing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence why Richard wasn't entirely happy with his energy levels. This guy is both eloquent and brilliant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rotated on what axis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  veggie bake and lucozade

Oh what gastronomical delights have we left behind on our homeland...  
Though I'm more inclined to think we're looking nostalgically through rose tinted glasses.  
I'm sure if you went into Greggs now, you'd very quickly remember why it was under a quid!  
EDIT: Maybe we should bring some horse meat burgers to the party? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is haggling in Dubai, [British style](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fd7UlC1cf_Y) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely that can't beat a cheese sarnie from Greggs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Googled...  
I'm coming! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah man, that'd make an awesome headboard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no good intentions, nor bad. Was merely a review of the current situation coupled with my opinion.  
You seem to agree with my sentiment, but take issue with my targeting a specific whilst ignoring the broader scope of the problem. My post was directed at one part of the issue (as was the context), correct, but do not assume I had not considered any other part.  
P.S. what a load of bollocks :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incorrect (albeit reasonable) assumption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's interesting. I don't understand why people would simply stop walking, just because the stairs are moving. It's still a walkway, and actually a bottleneck, so one of the worst places to stop, and I get frustrated when people do.  
P.S. South of where? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You go home, learn how to use an escalator, then come back and try again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An interrobang is a legitimate character, unlike a bloody goat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? This is a thing? What has happened to the world  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because in my part of town, you can't get one for any less than 80. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what others have said. On a British passport you can enter and exit as you please. Just don't stay more than 40 days without leaving (you can even do a border run every 40 days to Oman and effectively stay indefinitely) so if anything, your trip out will actually help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wear whatever you want. Just don't go topless anywhere other than a beach or pool.
If you really wanted to respect local customs, then ensure knee to navel covered at all times in public. But most people wouldn't bat an eyelid even if your shorts were shorter and most immigrants here aren't aware of this custom. You certainly won't get in trouble.  
Unadvisable to cross dress.  
Avoid black as it's too bloody hot.  
If visiting a masjid, 3/4 length shorts at minimum, preferably full length.  
In short, probably exactly the same as you wear already in your home country (unless you live in Alaska)!  
Welcome to Dubai! :D  
EDIT: looks like you're from Sweden... basically anything that'll keep you cool!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty reasonable by Dubai standards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well done, you arguably proved there are exceptions. I was saying that some colours just look better on cars. Just drive through your nearest town, and count how many silver and black cars you see. Then count how many pink, lime green and brown cars you see. Of the latter classification, tell me how many looked good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  not every Westerner would have the idealogy that people should learn English

The French, for example ;)  
And yeah, people learn at different rates so making it compulsory would be a bit harsh. But the effort should be there if you intend to spend more than a couple of years in a country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I hardly doubt that would be the case.

You saying that it's not likely that westerners expect foreign speakers to learn their language? Actually, it is a very common sentiment. And actually one that I don't necessarily disagree with. I think there should at least be an effort to learn the local language.  
Source: European, trying to learn Arabic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My question wasn't a challenge. I consider myself conservative, but also appreciate that not everyone is, and have no problem with that. I wondered why, from your point of view, that you were hopeful that my mentality would change. Again, not a challenge, just genuinely curious :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "y'all come to 'merica, y'all gotta done speak gerd English!"  
Generally Westerners consider it an obligation for foreigners to learn the local language. I have tried to learn as much Arabic as I can, but I'm by no means fluent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't think it's fair to force non-Arabic speakers to learn Arabic.

Try having that mentality in the West! You will be very unpopular! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought utility bills were cheaper too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with a conservative mentality? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> British Racing Green and Lime Green are NOT the same! :p  
That said, I'm not saying those colours are impossible to make nice, but simply that they don't lend themselves to car designs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 13:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that guy is Weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 13:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But why have we conditioned girls to like everything pink? It's not inate, but something they have been taught to like. I find it sad when girls get all excited over pink because it's most likely a manufactured reaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 13:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, I think it's terrible. Not because of any pinkness, it's just a bad design. However, I don't think pink is a good choice of colour for a car to start with. Some colours just don't work on cars; purple, lime green, brown, these colours just don't lend themselves to automotive design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, not disputing the owners, but for $200, you're getting crap bits of plastic with most designer frames. But with Oakley, they genuinely invest in the lens technology, and you're getting a very well designed lens.  
Source: Optometrist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out Oakley, you get a LOT more for your money (in lens technology) than some shitty Ray Bans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you under some illusion that government departments are part of one seamless entity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, with the amount I've spent there, I should probably have some shares! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If people are drinking though, it will exclude (most practising) Muslims. Muslims aren't just not allowed to drink, but aren't actually meant to be in the company of those drinking. No probs, I'm not saying you need to change your plans as it's your meetup, just saying it's difficult for Muslims to be a part of it :)  
We could arrange another "halal" meetup another time, all inclusive. Raw coffee probably a good choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this "Not the Onion" ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only because of the alcohol, but also because Friday is the sabbath for Muslims, so around lunch time there's the sermon at the masjid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about RAW coffee, after the rave reviews? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many hotels with low standards too. Hotels in Dubai are far more expensive than Europe. AirBnB can offer a nice place at an affordable rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Provision to pray almost anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, can claim split year treatment. As long as you were resident abroad for your previous tax year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP was after good things! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is mighty awkward for any Muslims who want to join in...  
EDIT: maybe we need to do a separate Muslim friendly one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That look right before the stands up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily, not yet anyway. But when she does, she should get an octopus tattoo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  since a couple of months  
  
There's one of those annoying phrases...  
It doesn't make sense in English with out the "ago" at the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I like the fact that Spinneys meat isn't pimped with hormones. I was impressed with the range of organic at LuLu too when I went. It's a bit further for me though, and I don't buy in bulk so distance is a factor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've found that I can align my chakras with well fitting boxers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll revert back to you at a later date, sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 07:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've not really found that to be the case, compared to somewhere like Carrefour. They do do some good stuff which one can't find in other supermarkets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I concede that an acquired taste it surely is. But nothing else can satiate the desire for a good Stilton! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm with /u/kcon15 on this one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dubai to Fujairah to pick up grandparents, then back to Dubai to shop, then back to Fujairah to drop off, then back home to Dubai seems like it'll take hours.  
Just how much can you save to make the trip worth it? Divide that by 3 people (you, and two grandparents). How much does it work our per person per hour? Even if my groceries were free, it wouldn't amount to enough to warrant the time spent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anywhere Barsha and southwards is good, so yeah, New-Dubai </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh ok, then my response should have been directed to those who do genuinely believe that. Apologies /u/Swie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Western culture (and Islam) dictates the dowry be paid to the woman. In some South Asian countries, it's the opposite.  
Why do you describe a wife as a "burden", that's disgustingly disrespectful to so many women worldwide who work tirelessly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told you that it's rude to ask!  
I've called my butler to speak to the rest of my staff about recruiting a small task force to hunt you down. Don't think about leaving the country, I've paid off all of the government sectors (at least the ones I'm not personal friends with) to recruit them in ensuring your capture!  
But to give you a clue... I don't earn much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't discuss my salary with my closest friends or even family, let alone disclose it publicly on the interwebs.  
As a Brit, [never ask me what I earn](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E837tnxRVS0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assumed "Cali" was California, not Calcutta. Mea culpa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Housing shortage? I thought there was a housing surplus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably true if considering the large labourer contingent. But I would have thought these don't form a large part of /r/Dubai demographic where I would expect this to be true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people here seem to be confused between arranged marriages and forced marriages. The former is simply the introduction of the two parties with no other intention other than marriage. Either party has the choice to decline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why should "class" come into it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not all dowrys are paid to the woman. A lot of Indians will have the dowry paid to the man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apreciate that it must be difficult, but I disagree with our identity being formed by what we do with half our waking lives as being something wrong. We typically spend more waking time with our colleagues than we do with our family, so it's bound to have an effect on who we are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not new, maybe I just found Spinneys and Carrefour gave me the familiarity, being from Europe, so never thought to try elsewhere. Carrefour prices are on par with Spinneys. The other supermarkets I've come across always seemed small, with limited options at best, and dirty at worst. I've been given several other options which I'll endeavour to check out.  
Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well look at Mr Two Grains here!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's what he's trying to verify...  
I was pointing out that I think OP already knew that.  
That said, have we verified it yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other replies have sugggested alternatives. I've mainly compared to Carrefour, or LuLu.  
LuLu is a mission for me to get to, so any saving is negated by travel time.  
Will be checking out the ones others have suggested :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa, that's a mission! Are you going there to save money or b cause the produce is good? If it's to save money, surely the time taken isn't worth it, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? Have you never been questioned "do you have any rechargeable lithium batteries in your check in"  
There are signs at the check in desk. It's a genuine question if we can't check in or take in hand baggage... what do we do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that they posted the question implies they were sceptical, therefor sought verification. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I don't understand is that they also don't permit lithium batteries to be checked in. So basically, laptops aren't allowed on planes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, wrong side of town for me, but will check it out if I'm over that way. Ta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, will seek them out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, will check 'em out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do go for organic. But even non-organic, where can you get fruit and veg for less than AED7/KG??? I've not found Spinneys to be any more expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fresh fruit and veg is way more expensive than eating out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's like me saying I'm British, and proud, because it's so much better than places like Pakistan. We should be proud of our culture, not that we're "better". Every culture has something to celebrate, and we should participte and enjoy the celebration of others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As pointed out by someone else, stay out of wadis during rainy season. Even if it's not raining where you are, the water may be rushing from elsewhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A/S/L...? Is this the '90s lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ok, no probs. But yeah for info, the compact cameras and phones etc will have software in which actually puts "filters" on to make them more vivid. They detect the subject and apply them automatically, e.g., Sky more blue and trees more green. At the very least it will auto detect the white balance. Even DSLRs will apply this (though not as much) if saving as JPG. A true "non edited" photo will be the "raw" file. They look very bland, and when my friends want to see my photographs immediately after I shoot it because I have "expensive cameras" they assume they are good. They need to be post processed to get them looking like what you image.  
That said, awesome shot, looks like a fantastic place! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you realise there's a massive amount of editing which is done automatically? If you were to shoot this scene raw, it would look very different.  
Nice shot, but ruined by claiming it required no editing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I can hear it now. I hope you doing ok. It's just some electrical discharge from the clouds, nothing to worry about. Sit inside your car and you'll be totally safe in the Faraday cage :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why have you changed plans? You can go much further into the dunes when they're wet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raymond? Is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh, I love them! The louder the better! I travel to Malaysia a lot where it's almost a daily occurrence. I love the tropical thunderstorms! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I have carried big bags of spices, wrapped up looking like blocks of cocaine, through the he airport. Nada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL how out of touch with reality I must be... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely you can afford driving lessons then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
