<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7781</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would hardly call the U.S. system from January 2011 - January 2017 a grand coalition. Genuine grand coalitions are based on the idea of compromise to depoliticize the essential consensus items. What we had was more of a cold war/stalemate based on wanting to avoid mutually unacceptable outcomes (default on U.S. debt) with certain areas off limits after previous confrontations almost went awry. We've been living under sequester-budget continuing resolutions for years. 

Supermajority requirements for basic legislation perpetuate dysfunction by screwing up accountability. Majoritarian parliamentary systems at least make it easy for the average person to figure out who's in charge so they can hold them accountable for the consequences of what they do (or don't). The opposition can't sabotage policies or force the governing party to water them down. But the governing party also can't blame the opposition for anything that doesn't work. Over time, this encourages parties to think twice as well as rely on facts and sound analysis before changing policies, because they'll own the changes.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. And in this flawed analogy, America has cancer and Trump is a potential cure that may or may not work but has brutally unpleasant side effects.

That's bass ackwards.
 
It's *Trumpism itself*and the forces that enabled it to gain powerthat are the *actual* cancer.       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just bad politics on their part.

Republicans are holding *their own government* hostage because their members are too extreme to compromise *among themselves* on anything. 

Democrats are in the minority and are the opposition party. They have no obligation to *help* Trump pass his agenda when they don't support it. This will just reinforce the correct perception that Republicans are incapable of actually governingeven when they have unified control of the Presidency and both Houses of Congress.    

Trump has no leverage to demand anything of Democrats. Whatever breaks on his watchor is actively sabotagedwill be on him. His party has control. They should be able to implement their own fixes. If they want Democratic help, they need to come to the table with *concessions*, *not demands*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you figure those numbers? Counting likelies? Based on the same map, I'd say 5-9 D to 2 R (lean + tossup). But if we're in an environment where Dems could actually take the 2 R, they likely wouldn't be losing many (if any) of those incumbent seats. 

Like I said, I don't expect Dems to take the Senate except in the catastrophic backlsh scenario. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super cool. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fully agree the Senate is hard in 2018. But it's not impossible.

In a midterm environment, with the other party holding the Presidency, the Democratic Senate seats up for re-election are defensible. [Cook currently has these seats as 12 solid, 8 likely, and 5 lean D](http://cookpolitical.com/senate/charts/race-ratings), with no tossups. [Sabato rates them](http://www.centerforpolitics.org/crystalball/content/images//2017-02-16_Senate_Map_600.png) as 11 safe, 5 likely, 6 lean, and 3 tossups. The risks of losing each seat isn't independent either. Rather, they tend to be highly correlated such that seats will often flip together. And the more nationalized these Senate races are, the greater this correlated effect. 

In 1970, Democrats faced a 25 D-8 R map with Nixon at 58% approval. 13 Democratic seats were in states that Nixon won (vs  10 Dems in Trump states). Yet, they ended up holding losses to only 2-3 seats (depending on how you count Sen. Byrd re-labelling himself an independent for that term but continuing to caucus with Dems) and gained 12 seats in the House. This was a pretty good outcome... for Nixon. I think the realistic best case for Trump is something like that. 

With that said, Dems taking outright Senate control in 2018 likely won't happen outside of the catastrophic backlash scenario. If it does, I think the best path is prorbably NV, AZ, and [TX](http://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/329445-poll-shows-cruz-losing-to-texas-dem-castro)
 (or possibly TN, [if Corker retires as he's hinting he may](http://www.wbir.com/mb/news/politics/sen-bob-corker-not-yet-ready-to-say-whether-he-will-run-for-third-term/432097887?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiTVRreVptVTVZell6WXpGayIsInQiOiI0RjUybm1QSkhYOWFZOFppT1N2amp4THIxcDNtM3Rva3h1ZGVOSzFWK3NBYWM1Q1BnTjV5OG9oOGRTcFZqM1dydER3YXdsRUp1OVJwM0VLMDg3d3V1SjJlMUEwM2dhQkJobm5IQTM1TDI4MnREUytIdUZXcGtKM01pUHg2SjZoZiJ9)).

Another possible path would be a 50:50 Senate where a Republican Senator abstains and denies Pence the ability to cast the tiebreaking vote. Then you'd get 50 Schumer - 49 McConnell - 1 Abstention. I could see this happening, for example, [if McMullin (a never Trumper) beats Hatch in UT](http://www.deseretnews.com/article/865678241/Poll-Evan-McMullin-beats-Sen-Orrin-Hatch-in-head-to-head-matchup.html) and McConnell has been exerting partisan pressure or errecting other roadblocks for the the Senate Intel Committee's Trump-Russia investigation (which McMullin strongly favors). Admittedly, the likelihood of this last scenario is pretty remote. But even in a 50:50 Senate controlled by Republicans, Dems would have equal staff and committee representation, making it much harder for Trump to get anything done without genuine bipartisanship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twenty-five million reasons the U.S. hasnt struck North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't talking about 2020, but 2018. 

You're right that a ton can change in 6 months, but I think it's fairly safe to say that Trump will not be popular enoughbased on everything we know so farto "win" the 2018 midterms.

*First*, like I said, Trump is *already* facing a legitimacy crisis, having lost the popular vote by a large margin, then pushing controversial appointments and a hard right agenda for which he had a weak mandate. He *didn't even try* to reach out and expand his relatively narrow starting base. Just as importantly, there's the Russian election subversion scandal. Until and if there's a thorough independent investigationwhich a large majority of the public says it wantsand such an investigation clears his campaign of any wrongdoing (which seems increasingly unlikely), the scandal isn't going away. Trump missed his own self-imposed deadline yesterday to provide a report on the hacking and interference, and he seems intent on stonewalling and trying to change the subject. That strategy can, *at most*, buy a bit of time or run down the clock. (I assume for purposes of this analysis that conclusive proof of an explicit agreement and *quid pro quo* between the Kremlin and Trump campaign *does not* come to light during before 2018.)

*Second*, let's come back to basic regularities of American politics. In 36 out of 39 midterms since the Civil War, the President's party has lost seats or a relative share of the House (while it was still growing). Trump has the lowest first quarter approval rating of any President in the history of polling. Democrats have suddenly become competitive in special elections held in Congressional districts that are significantly more Republican than the country overall.

Can Trump turn it around? Perhaps. But successfully doing so likely means limiting Republican losses to fewer than 24 seats in the House and picking off 1-3 incumbent Democratic Senators. More likely, he faces more typical/average first-midterm setback, which would be enough to flip the House and possibly net 0-2 new Democratic seats in the Senate. But Trump could also face a catastrophic 1994 or 2010 style wave that flips the Senate (despite the unfavorable map) and gives Democrats a working majority in the House. The last scenario is more likely than Trump somehow storming to the 60%+ approval rating that he'd need to defy historical odds and actually gain seats in the House. Nothing in his life or short political career has shown that he has the competencelet alone the inclinationto build that kind of consensus. 

Wracking my brain, I think it would take a major terrorist attack (for which he was not perceived by the public as negligent, which could be tough, given his disengagement from Intel briefings and lack of attention to details) and accompanying rally-around-the-flag effect. Domestic legislative achievements likely won't do it, because even if he manages to address the dysfunction of the House Republican caucus so that he can pass things, the things he wants to passlike repeal and replacement of the ACAare highly unpopular and would actually damage his prospects for 2018.

So, in sum, **over Trunp's plausible range of popularity, I think he almost certainly loses at least a dozen seats in the 2018 midterms, more likely than not flipping control of the House in the process.** And I think that a catastrophic backlash is more likely than a dramatic rebound. I don't think this analysis assumes and depends on him being especially unpopular. The point can't be emphasized enough: [midterms are brutal](http://imgur.com/M0So3BX) to the [President's party](http://imgur.com/VcIwq0v).

        </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's somewhat of an arbitrary deadline, yes. There's no rule that presidents have to have signed X number of bills into law by the first 100 days of their presidency or else.

Nonetheless, it's a deadline that presidents since Franklin D. Roosevelt have been measured up against. And no modern president who has struggled in the first 100 days has suddenly revved up in the next 100, nor in the next couple of years.

Presidents who failed to sign any major piece of legislation in the first 100 days  especially presidents whose parties also controlled Congress  have sputtered in their first couple of years, too, said Brooklyn College history professor and presidential scholar Robert David Johnson. And that should be a major warning sign to President Trump, who on Friday tacitly acknowledged he has had a lackluster start.

...

You could also argue that a productive 100 days isn't indicative of a productive presidency...

But with regard to failure, a meh 100 days has historically been a pretty good measure of a meh first few years.

Speaking of failure, you could also argue Trump has set himself up for this. Up until the health-care implosion, he was pretty clear that the 100 days construct matters. More explicitly than any other president who came before him, he laid out exactly what he was going to get done in these first few months  renegotiate trade deals, military alliances, tax cuts, address Russian hacking.

None of that has come to fruition.

Past presidents spinning their wheels at the 100-day mark have subsequently struggled to make something out of nothing. Which is why 100 days may not be a ridiculous standard to measure a president by. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump, heres why 100 days may not be such a ridiculous standard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, youth turnout in 2014 was the lowest in 40 years. 

This can be explained mostly with basic political dynamics without resorting to anything specific about Millennials.

 See below.

Presidential turnout was better than the hole it fell into between Gore and Clinton, but didn't quite beat the 1992 high. It's mostly been a general decline since the 1970s.



[Turnout as a percentage of the Voting Elligible Population (VEP)](http://www.centerforpolitics.org/crystalball/content/images/GVS2017030201-chart1.png) in 1992, 2004, 2008, 2012, and 2016 was higher than any Presidential election between 1972 and 1988 (a period during which you could see a gradual decline). In turn, 2004-2016 all have higher turnout than 1992. The recent high record turnout for a Presidential election is 2008 (61.6% VEP).

Turnout for midterms has been fairly steady, with minor oscillations around 39-40%. 2002, 2006, and 2010 had gradually increasing turnout, and each of these elections had turnout higher than 1974 and 1978. 

2014 is the low outlier (35.9%). Notably, though, the next two miderms with the lowest turnout were 1986 (38.1%) and 1998 (38.1%)both also in the 6th year of a two-term Presidency. Historically, this is the election where even popular Presidents can have their parties' ranks in Congress get decimated (absent unusual circumstanceslike the partisan impeachment of Clinton, which the public broadly opposed). 

I'd propose that the low 2014 youth turnout can be understood mostly as a product of these regular dynamics. 

*First*, the President's party almost always does badly in midterms. A large part of that is because the opposition's base is more mobilized and turns out at a higher rate than the President's party's base. Since Obama was in power, and Millenials vote disproportionately Democratic, we'd expect *relatively* lower turnout. Plus it was a 6th year midterm. And keep in mind that midterms have a lower baseline of youth turnout to begin with. *Second*, you had President Obama near the lowpoint (40%) of his approval. So when you combine these effects, it's not hard to see why youth turnout was historically low.

Compare this to 2006, where you had Bush at 38% approval in a 6th-year midterm. Unlike in 1986, 1998 or 2014, turnout was relatively high by midterm standards, at 40.4%. [A slightly lower % of Millennials and GenX'ers identified as Democrats](http://assets.pewresearch.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/12/2017/03/20144206/FT_17.03.16_generations_ideology_detailed.png) in 2006 (47/44) than in 2014 (49/48), and they represented different proportions of the electorate due to aging. Yet, turnout among 18-29 year-olds was [significantly higher in 2006 (25.5%)](http://civicyouth.org/youth-voter-turnout-increases-in-2006/) and increased by relatively more than it did among older (and more Republican) voters. For comparison, turnout among younger voters fell off a cliff [in 2014 (19.9%)](http://civicyouth.org/2014-youth-turnout-and-youth-registration-rates-lowest-ever-recorded-changes-essential-in-2016/) but declined relatively less for older voters.

In 2018, with an unpopular and divisive Republican President facing a legitimacy crisis, I would expect based on the fundamentals to see something much more akin to 2006 than 2014. Don't be surprised if we get a relatively high turnout (40%) midterm where young people comprise a higher proportion of the electorate than 2010 and 2014, and Democrats retake *at least* the House. 





      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it does seem like it was just yesterday that they hung out. Dementia can affect perception of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd never heard that badass annecdote. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (**Psst! You're still on fire from that burn.**)

You can't have it both ways.

You're arguing that Sessions referring to Hawaii (the State) as a singular island is factual because the big island in the chain is called Hawaii. 

Yet the seat of federal district court that issued the ruling is Oahua separate island. 

Thus, if Sessions was referring only to the island of Hawaii, versus the State of Hawaii or the Hawaiian Islands, he was *excluding* the very court he was criticizing. And if he referred to the entire State of Hawaii as an islandbecause that's close enoughhe committed a cultural *faux pas* and was just flat wrong.

So, no, Sessions' statement was not factual or technically correct. In addition to disparaging the State of Hawaii, its residents, and Judge Derrick Watson, he was *technically incorrect*.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the ~~Republican~~ United Russia Party is incapable of exercising even basic oversight over the Trump Regimeas demonstrated by its tolerance for perjurious testimony in a Senate confirmation hearing by a nominee to be this ~~country's~~ newly-annexed Oblast's highest law enforcement officer.       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily. It can also be understood as impulsivity and fabrication on the spot (demostrated constantly), over-estimation of his own abilities and popularity, as well as his miscalculation of what the public would find significant (which could itself be a symptom of living in a bubble filled with sycophants).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's a bullshit criticism from Ellis. It's a mistake to interpret the election results without factoring Comey and the selective Wikileaks disclosures (or the Kremlin's "active measures" to amplify them with fake news and social media bots). Comey's vague and improper letter, in particular, sucked up all the bandwidth for substantive issue discussions. The damage from this letter can't be underestimated. In addition to [tipping the election to Trump](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5nmxob/z/dcctqr2), it sabotaged the campaign's closing argument for downballot Democrats. 

In late October, with Clinton up 6-7 points, her campaign and [Obama began to pivot to an attack against the dysfunctional Republican Congress](http://www.cnn.com/2016/10/25/politics/obama-unleashed/) in order to build on the momentum from Clinton's [three dominant debate performances](http://fivethirtyeight.com/features/clinton-probably-finished-off-trump-last-night/) and tie Congressional Republicans to the cratering Trumpwho they refused to disavow. The whole election had been gradually building to this decisive moment. Then, right in the middle of it, the Comey letter hit and yanked the football away, changing the narrative and reenergizing the flailing Trump campaign. The rest of the campaign was defense against Trump's exaggerated characterizations and outright fabrications of what the new emails contained. Democrats dropped across the board in the Senate polls and generic Congressional ballot. 

And we got what we got.        </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not autistic people paying more for cancer treatments. It's anyone with autism paying more for that condition, and cancer patients paying more for that condition, for the reasons I describedit wouldn't be part of the basic coverage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. I also don't care about the superficial bullshit. Pelosi is not an entertainer. She's the most effective and consequential Democratic Speaker since Sam Rayburn. She knows how to build consensus in her caucus, count votes, and twist arms. The 111th Congress got more done under Pelosi than any Congress since the 60s. The ACA should be called Pelosicare just as much as Obamacare. 

Beyond the legislative accomplishments, Pelosi also led at key times. TARP (under Bush) together the Recovery Act (under Obama) saved us from another Depression. Both of these things passed because of Pelosi. TARP, in particular, was not popular. But it backstopped the economic freefall and has made back the money taxpayers spent. If the downturn had happened under a Democrat, could you see Republicans taking an unpopular vote like that? Hell. One doesn't have to imagine. Just look at what Boehner did in 2009 with the Recovery Act itself. Not a single Republican voted for it in the Housedespite Obama's best efforts at bipartisanship, at a time the economy was *losing 800K jobs per month*. 

It's a real shame she lost her majority in 2010. We'd probably have gotten the DREAM act and comprehensive immigration reform, cap   trade (which passed the House), an infrastructure bill and second stimulus, universal background checks, a regular budget without sequester cuts, the Buffet rule (30% minimum tax to avoid exploitation of loopholes by extremely wealthy), card check (to make unionizing easier), and the list goes on. 

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The House Freedom Caucus finds community rating (spreading costs more equitably over healthy and sick people) deeply objectionable because they don't believe in solidarity and pooling of resources to solve problems. If you are lucky to be healthy, great. You shouldn't have to pay for anyone else and should have the cheapest insurance possible. And, if you're sick, you should have to pay your own way. Something something bootstraps.

The way they get around not doing away with the ban on pre-existing condition exclusions (while abolishing the individual mandate that makes this possible) is to make it so that you have to buy coverage for specific conditions (*i.e.* plans will no longer be required to cover a minimum basket of things) sort of like a menu. The problem is that if you choose to buy a coverage add on, it's extremely likely because you intend to use it. But the insurance companies know this. Since people who don't think they'll need coverage won't buy it, there's no broad healthy pool to spread the cost over. So insurers will charge whatever premium that's enough to pay for what you will likely need. That, in turn, will make coverage so expensive that the vast majority of those who need it simply won't be able to afford it. 

What this plan considers important is **access***i.e.*, the theoretical option and right to buy coverage *if you had the money*, even though, in practice, *you don't have the money* and therefore lack the **ability** to buy coverage.            </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. He might make a half-hearted effort, but I think it's more likely to not come out at all. Like with the tax returns, he made a promise in the heat of the moment to lessen pressure, but is now he's realizing that the consequences of breaking it are negligible or at least less desirable than acrually following through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting timing. 

Might be preparation for next phase of investigation, possibly referral to the DoJ for prosecution, or it could be a way to respond to pressure from the Trump Regime to curb leaks.

There's been speculation that Chaffetz's resignation might be related, but as far as I can tell, no concrete report from a reputable source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Californianof "Trump would've won the popular vote if it weren't for 3 million illegals in CA" fameI stand with Hawaiians, and like-minded Alabamans, against this pernicious idea of second-class citizenship based on where we each happen to live.

None of us are "more American" than any of us.  Though I will point out here that it *wasn't* California or Hawaii who rebelled against the country to defend the right to maintain second-class non-citizenship of brown people for use as chattel.          </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty ironic that *the Nation* has to lecture "the left" to take the Russian election interference and the Trump campaign's alleged participation in it *more* seriously.

I know that Bernie or bust was a thing. But is it *really* this prevalent and stubborn that it would ignore the evidence in order to blame Clinton first?      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typical of the Trump Regime's lack of respect for judiciary and dismissal of anything that doesn't go their way, more generally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course Trump hasn't even started. It's a lose-lose for him. When he made this promise, he was calculating that the whole thing would've blown over by now and no one would seriously call him on it.

Suppose Trump were to put out a genuine, thorough, fact-based report. It would show that Russia interfered in the election to help him. We already know that. He was even forced to acknowledge Russian interference. If he were to turn the investigators loose on his campaign's involvement with the Russian intererence, it would turn up, *at minimum*, exploitation of the hacked information with knowledge that it was unlawfully obtained by Russia. The calls for an independent investigation would only increase. 

Alternatively, imagine that Trump puts out a whitewash report that completely exculpates him. That too would only intensify the calls for an independent investigation. If there *were* actually a completely innocent explanation for what's occurred, they would have already put it out there. High-level Trump Regime officials wouldn't be conspiring with Nunesthe person who was ostensibly supposed to be investigating the Regimeto manufacture too-clever-by-half pseudo-scandals to change the subject to Obama. Further, Trump wouldn't be focusing on leakers, but putting out information to refute the actual contents of the leaks to make his opponents look foolish for believing them. The unexplained and possibly indefinite delay in releasing this promised report shows that they can't even fabricate a halfway-colorable cover story for themselves.

Trump's only viable defensive play is stonewalling and distraction. He can hope that there isn't enough evidence to conclusively prove what happened and that  he can run out the clock as the investigation loses steam. In the meantime, he can try to change the subjectas he did fairly successfully with the Syria strike and North Korea saber rattling. 

It's our job to keep the public and the media focused like a laser on the Russian election interference until there are satisfactory answers.
           </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeff Sessions doesnt think a judge in Hawaii  a.k.a. an island in the Pacific  should overrule Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing probably. Ukraine isn't part of NATO. And looking the other way is alleged to have been the *quo* for Uncle Vlad's election help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically. The plan seems to be making the regions more and more economically and culturally integrated with Russia without formally annexing them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vladimir Putin is seizing on mixed signals from the U.S. to quietly tighten Russias grip on [two rebel regions of Ukraine](https://assets.bwbx.io/images/users/iqjWHBFdfxIU/ikWuvkTDuFTw/v3/1400x-1.png), burying hopes for a European-brokered peace deal and relief from sanctions anytime soon.

While the Kremlin continues to publicly back the accord that Germany and France oversaw in 2015, Putins real strategy in Ukraine is to fully separate the two border areas known as the Donbas through incremental integration with Russia, three people close to the leadership in Moscow said. He has no plans to recognize or annex the territories, they said.


Russia has been moving gradually, using a blockade by Ukrainian activists as political cover to take over key economic links with the separatist zones. Last week, Russian Railways slashed rates for shipping coal and iron ore to points near the rebel areas, where the metals industry provides most jobs. That will allow Russia to replace Ukrainian supplies halted by Kiev and ensure that steel plants continue to function, according to two people in the industry.

...

Earlier this year, Putin angered his Ukrainian counterpart, Petro Poroshenko, by signing a decree recognizing passports and other documents issued by the separatist governments in Luhansk and Donetsk, which have already declared the ruble their official currency. The Kremlin is also considering making it easier for the 2 million residents of the regions to become Russian citizens, which would dramatically complicate any attempt by Kiev to reassert control.

Moscow is implementing the so-called Transnistria scenario, according to the deputy head of Poroshenkos administration, Kostiantyn Yelisieiev, referring to the breakaway region in the former Soviet republic of Moldova, which hosts Russian troops but has no citizenship agreements with Russia.

Russia supports a string of separatist regions in former Soviet republics, using them as leverage over pro-Western governments in what it considers to be its sphere of influence. In 2008, Russia sent troops into Georgia to secure two such areas that are now essentially Kremlin protectorates. Last month, Russia absorbed some of the militias there into its regular army.

...


Putins moves in Ukraine pose a challenge to the U.S. and the European Union, which publicly support the 2015 Minsk accord that calls for Ukraine to regain control of the Donbas. A collapse of the deal would be a major blow to German Chancellor Angela Merkel, whos spent a lot of political capital trying to end the worst violence Europes seen since the the Balkan wars of the 1990s. The three-year conflict has killed 10,000 people and displaced 2 million more.

President Donald Trumps administration ... has sent mixed signals on its stance and even appears to be totally uninterested in the conflict, as one senior Russian diplomat put it. Trump has taken a tough line rhetorically, though he hasnt made his position clear and the White House seems focused on issues it considers more pressing like Syria and North Korea.

...

With the Minsk accord now basically at a dead end, the Donbas is drifting into a frozen conflict that may last decades.
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin Quietly Detaches Ukraine's Rebel Zones as U.S. Waffles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worrisome:

**The woman leading the Justice Department's investigation of foreign meddling into the 2016 election and possible ties between the Trump campaign and Russia has told staff members she will leave the department in May.**

Mary B. McCord has served at the highest levels in the national security unit, either as its leader or chief deputy, for the past three years. A longtime federal prosecutor based in Washington, McCord easily won the confidence of both career lawyers and her supervisors inside the Justice Department.

**McCord did not offer a public reason for her departure.** In a message to her staff earlier this week, she wrote that she did not make the decision easily, but she concluded "the time is now right for me to pursue new career opportunities."

**Her exit leaves a huge vacancy at one of the Justice Department's most important divisions, at a time when the Trump administration is struggling to fill the ranks.** Attorney General Jeff Sessions is the only leader so far in the building to have secured Senate confirmation. His picks for deputy and associate attorney general await votes by the full Senate. The administration has not yet announced political appointees for other top posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leader Of Justice Department National Security Division On the Way Out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They. Haven't. Even. Fucking. Started?!


Of course not. It's a lose-lose for Trump. When he made this promise, he was calculating that the whole thing would've blown over by now and no one would seriously call him on it.

Suppose Trump were to put out a genuine, thorough, fact-based report. It would show that Russia interfered in the election to help him. We already know that. He was even forced to acknowledge Russian interference. If he were to turn the investigators loose on his campaign's involvement with the Russian intererence campaign, it would turn up, *at minimum*, exploitation of the hacked information with knowledge that it was unlawfully obtained by Russia. The calls for an independent investigation would only increase. 

Alternatively, imagine that Trump puts out a whitewash report that completely exculpates him. That too would only intensify the calls for an independent investigation. If there *were* actually a completely innocent explanation for what's occurred, they would have already put it out there. High-level Trump Regime officials wouldn't be conspiring with Nunesthe person who was ostensibly supposed to be investigating the Regimeto manufacture distraction scandals. Further, Trump wouldn't be focusing on leakers so much as putting out information to refute the actual contents of the leaks, and make his opponents look bad for believing them. The delay in releasing the promised report shows that they can't even fabricate a halfway-colorable cover story.

Trump's only viable defensive play is stonewalling and distraction. He can hope that there isn't enough evidence to conclusively prove what happened and that  he can run out the clock as the investigation loses steam. In the meantime, he can try to change the subjectas he did fairly successfully with the Syria strike and North Korea saber rattling. 

It's our job to keep the public and the media focused like a laser on the Russian election interference until there are satisfactory answers.
      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the heart of it:

[T]he [Trump] campaign's descriptions of Page's role - including how he got it and how long he served in it - have varied and in some cases contradict each other. The conflicting explanations have raised questions about why no one seems to know for sure, or at least isn't willing to say, who brought Page on - and why.

Page's personal and professional history offers no hint of an interest in American politics or foreign policy, except for occasional blog posts between 2013 and 2014 in which he criticized the US sanctions on Russia as "sanctimonious expressions of moral superiority" and praised Rosneft CEO Igor Sechin for his "accomplishments" in advancing US-Russia relations.


The Trump campaign's explanation of Page's role is completely incoherent. And they still haven't given a plausible explanation for how this previously unknown political operative was brought into the campaign into such an important role. The whole thing looks incredibly shady. And their distancing themselves from him after the fact (as well as from Manafort*who ran the campaign*) only adds suspicion.  

Following the money would help here. But for that, among other things, we need documentation of the Roseneft deal, including the ownership structure of the various entities involved in it. 

More than anything, there needs to be a public presentation of the evidence. This is too important to be done behind closed doors. At some point, the window of opportunity to put country before party will close. If Republicans won't investigate, then Democrats need to weaponize this issue politically because the public is on their side. From [today's PPP poll](http://www.publicpolicypolling.com/main/2017/04/democrats-have-big-enthusiasm-edge-for-2018.html):

-The Russia issue isn't going anywhere- **61% of voters want an independent investigation into Russia's involvement in the 2016 Presidential election and ties to key Trump aides, compared to only 29% of voters opposed to such an investigation**. A majority of voters- **55%- continues to believe that Russia wanted Trump to win the election to only 22% who think it wanted Clinton to win** (although Trump voters claim 42/22 that they think it wanted Clinton to win.)

The finding of an independent investigation could be devastating to Trump's presidency. Right now voters are pretty evenly divided with 41% believing members of Trump's campaign team worked in association with Russia to help Trump win the election and 40% saying they don't think there was any direct coordination. **But if it does come out that Russia and Trump's team were working together, only 38% of voters think Trump should continue serving as President to 52% who think he should resign.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that surprising. The whole Trump Regime seems like it's stuck in the 80s, which is probably the last time the Orange One learned anything new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump administration is way behind the times on marijuana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

[Some numbers to make the cruelty concrete](https://twitter.com/jonfavs/status/855069362507481088):

Estimated spike in premiums if you have...

Lung cancer: $73k

Breast cancer: $28k

Diabetes: $5k

Autism: $5k

Asthma: $4k

A pregnancy(!): $17k


  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that it resembles a veto because it's negating something rather than affirmatively proposing, but it still needs bicameral approval and presentment for Presidential approval or a veto override. 

So it's more like regular legislation than the sort of legislative veto that was ruled unconstitutional in [*INS v. Chadha*](https://scholar.google.com/scholar_case?case=2221871582286121199 q=462+U.S.+919+\(1983\) hl=en as_sdt=2006), 462 U.S. 919 (1983).      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See [this comment](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/66byny/sean_spicer_cant_name_a_single_legislative/dghu8ky/). 

Because of his potential influence as a formal participant with veto power in the legislative process, it's appropriate to assign some accountability to the President. 

If he finds his own party incapable of enacting policy that he believes is beneficial and necessary for the country as a whole, he has the option of reaching out to the other side and trying to cobble together a bipartisan coalition. Trump hasn't even tried. His closest attempt at this was threatening to sabotage the ACA and hold the healthcare of millions of people hostage in order to extract concessions from Democrats. Democrats, as the opposition, have no obligation to help him govern--especially to implement policies that they disagree with. If he wants their help, he needs to offer something worthwhile in return. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a fair point. But he's also aroused national opposition, which makes the battle even more interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, there's a difference between selective disclosure of facts to create a misleading impression, on the one hand, versus focusing on a particular fact or set of facts that appear significant from a editorial standpoint in order to advocate for a specific disclosed partisan agenda, on the other hand. Here, there's no secret that ShareBlue's agenda is damaging the Trump Regime politically with factual information and opinion so as to facilitate its expeditious removal from power.

The beauty of Reddit is that it allows the community to upvote and downvote what it finds worthy. The proper filter here is the collective judgment of this sub, as well as the individual judgment of the submitter (me)--who can suffer reputational consequences for shitposting.

I think that a categorical exclusion of partisan sources would be worse than the problem it seeks to solve--with certain exceptions, since I think it's justified to impose bright line rules to impede dissemination of fabricated and objectively false information. Generally though, I think submissions should be judged on their merits, as well as the merits and practices of their sources and publishers. 

For my part, I have no regrets about posting this story. ShareBlue is not publishing false information here. Moreover, ShareBlue represents a minuscule fraction of media market share, and the views of its editors and owners are not excluding competing views from this sub in any way. If these stories have gained prominence in recent weeks, it's because they have conveyed relevant information to people in a form that they found both useful and appealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Counter-counter argument:

Not always. ShareBlue sometimes beats those organizations to the punch, possibly because, in exercising their editorial discretion, those organizations didn't consider the same aspect of a story to be particularly noteworthy. 

More importantly though, if I run across a story that I think is worth sharing, and I trust that ShareBlue is accurately reporting underlying facts that I find significant, I shouldn't be compelled to hunt for another source just to placate the minority of people on this sub who want to harp constantly on the fact that ShareBlue's reporting and commentary is from a *clearly disclosed* pro-Democratic, anti-Trump vantage point. 

I of course have the *option* of looking for another source that people of the opposite political persuasion might be more willing to accept. Or I can simply let a ShareBlue submission fight it out in the marketplace of ideas of this sub, which is what I did here. I thought this specific piece had a great headline and would spark a good discussion--and it has, including about how [repeals of administrative regulations via the Congressional Review Act are fundamentally legislative, not executive, in character](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/66byny/sean_spicer_cant_name_a_single_legislative/dghae7e/). To top it off, I still haven't seen another source reporting this particular story. So I have no regrets here, and would post it all over again without hesitation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Several already have:

[1](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/66byny/sean_spicer_cant_name_a_single_legislative/dghnrul/)

[2](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/66byny/sean_spicer_cant_name_a_single_legislative/dghtrhx/)

[3](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/66byny/sean_spicer_cant_name_a_single_legislative/dghsrbs/)

[4](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/66byny/sean_spicer_cant_name_a_single_legislative/dghseeh/)

See any of those exchanges for why this point doesn't have the significance that some attach to it. 

**[TL:DR] The President is a constitutionally-specified participant in the legislative process who wields direct and indirect power to shape legislation through his formal veto power.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not a legislator, but he's a [formal veto player](https://books.google.com/books?id=ZlCrBdHD4owC printsec=frontcover#v=onepage q f=false) in the legislative process specified by the Constitution. 

Even a bill that's successfully passed by both Houses of Congress can't become law without presentment and the President's signature (or else an extraordinarily difficult veto override).

Thus, enacted legislation almost always entails some form of Presidential participationranging from simply signing a bill into law, to actively negotiating with Congress and using the bully pulpit to shape what the bill contains. That's why credit for legislative accomplishments has traditionally been shared with Presidents, whether Democratic or Republican.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See [this exchange](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/66byny/sean_spicer_cant_name_a_single_legislative/dghsk14/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen several comments to this effect. See [this exchange](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/66byny/sean_spicer_cant_name_a_single_legislative/dghsk14/). 

**[TL:DR] The President is part of the legislative process and thus shares credit or blame.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as legislative accomplishments, no. But judges can get credit for the ways in which they uphold specific laws. Take John Roberts' two decisions upholding the ACA. 

More importantly though, there are important distinctions between what Presidents and Judges do. 

In upholding or striking down a law, Judges are generally announcing that the law does or doesn't comport with the Constitution. In other words, they're answering the question of *whether the law is permitted*--not whether it's a good idea. If it's not permitted, then the law is void due to the conflict with the higher law, the Constitution. When reaching such a decision, judges should avoid consideration of whether permissible laws are desirable or not (though there is a place for considering potential consequences when deciding how a law should be interpreted--in part to decide what the legislature intended.) 

A President, on the other hand, has direct and indirect input into the drafting and enactment of the law. And once a bill lands on his desk, he can choose to allow it to become law or not. That's an essentially legislative function. Unlike a judge, it's not only permitted, but expected, that his decision be based on whether he thinks the law is good substantive policy. 

Hypothetically, a President who knows something about the Constitution can also exercise his veto with Constitutional issues in mind. But even if he's an expert constitutional lawyer, his opinion on these questions doesn't bind the other branches like a judicial opinion does. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, but the President participates formally and informally in the legislative procss. See [this comment](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/66byny/sean_spicer_cant_name_a_single_legislative/dghpzfv/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't say that I blame her. But she did sign up for it. And we shouldn't have to pay for her work-around--even though we can't not pay for it and leave her unprotected, either.

It's almost as if a respect for norms could help us here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are lots of good proposals for reforming SCOTUS and other institutions. But it would likely take most if not all of the next President's initial political capital to push these institutional and process reforms through. Republicans would scream bloody murder--even if the changes were intended to benefit no particular party in the long term. And they might well regain control of Congress at the first midterm. It's hard to win on a platform of process reform rather than substantive policy. It seems like people lack the attention span for it and/or an adequate understanding of the deficiencies that these reforms would seek to address. It would take an exceptionally skilled politician to pull it off on a partisan basis or to build the bipartisan consensus to de-politicize it.

As much as I think process reform is desperately needed, it seems like a distant pipe dream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would have been good, effective political theater by the Democrats, at the very least. Most likely, he would have found a way to dodge the substantive question and mumbled something about the political questions doctrine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thoughts exactly. "Lavish bankruptcy- and taxpayer-funded lifestyle" would be more accurate.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't talking about the Trump-Russia scandal with that last post. Gorsuch knew about what McConnell did to Garland.

Think about Gorsuch's stature if he declined the nomination publicly--maybe even at the press conference where Trump announced it. The media would have been fawning over him. 

Trump could of course withdraw his nomination instantly, but it would look terrible. Trump couldn't undo his prior lifetime appointment by Bush. So worst case, Gorsuch goes back to being possibly the most high-profile federal appellate judge in the country (who would likely get nominated to SCOTUS down the line). 

If, on the other hand, Gorsuch manages to persuade Trump to re-nominate Garland (which would have been a smart political move by Trump that would take a lot of steam ouf of the current legitimacy crisis), there'd be tremendous pressure to re-nominate Gorsuch for the next open seat or if the Garland nomination failed. Democrats would find it almost impossible to deny him an up or down vote after such a dramatic stand. Indeed, he might have won many of them over with it, and would take his seat on the Court as a consensus choice, with much more clout than he currently enjoys (he'd be the guy who stood up to Trump rather than having the highest achievement of his law career handed to him on a silver platter after being usurped from another deserving jurist). 

This type of legitimacy is vital for judges, who lack the power of the sword and purse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd give credit for that to the institutions and popular resistance that have constrained him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except that even a bill passed by both Houses of Congress can't become law without presentment and the President's signature (or else an extraordinarily difficult veto override).

Thus, enacted legislation almost always entails some form of Presidential participationranging from simply signing a bill into law, to actively negotiating with Congress and using the bully pulpit. That's why credit for legislative accomplishments has traditionally been shared with Presidents, whether Democratic or Republican.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the alternatives to negotiation are strategic patience or conflict. They've ruled out patienceat least publicly. And conflict is unacceptably risky and costly. Yet, it seems like the only path they haven't foreclosed. The Kim Regime isn't going to back down. So we'll have to see if the Trump Regime is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although there's a good chance that the systemic damage can ultimately be fixed, for those harmed in the meantime, the damage may well be irreparable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fair. The original statement *literally* distingushes the phony orange hue from a tan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was under the impression, based on the other Reuters story, that the documents themselves had leaked. I may be mistaken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The GOP has been using a statute called the Congressional Review Act to strike down administrative regulations and prevent similar ones from being enacted. Technically, each resolution that does this (by passing the House, Senate, and obtaining a signature or veto override) is a legislative act rather than an executive order.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, they **assessed with high confidence** that Russia did actively try to influence the election. That assessment was based on evidence, which may have included this plan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if we agree that his objective is to undo Obama's legacy, it seems like repealing the ACA--his signature acheivement--would be the place to start. Trump failed spectacularly at that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the nature of evidence. It tends to show that some fact or version of events is *more*or *less*likely. An individual piece of evidence doesn't have to conclusively establish something in order to have probative value.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That ship has sailed. If he had any dignity and integrity, he would have publicly declined the appointment until and if Garland was given a fair hearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because it would be a CGI fabrication in their minds. When you start with your conclusion, you can easily backfill the reasoning to arrive at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, they haven't run out of tomahawks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The documents themselves have apparently been leaked, if I'm not mistaken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There can be knowing, culpable participation (technically, collusion) without an explicit agreement, *quid pro quo*, and direct coordination (which may have nevertheless occurred).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thoughtful comment, but you can't convince me that any potential silver linings outweigh the irreparable harmunless the election is annulled and every action taken by or involving Trump is declared void, starting with the Gorsuch appointment.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The synchronized timing is further indirect evidence of collusion, and is not inconsistent with an explicit agreement and *quid pro quo*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CRA resolutions have effects beyond simply repealing the relevant regulations, though. They forbid future enactment of substantially similar rules (which is vague and raises potential constitutional issues when authority to enact regulations has been expressly delegated by specific statutory provisions that remain on the books). Also, they bypass the standard procedures for executive rule changes under the Administrative Procedure Act. These are fundamentally legislative actions, which would have no force without bicameral Congressional approval and a Presidential signature (or veto override).

Also, the resolutions of disapproval are expressly designated as [Public Laws](https://www.congress.gov/bill/115th-congress/senate-joint-resolution/34/actions?q=%7B%22search%22%3A%5B%22privacy%22%5D%7D r=7). 

So I think it's pretty indisputable that these resolutions are legislative in nature. 

That's not to say I agree with them in any way, think they are significant legislative accomplishments, or fail to recognize the cynical political motives behind them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look I hate it too. See [my earlier comment.](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/66byny/sean_spicer_cant_name_a_single_legislative/dghae7e/) But that doesn't change the fact that involved a legislative act, not just an executive one. 

And the it's not the only item on the above list that involved Congress. For instance, here are the [repeal of the teacher preparation](https://www.congress.gov/bill/115th-congress/house-joint-resolution/58/actions?r=908) and [accountability and State plans](https://www.congress.gov/bill/115th-congress/house-joint-resolution/57/actions?r=909) rules mentioned above.

Here's an act [repealing land use rules](https://www.congress.gov/bill/115th-congress/house-joint-resolution/44?r=910).

I could go on. But the point is, the Republican Congress is fully complicit here. More reason to vote out them out in 2018.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of the things you mentioned were passed through congress.

Actually, that's incorrect. 

Take the [resolution disapproving of the FCC rule to protect broadband privacy](https://www.congress.gov/bill/115th-congress/senate-joint-resolution/34/actions?q=%7B%22search%22%3A%5B%22privacy%22%5D%7D r=7).

Passed Senate by 50-48 on a party-line vote on 3/23. 

Passed House by 215-205 with no Democratic votes on 3/28. 

Presented to the Orange One on 3/30. 

(Golf break)

Signed by him on 4/03, becoming Public Law No: 115-22. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CRA itself just creates the *procedure* for passing Congressional resolutions of disapproval. It doesn't empower the President to invoke the statute unilaterally. Disapproving of a regulation requires specific legislative action by both the House and Senate, followed by a Presidential signature (or veto and potential override). That's essentially the same procedure for passing a bill into law. 

There are some constitutional issues that could be raised with the CRA. But it's impossible to argue that invocations of the CRA, which are initiated by Congress, are executive actions equivalent to executive orders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, almost certainly. Re-read with emphasis on the phrase "minority in Congress." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See [this comment from elsewhere in the thread.](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/66byny/sean_spicer_cant_name_a_single_legislative/dghcbz4/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this sentimentwhich comes up in every Shareblue article that's posted on this subis pretty misguided. 

Shareblue has a [clearly disclosed partisan viewpoint](http://shareblue.com/company/):

Shareblue is an American media company. **We produce practical, factual content to** ***delegitimize Trumps presidency, embolden the opposition, and empower the majority of Americans to fight.***

There's nothing inherently wrong or unreliable with reporting factual information from a ***disclosed*** partisan perspective. For a good part of [our history, newspapers were explicitly partisan institutions](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/History_of_American_newspapers). That's why you see some older ones with *Democrat* or *Republican* right in their name.

Shareblue is not pretending to be neutral. *And they're not neutral*. But they're not making shit up either. That's what distinguishes these stories from fake news and tinfoil conspiracy theory sites. 

As usual, here, they quote the relevant statement from Spicerthe official spokesman for the Trump Regimeprovide a direct link to the video, and then give their interpretation of it.

Since the primary source is provided, it's possible to watch it yourself to verify that Shareblue's quotation is accurate and not out of context. This permits you to draw your own conclusion, and ignore the partisan commentary if you wish.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't disparage actual tans by calling the effect of the Orange One's chemical bath one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, /u/zxcvb94105 lists several items that were undertaken through the [Congressional Review Act](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Congressional_Review_Act), which requires action by both houses of Congress (*i.e.*, [presentment](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Presentment_Clause)) and Trump's signature. 

Those items *can* fairly be called legislative. Though, as noted in the original post, every one of the items was negative--*i.e.*, a repeal of something rather than an affirmative accomplishment. 

Even if we're generous and call these items "legislative accomplishments," they weren't actually cited by Spicer (probably because they're incredibly unpopular with the public). And, in any event, they compare pretty unfavorably with what other Presidents have managed to accomplish legislatively in their first 100 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone should have fired back the obvious reply that a unilateral executive action, like an executive order, is by definition not legislative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grudgingly. 

Spicer even [tried to spin the claim that the Carl Vinson carrier battlegroup was "heading" to North Korea as being technically true because it's heading there... eventually](https://twitter.com/peterbakernyt/status/854732422637912064).

He's utterly without shame.

So, if he won't even take a half-hearted crack at defending Trump's unpresidented record of legislative wins, you know know it's *bad*.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh. Failing to destroy Obama's signature legislative accomplishment and bolstering its popularity in the process is an accomplishment alright.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Spicer cant name a single legislative accomplishment for Trumps first 100 days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he doesn't run, it would open up a potential 3rd/4th Senate seat that Democrats might plausibly be able to take in 2018 with a strong candidate, creating another route to a 51-49 majority.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Bob Corker not yet ready to say whether he will run for third term </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NV is probably the most endangered GOP Senate seat.

Good article on his recent town hall:

[Sen. Dean Heller faces angry constituents -- and demands for specifics -- at rowdy town hall](http://www.cnn.com/2017/04/17/politics/dean-heller-town-hall-nevada/?sr=twCNN041817dean-heller-town-hall-nevada0716AMStoryVideo linkId=36606740).

Heller only won 45.9% of the vote in 2012, and NV has gone blue in three consecutive Presidential elections.

Here's a [chart showing all the 2018 Senate races, the candidates' most recent vote shares, and the last two Presidential results](http://imgur.com/VVwaldS).
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't take your eyes off the ball so easily, media:

President Donald Trump's missile strike on a Syrian regime-controlled airfield was presented to the public as an act of retaliation against President Bashar al-Assad for allegedly launching a chemical attack on the town of Khan Shaykhun.** Evidence from the last 12 days shows it has had no effect on the determination of Assad and his Russian ally, President Vladimir Putin, to bomb rebels in the area out of existence.** On the domestic front, however, it delivered a clear win for Trump.

...

...[S]ince Trump ordered the Tomahawk strike on Shayrat, **the major players in the Syrian conflict have gone about their business as if nothing had happened.** It's a relief that the action didn't lead to a direct clash between Russian and U.S. militaries -- but then, their priorities are still aligned on ISIS.

The Shayrat missile attack could be confidently written off as a relatively minor waste of U.S. resources and a major hot air eruption -- if its only effect were in Syria. Trump, however, is fighting a domestic political battle, too. **The Tomahawks have wreaked much more havoc in the U.S. media than in Shayrat, ruining the established narrative of Trump's alignment with Vladimir Putin.** Trump's son, Eric, has said the missile attack was proof that his father wasn't in league with Putin.

**If jaded U.S. pundits haven't quite adopted Eric Trump's view, headlines about Trump's alleged Russian ties have given way to analyses of his unpredictable flip-flops.** It has been noted that Trump is willing to go further to defend his "red lines" than Barack Obama was, and speculation has been rife that he's going to be more of a traditional Republican president than most people expected. His voter base is certainly worried that this might be the case.

**As one of Trump's habitual diversions, the Shayrat strike has succeeded brilliantly. Analysts are struggling to read Trump instead of mocking him**. He's getting praise from people who used to dismiss him, including some former Obama aides. And as for the voter base, there's plenty of time until the next election to worry about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Missiles Hit Domestic Critics Harder Than Assad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There was a special election 11 years ago eerily similar to Georgias. Heres what happened. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there's reason to be cautious, but it's not inherently implausible given the ~20-point swing toward Democrats observed in KS-04 and GA-06. 

If the poll cited in the article is indeed correct, there has been a 17-point net swing toward Julian Castro compared to [this August 17, 2016 PPP poll](http://www.publicpolicypolling.com/main/ted-cruz/) which had Cruz beating Castro 48% to 36% in their hypothetical matchup. The same August PPP poll showed Cruz with 39% approval and 48% disapproval of his job performance (net -9). A 17-point swing toward Democrats is also pretty consistent with Trump's underwater 42%/54% (net -12) approval rating in the new Texas poll and the reality that this would be a midterm election, which the President's party almost always loses.

Finally, recall that Trump beat Clinton by 52.2% to 43.2%, which is a 6.8 point improvement from Romney's 57.2% to 41.4% victory over Obama. Texas isn't as red as it used to be when Cruz won his seat. Cruz won his election by 56.6% to 40.5%a 16.1% margin similar to Romney's 15.8%. He has had middling to low approval ratings throughout his term (creating speculation that he might even get a primary challenger) and is almost universally disliked on a personal level. Cruz is also only a first term incumbent, which is when incumbents are most vulnerable.

In light of all of this, Texas is arguably the most promising of the potential 3rd Senate seats (*i.e.*, after NV and AZ) that Democrats would need to flip in order to gain a 51-49 Senate majority in 2018.  It will be an uphill climb, to be sure.

     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I don't, because brown is Obama's *actual* skin color as opposed to the phony hue that Trump's takes on after being drenched in chemical spray. 

Secondly, Brown One could have fairly clear racial connotations, whereas I intend Orange One only to poke fun at Trump's falsity. For this reason, I wouldn't ever call Trump the White One. Just as I wouldn't call an American Indian a Red One. 


  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money has diminishing marginal returns. But in any event, what made that tremendous fundraising (a large part of which was small dollar contributions) possible was precisely Trump. You wouldn't see such an outpouring with a generic Republican President to oppose. And similarly, people wouldn't be as receptive to the message without the Orange One doing stupid shit in the background.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's some Trump supporters at the margins who can be won over. I also think it's worth a try because of how persuasion can create a two-vote margin compared to the one-vote margin of turning out a low propensity vorer. But Democrats should make this appeal without embracing his tone or worst positions. I think that Trump's core supporters are probably unreachable. Don't know what group you fall in. But the civility of your posts gives me hope.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans have held this seat continuously since they won it back in 1979, 38 years ago, at the midterm of Jimmy Carter's Presidency.

During that time, GA-06 has produced a Republican Speaker of the House (Newt Gingrich), the senior and currently-serving U.S. Senator from Georgia (Johnny Isakson), and the currently-serving Secretary of Health and Human Services (Tom Price). Calling it a Republican bastion is an understatement.

A 30-year-old political newcomer who's never held elected office nearly broke this streak *without the need for a runoff*. 

The Orange One's political toxicity made that possible.

The Republican Party can try to spin this any way they want. But if they're not concerned, they're deluded or foolish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have to overcome the unfair playing field first, then make it fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly has he won?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, except I think turnout was actually quite high for a special election. Also, I don't think Trump has to make a huge blunder. Who knows where the election interference investigation will be at that point? Maybe we'll even have indictments of people like Carter Page, Paul Manafort, or Mike Flynn?  Hell, maybe Price himself will be indicted on his alleged insider trading? There're so many possibilities for what can happen in 60 days.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Updated results and some thoughts based on the running total:


------------

Total Democratic Votes: 92,229      | 49.06%


Total Republican Votes: 95,571	| 50.84%


Total Unaffiliated Votes: 175	| 0.09%

----

**TOTAL VOTES: 187,975**		

---------------

**Aggregate Democratic Party margin over Republican Party: -1.78%**


--------------
**Ossoff's first round margin over Handel: 28.60%**

Based on --

Jon Ossoff (Democratic) 	48.30%	90,732

Karen Handel (Republican) 	19.70%	36,944



-----------

**1)** Foremost, remember that GA-06 is Sec. Tom Price, Sen. Johnny Isakson and former Speaker Newt Gingrich's  district. **Price won it by 23.4% just 6 months ago. The 2017 PVI is R+8. The 2012 PVI was R+12.  Republicans have held this seat continuously since 1979.** 

***84 Republicans hold seats in districts as or more Republican than GA-06.***  

Let that sink in. 


The Orange One is so toxic that he's allowed a previously unknown 30-year-old Democrat, who's never held elective office, to basically erase Republican partisanship advantage in this formerly safe Republican district. *And he's still supposed to be in his honeymoon period.* It would have been nice to win today outright. But at leas now, Ossoff gets two more months of Trump's fuck-ups to run on (with Trump seizing every opportunity to nationalize the race and make a referendum on him). 

-----

**2)** It's nowhere near a foregone conclusion that Republicans will win the runoff. 

Using the projections from [this regression model](https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/handicapping-the-georgia-6-special-election/) incorporating data from 181 prior runoffs between Democrats and Republicans, we'd expect either:

***(a)*** **Runoff margin = .66 * Aggregate party margin + .22 * Top-two margin**


.66 * -1.78 + .22 * 28.6 = 5.12% -- **+5.1 D**

*or* 

***(b)*** **Runoff margin = .53 * Relative presidential margin (weighted 75:25 weighted average of 2016 and 2012 PVI) + .35 * Aggregate party margin + .19 * Top-two margin**

.53 * -10 + .35 * -1.78 +.19 * 28.6 = -0.49  -- **+.5 R**

(Subject to margins of error discussed in article). 

In other words, a slight D advantage to a true tossup. Not bad. I'll take those odds in what should be a safe, noncompetitive Republican seat. 

------
**3)** Let Republicans believe that the deal is sealed and that this dramatic 20+ point Democratic swing means nothing for 2018. They're more likely to be blindsided by the wave when it hits. 





  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrat Jon Ossoff faces runoff after falling short of winning outright a Ga. House seat held by GOP since 1979 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Updated results and some thoughts based on the running total:


------------

Total Democratic Votes: 92,229      | 49.06%


Total Republican Votes: 95,571	| 50.84%


Total Unaffiliated Votes: 175	| 0.09%

----

**TOTAL VOTES: 187,975**		

---------------

**Aggregate Democratic Party margin over Republican Party: -1.78%**


--------------
**Ossoff's first round margin over Handel: 28.60%**

Based on --

Jon Ossoff (Democratic) 	48.30%	90,732

Karen Handel (Republican) 	19.70%	36,944



-----------

**1)** Foremost, remember that GA-06 is Sec. Tom Price, Sen. Johnny Isakson and former Speaker Newt Gingrich's  district. **Price won it by 23.4% just 6 months ago. The 2017 PVI is R+8. The 2012 PVI was R+12.  Republicans have held this seat continuously since 1979.** 

***84 Republicans hold seats in districts as or more Republican than GA-06.***  

Let that sink in. 


The Orange One is so toxic that he's allowed a previously unknown 30-year-old Democrat, who's never held elective office, to basically erase Republican partisanship advantage in this formerly safe Republican district. *And he's still supposed to be in his honeymoon period.* It would have been nice to win today outright. But at leas now, Ossoff gets two more months of Trump's fuck-ups to run on (with Trump seizing every opportunity to nationalize the race and make a referendum on him). 

-----

**2)** It's nowhere near a foregone conclusion that Republicans will win the runoff. 

Using the projections from [this regression model](https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/handicapping-the-georgia-6-special-election/) incorporating data from 181 prior runoffs between Democrats and Republicans, we'd expect either:

***(a)*** **Runoff margin = .66 * Aggregate party margin + .22 * Top-two margin**


.66 * -1.78 + .22 * 28.6 = 5.12% -- **+5.1 D**

*or* 

***(b)*** **Runoff margin = .53 * Relative presidential margin (75:25 weighted average of 2016 and 2012 PVI) + .35 * Aggregate party margin + .19 * Top-two margin**

.53 * -10 + .35 * -1.78 +.19 * 28.6 = -0.49  -- **+.5 R**

(Subject to margins of error discussed in article). 

In other words, a slight D advantage to a true tossup. Not bad. I'll take those odds in what should be a safe, noncompetitive Republican district. 

------
**3)** Let Republicans believe that the deal is sealed and that this dramatic 20+ point Democratic swing means nothing for 2018. They're more likely to be blindsided by the wave when it hits. 





    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some quick math based on the running total:

Total Democratic Votes: 73,115	| 51.12%

Total Republican Votes: 69,775	| 48.79%

Total Unaffiliated Votes: 134	| 0.09%

----

**TOTAL VOTES: 143,024**	
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you say so. Hopefully Congressional Republicans will be equally self-assured. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that people wanted to have something tangible to point to today, but this is an excellent result even if Ossoff ultimately falls just short of 50%. 

Ossoff is running ahead of Clinton in Fulton, DeKalb and Cobb counties (Clinton lost the district to Trump by 1.5%), and he's erased Tom Price's 23.4% margin over Rodney Stooksbury to make the runoff in this formerly safe Republican seat into a true tossup. 

There are 84 districts held by Republicans that are equally or less R-leaning than GA-06, based on [2017 PVI](http://cookpolitical.com/file/Arranged_by_PVI_rank.pdf). Democrats need to win just 24 of them (28.6%) for control of the House. 

If the GOP is holding on by the fingernails in GA-06 when November 2018 comes around, the House and possibly even the Senate will be long gone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Federalist Papers are a good place to look, as are the minutes of the actual floor debates on July 17, 19, and 25, 1787, when it came up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anger Isn't Enough, So the #Resistance Is Weaponizing Data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a huge proponent of the 20-point swing. But I'm also not making that number up. A 20-point shift is approximately what it would take to unseat someone running just slightly less strongly than Price in GA-06. 

Keep in mind that it would only take about 7-8% of the electorate to switch sides plus a 5-6% enthusiasm gap to produce a 20-point swing.  

Remember that, prior to the Comey letter, [Democrats had been up in the generic congressional ballot](http://dyn.realclearpolitics.com/epolls/other/2016_generic_congressional_vote-5279.html) by about 3.7 points according to the RCP average. They ended up by .6 after leading it all year--sometimes by up to 5-6 points. 

The GOP ended up winning the House popular vote by about 1.1%, basically at the nadir of the post-Comey swing. 

Now that temporary effect has worn off. So we might expect a return to more or less the baseline. 

Starting from there, add [Trump's historic unpopularity](https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/trump-is-beating-previous-presidents-at-being-unpopular/) and cloud of illegitimacy, and then pile the GOP Congress' inability to govern on top of that. When you do this, it's not so hard to see how you could get a 1994 or 2010 style midterm wave--or possibly something even greater.

There are fairly recent examples of a large swing that Trump could outdo under the right environment. 

For instance, in 2004, Republicans had won the popular vote for the House by 49.40% to the Democrats' 46.80%an R +2.6 margin. In that same election, Bush won 50.7% of the popular vote to Kerry's 48.8% (the only time in the last 7 Presidential elections that Republicans managed to win the popular vote). Post-election, Bush's approval stood at 55%. Anti-gay marriage initiatives passed in several states and were cited as a factor in his victory. Karl Rove was talking about a permanent Republican majority. (These were much stronger starting positions than Trump enjoyed immediately following his surprise Kremlin- and Comey-assisted victory.)

Yet, just two years later, in 2006, Democrats won the House popular vote by 52.30% (+5.5%) to 44.30% (-5.1%)a D +8.0 margin. **This is a 10.6% net swing.** At the time, Bush dropped to 38% approvaljust a bit lower than where Trump's average currently stands... during his honeymoon, right after its recent post-Syria-bombing rebound. 

Maybe we won't see a full 20-point swing.  And Democrats certainly don't need that large of a swing just to take control in 2018. But it wouldn't be the strangest thing if we did see it because of the uniquely anti-Trump/anti-GOP environment that this midterm may well present.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For one, there's incumbency. Tom Price won this seat 6 times. That's good for a few points at least. Then you have people's expectations. Given the gap between Price and Trump, there must have been a lot of ticket-splitting by people who voted for Clinton expecting her to win (and not wanting Trump) but presumably wanting a Republican to act as a check on her power.

Many of those people may now vote for a Democrat to check Trump's power. And they're super important, because by switching allegiances they create a 2-vote margin (they take one vote away from the Republican and give one vote to the Democrat). Because of this, Red to Blue defections are twice as powerful as turning out a new Democratic voter or a discouraged Republican voter staying home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At a certain point, money has a diminishing marginal effect. So even if most of the money is coming from the outside, it can only move voters so much. 

Of course, I have no problem with Republicans thinking this is an outside money story. That just increases the chances of them being blindsided by the wave.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Price won his seat **61.7% to  38.3%a 23.4% R margin**. Trump carried the district **48.3% to 46.8%a 1.5% R margin**. According to the [recently released 2017 Cook PVI](http://cookpolitical.com/file/Arranged_by_PVI_rank.pdf), **GA-06 is R+8**, meaning the **GA-06 is 8 points more Republican than the country as a whole**.  

To give some idea of the significance of flipping this seat, by my count, **there are 84 seats held by a Republican in districts that are as or less Republican than GA-06 by PVI**. 

Alternatively, if you go by vote margin, and assume that there's a **+20 to +25 uniform shift toward Democrats from the 2016 election results** (which is what occurred in KS-04 and about what would be necessary for Ossoff to make up Price's margin), here are some simple projections of what the House might look like on the [**high**](https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://img.washingtonpost.com/news/politics/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2017/04/2016_2_Houseb.jpg w=480) (**+105 Democratic seats**) and [**low**](https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://img.washingtonpost.com/news/politics/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2017/04/2016_3_TC.jpg w=480) (**+72 Democratic seats**) end of this swing range. 

Thus, Ossoff flipping GA-06 could be the forerunner to a huge anti-GOP wave in 2018. And fear of that wave would likely start changing Republican behavior right now. So the importance of winning this seat can't be overstated.

People forget [how bad midterms can be for the President's Party](http://www.centerforpolitics.org/crystalball/content/images/KDK2017033001-table1.png).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just loaded fine for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the framers of the constitution put the electoral college in for a reason.

Yeah, to protect the political power of slaveholders in relatively populous southern states without needing to expand the franchise to blacks or to whites without land. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be interesting to see how Trump's base will respond once (if) Breitbart becomes more critical and Bannon is potentially ousted. Will they stay home or will they primary GOP incumbents and remain engaged? It's pretty early in Trump's presidency for this kind of civil war within the GOP. But here we are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think anything more than a 45% will be interpreted pretty positively.  If Ossoff can pull out an outright majority, it would be impressive. I'm hoping that Trump's attempts to nationalize the race backfire and accomplish just that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breitbart and Trump relationship: it's complicated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL:DR

People are pissed and running in a midterm as a member of an unpopular President's party is hard. Even the unfavorable Senate map may not prevent the GOP carnage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Georgia special election is the least of the GOPs worries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their vote would absolutely have mattered. It would have mattered equally and proportionally to every vote cast in the election. In fact, the votes of Republicans in Blue States and Democrats in Red States would suddenly matter a great deal instead of having their entire effect wasted by the winner-take-all rule if a plurality of even just one more person statewide voted for the candidate who they opposed.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how the NPV Compact is doing anything improper. It can't and wouldn't replace the Electoral College without a constitutional amendment. States essentially have plenary authority under the Constitution to choose the method of appointing Presidential electors. The NPV Compact would just implement a coordinated change to the winner-take-all rulewhich states may want to replace, but cannot abolish individually without putting themselves at a disadvantage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting question.

I feel like we'll be at the point soon where many local and regional government processes may be able to be automated. Take filling pot holes. It's tedious, but (nearly) everyone agrees it should be done.
 
Assuming the necessary funds are there, it might make sense to put an AI in charge of identifying potholes, prioritizing them using various criteria (such as the potential to cause damage or disrupt traffic), scheduling repairs, dispatching repair drones and optimizing their routes, monitoring and re-ordering supplies, etc. Although humans are capable of doing each of these individual steps, we're not good at doing all of them together, in real time, using all the data available (*e.g.*, supply prices, traffic patterns, etc).  

Once people got comfortable with AI performing routine tasks like pothole-filling, they might be more open to it performing more critical tasks. This would be an iterative, bottom-up way to deploy AI. Consent could be obtained by having the AI itself run in the election (for maximum transparency, the platform could be the initial source code). Alternatively, we could elect a person to implement, maintain, and oversee the AI (this is probably makes more sense for  specialized, non-general AI).

After an AI were in place for a while and had been managing a process well, one could have a referendum to permanently automate it and transfer oversight authority to some higher bodylike a city mayor or planner, a county or city council, or a new public authority created specifically for the purpose of managing and overseeing automated government processes. As general AI gets more sophisticated and potentially even capable of recursive self-improvement, the management of automated government processes could be handed off to this second tier of AI using similar steps (*i.e.*, election of a human overseer or the AI itself). 




  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's one exit poll consortium. CNN's website has them. Google "exit polls 2016 cnn" and you should find it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're correct that, in certain instances, you can owe negative taxes and get money back via a refundable credit even if you didn't pay/owe any federal income taxes. The most notable instance of this is the Earned Income Tax Credit, or EITC. You're also correct that there's no formal citizenship requirement for this credit (but that's normal, since legal permanent residents can get tax-funded public benefits that they also pay into.)

However, you *do* have to have a valid SSN in order to claim the EITC's refundable credit. Specifically, ff you pay federal taxes via an individual tax ID number, or ITIN, you aren't eligible for the credit. You also apparently cannot get the credit by filing or refiling your taxes retroactively after obtaining a valid SSN. 

Do you have any evidence that undocumented immigrants are benefiting from refundable tax credits like the EITC? Or were you reasoning to that conclusion by combining the premises that (1) refundable tax credits exist and (2) many unauthorized immigrants pay federal income taxes?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who don't know, unauthorized immigrants and others who are not eligible for a Social Security Number can obtain an [individual tax ID number (ITIN)](https://www.irs.gov/individuals/individual-taxpayer-identification-number-itin) to pay federal taxes. There are other ways they pay as well, such as by paying into expired or invalid SSNs, or SSNs not authorized for work. In any event, they can't draw the benefits (like disability or college loans) even if they paid taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Im an undocumented immigrant. I pay my taxes every year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at the plain meaning of a statute is a starting point. But it shouldn't be where the analysis ends, particularly when hyper-literalism produces an absurd result or there's ambiguity that can be resolved by looking at how a term is used in the overall statutory scheme and other indicia of legislative intent.

From the article:

Gorsuch's obsession with wording and the "plain text" of laws has led many to note his similarities with the man he is replacing, the late Justice Antonin Scalia.

Scalia was known for his adherence to textualism - a manner of interpreting laws in accordance with their plain text, rather than by assuming or inferring the intent of lawmakers, or the potential consequences of the laws' implementation.

While many of Gorsuch's rulings show he too is a clear adherent to textualism, perhaps nowhere is his dedication to unearthing the meaning of a law as "the words on the paper say" more noticeable than in one 2015 decision in which he used "plain old grade school grammar" to determine the legal penalties imposed on defendants accused of using a firearm "during and in relation to any crime of violence or drug trafficking crime."

In that 2015 decision, Gorsuch was ruling on a case in which prosecutors were attempting to charge a defendant, Philbert Rentz, with two violations for allegedly firing a gun once. Prosecutors argued that since a single shot hit and injured one person, then struck and killed another, two separate "crimes of violence" had been committed and should be penalized accordingly.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Supreme Court picks first question on the bench shows his similarity to Antonin Scalia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The era of strategic patience has ended; the era of impulsive haste has begun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trumps impulsive problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... Donald Trump appears to have made a cynical calculation that he will not pay a high political price for being the most secretive president since Richard Nixon.

All the leaks about infighting among senior staff and the presidents proclivity for tweeting have created a false sense that the public knows what is happening inside his White House. In fact, the administration has gone to great lengths to conceal pertinent information from the American people.

After dodging questions on the subject for weeks, the administration waited until the afternoon of Good Friday to dump the news that it will not follow former president Barack Obama's policy of voluntarily disclosing the names of most visitors to the White House complex. The presidents communications director cited grave national security risks as a justification, even though Obama had made an exception for national security.

Then on Easter, Trump lashed out at the tens of thousands of protesters who marched in dozens of cities on Saturday to demand that he release his tax returns. ...

Despite constantly ripping Hillary Clinton for being secretive, Trump was consistently less transparent during the campaign. ...

Trump seems to feel that the results in November validated this obfuscation, and that takeaway has emboldened him to continue the same approach as much as possible.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does Trump have to hide? Secretive White House unapologetic about clawing back transparency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're saying that the apparatus to initiate fusion would be trivial for someone with Lithium 6 and Deuterium (or Lithium-Deuteride in the proper proportion). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Cuban Missile Crisis in Slow Motion in North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe China or Russia shared nuclear technology with NK. But it seems unlikely that they'd give them material assistance with an H-Bomb, such as sharing an actual functional design. If NK ultimately uses a thermonuclear weapon, whatever the context, they wouldn't want their fingerprints on it, because someone might hold them vicaeioualy responsible for NK's actions. Obtaining a design through espionage is also a possibility, but NK seems to isolated to successfully pull it off. I'm just speculating with this last point though. Maybe they could get their hands on a Chinese design or buy someone off in the US and Russia. They've been known to counterfeit $100 dollar bills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can probably miniturize a warhead to fit on a missile. But it's important to understand that it would likely be, *at most*, a boosted fission weapon with a max yield in the 60kt range. More likely, they can weaponize something in the 10kt range. That's about 1 Hiroshima bomb. Such an attack could kill 100,000-200,000+ people if launched at a densely-populated area. But it doesn't pose an existential threat to the US, Japan, or South Korea.

For comparison's sake, consider that each U.S. [*Ohio*-class ballistic missile sub](http://www.fas.org/nuke/guide/usa/slbm/ssbn-726.htm) can carry up to 24 Trident II missiles, all of which can be launched in less than a minute.  On depressed trajectories from about 1150 miles at sea, these missiles would reach NK in 7 minutes or so. So if a single *Ohio* were to unload on NK (not that this would necessarily be the retaliatory approach chosen), it could blanket NK with 336 independently targetable warheads (160 by treaty) for a total explosive power of 159.6 (63.4 treaty) megatons of TNT. For comparison, during *all of WW2* (1939-1945) the Allies collectively dropped a total of approximately 3.4 million tons (3.4 megatons) of bombsincluding the two nuclear bombings of Hiroshima and Nagasaki. 

So in 8 minutes, a single sub could unleash anywhere between *about 18.5 and 47 times the destructive power of the entire WW2 Allied bombing campaign* on an area slightly larger than Pennsylvania. 

And the U.S. has 14 of these subs.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's some sophistication to it, including in how radiation pressure is used to ignite and efficiently consume the fusion-fission secondary before the structure is blown apart by the primary as well as the building secondary explosionwhich can fizzle if everything's not right. Then, you have to miniaturize the physics package and ensure that it can cope with the forces it will be subjected to during its flight and re-entry before you can have a missile-deliverable weapon. 

NK may be able to pull it off eventually. After all, they don't have to prove that these weapons are viable, just develop and build a design that solves the practical problems (once they become fully aware of those problems). But my understanding is that it's currently beyond their technology. In fact, it's not even confirmed that Israel, India, or Pakistanfar more technologically advanced counties than NKactually have hydrogen bombs, and it's considered implausible that they might not. That's not to say that any of these counties couldn't develop an H-bomb, but it would require additional testing to troubleshoot the kinks.             </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 10:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article you cited states that, with the modifications, the NK test site itself *could withstand* up to a 282kt detonation. But it didn't say that the 6th test would actually produce this yield. My understanding is that NK likely couldn't get up into the ~300kt range without a Teller-Ulam fission-fusion-fission bomb. My further understanding is that they can probably weaponize a 10kt fission bomb, or possibly a [boosted fission bomb](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Boosted_fission_weapon) in the 30-60kt range. Yet, they still lack the ability to build a *true* thermonuclear weapon capable of scaling abritrarily from hundreds of kilotons into the megaton range.

So, based on what we know, with the throw weight and volume that NK has to work with in a KN-14 ICBM, they might *conceivably* be able to develop a 60kt fission bomb and put it in a blunt re-entry vehicle that would be slow and vulnerable to interception by the the two final layers of the US ABM system (*i.e.*, GBI, THAAD, Pac-3).      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A small [sampling](http://www.slate.com/blogs/the_slatest/2016/12/14/a_look_back_at_trump_adviser_stephen_miller_s_college_writing_career.html) of Miller's views on women's issues.

**On feminism and closing the pay gap:**

 What feminists don't realize is that bosses simply want to run a successful business. They will reward and promote whichever employees are doing the best job. If John sells more than Jill, he gets promoted; if Jill sells more than John, she gets promoted. That is the simple beauty of the free market. ([Sorry Feminists](http://www.dukechronicle.com/article/2005/11/sorry-feminists), Nov. 22, 2005)

 It's vital to keep in mind what it would actually mean for women if we were to close the pay gap. For many, it would mean giving up a noble career in social working or putting in 50- and 60-hour work weeks and not being able to spend time with the family. It would mean trading in jobs like housekeeping for night shifts doing road repairs; it would mean giving up the joy of being home during your child's first years of life. (Ibid)

 It's not chauvinism. It's chivalry. (Ibid) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of these costs are per trip. So we should multiply it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ####President Trump's trips to Mar-A-Lago

 Total cost for security in Palm Beach: $3.7 million

 Roundtrip flights from Joint Base Andrews, Maryland to West Palm, Florida: $700,000

 Overtime for local law enforcement during Trumps trips: $60,000/day

 Total golf cart rentals ordered by the Secret Service "for POTUS visit": $35,185

 Loss to business due to airport closure: -$30,000/weekend

----

####Keeping the first family in Trump Towers

 Request for additional Secret Service funding to secure Trump Towers: $60 million

 New York Police Department security costs: $127,000-$146,000/day

 "Elevator services" ordered by the Secret Service: $64,000

 Air Force One flights to New York City: $180,000/hour

----


####The Trump children's trips around the world with Secret Service

 Eric Trumps hotel costs in Uruguay: $97,830

 Eric Trumps hotel costs in the U.K. this week: $11,261

 Eric Trumps limousine services in Dublin: $4,029.85

 Rental ski equipment and clothing for secret service during Ivanka Trump's trip to Aspen: $12,208

 Donald Trump Jr., Eric Trump and Tiffany Trumps hotel costs in Vancouver: $53,155

 Donald Trump Jr. and Eric Trumps hotel costs in $16,738

----


The provided costs don't even include airfare rates for Secret Service agents taking each trek with the Trumps, nor does it include the data on those agents salaries and other expenditures taxpayers may be footing the bill for. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breaking Down All of the Trump Family's Travel Costs and Lavish Expenditures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They saw the Faith Militant beating up gays, dragging sinners through the streets for public humiliation and were like"yes, please!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For any current Trump position, there exists an earlier Trump tweet (or statement in the public record) directly contradicting it.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said, the situation is *already* being portrayed in symbols and stereotypesnamely, of Comey as a call-it-as-I-see-it good guy whose fierce independence is misunderstood as partisanship by the people harmed by his decisions. This is the public image Comey has cultivated of himself. I'm merely providing an alternative that's more apt.

If you read what I've written or cited on Comey, you'll see that my criticism of him is based on what he's said and done, not on generic prejudgments:


https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5ayble/z/d9kctvb

https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/656x3r/z/dg8z7sa

http://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/629qt4/fbi_director_james_comey_tried_to_reveal_russian_tampering_months_before_el/dfkz9ci?context=3

It's not just my assessment that he's "[unapologetic and obdurately self-assured](http://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2016/09/james-comey-fbi-accountability-214234)."   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Dunning-Kruger plus projection of the same state of ignorance onto others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunning-Kruger + Projection:

It is what we might call the consensus judgment that President Trump is a deeply ignorant man and perhaps a profoundly ignorant President. But it is worth stepping back and considering just what this means, the different kinds of ignorance that exist and how they differ.

...

**What is both ... terrifying and hilarious about Trump is not simply his ignorance, really his militant ignorance, but his complete lack of self-awareness about his ignorance.** Trump told a reporter for The Wall Street Journal that his understanding of the problem of North Korea changed dramatically after hearing ten minutes of history from the President of China. Needless to say, Trump didnt need to admit this. But neither was it candor.

So far the Trump Presidency has been a sort of Mr Magoo performance art in which the comically ignorant Trump learns elemental or basic things that virtually everyone in the world of politics or government already knew  things that the majority of adults probably know. Health Care: Nobody knew health care could be so complicated. North Korea: I felt pretty strongly that they had tremendous power. But its not what you think. There are perhaps half a dozen examples equally stark.

...

**What is key though is to understand that this is not just ignorance. Ignorance is just the first stage of Trumps fairly advanced problem. He is not only ignorant but clearly unaware of his level of ignorance. This is compounded by a seeming inability to understand that everyone elses isnt equally ignorant to him.** Those of us who are parents know the wonder of discovery experienced by small children. They find out there were things such as dinosaurs or close primate relatives called lemurs. As loving parents we indulge them, sometimes feigning ignorance of things we actually already knew to support a childs joy in discovery.

But Donald Trump is a 70 year old man. And not a terribly nice man.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump and The Problem of Militant Ignorance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
