<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4091</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if rt or not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metal gear! Cinematic hideo + 3d is the shite. tho i must admit, i turn the 3D off sometimes when aiming for a distant mob but that just promotes a further immersion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandma did this after my grandpa had died. Her health wasn't going so good then so it seemed logical to her. Funny enough, her health dramatically got better after that.

She'll hit 90 this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you and your roommate on a date now? Update pls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Turbo whistle gone"

I love this topic but i wonder if i can move the conversation just on optimism alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of the time this family hired a mascot for their son's birthday. The kids beat the shit out of the mascot. Funny as hell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/bettereveryloop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your turn north korea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i get you. Tho its the same reason why i liked this photo--makes a good reference for drawing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man! Really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this so accurate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ill keep that in mind. I believe the ideal boost for the stock turbo on this one should be 12-17 psi. At what pressure should i test it?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does rotate. I'll try to test the wastegate when i see the truck again in 2 weeks.

We're also considering changing to a better kit if the turbo is faulty.

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got the pic from google to show the model. Unfortunately, i wont see the truck for 2 more weeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not actual photo. The truck it's in(a hummer replica that we built), is at my hometown rn 400km away from here unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think she's really pretty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are not fragile at all. You can step on it and they'd still survive

Fun fact #1: these plants are called "makahiya" in the philippines. It literally means shy plant.

Fun fact #2: you can carefully remove the branch and it would still react to touch.

Source: i grew up near a cornfield where these plants would sprout randomly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's that damned bot when you need it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Problem with turbo? Whistling sound on the Isuzu 4JG2 3.1L Turbo Diesel engine's turbo seem to have disappeared. Slightly noticeable power loss. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not this specie in particular but some shipworms--the ones that consume plants/wood instead of bacteria fart, are actually quite good. Especially with a good sauce or a simple spicy vinegar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're good with vinegar. Spicy vinegar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit.

^was my actual reaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im also preparing for a PFT(for sf) and this is how im going about it.

I know youre only asking about situps but since there's plenty of answers already, i'll talk about the entire fitness test.

Train every other day AT LEAST since you have very short time to prepare.

Increase your situps by 4-5 counts each time.

Focus your energy on the going UP part and try not to slowly go down but not too fast that you'll lose the momentum. This way you'll conserve energy.

Go beyond the passing count

Im guessing there's a series of tests; running, push up, sit ups, pullups(prolly not this one). Train your body imitating the ORDER of which the tests are gonna go. This will give your body an optimal muscle memory.

Lastly, and this significantly improved my training. Watch your DIET. If you're used to eating a lot, that's okay. No need to decrease the amount since youre used to it already anyway but try not to ingest too much fatty food. Substitute this with something like apple which is a great source of carbs-helps with endurance.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pyongyang is now trying to deduce who this employee with a geology major on that specific job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Factorial is good for calculating odds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My beautiful dark twisted fantasy. Do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking knew it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! Youre on a lost now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had been through something similar. In fact im still going through it right now. 2 years ago i applied for a fashion degree in london at one of the-if not the best fashion uni in the world. Through out the process my family was very supportive. When i finally got in, they basically just stopped supporting. I don't know if they thought i wouldnt get in or something but it was just so unfair. I already poured in all of my savings to it, through the application, housing, tuition fee deposit, all because i believed they would help me. Then suddenly they wont. Why did they have to wait till it's very late?

It was my dream and to me it was the greatest achievement ive ever got and for it to be shattered... They even went so far as to dismiss it as if it was nothing.

It feels like death, maybe even worse--to have a dream snagged off of you like that. Its been 2 years and I still cant get over it. Anything i do comes second rate. Ive lost my sense of purpose for a while.

Every family gathering/meeting has been difficult for me. I have had terrible anxiety attacks(i hope it doesnt happen to you). Im only getting back up lately and im trying so hard to work so that one day i can go to that uni, preferably without my family's help.

Ive avoided some of my friends for a while out of embarrassment. I shouldnt have. They were the ones that gave me strenght to get over it somehow. Talk to your friends, maybe talk to your husband about it as well.

As for your mother and sister, i hope they would just admit to it. It may not give you closure but maybe it would help in the process.

Ill stop here for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classic Theresa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 09:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm.

Source: am dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get it but if you followed the sub, youll know that the reason they made it so big was to grab attention for the game itself; perhaps to invite.

However the osu's ugliness is beyond reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprise her too by buying similar tickets!... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you the past-us? This used to be a secret too! Giggled every time she goes "xoxo"

Bonus: gf kinda looks like leighton meester!
Gg i fucking love her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
