<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4592</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UCAR praises passage of Weather Research and Innovation Act </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UCAR PRAISES PASSAGE OF WEATHER RESEARCH AND FORECASTING INNOVATION ACT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question: Was Trumps budget already approved? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea, but it's not going to happen. Last few updates and expansions have clearly show that Paradox wants to railroad the game rather than give players more freedom.

The ages system, lifted from Civ, is clear example of that, numerous buffs to Ottomans, France, Spain and others are another.

This event while historically accurate could change the course of history in one click and thus I don't think it's going to happen.

But I would download shit out of mod implementing it, and I would pay for DLC with it as a feature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you know Trumps presidency might be such a clusterfuck that, along with ruining image of USA for decades and causing massive damage in other areas, it might even drain the swamp! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Winds of Winter are in bookshops RIGHT NOOOW!!!!!

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans really stepped into a steaming pile of shit by letting DT become president. Can't say I feel sorry for them.
But I do feel sorry for America.

Well, I guess that it will at very least get people to voting boots in 2018, so I still have that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean there are people who thought New York billionaire is going to be corruption proof candidate so I think that there are people willing to believe literally everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *If you rearrange the letters of word Sith it gives you a different word... Tshi which is Chinese for Disappointed in the cooking of the duck meat.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOW DARE THEY! /s

Seriously good job Israel, you are better than almost all other middle eastern countries when it comes to human rights.
Well probably all of them but, I don't want to make absolute statements. 

I'm no Sith.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be careful so you don't get banned people. Mods are really afraid of hate speech for some reason.

And BTW it's hate speech even if you write something like:

I wonder who were these young men. I really don't want to jump to conclusions but...

So be careful not to hurt anyones feelings. We all know those matter more than someones teeth. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, what ethnicity, religion or nationality I refered to?
And what kind of hate are you talking about?

I want clarification on that, because if you think this is hate speech you should probably visit some specialist, linguist or English teacher preferably.

Btw: I want the comment restored and I insist on my innocence until you show me what rules I broke and in what way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purge the Xenos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, especially when things got violent beforehand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if he speaks ex cathedra and has almost universal agreement from clergy, otherwise it be turned over when the next Pope comes along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, copyright laws are one of few things I envy Americans. Sure they got extended for longer periods of time recently. But I would take their approach over ours any day.

Edit: To clarify, I worked in publishing industry in central Europe for a while. So I did get in contact with local copyright laws and agencies that enforce them, and it isn't pretty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that it doesn't change much. Seriously, change for sake of change is bane of efficiency.

I get that they called it 4.7 for marketing purposes and that it might confuse some people, but stability beats feature creep any day.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe disgruntled former lovers? Just saying it could be a possibility, although unlikely one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you have no reason to trust me but I have to tell you this:
I WANT integration to work, I want to believe that all cultures are equal and that different religions don't lead to people behaving in different, possibly violent ways. But time and time again I see evidence to contrary, and when there are barely weeks between individual terror attacks and days between incidents like these I can no longer deny the facts.

Sorry I came off as racist, I will try to omit race in my posts in the future, oh wait, I never mentioned anyones race.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 12:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the problem is what people consider a "bad behavior".
I know many people who are not racist and say illegal instead of undocumented immigrants, and yet there are those who would put them in same bag as KKK or Donald Trump.

And there are certainly people who just use anti-PC as a way to be as racist as possible, and these people should be called out on it.
But the moment when you start castigating people for calling someone disabled instead of differently-abled you are no longer in the same ballpark.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 11:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leaving Catholicism de jure is very, very hard. In a way it is impossible, even the worst heresiarch is still Catholic and can return to right path if he really wants to.

The excommunication means that he can no longer take part of Church activities and is no longer de facto priest, but he is still Catholic and excommunication can be lifted.

That being said, he can not attend mass or act as a priest in any way so for laymen purposes he is no longer Catholic, but by the church law he still is, he just "strayed". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder who were these young men. I really don't want to jump to conclusions but... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Handmaids tale, Americans talk about it Malaysians live it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The studio should shut down and all people involved should get their mental health checked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. The animation is just part of it. The writing is bad, like young adult novel bad, voice acting sucks and the game glitches all over the place.

Finally there is just one multiplayer mode, the horde mode. Nothing else just bunch of microtransactions.

Take a look at this video and ask yourself if you really want to waste your money on this: 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7KWkao73HuU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I appreciate your effort and your apology is accepted.
Again thank you very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem with Marvels particular brand of diversity is that it feels forced and like if someone was ticking boxes on a form.

For example Miles Morales, good story, an interesting character, but the announcement of new Spiderman was overshadowed by how forced it felt.

It felt like bunch of suits sat around a table and said: "We need minorities in comic books. Lets make new Spiderman black. And you know what, lets make him gay too, I bet that will get us the queer readers, everyone knows they just read about gay people."
And then another one said: "You know, our readers are mostly liberal. I heard that liberals like mexicans now. Lets make him Hispanic too!"

It felt forced and for many people it was incredible turn off that made them shy away from entire series.

And even though it was good the stain remained.
 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well did have a banner for London and there were fewer victims. 
I think we had one for Paris, Nice and Brussels, why not Petersburg?

Plus that ribbon is really tiny and it doesn't say what it's for. All I know it can be still for London.

It just feels like, I don't know, those Russians are not important enough to have a banner. Or that those little hearts from /r/place are more important than eleven dead people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what exactly does this law do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are those real courses? omg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks stranger, always happy to learn more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could we get header in honor of victims of recent St. Petersburg terror attack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get your shit together Sweden, you used to be cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have capitalism and universal health care in Czech Republic, the same goes for almost entire Europe and almost entire developed world.

It's just that Americans decided that government is satan so they don't want to give it money to save their lives. And american politicians turned that into policy. If you Americans trusted you government a little bit more you would have healthcare like rest of the developed world does.

But instead you vilify the very institutions that ensure your lives and safety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking clickbait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, the problem is that in this case it seems to me like an easy excuse rather than real reason.

As for those asking if these things are real. Yes they are, and not just in China. Along with sterilizations they are classic tool of authoritarian regimes, I speak from second hand experience in this case (I'm a man) but I know that it used to happen in my country (Central Europe) just few decades back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here lies the problem. Some argue that it's hard to draw a line at some date. The argument that women have right to choose if they want to have the baby or not can be made one or eight months into pregnancy. There are some who suggest that there should be no time limit on when you can terminate the pregnancy.

Now it is a fringe argument, but it was made. Another problem is where should the line be drawn and if there are any real reasons to think that it should be allowed 24 weeks in and not 25 weeks in.

The earliest viable birth was 22 weeks in pregnancy, so technically the limit could be put further back. In Europe most countries allow abortion on demand only during first trimester (12 weeks of pregnancy) and allow abortion later only for serious reasons.

So in a way Americans have de jure looser laws about abortion than Europeans already. On the other hand the access to health care is much, much better in Europe. I would be death if I lived in USA for example, or at least in debt and homeless. 

On the gripping hand, the entire debate is extremely heated and irrational, because one of few things all humans agree on is that killing babies is wrong. And when you define fetus as a baby then you can hardly argue for someones right to kill it. And if you see fetus as collection of cells you can hardly understand position of those who would want to preserve it at all costs.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once in a while, Trumps policy I can support.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KNOWLEDGE MAKES YOU RACIST! 

Now everyone repeat: War is peace. Freedom is slavery. Ignorance is strength.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was depressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you like to "play", other campers are not so good for "games". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Red dwarf, smegheads? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since it involves time travel apparently...

Let's not get our hopes up and expect Mark Watney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The money part is very difficult to capture, as for alone, you can have alliance with king of France or Emperor of Byzantium in just few clicks.

And, even better, they will help you in war, unlike in real life when they couldn't be bothered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the flag is almost gone now so.

Yeah... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck those Luddites.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 07:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's very similar to arrangement in other multi religious areas at the time. From Spain to Persia, the system was generally set up favoring the ruling religious class while granting certain autonomy to religious majority in return for obedience.

In fact similar setup was later used by Ottoman empire, Muslims ruled and were favored, but frequently delegated power to Christians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea, but it would require a lot of possibly faulty mechanisms and we simply can't afford that when survival of species is at stake.

I say: keep it as simple as possible, fewer things can go wrong the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long Now foundation does some work but in very specific area like clocks and languages.


The good thing is that most conceivable cataclysms, even large scale nuclear war for example, leave at least some industrial capacity intact. 

Just by virtue of all nuclear powers being on northern hemisphere the southern hemisphere should survive relatively unscathed. They would have to endure a nuclear winter, but their cities and factories would be spared the blasts.

The catastrophic climate change is even better in way, because its effects would not be so harsh for industrialized, modern nations.
Thus possible recovery would be easier.

One way or another we should make reserves and have some sort of plan B in case our first attempt at world civilization does not work out.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know about them, that's what inspired me actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People often assume that medieval Europe was primitive. But in reality the upper echelons had access to much of the same things that late romans did. Especially in western and southern Europe.

Cyphers, basis of espionage, banking and accounting all of it was there along with centuries of experience with diplomacy and subterfuge. King Phillip IV actually had a guy very skilled in those things.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Guillaume_de_Nogaret

Nogaret was, in CK2 terms, lowborn and yet he became one of most important people in medieval France. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one really did much of a research in that regard.

We know how it happened in history but how would it work if we got hit by comet or nuked ourselves to oblivion, I don't know.

What I do know is that if shit hits the fan we probably won't have access to computers. Or that we shouldn't count on it.

So if I would make some sort of doomsday Vault it would have to be pretty lowtech, with lots of resources like metals, fuel and polymers so that civilization can get a head start.

For example, right now a metric ton of copper costs 5848 USD, lets we would buy about 500 000 USD worth of it, that's roughly 85 tonns for price of 7 Teslas model S.

That's not so bad for a supply that could prop up a town or two.

Same goes for steel, iron, nickle, tin, pretty much all basic industrial metals, seriously storing them in case something goes wrong might not be a bad idea.

As for the knowledge itself. Unless we get very, very unlucky, some people will still be able to read, at least for a generation or two.
So if you write it down in all the world languages you have pretty good chance of them being able to understand it.

But it should be resilient, rock preferably or ceramics, not paper or something else that can mold or burn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe this show is why my cousin started studying history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the very fact they superseded nations and kingdoms led to their downfall. 

Shame really, compared to other organisations at the time they were pretty progressive and meritocratic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but we should cover as many possibilities as we can.
We owe it to our children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be preserved. Otherwise we are at mercy of fate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be right thing to do. No legitimate country can leave it's territory and citizens at mercy of a foreign power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, stone doesn't care about electricity and can withstand punishment far greater than circuit boards.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know about them. That's why I recommended the discs. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or ,as I already said, a plant that produces oil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were not enthusiastic about it, but most of them were Christians anyway. The area got Islamized in last few centuries, before that it looked like Lebanon or Smyrna looked in 1800s.

No the biggest problem was not religion but economy, the region was not very rich back then, the trade routes could easily bypass it, and to make matters worse there was almost no support from rest of the Christendom after Crusade itself. 
Romans mostly wanted to make crusaders into their vassals, they even signed treaties and everything, Italian cities saw the holy land as source of profit and didn't hesitate to put money ahead of faith (4th crusade for example) and secular realms of western and north Europe had their wars between each other.

So only one left to actively support the crusader states was Pope, and even back then he was mostly ignored by secular rulers when it was convenient. 

So they were alone, surrounded by enemies, with no money and internal strife. To be honest it was not a situation they could win.

Unless of course the Mongols converted to Christianity, which was a real possibility for a while.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually local muslim population worked rather well with their new overlords. I think I even read about one arabian scholar who was really pissed about that.

Edit: Found him Ibn Jubay of Andalusia. Here is what he wrote about local situation

*We left Tibnin by a road running past farms where Muslims live who do very well under the Franks-may Allah preserve us from such a temptation! The regulations imposed on them are the handing over of half of the grain crop at the time of harvest and the payment of a poll tax of one dinar and seven qirats, together with a light duty on their fruit trees. The Muslims own their own houses and rule themselves in their own way. This is the way the farms and big villages are organized in Frankish territory. Many Muslims are sorely tempted to settle here when they see the far from comfortable conditions in which their brethren live in the districts under Muslim rule. Unfortunately for the Muslims, they have always reason for complaint about the injustices of their chiefs in the lands governed by their coreligionists, whereas they can have nothing but praise for the conduct of the Franks, whose justice they can always rely on.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends how much time would we have.

For example we could use genetic engineering to make a fuel crop.
Quick growing, resistant to disease and pests, that would produce plenty of oil in its seeds.
Essentially sunflowers or rape but easier to grow and more quickly reproducing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, does metallic glass count as metal in allomancy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't help, it's agents can still destroy them. I would rather give skaa something to eat so they wouldn't rebel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 14:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I would go for granite pillars engraved with all knowledge needed to restart industrial society.
Plus I would store few thousand tonnes of steel, copper, aluminum and tin beneath them in an insulated chamber so that the new civilization has a something to work with.

Bonus for thousands of ceramic disks inscribed with same text in several world languages, New Rosetta style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. I get the feeling that Rick might be the villain in this season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rick just lost it. I think that killing him is not out of the question anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 12:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure doing nothing would end ISIS in a week or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Bill and I'm Bill and together we are Bill and Bill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok let's do this, but I think we need to annex Carniola first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Gott erhalte Franz, den Kaiser,
Unsern guten Kaiser Franz!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New South Africa finance minister Gigaba calls for radical reform - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way to go Germany, this goes on you will be worse than USA when it comes to information laws.

Well you sort of already are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Run, run while you still can. Because next thing they do is shut down the borders and build fences.

They did it to us, they did it to others and they will probably do it here.

Run before you become prisoner in your own country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found this on CNN http://edition.cnn.com/interactive/2017/03/europe/isis-behind-the-mask/index.html

It's not exactly documentary but it has a lot of information about the subject with videos and such.
Does anyone know where should I post it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is an interview with ISIS fighter from Belgium so I think that it is relevant for our subreddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From altar boy to ISIS fighter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but what to do about it?

About every solution I can think of involves violence or can end with it if things go wrong.

One way or another lots of people will die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are not idiots. Only thing worse than having Britain leave EU is Britain leaving pissed, hurt and whole thing looking like a punishment.

It's like a divorce, even if your wife files for it and only she wants it, it's still no reason to act like a dick and make no compromise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we are so much better then Brits and 'Muricans right?

Fuck this shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crimea Pays a High Price for Russias Takeover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh don't worry, communists will blame USA one way or another.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Run, run before they establish work camps.

That's my advice as a guy from Czech Republic, we have experience with this kind of things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I am worried about right now is where is the EU going.
On one hand the integration might work better without UK, on the other hand the UK was one of 4 largest contributors to budget so we will have to tighten our belts.

On the gripping hand we have hostile dictator in Turkey, war in Ukraine, refugee crisis in in the Mediterranean, Putin in Kremlin, Trump White House, anti-EU parties making gains in south, separatists in Spain, very bad economic signs from Italy and Spain and to top it of Greece which is in worse shape now then it ever was.

So, to sum it up I am worried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 10:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would call this a dick move but... the context is unfitting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 10:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even British, I'm actually Czech living in Czech Republic who would vote Stay if I was British. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About million Polish citizens, massive contribution to EU budget, just two bargaining chips from top of my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not pretending anything of the sort. 

All I'm saying is that his contribution to the problem is not nearly as immense as some people try to portray it.
 I think the guy is an asshole who lived on his fathers money and wasted a lot of them, I think Russians helped him into the White House (whether he knew or not is a different issue), I think he is about as fit to be president as socks of  G. H. W. Bush.

But I do resent sensationalism, I do reject hysteria and I do not like when people twist facts just to push their view. 
I also don't like people locking themselves from other opinions.

And you know why I don't stand for those things?

Because that's what got DONALD TRUMP INTO OFFICE, sure Russians helped, sure DNC sabotaged Bernie and sure Hillary was overlooking blue collar workers. 

But real damage was done by people who remained locked in their newsfeeds, torturing facts, whipping numbers and overlooking hard truths only to pretend that America was falling apart and that only solution was to Make It Great Again.


Rant over, sorry if I came of harsh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did I dismiss Chinas and EUs contribution to stopping climate change? What I said is that it's not just up to USA and no matter what Trump does the world will go forward. 

The technology does march on, the coal will not get magically back where it was in fifties because of fewer regulation.
Unless they ban other power sources, which lets face it, is not going to happen.

And last but not least, entire world NEVER cooperates on everything and if our survival hanged on that, and it does not, we would be dead already. 

So please, don't give up, don't panic, start working on solutions and for the love of all that's good in this world don't pretend that Trump is going to end the world.

He lacks both intelligence and power to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to burst your bubble people but Trump is not going to cause Armageddon. 

Even without the rules he just scrapped the trends are set, renewables get more effective every year, technologies advance with or without his approval. 

Plus USA is not the only country in the world, EU and even China, both match or exceed America in the contribution to global warming and in research into ways to stop it. And they are very unlikely to listen to Trump.

So no, sky is not falling on our heads because of one executive order signed by an asshole in costume of a president. IT IS falling on our heads because of last century and half of pollution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends, at this rate about 1 meter is a reasonable possibility.
Mind you, it will take decades to get there.

But the flooding is not the biggest problem. See, when sea water gets in the ground it ruins the soil. So goodbye produce from low laying coastlines. 

Anyway there are about five solutions, just out of my head to take care of that. But nobody has the balls to actually start working on them.

Oh and BTW, reducing the emissions will not work anymore, we should have done that a decade or two ago, right now the house is on fire, no use to stop indoor smoking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Melawan raja! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the weaknesses of the mind Omnissiah save us... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look around for Teddy, he's bound to be somewhere nailed to post or tied to tree or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depleted soil, lack of machinery, heavy corruption, voodoo for a religion... it goes on and on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest it does seem as a possibility at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you don't want to get your hands dirty, and neither does EU or anyone else.

See, Haiti is failed state, almost a definition of one to be honest. The government acts more like another gang, bribes are universal, infrastructure gone, people malnourished, healthcare worse than in USA (couldn't help myself, sorry), exhausted soil, no natural resources of note, superstition entrenched in all strata of society and oligarchs acting more like feudal overlords on top of it.

You can't solve this with just money or by sending doctors and engineers.

If you want to solve this you need PROTECTORATE, you need to overthrow the government and create new one from bottom up, crack down on crime, create new legal code, reeducate the population so they give up their superstitions (religion is fine but witch doctors and witch hunts are too far) and create new regulations and institutions.

And you need to do all of this with army on the streets or else they will just ignore you, and you need to restrict freedoms of the locals so they don't stop the process when they get uncomfortable (and they will).

Media will paint you as next Hitler, people will die, your popularity will plummet and it will cost like Iraq-war.

So it's no wonder nobody wants to actually help.
It's much less of a hassle to just send them few million USD now and then, or let UN nations ship their reprobates there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea, most first world countries issue ID to their people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 11:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My childhood, why?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 11:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed, thank you very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's why English became the world language of today.

I would say lingua franca, but considering the context... nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could we get UK themed header in response to recent terrorist attack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly it goes for them too. Assyrians have been leaving during entire 20th century, since turk led genocide, and those that were left were slaughtered by ISIS or others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there is one significant factor, the Structure gel.

We know that it can accomplish incredible stuff even without WAU directing it. 

The thing hangs on if Simon can gather enough willpower and start acting, rather than just sit there and fall apart or just run around panicking.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Face Is Tired </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were not even trying. This is just painful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember that one. It really pissed me off back then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that. It's sad and stupid decision. 
But if you are suffering from Alzheimer you are bound to make those a lot.

At least I can comfort myself with thought that there are still sane people in congress and that all the bullshit he stirs will force people to ACTUALLY VOTE in midterms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As /u/deudeudeu said the syntax is the obvious problem.
It complicates things for developers, especially now when almost all major languages use extremely similar syntax.

Another thing is that different platforms like to add things to the language with very little regard to ANSI norm.

That creates inconsistencies and complicates things during migrations and education. In some cases SQL on different platforms looks more like different dialect than the same language.

Granted those are mostly cosmetic problems.
But just like that wart on a toe that no one sees, it keeps reminding you that it's there and sometimes it hurts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so NASA will now focus on space instead of earth science, I can agree with that.

But if at the same time they don't devote more money to climate research under other agencies than that's a major issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to take a look at your github. Stuff like this is gravely needed in this age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The five most religious countries were Qatar, Indonesia, Egypt, Jordan and Tunisia. In terms of religiosity, Ireland ranked 36th on the list.

That's like second paragraph.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now there is post in /r/worldnews filled with this kind of absurdity: https://np.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/60l9hv/religious_countries_likely_to_perform_worse_in/


If you are asking, no I didn't find the chart in comments yet, but I bet it's only matter of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 10:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Law is one thing, but in the end it comes to you, doctor and a thick envelope.

Same goes for Female Genital Mutilation, signs of abuse etc. never underestimate human corruptibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where has mah country gone, where has mah country gone... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly doubt Republicans would let go of the office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly, but what I wonder is if he wouldn't implement more damaging policies.

I mean, part of having an idiot in charge is that he is sabotaging his own efforts, Pence could actually do substantial damage to American people by being capable of implementing terrible policies.
Just with prettier face and less insults.

And let's face it his policies are terrible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question we should ask now is if Pence is really better than Trump. Or just has better PR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wouldn't be out of character for him to lie about staying in Moscow.
That being said I don't know for sure if it's true that he run away so I will hold my judgement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a good reason, we saw what happened to Greece and are very aware of how corrupt our politicians are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
