<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4934</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting a pretty serious movie given the title.

But holyyyyy shit does this look like a fun movie. Could easily be the best looking Marvel movie to date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That entire Davos burst after the battle... God dammit do I love that character/actor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask why?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's up with the like/dislike ratio on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must be in the minority. 3 is my third favorite, behind Black Flag and Brotherhood. The story wasn't all there, I know, but damn did I spend an extraordinary amount of time in the frontier just hunting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you want me to respond with? You're calling someone a retard because of their political stance and their stance on abortion. There's nothing to say other than you used the wrong form of allowed/aloud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allowed*

I'm gonna be that guy, fuck it. Aloud is the noise version of the word. Speaking aloud. Allowed is the permission version.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost like your support for a political party doesn't define every belief in life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 14:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd kill for a Superman one. Keep doing gods work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Singed and Zilean

Helluva patch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Standing beside a skinny 14-15 year old while wearing a generic fitting shirt may make it seem that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, YT Red? Isn't that a US only service? I looked into it when it was announced way back when and was unable to buy it here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has votes, but it doesn't answer anything. Why are there songs missing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spotify is global. 

Netflix is region locked. Content for most nations really can't hold a light to the US/Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After your 30s or so, sickness and injuries become way harsher on you, and a flu that could have lasted 2-3 days a few years ago, maybe hold you down for a week or 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even as a League player, this is fucking hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The really sad reality about this is that a lot of people will start to use the strength of the Stark's as a flaw. Most people were hooked in by how often main characters were destroyed. But now with Jon straight up coming back from the dead, charging an army solo, and ending up as the king in the north... 

I hate that it'll most likely be a "this story is gone to shit" kinda thing, with plot armor being used as reasoning to give up and wait for the books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can, but being on mobile, it's way too much fucking hassle to go through a bunch of posts and copy the links, as opposed to doing it on a desktop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How important is owning all dlc for this mod? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a deep love for GoT, and I enjoy CK2. I haven't fully delved into the base game, but I bought some dlc around Christmas. I have: 

Legacy of Rome, Way of Life, Ruler Designer, The Old Gods, Charlemagne, South Indian Portraits. 

I've looked into the mod a bit and it says Sword of Islam adds in horses for the Dothraki, and I'd feel weird playing without such a thing, but even with the sale, I'm in no real position to buy any more dlc. 

So, how enjoyable is the game with only half or less of the DLCs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Wars being the second best movie of all time...

Jesus Christ, nothing good will come from this. It's every stereotype of the sub wrapped up until a very well made graphic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahmed's insight was very interesting IMO. But... I doubt it'll ever change how the hosts deal with matters and material when it comes to that section of the world.

That Pepsi ad fuckup was pretty funny. Having already seen it I was baffled that it took them a few minutes to realize that riot footage was not the actual ad, then to follow it up with the wrong ad the second time was pretty funny. 

Also, thinking back on it.. It was very odd for Woody to not get too specific about who the family member in the army was. Hasn't he brought him up multiple times in the past?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not even closely related. 

Drawing gay clown Putin is a straight up fuck you to one specific person because of his out dated and obnoxious ideals.

Drawing Muhammad is simply not giving a fuck you to anyone. And if it's a Muhammad drawing like the one that caused the drama in France way back when, then it's just being an asshole to be an asshole, and that's not even targeting someone. It'd just offend an entire religion for no reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the quality is what matters. It's the fact that the image or overall idea being brought into media is illegal there, so it's the "fuck you" that I appreciate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I guess I'll give that a try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I lower my graphics these days? (outside base settings) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking at posts that talk about going to the config file and searching for ____, but it appears to be that a lot of those search terms are missing. For example, I've looked into texture_quality, and it's not an option that appears.

I'd love to give this game a shot, but I already find it clunky to play, and the low fps is making the adjustment way too big a' struggle. Thanks for any help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are some reallyyyyyyy nice costumes. Arya takes the cake though, that warrior style outfit looks amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its like you mixed 80% Casey Neistat with 15% Woody, and topped it off with an additional %5 nose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way that could be it. He's been im the game since the beginning, if he did actually forget it... The fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really feel weird because of this. Ive mained support on lol for 4 seasons, and no matter what game I go to, whether its smite, dota, wow, overwatch,eso, lotro... I always find myswlf at home as a healer or support.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, because playing a game will definitely solidify your odds of never having self respect, getting laid, or having kids that like or appreciate you... 

/s

Talk about have an outdated mindset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Woody'sLab.

Joined Sep 15, 2014

Jesus fucking christ we're never actually getting an upload on that channel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't even an unpopular opinion, you're just a petty asshole. 

+If you dont care about the 13lp then why even play ranked?  

Also, being rational about it, if you're 3-4-5 pick, and you're hovering a high pick rate champ.. its just basic reasoning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw the upvote count on this and thought "damn, people are playing a joke on him, continuing to convince him its Thursday instead of Wednesday"...

I've spent the entire fucking day thinking it was Wednesday, and now at 9pm I've found out otherwise because of Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's never been a selling point, but it's something people really tend to underestimate or refuse to acknowledge. Shit, MW1/MW2 are some of my favorite FPS stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is only two times when LP counts the most: in promos, and when you're about to be deranked.

Am I the only one that really doesn't understand this? Every game matters. You don't get to the promo game, or  the deranking game without those games in between. The 5th promo for a new tier should be taken as seriously as the first 20lp into the 1st division of your current tier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 10:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm legitimately curious. What is the point? This guy complained about 3 and a half minutes. Why did you go on to watch multiple videos, and if so, what ones did you watch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you really take you the entire video to realize you didn't like it? 

If anything, you deserve the loss of time for sitting through a video you had no reason to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  he should have ran as part of an independent party

Realistically, he never would have been heard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a shame, but thanks for the back and forth tip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck Star Guardian Ez man... I just want them to fix the mess they made with Pulsefire. The entire Arcade lineup looks better than that skin, and they were released 9 months ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] How do I stop her hairs from spreading through every room she enters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 1 year old Husky, and lately I've realized most of my clothes and furniture have hairs on, or around them, and this is new to me. I've tried brushing her thoroughly, I've tried washing her down with water while brushing, I tried dog shampoo to clean her coat, followed by more brushing.. Absolutely nothing works. 

I'd much rather keep her indoors, but it's getting pretty noticeable so I've had her in her kennel lately when I'm not walking her or letting her roam the garden. 

Thanks for any advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I didn't fully believe the announcement that they'd work in sync with one another.. But shit, that dual recall is a fantastic idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  can go untargetable with her ult

I'm hyped for a dual release... But damn, not again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, and I don't keep up so I may be wrong, but Bernie definitely seems like he's legitimately one of the people. Always in with his crowds, in the midst of the protests, marches, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also a mid tier player who cries like a bitch... evidently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Everyone hates him, no one respects him" .... "He's over rated"

God I can't stand his absurd fucking hatred for Crosby. It's very clear at this point that he only follows the sport through the stats, newspage to NHL, and the occasional YT vid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's an inside joke. Look at my name. What I'm saying is that you're talking about people going to a subreddit, and those people being 12 year old kids who need affirmation about their interests, yet you're saying everyone at /r/pka is a rape squad killa.. And not only that, but you're acting like those who downvote you are the 12 year olds. No, those are the people who aged out of the rape squad killa shtick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 10:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say people from other subs do it because they're 12 year olds, then go on to say: were the rape squad killas!

Criiiiiiiinge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  5Ghz wireless

How do I figure out what mine is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be plugging into the box that shares the wifi, just so we're clear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would downgrading my color depth through the graphics card menu increase fps while gaming? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just noticed my options, and I can run the color depth at 32bit, and 16bit. It was set to 32bit, so I'm wondering how many games would get a boost in fps if I were to downgrade to 16bit. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does connecting an Ethernet cable from the pc to the 'wifi box' increase the speed/ping? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call it a wifi box simply because I know people refer to it as both a router and a modem, while also referring to the 'box in the wall' as a modem and/or router. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 03:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that's unpopular at all. 

The first movie builds up this captivating and breathtaking world. 

The second movie builds on it and gives us more detail, and the darker side of the world.

The third movie knocks it home with some of the most epic and moving scenes in cinema history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, people for some reason think he was a stay at home dad without the kids.

The guy said he was a stay at home husband. There's still shit to do around the house even without kids in a family, so, even with it being easier than most jobs, I'd imagine he's doing more than what someone else imagines to be a stay at home husband.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I know they're over doing it, but it's definitely on par with the first two seasons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kanye deconstructed: The human voice as the ultimate instrument </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name a movie that deserved it more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the category they won it in? Of course. I know it's a fucking joke to call it an Oscar winning movie, that's also what it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems exciting, but I'll also just wait to see it myself. 

Most likely going to be crushed by reviewers, but at this point I care little for their thoughts on DC. 

EDIT: I should clarify, I don't ignore reviewers because I'm a blind fanboy that believes they're perfect movies. I definitely see the flaws, but damn do I love Man of Steel and BvS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrow is consistent up until mid season 3ish. Then it drops off to season 5, but picks up with a bang in quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe even get drunk sometimes and play games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could have expected him being fat.. Him being a neckbeard..

But god fucking dammit did I not expect him to be white.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only Return that matters in my eyes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Against a tiger? No way. How does he win? Overpower the tiger? Take him from the back? Sweep it's legs? There's so much thought that would have to go into it, and all the tiger needs to do is land one swing and Yoel is in serious trouble.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ---- Number of Yasuo mains inting today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woody really needs to get over the alpha hunter thing. We are the top of the food chain because we created weapons. 

It doesn't matter if they have eyes in front, or at the sides, if they eat meat, or grass. The majority of large animals would absolutely fuck you up if you're fists only.

That being said, I fucking love the opening to the show so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  3: Just noticed that Bardem is the vilain

I guess I'm in now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel so bad for that champ. I get the jokes, I really do. He's a piece of shit with those shrooms, but for the love of god he does well in lane vs a good few champs, and late game he can be pretty fucking good. But nooooo, every time I lock him it's "Well it's a 4v5 with a troll top". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't completely dropped it, but Flash is taking a real decline lately. To the point of this week being the first time in the show's history that I watched an episode a few days after airing, rather than the morning after it releases.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are we? Some kind of... Pirates of the Caribbean?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  if I can somehow keep my bungie account and get my legacy stuff on PC too 

They really, really should make a console to pc upgrade for those that played on either console. Like how they allowed ps3 to ps4, xbox360 to xboxone. They didn't allow ps3 to xboxone though, so there may be a slight problem with crossing over. 

I guess only time will tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well of course not everything is going to be silly, but comedy sells. Cayde was the most loved character in the first game, it makes sense to have him lead the marketing. But I bet when you get to the next homebase, there will still be Shaxx screaming for combat and whatnot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh come on. Almost every comment in the promo thread a few days ago was about how fantastic Cayde is, and how he alone made TTK worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HBO realllyyyyyyyyyy know how to make a promo for the show that gives us absolutely nothing about the coming season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Injustice 2 - Its Good To Be Bad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Injustice 2 - Its Good To Be Bad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **begins to beg for some Janna chromas** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd imagine there's definitely a money side about it, because of the Star Wars sponsor, and the mobile games he's often pimping..

But at the same time, I'd imagine he's hella comfortable on what he's got right now to the point of "yeah sure, I guess I'll pimp this game" instead of "oh shit, ____ amount for 2 vids? Easy money" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  absolutely fucking nuts.
 It is a popcorn flick at its finest. Story is semi there to keep everything moving, but I expect insane explosions,

Uhmmmmm, I know I left out the impossible car stunts and 5 year old thing, but this comment also sums up Call of Duty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just me or is there always an upcoming movie with Fassbender in it? Seems like just as a movie of his is about to drop we get posters for his next release. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Janna main I'd kill for this. I'm tired of being called useless because my shields get shredded by the 20-0 midlaner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That final shot of him running at the kid... Fuuuuuuuck this looks good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain why there's so much hype around this movie? I understand it's from the guy that brought us Fifth Element.. But he also brought us Lucy. +this movie looks awfully similar to Jupiter Ascending, so seeing his recent record and my personal comparison.. 

I'd legitimately appreciate if someone could fill me in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What else is there to use? Meta is a common word on Reddit and almost everyone has a grasp on what it means. Jokes from one thread become meta and cross into other threads. Shit, Meta is used as a common term in almost every competitive game. 

+You'd actually walk away from someone for saying a word? Reallyyyy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: People are out of the loop in regards to the title. 

It's a meta post guys, relax.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems fake. The account tries to act like him, but I'd imagine Dom has been aware of Reddit for much longer than 2 months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 01:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it may legitimately be a clean shooting in self defence, but 2 were in the kitchen, 1 in the driveway. How did it get to the driveway? I'm actually curious how 1 of them came to die in the driveway. 

Was he running away? Then that's not a self defense kill. Did the guy crawl out there? The questions..

EDIT: Read it some more. They broke in through the back and I guess after the chaos he ran for it? Also says the burglars were 16-18.. What a damn shame :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Releasing their shows within 2 weeks of the trailer.. God bless you Netflix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the pay that matters, just a different level of employee there these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone with probably 1000 hours, if not more in Destiny.. I genuinely hope this game is everything we've begged for, if not more. The first game was very hit and miss. I'm sure they regret how they handled story/lore, but it's also Bungie we're dealing with so I imagine they're fairly in tune with what their player base wants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the last call for Destiny. Being realistic this game will sell incredibly well, and each DLC they'll sell after will only add to the game's lifetime, leading us right into whatever the follow up game is. 

They said in the beginning that Destiny is their 10 year mission. We're 2 and a half years in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Destiny lore is legitimately fantastic, they just made it really hard to read. There are sites out there with every codex in the game, leaving it really easy to digest if that's your thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't he leave her after he promised her dad that she'd be safe away from it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, I've looked into it and was incredibly disappointed by it when I found out it's not here. There is also Sky. I've heard Atlantic streams it at the same time.. But there's no way I'd pay 29 euro a month, along with having it installed and put on a 12 month plan etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to give away the overall arc, but damn I'm sold simply because of the cast and A24. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just it though, isn't it? You can predict most of the movie just by the premise and cast etc. The only thing we didn't expect was probably the suit situation, but it being a Marvel movie means it can only really go so many ways, and we all agree on that, but once they show it, everyone begins to shout about it spoiling too much, as if we didn't know to begin with. 

It's like with Justice League. Absolutely everyone agress Superman is going to show up at some point. Shit, most of the comments are about how he WASN'T revealed yet. So by proxy of it, we all know he's in the movie, yet for some reason, when he finally shows up in a trailer down the line, everyone will go crazy saying it's spoiling the entire movie. 

Reddit baffles me with trailer thoughts sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: People over exaggerating how much the trailer shows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. We still have no idea why Donald Glover is in the movie. How Peter manages to best someone clearly out of his league, and whether he gets the girl or pulls an Amazing Spiderman by leaving her behind. 

It gives a lot with the suit reveal, but there's a lot of movie left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gives away a little too much but damn does this looks like a fun movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it is. Their HBOgo or HBOnow model is fucking ridiculous. It's limited to how many countries? I'd say the US only but it may be for Canada too.. 

If they spread beyond that I'm sure there'd be a downfall to some degree. Shit, I'd pay 20 a month if it came to Ireland, just because I'd get to watch episodes live without having to find a shitty stream and then torrent a HD version later.. 

Until then I guess I'll continue being a thief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand by what I said tbh.. Sure 19% completed it 2 years ago, but I'd imagine there was some level of growth. I'd also take into consideration that there's a demo or trial for the game you can get for free on the store (or there was last time I was on ps4) so you'd have to account for thousands, if not tens of thousands of "players" that played for an hour or two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see a way for this to work reasonably for any company.

Release it digitally? Okay, and now it's on a torrent site. Ship out discs? Oh look, someone ripped and uploaded it to a torrent site AND you have to pay for shipping/production cost of day-one discs.

I'd enjoy it in specific cases, whether it be I'm not close to a theater of my liking, or I'm stuck in bed sick.. But no way this could ever be profitable for those selling the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, Destiny's style was most definitely not aimed at casual players. It's an incredible time vacuum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all for agreeing that the grind was veryyyy tedious after a while, but there's no fucking way you can say that he realized it was an unrewarding loop BEFORE playing a raid. It's like playing WoW and never leaving Stormwind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: People fucking haaaaaaaaaaate this guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The ranked ladder is for tryharding, because some people enjoy winning games

So what you're saying is those who do good are... having fun?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  who want to report someone for having fun

This is a veryyyy blurry area. Having fun is fine and well if you're actually putting in some level of effort, but if that person that's playing for fun by building some complete shit on a champ and replying with "lol" every death... That's a different situation entirely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's a 6 second clip, but god damn do I love that suit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'd have no idea where to find them though.

While I agree the idea of meeting the hosts would have been cool at a convention or a meetup etc.. Now that they're not exactly in a spot to do meetups and whatnot, I'd imagine anyone trying to meet them in person is slightly out of their current comfort zones, unless it's a legitimate "i just bumped into...." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was Popstar legitimately a good comedy? I saw a trailer for it and had a chuckle or two, but passed it off as basically a 1-2 hour version of one of their music videos.

If you're tagging it in with The Nice Guys... That's a high bar IMO. Is it true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you hate Aram players so much? I have thousands of games on the rift, but id imagine im at least 1200 into aram and damn do I love it. 

+Aram ranked is just fine. Are you mad at 3v3 players for having an extra icon?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 60 within 2 weeks,  pushing to 830k 3 months into the year... He should easily reach it by August or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So since the 25th, amid all the sadness and bleak outlook at the future, it seems like Suptic has gained about 30k subs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm watching his vid "Why I think Sourcefed was cancelled" and he talks about getting a message saying "congrats on 800k", and this was pretty confusing to me, considering now, 2 days later, he's at 831k. 

I understand a lot of people are branching out now that the channel is gone, reaching for more of the hosts, but even then, that's insane growth right? At least for a channel of this size. 

EDIT: [Here's the vid] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzFzx8s50NY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mike too if he has the time.

And why would he not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bye Bye SourceFed [A vid from Ava's channel] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah.. There were so many moments that had me with a huge grin, or laughing during the livestream... Only to be followed with "It's all ending now" and the tears did their thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't gotten too far into this week's ep. What's the context to Kyle's comment? This really doesn't sound as much like a shot as it does a shoutout to Key and Peele.. (Solid specials btw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I'd kill for Sam, Suptic, Ava, Bree, Stee.. the list of people I want is too long, but nonetheless.. I wonder if he can build a new team that will one day be as loved as the other's were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I missed the start of the livestream by like 40 minutes, so instead of jumping in late I waited for it to completely wrap up before watching.. It started at 9pm, so I didn't sleep until 9am, and by did I cry myself to sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DL post-win interviews are spicy as always. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure of matchfixing is the rise of a meme, or idiots who actually think it was fixed.

+DL dropping his dick on the table right there to show his power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was more wondering if there is a way to factory restore it even, or get into the files through pc but after trying that it needs to be open for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been around a while now to see quite a few come and go, I agree with you for the most part, but god damn it did I fall in love (no homo) with Sam over the time he was there. From an awkward new guy to fully embracing everything he loves, and getting to see him (and Will quite frankly) grow up on the channel leaves way more of a mark on me than the original hosts did, which is saying a lot. Don't get me wrong, those hosts were the ones that hooked me, and it's genuinely wonderful that they haven't changed a bit across the years, but I felt at home with Sam/Will simply because although I'm 2-3 years younger than them, I feel as they grew up I did too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Joel was the worst part of

Well, you lost me right there. Joel is easily one of the most fun going, open to whatever guys I've watched over the years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The only really new thing he talked about was his butt injury

Wait, I got a few topics in and he was incredibly involved in Magic, even some sports slightly, and conspiracy talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm holding out a hail mary prayer for GL at the end. It kills me seeing that the movie is set up to be 5 heroes, and Superman returning at some point.. The Justice League is 7 heroes united. Give me it please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lois Lane is a pretty important character when Clark is not around.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Aquaman riding the batmobile] (https://gyazo.com/600c3d0e9c0783fdf6d17d2d7b6e1a06) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may be a 50% RT kinda movie... but god damn it do they kill it with trailers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it'll be near impossible to slip in Hal without the press or paparazzi knowing... But the grin I would have on my face if a GL showed up towards the end of the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who is interest in Magic, [this] (https://gyazo.com/6fcfefd1076d6f74f1b356c2ae0bd74b) really has me excited for the episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love: House of Cards

Boring: Making a Murderer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am. I've been reading The Final Empire lately by Brandon Sanderson. It may not be the most imaginative, but it is the first fantasy I've read that I didn't know the setting of. (Read GoT after the show, Lotr after the movies) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to get past that "feeling sleepy" phase of reading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I don't read as as often as I once believed, and after the resolution of read an hour a day failed, I slid away from reading. Now I'm getting back into it, and as much as I come to enjoy a book, there comes a time when I find myself yawning, and I can't help but relate it to how I was read to as a kid, or how I was always exhausted when reading for school work (usually rushing into class, or before bed).

I'd imagine someone else has the same struggle, so if anyone has thoughts or opinions I'd love to hear them. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Thankfully 11-13 were by comparison phenomenal

I felt the opposite. I got through the first 8 episodes on the release Friday, but it took me the next 6 days to get through 8-13. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man... It kills me how much that show has fallen this season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I genuinely do understand why people complain about him, but as an avid comic reader, and someone who loved his style in 300.. God I can appreciate his lead on this. Sure it may not be as well setup and organized as Marvel movies, but shit are they way better looking than most blockbusters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "resurrected to fight for the hand. He doesn't have time to deal with this pointless shit"

Considering the enemy for most of the season was the hand, I'm reallyyyyy confused as to why you think Elektra being built as a weapon takes away from Matt's reasoning to help. If anything it was the perfect show to start adding the group together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I have no clue where the critics were comparing the story to s3 and s4 of Arrow."

Because the writing is easily some of the worst writing I've ever seen in a show, and that's from someone who enjoyed the opening few episodes and the premise. I honestly believe I ignored the negatives, just to go against the hate the show was getting, and enjoyed it because it's a Netflix show. Nope. After about 6 episodes I finally caved and noticed the absurd amount of flaws. 

There are just wayyyy too many flaws for it to be considered as good as DDs2, but I'd just about agree with it being Luke Cage leverl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 22:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellowship of the Ring. 

Return of the King.

Interstellar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :(

"We apologize to our international fans, but this item cannot be shipped outside the U.S. due to legal agreements." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If life over 60 involves flat caps and suits that fit perfectly... Sign me up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm not saying this is Breaking Bad or the Sopranos level of amazing plot and expert character development. But for what it is, it nails it spot on.

You said, and I quote: "I think it should be up there for best written series of all time, children or otherwise."

You didn't compare it to those shows, but the shows are the top of the top tier, therefore it by proxy is compared to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend, a link will be required. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was crying often enough up until the end.. then Maude did the silent goodbye, it got worse.

Reading "Colorful birds" now has me doing that kinda cry that involves your throat. Shit it's gonna be a rough time browsing my subs with no vids from the channel to look forward to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  or putting a second router on the second modem will be fine too.

Wait, so you don't have to pay for more than one modem?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Him listing all the names at the end realllyyyy got to me. The guys working there all seem genuinely great, and damn do I hope they land on their feet after all this. +It didn't help that Steve sounded like he was holding back some emotion as he wrapped up his talk beside the sign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm sorry I don't know the terms, this is a new area for me. I've looked up the difference and it seems that Modem is the box attached to the wall, while router is the device that spreads wifi. I know that's painfully basic but I imagine it's worth it so we're on the same page.

There are 2 modems in the house. One has a router setup with it, near my front door. I have another router so I was curious about setting it up at modem 2 upstairs. Considering I have to pay for it, I'll pass. 

On that, I wanted to know if I took router 1 away from modem 1, could I connect it to modem 2 upstairs, or would there be some weird installation flaw that stops that from working.

I know my wording is really off and whatnot, and considering I spend most of my life at a desk I hate how out the of the loop I am here, but also don't wanna just say "ah fuck it, plug it in" only for everything to crash and burn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Last Samurai

If this movie is on par with that movie, I'm completely fine paying to see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A quote (paraphrased) from a similar post on here by a redditor I forget the name of:

Great message, but a terrible messenger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moving my wifi router to a new modem in the house and just have a question or two. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm moving in the next week or so and I'm organizing where my wifi is setup. There is of course the modem in the hallway, and that's where the guy installed it, but looking around, I found a modem in what I guess was the office room. 

So my questions are: 

I have two routers. If I plug the second router upstairs, while the first is setup downstairs, will this cause some problems? I've heard unless the provider knows of this modem, it may just stop working throughout the house.

Also, if I were to move the downstairs router to the upstairs setup, will it work? Or was the installation process focused on the bottom floor modem?

Thanks for any help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why exactly didn't Ryu have a QSS? Playing against Faker, who was and still is easily the best mid on the planet, in a Zed matchup.. Quite frankly the dude should have made sure he had it before 6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And get hotshotgg in just to feed regi mushrooms throughout the game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ofc that's part of it, but that's still one of the greatest outplays of all time. The pinnacle of zed gameplay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no even the slightest chance this could every possibly happen or work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked about Sanderson a week or two ago when there was that post regarding his fantasy being.. revolutionary is not the write word, but you may know the article I speak of.

That being said.. I just read the opening section of American Gods again, up until he finds out about his wife, and good lord is it a fantastic opening. Hooked already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also gave warnings. Applying "literally" to it does not emphasize yoir point on this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not every student in college has triangles in their field though.. and those students are fuuuuuuuucked if they're on here instead of learning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why exactly? I'm out of the loop on this one..

EDIT: Well hot damn, seems like he's a real piece of shit. That being said.. He's also pretty good in the movies he is in, so I'd still like him this Scorcese hit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, people banned him instead of letting me play him in ranked. The guy has an incredible kit and its easy as shit to learn. I'm so tired of people acting like new champs or reworks are Satan for the first few weeks of release. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So now I'm we know there are two fantastic games in this pic. I wonder what else we'll find </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I'm not saying it's they've been buffed or anything, but as far as coding is concerned they seem all outta whack. Although I agree that there is some level of me being on the receiving end  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, am I crazy or do the range and width of hooks these days vary drastically? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played blitz/thresh/Nautilus a lot last season. Those 3 champs probably had 80% of my ranked games just because i loved the incredible engage style. 

This season however I've gone to peel supports, and up until about a week or two ago a blitz was a pretty rare sight, but damn when he's played now I get spooked.

I have about 4k hours in the game so I feel it's fair to say i know for the most part what an abilities range is. Not the actual numbers but an in-game feel to it. 

But with that said... I can't help but think "he's out of range" or "I'm behind this wave" right before getting hooked by the 3 champs I listed. Shit, even once getting behind basw wall, legitimately around the corner, only for Naut to drag me back into lane. 

So have any others, preferably bot/supp mains noticed this? Thanks for any thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read every issue in her Rebirth run. Please explain how that would make for a good R rated movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you didn't mean it, but I'm genuinely crying from laughter right now, because everyone time i think it's over, I see another and I cant help but read it in the voice.. godbless your phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He was in Man of Steel though.

I'm not sure if you're saying this gave him more recognition, or doing the typical Reddit thing and saying that worsened his odds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [FUCK] (https://gyazo.com/c8e1bd53317c4d7ce43c2b62ea5f5ea5)

As someone who grew up with him as Gandalf and Magneto... Damn will I be sad to miss this event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The keeper has a pretty solid save ratio when it comes to penalties. The guy taking it is also Lionel Messi, who is widely considered to be the best player on the planet, and even one of the best of all time, so I'd imagine the keeper had a pretty high level of respect for having Messi score on him. 

Poorly worded toward the end but I hope you get my point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because assuming a movie will be bad based on movies connected to it is a great way to work out the good from the bad.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe there was blood on the corpses or whatever, but even without blood, the Joker did still kill a guy with a pencil through the skull. That's pretty gruesome for a 12 movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but clearly they aren't going to go for a "Saving Private Ryan" level of brutal and horrific realism.

Thank fucking god. Wonder Woman is not a gritty R rated kinda hero. Sure, give BvS that rating, even give it to the solo Batman movie, but no way is Wonder Woman an R rated hero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, I feel the opposite. I can't imagine juggling books. Opening one up like "Yeah, let's see what these characters get up to now.. Ok, I guess it's time to pause their story and read a completely unrelated piece of text about an entire different universe"

Different strokes for different folks I guess. I also wouldn't say you have ADD from reading that, but who knows.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, if you've been enjoying the Flash or Supergirl so far.. This episode isn't too far outside the norm. They're both pretty cheesy shows to begin with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watch High School Musical as a kid and he definitely had that "I'm on screen for the girls" kinda vibe, and his first few movies after it were definitely that. 

So glad he took a comedic turn. The guy is pretty good at the area he's in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks absurd. 

The Rock and Zac seem to have fantastic chemistry.

+Alexandra Daddario 

Yeaaaahhh, I think it's safe to say I'll be seeing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [God bless you sir] (https://gyazo.com/876b543df91fed565fdc4a45510f6603) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should add a flame, kinda glow to the trail left from his kick as he spins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still working through the opening chapter after the prologue, but I've honestly put it on pause until I pick up American Gods. I'd rather not miss what could be a great read by reading it over, with another book in mind.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please dont drag politics into /r/books .. it has taken too many of my subs, leave here now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a beautiful hardback copy of Lord of the Rings, illustrated by Alan Lee. 

[Here] ( https://www.bookdepository.com/The-Lord-of-the-Rings-J-R-R-Tolkien-Alan-Lee/9780007525546?ref=grid-view) is a link to it, although sadly for me it cost around 65 euro.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my struggle right now. I picked up The Final Empire by Brandon Sanderson a few days ago and have enjoyed it for the most part. 

Then yesterday I walked past a hardback copy of American Gods that caught my attention, and after 2-3 pages of in-store reading I was hooked... 

So now whenever I pick up Empire, I can't help but wish it was American Gods, and lose interest immediately. I guess I can always come back to Empire... Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  uninteresting characters, broken motivations

How do you feel these 2 points hold true?

If you're talking about Bruce killing people, that feeds right into the mystery that is WHY he is killing people, therefore giving his character some depth and a past, while also seeing as most believe Joker killed his partner, he jumped off the deep end, and Alfred himself said so in the movie, giving him actual motivation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  he talked about the Scarlett Johansson (sp?) leaks a few years back?

To be fair, that was a few years back. There is a chance his stance has changed on the topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dragonslayer Braum :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have 348 hours, given that it starts at midday tomorrow until midnight on the 5th. 104 minutes per game, but that's also without sleep.

GLHF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just having a conversation about the article. Because my answers are long, and I care for the topic, that doesn't make me angry.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   at least our hero is still likeable and sympathetic

Because Danny Rand is anything but sympathetic, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? I'm sorry, but you can't say I'm experiencing cognitive dissonance because I don't care much for veganism being a label that everyone wears when they eat a certain way. I don't label myself as a meat eater, and unless it gets in the way of a meal or brought up by another, vegetarians don't go bragging about being a vegetarian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but I'm upset that every time someone famous goes vegan there's a huge deal about it, or another vegan will explain how it's the way forward and how unnecessary meat is in the day to day meal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's perfectly healthy for any adult, yes. If you're not a fully developed person yet, it most definitely has it's downsides and it's the perfect idea that some may want it to be.

I was also pointing out that when someone is vegan, they make sure it's known. You saying it's a healthy lifestyle doesn't somehow mark out what I said.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title talks about an incredible growth, and lists 3 athletes that made the switch. It's not directly saying that we should go vegan, but it's doing the typical thing of making sure people know vegans exist and they're out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd honestly say it's game dependent. Take it with a kog/cait/vayne maybe, but depending on who you're laning vs, or better yet, who the junglers are, you may need redemption first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no idea about the Brady thing, which is saying a lot because I'm a Pats fan, but I did know about the Phelps calorie count, simply because of the Olympics last year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing the other guy's reaction in the first video is fucking hilarious, and he just continues to read Hitler facts. Damn I hope he's on the show soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, but does it a really fucking matter? So a few pro athletes are opting for a different eating habit than my own, that doesn't mean I'll follow them to it. Shit, has anyone ever seen The Rock's diet, or quite frankly any NFL player's diet and made a genuinely worthwhile article about it? 

That joke about vegans needing validation constantly really is accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of humor are we talking?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitting us with the semi-related, but entirely true facts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And does it often make it clear as to which gods are which, or does it make it very vague and you work it out, like such for Odin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
