<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2956</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shooting at a snake, WCGW? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [We kaffirs never understood what those devout roars where about](https://www.youtube.com/results?search_query=lion+allah) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Male lions are more Islamic. They have a beard and many wives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant](http://m.timesofindia.com/india/Kejriwal-a-leader-worth-betting-on-Rajiv-Bajaj/articleshow/30646465.cms) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As if it was waiting for this particular car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I posted the source in another comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/MCjtvG9CxX4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cat is just a probability function (Lewis Caroll - Erwin Schrdinger) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boo! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you OP. [I cant stop laughing](https://gfycat.com/ColorfulThoughtfulBee). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cat and mouse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://m.liveleak.com/view?i=01d_1485702977) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ice breaks under a tractor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noticed the shirt right after posting, when I was checking if the gif link was okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This [link](http://m.liveleak.com/view?i=375_1485499540) says it is from the Philippines. But 'Treinamento' sounds Portuguese. Brazil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man pulls out a knife to rob a supermarket in the Philippines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 10:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=ea5_1485378900) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At a train crossing in Poland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 10:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 09:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=ea5_1485378900) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At a train crossing in Poland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 09:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot to mention the cut part. Have never tried pudhina. I'm going to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vodka with a pachha milagai. No water or anything else. Have to wait atleast 10 mins before first sip. About 50 absolutely love it, the rest absolutely hate it, no in-betweens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [India's greatest gay icon was brought down in 1992](http://www.thehindu.com/books/books-columns/an-emperor-with-foibles/article5692770.ece). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 08:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Migration rate includes migration within state. People moving from their villages to towns/cities for work. There are far more Marathi migrants into Mumbai than anywhere else, for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything back to normal in Chennai. No roads are blocked, metro trains/buses are running, office and schools open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jallikattu protests: Will the real Chennai arsonists please stand up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right. Never said they are. Also true of muslims and xtians. But if you run into a anti-hindu, anti-modi tamil nationalist, there is a very high chance that they are from one of these groups.

I also wouldn't call these people Ambedkarites because Ambedkar was definitely a nationalist and a patriot. He was also a very intelligent, very classy man. These people are none of those things. Periyar's rationalism had a lot of good points. His anti-Brahminism was also probably justified for his time. But these people are only driven by their hatred which in turn is fueled by their insecurities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is a self-made chutiya. No need for leftie propaganda. He is probably a dalit, xtian or muslim. He is just trying to get his anti-uppercaste, anti-hindu message across using some pro-Tamil bullshit. The tamil nationalist space is almost entirely dominated by these three groups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The primary organisers of the protest had withdrawn yesterday itself, because of the ordinance. Only the anti-Modi, Tamil nationalist and Muslim groups are trying to misuse this now. They say an Indian flag was burned in Coimbatore yesterday [causing one of the main organisers to pull out yesterday itself](http://www.news18.com/news/india/hip-hop-tamizha-quits-jallikattu-stir-after-insult-to-national-flag-1339222.html) As long as the protest was by the students and the general public, there wasn't a single incidence of violence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 12:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quality post sir. Forwarding it on my Whatsapp groups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 08:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are replying to a troll. Check his post history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Cover your face and lower your eyes while walking, WCGW?](https://gfycat.com/ImmediateDismalDevilfish)

[Tum naqaab mein raho, zamaana aukaat mein rahega](https://gfycat.com/NeighboringGrandioseAmphibian) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great post nanba. I am a city boy like you too, and have similar feelings about this issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 14:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you volunteer for PETA by any chance? Or know some girl there. There must be a lot of girls there, just like in Greenpeace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 14:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know about the milk part. Also found out they are against people keeping pets. Dogs, cats...anything.

I know very little about these sort of people since I usually avoid them. Used to date a Greenpeace volunteer a few years ago, but that didn't end well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, how many of you cruel fucks support the barbaric practice of drinking milk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 13:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL, PETA is also against milk consumption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 12:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 07:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes you are right. But they have not exploited the issue like the other parties have. Considering there role as supporters of Indian culture/traditions they should have been the most vocal. Let me make this clear, unless they are as vocal about Tamil issues as they are about Hindu issues in the North, they are not going to get full support here. They should realise, for Tamils, Pongal and the traditions associated with it are as important as Diwali/Holi in the North. If they want a national footprint, they should first start supporting all Indian/Hindu traditions equally and vocally. Not just the ones followed in the North. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 07:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a BJP/Modi supporter and dont give a fuck about what the DMK/Congress did. What has happened is that the BJP has missed a huge opportunity to exploit an emotional issue, just like they did with the Ram Mandir issue. They are in the same position here that they were during the 1980s at the national level. They are not big here and they should have hit the streets as a guardian of Tamil culture. That is how you win an election in TN.

BJP has to start thinking locally in TN, and not just depend on Modi and national issues to win an election here. And the best way to do it is to stand up for Tamil issues. If they don't, people are never going to abandon the Dravidian parties. Their vote share is higher than the Tamil nationalist fringe groups. If even those monkeys could organise themselves so well, why couldn't the BJP/RSS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First the BJP and the RW missed a golden opportunity by not taking an active part in the agitation. Now these idiots want to discredit the whole agitation as a Christian conspiracy. The agitation is much bigger than the crowd at Marina. Even the crowd there is a mixed one. Fringe groups have been trying to take control of the protests there, but they do it for every tamil centric emotional issue. It should have been the BJP and the RSS which should have been there first to protest against a ban on a Tamil-Hindu-Indian cultural event. Do they standup only for north indian culture? If so TN is better of with the Dravidian parties.

And it is time we stop giving importance to these tamil nationalist, evangelist, maoist groups. They have rarely won even a panchayat election in TN. As for as the LTTE is concerned, there was a lot of sympathy for Srilankan Tamils, but not for the LTTE after the Rajiv Gandhi assassination. Have you ever heard of a single Indian Tamil fighting along side the LTTE in the past many years?

The article is silly on so many levels. Probably written by some pseudo-Tamil like Subramanian Swamy sitting in Delhi. If students from Stephens take part in an agitation in Delhi does that mean it is sponsored by the Church? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JPL next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has always been an anti-national, left-leaning, anti-hindu fringe in TN, like in any other part of the country. But their numbers and influence has always been blown out of proportion because they use tamil cultural identity as a tool to get into mainstream movements. Whenever there is a distinctly tamil issue, they would be the first people to speak out, creating the impression that the whole of TN is behind their anti-national agenda. Tamils in general are overly chauvinistic but they are rarely anti-national. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be totally against any ban on any of *our* cultural symbols or practices. This includes gau mutra or animal sacrifice in Garhwal or dog eating in the NE, because I consider them to be part of *my* culture. What bugs me is that you don't consider jallikattu to be part of your culture.

I strongly believe in a pan-Indian nationalism based on our shared cultural identity, and have considered people like you and others on this sub as part of it. Am I a chutiya for considering your culture as mine, when you don't consider mine as yours? You should have been the first person to take your trishul out when the ban was announced. You should be as pissed off as you would be if somebody says something against karwa-chauth or Deepavali crackers or Holi.

A lot of protesters on Marina are like the IAC protesters in Delhi who later became AAPtards, and similarly anti-national and left leaning. But the pro-jallikattu movement has much wider support just like the anti-corruption movement did. Don't judge the motives of the movement by the activists and movie stars who like to appear in front of tv cameras. And I hope you are not lurking on randia where the same kind of Tamils hangout.

I am not going to argue about the rights and wrongs of jallikattu. I don't have to. I would just consider it a betrayal if you and other non-tamil RW people don't support it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 07:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go back and check the tone of your post. Replace all mention of jallikattu with cow piss drinking. And imagine the SC had banned piss drinking because it is a primitive unhealthy practice. Are you feeling pissed now?

Where have you given space for discussion in that post? Are you asking me to admit something just because you think it is true? And that insulting tone you have used belongs in bakchodi, not here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 06:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go slow on the gau mutra mate. And the gobar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Humane society" from the USA where you can't eat most foods without biting into and chewing a dead cow/bull. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The majority is always ready to tolerate small bites initially because they don't feel threatened. This emboldens the mosquitoes and continue with their bites. Then there is an inflection point and 2002 happens. This is the genesis for most large riots and genocides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 07:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of the 19th Century [Salt Customs Line](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Inland_Customs_Line)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why have Jessica's dish when you can have Ayesha's, Mehbooba's, Shakila's and Fatima's? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BJP has to first compete without allies in both states to gauge their own strength. As long as they ally with the TDP in Andhra they will never learn to stand on their own feet. And people like me would never vote for them in TN as long as they ally with clowns like Vijaykant. I have to know that I would get a BJP CM if I vote for them. They should also not ally with the ADMK in the next election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BJP is increasingly being seen as the biggest future threat to the commies in Kerala, not the congis. Hence the violence against them. Same in WB.

The most surprising thing is the talk in TN that BJP could inherit the traditional ADMK voter base in the future. They need a charismatic, strong leader here for that. Just Modi's goodwill wouldn't do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jallikattu was not known in TN outside rural areas before the ban. Personally, I knew almost nothing about it. Now I'm willing to pay to see one.

If the ban is lifted, it is going to become a mass sport with big crowds, commercial sponsorship and live TV coverage. Till then, with people considering this ban an insult to Tamil culture it is just going to grow bigger and bigger as an underground sport.

Thank you SC, PETA for making it so popular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=cdd_1484541329) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goose is a jerk for attacking human, dog is a bro for protecting human and also for not biting goose too hard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=cdd_1484541329) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goose is a jerk for attacking human, dog is a bro for protecting human and also for not biting goose too hard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This [source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=6d8_1484553603) says it happened in Malaysia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [From Brazil](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=68c_1484543214) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neighborhood Spider-Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 14:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This [source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=6d8_1484553603) says it happened in Malaysia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Launch failure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 13:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Failure to launch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 13:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 11:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Mulayam's second wife involved in this? Don't see any other reason why he would go against his own son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 19:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a bakchodi like sub. Or are you trying to achieve something else. Anyways subscribed, since the posts here are really funny. I came here following /u/Indian_Nazi from one of his bakchodi post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 17:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you think gifs are made? You play the video and record the screen with your phone after muting the sound. My hand was shaky because I was sitting on the speakers to cut out the sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 14:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/s94hy9gZmvE)

Couldn't find original source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 14:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the [song](https://youtu.be/75Oct1Qv8x0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With a little help from my friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 13:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HMB, while I take a nice hot shower </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 11:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 11:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=57a_1484462309) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And then there were three </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 10:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bike accident in China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 10:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mass molestation that wasnt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 08:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mammalian butterfly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 13:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=ac6_1484275992) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wheelie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 13:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 13:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=ac6_1484275992) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Up the hill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 13:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 08:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indias contribution to world GDP *growth* to reach 17% this year: PwC

The original headline and part of the article is misleading. Also China's contribution to world GDP growth rate would be much higher than India because of their total GDP, despite lower growth rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Collision </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind? Anything with a plot/story, nice tits, matures and Jap porn are my favs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fan was better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, what do you watch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/M9rpBvbI19s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kangaroo embarrassment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flip this and flip that </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 11:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=0da_1484127897) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese man built himself a robot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 11:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [Varangian trade route](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Varangians) along the Volga. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 10:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read her Facebook post? Can't link here so copy-pasting:

A LOT OF PEOPLE ASK ME WHETHER IM AFRAID OR ASHAMED OF TELLING THE TRUTH THAT THIS WAS MY BIOLOGICAL FATHER AND I WAS NAMED PRIYADARSHINI WHEN I WAS BORN..
MOSES[ MOOSA] AND kRISHNA WERE ALSO BORN TO OTHERS N ADOPTED BY OTHERS..
KARNA OF MAHABHARATA WAS NOT DEMEANED WHEN HIS TRUTH WAS REVEALED..
ANS jESUS CHRIST TOO WAS conceived BEFORE HIS MOTHERS WEDDING DATE..
YES I WAS a hindu parsi, ADOPTED BY A SIKH FAMILY..with a jewish mother.and hidden with missionaries..
And yes my mom sheila singh paul told me the description of my father n Aunty Vimla Gujral told me the truth which i have lived with suppressed for years..
MAY MY TRUTH NOT HARM ANYONE NOR MY BIOLOGICAL MOTHER N FATHER..or their families
AMEN TATHAASTU AMEEN WAHEGURU SHALOM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 10:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was born in 1969 when Sanjay Gandhi was 23. That would make her the oldest of Nehru's great-grandchildren. Probably the smartest too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When an elephant notices the presence of angry bees it [warns the rest of the herd](http://www.wired.co.uk/article/oxford-scientists-discover-elephant-bee-call) and then sucks the bees into its skull using its trunk. Then it moves far away from the herd and snorts it out. This applies only to elephant herds that haven't discovered fire yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Photo by Andrew Rice](https://www.instagram.com/p/BOZKYI0BFIB/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spray follows trunk's path </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 15:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/8WTT8NyxDgM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Car gets rear-ended </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 15:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Narendra Modi: The man who would purify India </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 14:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Learned two new words today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does "durjan" mean? My hindi is limited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen this sort of behaviour in the MG/Brigade Road area on New Year eve before. Bengaluru is a far cry from what it was when I was a child. It has gone from being the safest and most women friendly of all major cities in the South to the worst. I wouldn't be surprised at all if this had happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haryana gives nod to rename 'Ganda' village </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 10:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The greatest Indian cricketer ever. Above Tendulkar, Kohli, Gavaskar, Kapil Dev... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Poor Ayesha](http://m.indiatoday.in/story/abu-azmi-remark-on-women-ayesha-takia-azmi-farhan-azmi/1/355159.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 09:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, Delhiites had to choose between these clowns and some newer clowns in the last elections? No wonder they just voted for the newer clowns hoping for the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen the light. I shall never drink again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 18:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does bring the worst in you

No, it just amplifies whatever you are or trying to be at that moment. It's a laxative for your emotions, good or bad. Only nice, happy, confident people(like me) should drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 18:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this on top of this sub? OP is right in rising this issue and posting it here, but there are more interesting issues than what happens in some loser hangout. This should just be lower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that happens Antartica would become the new "New World", like America in the 16th Century. Also if Siberia and Canada become warmer, think of all the extra land we would get for farming, living, etc. There would also be a lot more rain if the world heats up, much more potent monsoons. And if solar power becomes more efficient, we can just move inland and live in a world where every building and every vehicle is air-conditioned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 10:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judges too should not pass judgement according to their political views </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Expulsion of UP CM Akhilesh Yadav and Ram Gopal Yadav from Samajwadi Party revoked, Shivpal says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 09:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 09:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a hindi song, tamil song. [Mental Manadhil from OK Kanmani](https://youtu.be/ryD8BqVexJI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Yadav vs Yadav, The Role Of Aparna, Mulayam's Chhoti Bahu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 07:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 05:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might look like he is praising Modi. But the tone of the article suggests Patel is worried demonetisation is going well for Modi, and he is desperately hoping that something goes wrong. He is trying to paint demonetisation as a failure and that it is being held up only by the respect people have for Modi. He is saying one good thing about Modi to trash him on the more important thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=e5e_1482992291) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HMB, while I use the blowgun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 11:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no chance of these cucks winning a single election after this. And Modi wouldn't let them loot till then, hopefully.
Hope somebody splits this party soon and puts TN out of its misery. 

One surprising thing is that the governance under OPS has been pretty good. The cyclone aftermath especially was handled well, but I don't expect it to last long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self-driving vehicles are really useful when you are drunk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shark on the beach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 12:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 08:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Indus Valley proto-Shiva and the dancing girl are not new discoveries. Any religion that was followed in the Indus Valley is the oldest form of Hinduism. The Vedas are not the roots of Hinduism, just an important part of the evolution of Hinduisms many ideas. It doesn't matter if the Vedas originated in India or that there was an Aryan migration. The fact is that there was Hinduism before that, and Hinduism has continued to evolve after that.

Vedic Hinduism which was probably promoted by a powerful, ambitious priesthood, had always tried to appropriate gods from other strands of hinduism to bring in more followers. Other gods were made avatars(Ram, Krishna) or relatives(Ganesh, Murugan) of vedic gods. The vedic Shiva himself is probably a evolution of other gods like the Indus Shiva and Rudra.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 21:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's say I'm a below average guy with low self esteem. What sort of partner would I possibly expect to get? I would expect to get a below average looker.

Wouldn't it be better for me if my plain-looking wife covered herself, so nobody knows that I could only get an average looker? But then, wouldn't everybody think my wife is not good looking because she covers herself?

The solution is to make sure that every woman covers herself, including the good looking ones.

So **MODESTY. Because GOD said so**

If you are a normal guy, you already are thinking "but why should looks matter at all?" It doesn't, but for a guy with low self-esteem, anything that he doesn't have and can't get matters a whole lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 13:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Gujarati news report]( https://youtu.be/391Dr4BQ-TY) of the incident. I understood only the few english words in it. Not sure if they were caught. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 12:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Another view](https://gfycat.com/BelovedSnoopyFrilledlizard) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thieves in Rajkot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 12:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going by the description in the video, hope you read that. I can't be sure if it's true, just like you. Maybe some Chinese here can confirm or debunk the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 16:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/PgjGRi92G3g) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 15:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/PgjGRi92G3g) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every single bank note (25000 yuan/3570 USD) was returned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 15:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People help a man who dropped 25000 yuan(3570 USD) in the street. He didn't lose a single bank note </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 15:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 09:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were the original European ass-lickers. They have been licking since the mid 17th century. The British considered them one of their own, the Empire's children. The British always thought they could depend on them. They were given special privileges during the Raj just like Anglo-Indians, and to a lesser extent xtian converts. They also had no religious problems with traveling abroad that other late 18th century, early 19th century Indians had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taimur is to India what Hitler is to Israel: Saif and Kareena, please pay attention </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 12:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 13:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is okay after the incident says the [source](http://m.liveleak.com/view?i=823_1482304157) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tree falls on man filming flood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 13:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Timur was widely known as "Timur the Lame" because he was shot in the leg with an arrow when he was young, and had a bad limp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 14:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's as if nothing has changed in Pakistan since then. The denialism, Jehad, China... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 14:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We are trying to honor all disabled people by naming our son after one of them" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 13:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll come up with a lame excuse for that name soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now, Pakistan passes resolution for notebandi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 12:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman throws neighbour's 5-year-old daughter from 15th floor after quarrel in Mumbai </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 08:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Son in Googles Seattle office, father labourer by choice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 06:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a flawless diamond stuck in a shithole. You are like Tarzan among the apes. All your defects, failures and  shortcomings have nothing to do with you. It is all because of your country. Nothing wrong with you at all. Rejoice.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 18:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good choice. Thank you /u/soonwar, for accepting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> `Very severe' cyclonic storm to pummel Chennai today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 01:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/fcYUTVnOH80) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leopard grabs a python </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 18:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/HH1rhkbWxhM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 18:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/HH1rhkbWxhM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Log barge is unloaded by deliberately tilting to one side </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 18:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Log barge is unloaded by tilting to one side </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 18:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chennai youth roughed up for not standing for national anthem in theatre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 15:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 12:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably ADMK's funds. There is a fixed rate for all building permits, government contracts etc. I heard even party men are supposed to pay, everybody is equal. It is a very well organised corruption racket. Guess voters are not going to get those 1000  notes for the next elections, if it happens soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog helps a child cross the road </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 05:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once again in Chennai, a collective sense of decency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 04:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/sa-V2S2nYRc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Scratch...don't stop" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 06:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is the source](https://youtu.be/BMUD3l1KbS8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Repo man having a bad day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 06:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 05:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sasikala is probably the most hated person in TN today. Don't see this arrangement lasting more than 6 months. Unless the party MLAs agree on a reasonably able leader from among themselves soon, the party itself is not going to last long. And that might be a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 20:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably an instinctive reaction to danger. I once saw a cobra throwup (what looked like) a small rat, when it could have very easily slipped into a drain without wasting time.

In this case the cobra would have found it difficult to move fast with 7 unbroken eggs inside it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 13:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/S9d9tQqfXvM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Startled cobra gets ready to flee, by throwing up the eggs it had recently swallowed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 13:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 11:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/4IUJXgiU9j8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crazy Strayan covers himself with clay and a coat he made from the hides of roadkill, to raid a wild bee hive, WCGW? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 11:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I will HMB and do a backflip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/_BLhtDETzJs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boeing 737 at 37000 ft is overtaken by a 747 at 35000 ft, as seen by a 777 at 33000 ft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "F**k your cucumber, I want grapes too" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 08:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 14:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=321_1481087742) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man left his car running with his child inside. Child tried to drive the car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 14:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 11:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://m.miaopai.com/show/channel/DcHT7gL~EvJL4il00HgZlw__)

Gif speeded up 3x. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of control truck at an intersection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 11:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was commenting on the other comnents here, not your post itself.

Burial is not a prerequisite for a memorial, but children, saints and people who die at a very old age are sometimes buried in hinduism. My great-great grandfather was a philanthropist and a freedom fighter and he was buried and a memorial was built there.

Cremation is a custom, not an absolute rule in hinduism. In ancient times people were always buried in the south, usually in large pots. Archaeologists have excavated a large number of these sites, both in the south and at Indus Valley sites. Cremation became more common only after Vedic practices became more common, after rulers here brought in brahmins to run their temples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking morons. How the fuck can you get a memorial tomb if you get cremated. Way too many ignorant bhaiyyas here judging tamils by what people post on randia. Comments like "secret Christian" just shows how much that stupid sub influences your thinking. Am I to judge you clowns by what the aaptards post there? If you are reading this, and if any of your Reddit accounts are still subscribed to that sub, you guys are as insignificant to me as a hair on Kejriwals left ball.

/Drunk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 17:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look at my post history, you'll notice I usually title gifs with an unexpected twist, but not on this sub. There is a specific rule about descriptive titles here. I am not sure if even this title is descriptive enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Filming the storm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man steps on the wrong pedal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three little words no bureaucrat in Jayalalithaa's government wanted to hear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 04:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=943_1480945986) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dancing in the street </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 09:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [French soccer coach freaks out after being hit by a paper plane](https://www.google.co.in/amp/www.foxsports.com/soccer/story/watch-this-french-soccer-coach-freak-out-after-being-hit-by-a-paper-plane-112816.amp.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French soccer coach got hit by a paper plane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 09:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 18:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, stupid title. Apologies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 17:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds ominous considering bad news is announced late night usually, to avoid trouble. Maybe we are just being prepared for more bad news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 14:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A whale shark is a shark, not a whale. It is quite common in Indian coastal waters not just in the Pacific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Finance Minister Chidambaram makes embarrassing mistake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 14:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 14:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/YdzIslm-i6c) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lion snatches a wild dog meal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 14:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 10:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also boycott newspapers and magazines which are printed on paper, since paper is made from trees.

 Each Year More than 20 million trees are consumed for production of book papers and about 95 million tress are consumed for newsprint.

 Deforestation is the source of 25% of human caused greenhouse gas emissions.

 Over 40% of the global industrial wood harvest is used to make paper.

 Forests that have been cleared and allowed to regrow do not store as much carbon as an undisturbed forest. In one study in Ohio, a forest that was cleared and allowed to regrow for 70 years stored only half as much carbon as a nearby forest that had never been disturbed.

 The pulp and paper industry is the 4th largest emitter of greenhouse gases among U.S. manufacturing industries.The paper industry contributes 9% of total carbon dioxide emissions from manufacturing.

 Paper makes up 26% of landfills. Degradation produces methane a greenhouse gas with 23 times the heat trapping capacity of carbon dioxide. Landfills are the source of 34% of methane releasesthe single largest source in the U.S.

[Source](http://www.greenpressinitiative.org/impacts/climateimpacts.htm)

Ofcourse the press would never mention the environmental disaster they are responsible for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 05:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprised how well informed Goyal is, even of a clown like Krugman. Krugman is a known Clinton ass-licker who highly praised Bill Clinton's bills which made it very easy for poorer people with low credit ratings to get housing loans in the 90s. These housing reforms led to the subprime crisis. When the crisis actually hit, he became a big critic of Bush without mentioning once Clinton's role in it and his praise for it.

He was a big critic of Obama during the 2008 primaries because he was expecting to get a role in the US government if Clinton won. Hence his opposition to Obama, nothing to do with economics.

And the day Trump won and Hillary lost, he wrote in the NY Times that US had become a failed state! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 16:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=772_1480776638) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 16:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=772_1480776638) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kitten has a close call </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 16:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kitten on the road </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 16:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 15:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think the catfish were eating in the car? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Losing all hope, suicidal pigeon chooses a BONE SHATTERING end </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 14:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hauling a car out of a river </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 14:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> India takes Goa - 1962 (News reel) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 13:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 15:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Source](https://youtu.be/CalrMW-jvPk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 15:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video source](https://youtu.be/CalrMW-jvPk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
