<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject547</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they were expecting them to drive it out of the garage which they didn't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then i don't know what to tell you, maybe you freak out alot and lose ability to aim? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not as good as you think you are; sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of them, destiny is horrible buy minecraft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And just like in video games you lose information that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two girls one cup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moment that changed everything.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, go on ebay and buy now option for sega game colection with sonic, you'll have more fun. Unless you love banjo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did at the end (i feel) she said that she isn't prepared at all and is basically like an idiot, and that's probbably why people don't like her. But then again we havent seen her campaign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna live, live, live til i die! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love space ghost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finaly...origins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> season3episode1spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come one of the rick's from seal team ricks tells our rick that the council has his summer and morty? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where are we going? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude wtf? That is scary, my nephew already watches youtube videos of boring shit, imagine how soon these kids learn that the internet can be borring really fast  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lolol my 3yo nephew already watches a youtuber and some episodes of some lady playing with toys has like a kagillion views, why the hell are we leatting kids watch youtube at the age of 3-4? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe you let him touch that, it's not 20$ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gamertag's don't have _
Is it psn account or no underscore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds halarious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good gimmick for a beach restroom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be taken two ways, a joke as in it was a fake episode(i don't think so) or that he did it on purpose to cliffhang everyone because(no spoilers) but after yiu watch it, You'll be like well why the hell did they even show us that if we have to wait( the writers want to piss us off) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adult swim
Reddit
Kiss cartoon
Qperantly daily motion has it too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, go back to rehab
Lol kidding3 but probably go back anyway because we have to wait 3-5weeks for them to air the rest. They gave us a sneak peak and aired the whole episode 1 of season 3 on april 1st </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah man, rude
I was just saying that you could either say it's funny because women are jokes, or it's a joke because she's stupid and doesn't realize that god loves men better because he gave us several fuck toys for life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess i would be pretty mad too if people were just ready to throw me to a death sentance without hard evidence.
it also maybe seems like the council was trying to get rid of him just because, and not because they care about random ricks
Yeah, it seems like he really really hates the idea that ricks thinks that they need eachother in order to do good or be safe in the galaxy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tammy's obviosly going to use mecha bird person to make rick want to kill himself and then she will refund the galactic federation and then re flood the earth and get the secret to interdimensional time travel and kill the smith family </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was that payback for? Trying to kill him i doubt it, was it for accusimg him of killing ricks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use 4 demimsions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That joke could be taken two ways... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that he new that he was going to have the first episode air on april 1st so that he could get the jump on us and make the people who were watching adult swim that night and thinking that dragonball super would be on and then we see a new rick and morty scene and hear "and that's how i got out of space prison!! Because pretty much right after he says that, he states that he knows that he's in a brainalizer and that makes the intro "and that's how i got out of space prsion" extreemley irellevant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But also the fact that morty doesn't ever pass puberty in almost any deminsion because that deminsion's rick gets him killed (comic book) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that his character is one that likes too keep people in the dark unless he needs to include you in something, i mean he had to know that morty was going to be spitefull and shoot him during the hostage negotion without looking at the note on the gun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, not one bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just seems kinda like they're trying to hint to the reason on why she loves rick so much? It's suspicious to say the least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Season3episode1? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why does rick wink at beth when he says for everybody at the end? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it has a huge delay, i tried playing mw3 1v1 on it when the xbox one first came out, and i usually dominate that whole playlist and demolish everyone. I got like 4-6 kills as apposed to like 30-50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An alarm clock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did your dad randy buy it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was so much better in this picture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll just sign in to xbox.com on safari then to find out when people are playing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, honostly i've only stuck with xbox my whole life is because it's the only consol with halo's ongoing franchise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xbox one app for apple store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not working, tried uninstalling it and turning the phone off and on again before reinstalling it and did this several times, this get's very annoying becaise it crashes everytime i open it.

Has anyone else had this problem and possible have found a solution? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you update it? You can make it so that you're xbox doesn't atomatically update so you might not have it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely true:( they should've had all these small features to begin with, liks clubs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also don't approve of them removing snap either, or the new update making it so you don't go home when you click the home button, and now the home screen is completely uselss so i don't know why they didn't just take it away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What!? That's an awesome feature. Thanks for pointing it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, i love this show so it's cool to see it get another season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Copenhagen makes a lot of bikes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, but it's not like abc shits out like 5 new shows a year that could take it's place just because the execs are bored with a show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, i enjoy the show and that's why i'm angry about them not wanting to renew it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, but they don't and it's bullcrap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not to be a "bitch", i did because it misinformed people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, salty because you're wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first reason i thought of that the ratings are lower than expectations is because of streamimg services </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know that, i thought it was a series. But that still won't matter to the fact that abc doesn't air comedies if they're low in ratings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's another possibility. But at the same time if abc doesn't like the ratings(which they do not) they won't bother airing it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if you read or not but it would be helpful if you did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jimmy the oldest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but they express displeasure of the ratings, also they have imaginary mary and they are making a new series as i just said with the recast of the brother. But that doesnt mean that they won't change their minds and keep it because it does have a pretty decent plot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> abc's real o neals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this show probably ended because abc doesn't like the ratings. Of course i love this show, but abc doesn't i guess  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But why does he ask for light beer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rude comments.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people who are complaining about it not being aired don't want to watch it in japanese because then english dub will just be aired this upcoming saturday( not trying to say that you're not helping) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how you do it? But my friend's says something like love demon or some other random stuff like donky rider and a yellow star </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well...body. Technically character has nothing to do with someone's body, nevertheless rick's c137 brain is still alive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mcdonads gives juice boxes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And people wonder why our society as humans keeps failing in new ways on a daily basis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to read the bottom/question first, the top runon paragraph should be common sense to true fans, but is also a great refresher for shawshank rickdemption's twists or addition of information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably, minecraft is so boring now, especially to consol players, lego games have always heen much much better than minecraft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was from a tottaly fabricated origin story, so none of this true right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would've guessed aids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well anyone can improvise, but he lost his training for it, so it's like a pokemon battle with a veteran who hasnt played the last two new games and doesn't remember exactly what kind of type a pokemon is by looking at it. Rick has lost this abillity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
