<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7338</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political reality limits the de facto application of discretionary fiscal policy as reaction to economic shocks by between 1 and 2.7 percentage points of GDP (research paper) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 10:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a significant degree of attenuation bias due to recall error amongst a representative sample of mortgaged Irish households (research paper on housing wealth effect) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 10:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long-term detrimental education effects of Spanish and French colonial systems revealed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 13:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theory and evidence that the demise of Jewish proselytism was due not to the destruction of the Second Temple but to the apostle Paul's strategic decision that Gentiles need not convert to Judaism to become Christians. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 13:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nice Guys Finish Last: Do Honest Taxpayers Face Higher Tax Rates? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 11:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High party discipline and high party strength induce legislators to stay committed to the party's promised policies because party leaders are able to punish deviations (research paper) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 10:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 11:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes... as almost all instruments, this one is highly problematic and questionable. However, the simple correlations seem quite strong and the problem with the exclusion restriction is at least discussed. Others (Gorodnichenko and Roland 2011 AER) have used distance of frequency of blood types A and B as an instrument for individual responsibility which is also questionable. But not matter what you do, it seems that there is something interesting in this variable "individual responsibility" which needs to be further explored.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a negative correlation between rainfall variation (exogenous agricultural risk) and individual responsibility. Using rainfall variation as an instrument, a large positive effect of individual responsibility on economic development can be observed (research paper) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 15:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The burden imposed by tax codes and tax compliance constitutes a barrier to firm entry which is independent of general taxes on corporate profits (research paper) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prediction Markets, Social Media and Information Efficiency: Exploiting Twitter data surrounding a unique, newsworthy and identifiable event (research paper) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 16:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prediction Markets, Social Media and Information Efficiency: Exploiting Twitter data surrounding a unique, newsworthy and identifiable event (research paper) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 14:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shared mental models: Learning to cooperate by improving interorganizational systems thinking (research paper) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 13:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 10:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose the authors speculated that your argument would also hold for Belgium but the results show that it was not the case.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
