<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8607</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Jersey teen pleads guilty in foiled plot to kill Pope </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ICE Seized a Mother of Special Needs Kids With No Criminal Record Before She Could Say Goodbye </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're already down 50% fewer eggs from 2016 because they *missed the manufacturing deadline*  the kids would do a better job running the White House at this point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The White House has also ordered half the amount of Easter eggs as President Barack Obamas White House did in 2016 due to the limited manufacturing window for this years Easter Egg Roll, White House official retailer Lara Kline told the Times.

So already 50% fewer eggs than Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ACLU gonna sue the fuck outta Jeff Sessions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens when you blow up a nuclear missile mid flight?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rich or poor, black or white, 

Healthcare is a human right!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mosquitoes have more integrity than the GOP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [meanwhile](http://i.imgur.com/94Y8h2u.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only we could just flip him on his shell, but I think it's all jello back there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is a shit stain on history. Who shouts "you lie!" to the first black president of America, in the middle of his first speech to Congress? And of *course* he would be from South Carolina, a wannabe Calhoun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should've brought tomatoes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all to distract from their Russian paychecks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only by comparison </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New York and Palm Beach and America need to tax the fuck out of the Trumps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our commander in chief, on the other hand, probably thinks he could just build himself one of those luxury bunkers in New Zealand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The VA would be largely defunct if we had a single payer system, but we should probably keep it until then.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But who listens to foreigners these days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The boss won't listen when one man squawks / but he's got to listen when the union talks" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The U.S. is already getting hit with more intense droughts, but only 10% of farmers think climate change is fueled by human activity...and they supply 25% of all the world's grains. What happens when the droughts don't end? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everybody Wants Freedom  a civil rights record album performed anonymously by singers called the Carolina Freedom Fighters, who remained unnamed for their own safety. USA, 1963 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gloria Richardson brushes off a National Guardsman at a civil rights demonstration in Cambridge, Maryland, June 1963 [1024x885] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of Americans also stood up in Texas for their immigrant neighbors  This is what America looks like! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right-to-work backers in Missouri turning to courts to stop union-led ballot initiative </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole point of fake news is to appear impartial, like an alternative fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any non-anecdotal evidence?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the only way they can sustain an erection without Viagra. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An honest partisan is more trustworthy than a lying fence-sitter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands take to Dallas streets to stand up for immigrants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under the new law, all felony charges against juveniles will begin in a newly-established Youth Part of the criminal court system, presided over by a family court judge where offenders will have access to additional intervention services and programming. 

Any violent felony charge that fails a three part test will be automatically referred to family court. 

When detention is necessary, juveniles will no longer be held in adult county jails but youth detention facilities regulated by the state office for children and family services. 

If a juvenile is convicted in the Youth Part of the criminal court system and sentenced to state prison, they will instead be incarcerated in an adolescent offender facility separate from adults. 

All non-violent felony charges and misdemeanor charges will be automatically referred to family court, unless the district attorney demonstrates extraordinary circumstances that justify retaining them in the Youth Part of the criminal court system. 

http://nyassembly.gov/Press/20170407c/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York will no longer prosecute 16 and 17 year olds as adult criminals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget Gulf War syndrome 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gulf_War_syndrome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be useful to see what % of followers are eggs for other celebrities for comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We weren't planning on traveling anyway" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ignorance is strength! 

War is peace! 

Trump is president! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How did that work out?

Once in power, the communists embarked upon a program of rapid modernization centered on separation of church and state, eradication of illiteracy (which at the time stood at 90%), land reform, emancipation of women, and abolition of feudal practices.

Traditional practices that were deemed feudal - such as usury, bride price and forced marriage - were banned, and the minimum age of marriage was raised. Education was encouraged for both genders and it became normal for women in the cities to wear whatever they wanted and for men to go clean shaven.

These new reforms were not well received by the majority of the Afghan population, particularly in rural areas, who saw them as un-Islamic and as a forced approach to Western culture in Afghan society. Several rebel groups declared a Jihad against the new government. 

The US took advantage of that and funneled billions of dollars to Jihadi rebel groups via the CIA's Operation Cyclone. The USSR also intervened but ultimately retreated, and in 1991, the USSR collapsed. In 1992, the Afghan government was replaced with an Islamic state. Jihadi groups then fought each other until the Taliban took over in 1996.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yeah but I never believed in fiscal responsibility anyway." - Every Republican in America </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't betray people you were never with, either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
 **I can look in their faces and say 'You can't come'. I'll look them in the face.**

The only children Donald Trump cares about are the ones he appoints to office.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come all the right-wing radicals grieving over their lost America can't even use punctuation properly? Trump is losing it over immigrants, yet he doesn't even know how "quotation marks" work. And God help the next idiot who THINKS THIS MAKES THEM SMARTER. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The rule would require financial advisers to act in their customers best interest  not in their own interest or in the interest of their investment firm.

Just more leftist propaganda! The exploitation of the working class is what makes America great! 

/s

Fuck this president and everything he stands for.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some countries actually do have upper age limits for political office, including the two most populous countries, China and India. The state of Pennsylvania also imposes a mandatory retirement age on its judges.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *don't run </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fill the jails, militarize the police, erase civil liberties, terrify the children, criminalize the harmless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Union, Victory And Freedom Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, USA, 1930s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're Next! CIO, USA, 1941 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long Live the Strike! United Farm Workers, USA, 1960s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, we're living in a much shittier version of the Cold War. These baby boomers are going to get us all killed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lazy ass shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I was not allowed to call my husband, who was waiting outside with our children. Instead, an agent seized my phone. When it was returned, nothing worked as it had previously. I am left to assume that its contents were copied.

Fuck that shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a deterrent alright. Travel, tourism, patriotism - all deterred. 

But terrorists? They already use burner phones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I can start a movement trying to clear up space to make reserves for invisible unicorns, and use the defense that "people were laughing at other movments too"

You could, but it's quantity that matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TLDR, China is willing to end the ban on U.S. beef and allow foreign investors to become majority shareholders in Chinese financial firms, but this is just an offer for the start of negotiations which the Trump administration is yet to respond to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any new disease outbreak would be great for Trump, another excuse to militarize the border. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America, land of the scared, home of the groped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should really ask the people who work there. Madina Toure wrote this article, she has a public Twitter account and LinkedIn, I'm sure she can verify all your conspiracy claims.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "CREDIBLE" is completely subjective. Women's suffrage was laughable until it happened. Civil rights was criminal until it happened. Gay marriage was absurd until it happened. Saying that you don't like something doesn't mean anything unless you're organized - and historically, the left has been better organized (out of necessity). 

Also, your complaints about absentee fathers and "internal" problems are badly dated, from a time when people didn't acknowledge that the economy is the basis of social relations. That's why black activists call for practical solutions like jobs and housing and criminal justice reform, not useless guilt tripping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are all these offended onlookers? If they exist, they must be pretty silent or disorganized (which in politics is the same thing). Plenty of people were laughing and fuming when women protested for suffrage, when black people protested for civil rights, when gay people protested for same sex marriage, and look where being a disdainful onlooker got them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jared Kushner isn't editing the Observer anymore than Jeff Bezos is editing the Washington Post. Newspapers have owners, editors and writers who are all independent individuals, not tentacles of an octopus. Thinking black people are puppets of Jared Kushner rather than the subject of one journalist's article is, frankly, batshit insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Organizing is mostly about numbers. I don't know what you imagine a "high quality" protest is, but it probably isn't as useful as getting the names and numbers of a hundred volunteers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non-profits, PACs, political parties, advocacy groups - they all need money to hire people and fund their operations, like any business. Working for free is an unsustainable business model. That's just how the world works. You can try it yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That narrative would make sense, except that black activism was on the rise, not decline during Obama... Technology, not society, is fueling the resurgence of black politics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with professional organizing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real irony is Observer Media is owned by Jared Kushner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Activists Call Donald Trump the True Face of Our Country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here we go again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anyone Trump won't betray?!

Seriously though - if this guy fucked with the elections, he needs to subpoenaed. Who knows who his accomplices might be?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knew a spoon-fed billionaire would be a lazy-ass layabout? Not even a hundred days and he's already given up on the job. This man is proving every comedian right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone's getting flustered... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young supporters of the left-wing communist government in Afghanistan celebrate the first anniversary of the April Revolution, 1979 [980x645] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police and state troopers attack a civil rights march in Canton, Mississippi, 1966 [670x456] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Nixon visits U.S. troops in South Vietnam, July 30th 1969 [1500x1008] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Delegates from Somalia in Moscow for the 6th World Festival of Youth and Students, 1957 [800x543] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antiwar Activists Challenge Armys Domestic Spying Apparatus in Ninth Circuit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Border Patrol agents pose with Mexican alcohol smugglers and their contraband, Texas 1920s [758x517] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Naco Arizona and Naco Mexico, hand-in-hand after their annual binational cross-border volleyball match </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 06:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The Masses* was a short-lived American socialist magazine that existed from 1911 to 1917, when it was shut down by the U.S. government. This cartoon comes from the January 1915 edition, and refers to the ongoing developments in imperial Russia (later to become a full-blown revolution) as well as in WWI. 

Six months earlier, Germany had declared war on Russia on July 19th 1914 - a largely anticipated event. But barely a week before that, the Russian capital of St. Petersburg had already been under siege by its own workers, in a widely-covered massive and violent general strike. St. Petersburg was in anarchy from July 3rd to July 10th, as workers flooded the streets, clashed with police, and destroyed public property. 

Not until the 17th - two days before war - was the city back in order, and in the wake of the strike, several left-wing publications were shut down, sympathetic members of government were exiled to Siberia, and tensions remained high between the people and the government. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another World is Possible Mike Alewitz, USA, 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [And old-fashioned snake oil.](https://www.infowarsstore.com/super-male-vitality.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America: the most expensive schools for the most indebted students </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Graduation](http://i.imgur.com/VqFXxKh.jpg) by Steve Sack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surely the Germans will not get this far! The Masses, USA, 1915 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, so emotional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fascinating advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell did I do to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Some Things You Research](https://i.redd.it/vbe23y982dqy.jpg) by Tony Auth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
