<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8985</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bots? How high are you right now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think morally you've forfeited your right to life. 

Why? What magic spell is cast upon breaking and entering that turns it into a capital offense?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sooo cute. You should definitely post this over on /r/aww too it would do very well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sauce: https://www.nasa.gov/feature/goddard/2017/scientists-find-giant-wave-rolling-through-the-perseus-galaxy-cluster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA Simulation of Distant 'Tsunami' of Gas in The Perseus Cluster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, I think it was this one showing spalling: http://wordpress.mrreid.org/wp-content/uploads/2013/01/hypervelocity-impact.jpg

Meanwhile this is the kind of shielding (called Whipple Shielding) used for spacecraft: http://wordpress.mrreid.org/wp-content/uploads/2013/01/whipple-shield.jpg

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at those little beans!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are, although not exactly constantly. There are attempts made to place them in orbits free of large known debris, and for small debris they're shielded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For better or worse, cryptocurrency has made that difficult or impossible, depending on how intelligent and resourceful people are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reactiongifs.com/r/btchplz.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) No, they aren't. Kansas, for example, has a significantly lower poverty rate than, say, California.

Uh huh... now lets compare median income and property values. 

2) Wood construction is standard in the US, even in high-end housing. However, when the cost of housing is 1/10th that of LA or NYC, material cost becomes much more important.

Yes, it is standard, but then most of the US population doesn't live with the threat of a tornado. 

3) A strong F3 or above will relocate a brick home just as easily as a wood frame.

Yes, but that's not why people in places like Okie still don't often have good storm shelters, that's a matter of money and the depth of bedrock. 

4) The odds of a tornado hitting a particular house is very slim. Much more cost efficient to have a single reinforced room.

Unless that room is underground, see your comment #3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sounds like you have been. You spam random crap with poor grammar and spelling so I assume you are the only one who can read it.

Moments earlier...

made more than the *knowckoff* mcdonalds you manage and spent more in clubs than you were offering to bet.

*lol*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smiling Face, Blurry Tail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cyber-Insecurity Is A Gift For Hackers, But It's Our Own Governments That Create It. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...And we spy on them... and everyone else... and everyone else spies on us and everyone else.

Have you not been paying attention?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  All they do is complain about how criticism of Israeli policy (especially towards the Palestinians) is antisemitism.

Hyperbole

They have fundamentally bribed the US government into being footstool for Israeli foreign interests

Cite?

Their sanctimonious approach in the Middle East is quite frankly disgusting.

Ironic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's usually meant to protect against the kind of thing we see here sometimes in the US, when some old bastard decides that "Castle Doctrine" means it's a fire sale on murder. You're allowed to defend yourself, and if that means killing a potentially armed intruder, so be it. A lot of these laws cover the less savory outcomes, like chasing them and then killing them, or restraining them and killing them. 

Very few countries in the Western world don't allow for you to kill in self defense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a handy rule: Always find the actual study and read it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Palestinians are too convenient a political bludgeon for too many people to ever really catch a break. It's good to see Bernie cut through the bullshit on this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gears and Gears and Gears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Wow, this Bob Smith sure says "Inshallah" a lot..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strong argument, maybe you two went to the same pre-school?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Because sometimes people don't leave their windows open; in fact the people you probably most want to home-invade are probably pretty paranoid about you doing just that. It's also very hard to perform the kind of low-effort mass SIGINT of just... reading everyone's messages and mail, when people encrypt. 

They don't want to break into houses, they want to have a master key and you just trust them not to abuse it. "They" in this case, is not just the UK either, it's the US, and many other governments. In China they're more invasive, but also a lot more open about the fact that they're invading every part of someone's life. Here you're supposed to cheer about some magical concept of absolute freedom while everything you say and do is algorithmically scrutinized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Your premise? Yes it is. 

Really? "I know you are, but what am I?"

Jesus... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yea, guilt by association? 

Well you do make a valid po-

 Idiot leftist.

...Well that was quick. *lol* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least roll an account without you in T_D *lol* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slow-Mo Bird In Flight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no... it's retarded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you never tell anyone and keep a perfect secret, that also means you can rarely or never use it; at first that's not so hard, but the longer you try to keep the secret, the harder it becomes. Every time you act or don't act you create a datapoint to be tracked and analyzed, and you can obfuscate for only so long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no... claim to have discovered incredible means by which you can produce and harness black holes, and use them for nearly limitless energy. Free energy would solve a lot of problems that most superheroes couldn't hope to even think about. The best thing is that nobody (or very few people) would know the truth; that you're a superhero who saved the world by becoming its most wealthy and powerful person... =D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a pretty well known event; a record-breaking cosmic ray... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what I'd do without my ~~6' long prehensile tail~~ hands! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people who live there are overwhelmingly dirt-poor, and all of what you describe would cost money, especially in regions with very deep bedrock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impressive non-sequitur!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would never work! She's a shark and he's... made of meat. *Sob* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to guess without even checking that you're a T_D troll on a new account. Am I right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you just need them to work on "evenhanded" and "fair" because "not lying" is a low and shitty bar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, nothing is less safe than keeping it with Trump to begin with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually a really good point, and the tiger could be a Navy SEAL too! 

No wait... none of this can work. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can You See Through My Mesh? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then cite "most economists" by all means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...And who as proven to be more evenhanded, fair, and honest than Wikileaks?

*lol* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point... being the point at which people with accounts younger than the election in question say so? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... *that's* a rumor, but you've already swallowed the drug thing?

*lol*

Whatever you say, 10 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've never heard of an 88 year old man?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what happened.. I didn't delete it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sell? They just get subpoenas and roll over like dogs; they sell to everyone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really... crocs can't really fight for very long before the exertion itself would kill them; they're ambush hunters who give up after a miss. If it couldn't drown the bear or otherwise disable it at once, the bear would just... crush it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC The answer was on an episode of QI, and in fact bears and tigers *were* made to fight to the death in previous eras... by assholes. Again, IIRC, the bear just bites the tiger's skull and kills its every time. Tigers are amazing ambush predators, but grizzly bears are tanks; it's no contest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...In a dark room.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hollande vows 'response' to Macron hack attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVERYONE Loves Scritches... Everyone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Yeah, I can see how that would go wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd tend to agree that this kind of action is a red flag for mental problems, the worst being a personality disorder. It's a good thing that this happened in Canada; in the US he would simply be in prison, which I think we can both agree is the wrong move. If he turns out to be a hopeless case, there's time to figure that out when he's an adult after all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fast asleep. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pop-sci neurology aside, 16 year olds are quite varied, just like people of any age. Most people at any age wouldn't seriously consider SWATting someone, and few of the ones who would consider it would actually do it. Not to mention that 16 is fairly developed from a neurological perspective; you're potentially old enough to move on from a diagnosis of "Conduct Disorder" to "Anti-Social Personality Disorder" for example. 

Sure, they're still kids, but they're not blank slates who magically become new people a few years later either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And so cute too... those ears. XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems... *way* too lenient; how is that not life without parole?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Basically just a furry little kid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooh!! That's a great shot of a puppy too... you must have been patient or lucky to get this one without lots of motion blur. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, his downfall was being the kind of impulsive psychopath who would SWAT someone, which then explains the rest of the behavior which got him in trouble. The kind of people who could carefully plan a SWATting are almost overwhelmingly not the kind of people who *would*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't know, but really... who cares? It's a gif on Reddit, just enjoy it or don't; if you find yourself nitpicking titles maybe it's time for a break?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point, I honestly hadn't considered it; I just take all of the coded language and symbolism and "it's about pride" nonsense for granted at this point... and I shouldn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Play With Me!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing that's leaked or otherwise been released so far indicates that they've had much luck attacking encryption directly, which is why they're shitting themselves inside-out to try and *legislate* the problem; if you make it a crime to encrypt, you don't have to deal with the technical problems.

Step 1: Spend years smearing anyone who using encryption as either paranoid, or criminal, especially a terrorist or a pedo. 
 
Step 2: Link high-profile crimes to "encryption" and refer back to Step 1.

Step 3: When public sentiment shifts, possibly after an inevitable attack, shove through legislation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^This, except that the pro-confederate/christian-nation types in the US are *much* more prevalent (especially in the military) than neo-Nazis are in Germany. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inner Torus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://arxiv.org/abs/1310.4319 Might not be a bad place to start. 

And the answers here have some good recommendations for further reading: https://physics.stackexchange.com/questions/36303/introduction-to-ads-cft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bottom line: the Tories want a privatized NHS, and they realized that if they slowly gut the NHS they might get their way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also true! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just had to say, great answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh look at those eyes and ears! That pup is already totally into you. 

And that nose, my god what a cutie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Catch Me If You Can!!!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charlie Brooker lines up some pretty good stuff, and that was from his "Yearly Wipe" specials. Adam Curtis (the documentarian who made the clip) is also a very interesting guy. 

I'm glad that you liked it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wcy8uLjRHPM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhere, the Louis Slotin of robotics has no idea what his future holds... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://prod.sandia.gov/techlib/access-control.cgi/1991/910657.pdf

It's at Sandia National Labs, using 4 dual-stage light gas guns to accelerate (to over 8 km/s) small objects simulating space debris or micrometeoroids impacts on shielding and that kind of thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a totally understandable issue to run into, I'm glad you found the link helpful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, the degree to which Murdoch's tentacles are deep into the UK can't be overstated. Surely after the News of The World ended in... what...a sham inquiry and The Sun on Sunday? 

He could murder an MP on live tv and he'd get away with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been asked and answered a lot, so I'm going to be brief:

Current fusion schemes produce high energy neutrons which cause atomic sputtering of the reactor, turning previously strong materials brittle. There is no known way to prevent this, and a practical power plant needs to spend most of its time generating power, not down for maintenance. 

D-T Fusion is the most commonly explored, and it requires Tritium which is rare, radioactive, and is currently produced by fission reactors.

D-T Fusion requires a "breeding blanket" which can produce tritium fuel, otherwise you're just using fission plants to crank out tritium very inefficiently and at great expense, producing high-grade waste, etc. 

The diverter: a way to channel some of the plasma out of the reaction (in toroidal designs at least) is *incredibly* hard to model, and the instabilities in introduces are problematic, also leading to rapid wear.

In general, modern fusion reactors (not power plants, such a thing is nowhere near realized) can't run for very long, or very often before parts need to be replaced. 

This is related to the issue of the plasma coming into contact with the chamber, which burns the chamber and cools the plasma; both are undesirable outcomes. 

It is almost comically difficult to squeeze plasma with magnets to the incredible densities/temps required for fusion on Earth. It takes a lot of computing power, experimentation, time, and money; none of which is about producing a power plant, but just about learning more about how plasma works under those circumstances.

There are a lot of reasons to have hope for fusion as a source of power... in a hundred years or more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you need to go back to square one on this, but that's not a problem.

http://www.quantumdiaries.org/2010/02/14/lets-draw-feynman-diagams/

That should answer your questions, and more importantly, teach you the various conventions of the diagrams.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Well that was my one guess, sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Essential even! Kidding aside though, it was designed to study that style of locomotion through trees, called "Brachiation." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, not bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, then what you're seeing may well be the trucks of guys/gals who spend a significant amount of leisure time hunting. Drive up to the mountains for a weekend... that sounds doable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's impressive, but still nothing like a power plant, and fundamental issues have *not* been solved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's impressive, but still nothing like a power plant, and fundamental issues have *not* been solved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Are you supposed to be on the couch?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then it sounds like would have to be cultural, either as a way of saying you're that kind of guy, or maybe that you haul ass out of state on a regular basis to shoot deer? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flower: Ok, yeah, oh fuck yeah... now flick my stamen with your proboscis!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddamn it how many times do I have to tell you to stop looking at cute dog pictures when you should be working?... and it's creepy when you call the Golden Retrievers "blondes" Cypher! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be that; it's been a long time since I've been in Arizona and couldn't tell you. The culture it comes from though, would be hunting and off-roading... the latter seems less likely in Phoenix at least. Hunting though, I'd guess you'd find a pretty active hunting scene in that part of the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're usually used by off-roaders and hunters, and you're right, they're not meant to be used on the road. AFAIK that would be entirely illegal in any state in the US, to run them on the road.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean... is there a chance that you have the windows down on the warm days, and up on the rainy cold ones? The position of the windows make a huge difference in the quality of sound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You too, enjoy the vodka and the weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably remembered that they're all one sex, and just mixed up which... still it means you once knew, that's good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pleasure. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You joke, but I'm 99.99999% sure that this is fetish and someone, somewhere can't believe their luck. :|

Also, Six Seasons and A Movie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's... completely backwards; drones are male, workers are female.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Face of Patience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean... when I was a little kid I'd catch them in jars, look at them for a few minutes, then set them back on a flower. Adorable, and very necessary little creatures.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bumblebee shaking pollen onto herself, in slow motion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cranky?...No... Sleepy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...But half are men.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boots Full of Bunnies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rest is hugely varied, and probably subjective, but young and bored is a deadly combination on its own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she just threw it away, she'd have fewer problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of that aside, you have a bunch of young, physically fit, (and please let me emphasize this next one) *BORED* people... they're going to do a lot of stuff involving sex. The fact remains that our military is filled with many interesting people from a diverse range of backgrounds... who were crazy/ideological/desperate/dumb enough to enlist. To be fair, a fraction are not that, but a huuuuuge number are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A unicycle... wouldn't it just be quicker to walk, or run?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truly, a moron and a jackass; it's hard to imagine what an opossum could do to warren that reaction in the first place. 

...And why fire?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Look! Ith me! I'm Tuthk! Get it? Tuthk?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a nice spot for it too, and such a lovely pup. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think people wanted a hero out of it all, and Charles was never going to be that. Truthfully though, Diana wasn't that impressive IMO; just sort of privileged and depressed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh it's a lot... for a lot of people he's just seen as a moron, he believes in homeopathy... that kind of thing. 

It's not that he's seen as a bad person, just... a complete tool. There's an excellent answer by one David Stewart over on Quora:

https://www.quora.com/Why-is-Prince-Charles-unpopular

He's never really been a man of the people. He has a very posh voice, a very aloof demeanour and his attempts to connect with average people often comes across looking like someone desperately trying to conceal their true feelings, which appear to be a sort of baffled contempt.

While Britain is trying to modernise he still comes across as a guy who hasn't found anything funny since the Goon Show stopped broadcasting and only likes music if it's older than he is.

It doesn't help that the issues he seems to really care about don't connect with the people at all. While many of his subjects are struggling to make ends meet and concerned about big issues of the day, Prince Charles is really, really concerned about modern architecture which he loathes and despises. Instead of getting passionate about the state of public schooling or the something that affects people's day to day lives, he gets worked up because someone is designing a building he doesn't like. He's also concerned about the fact that scientific based medicine that has been tested and found effective takes precedence over homeopathy in the NHS. Something that hasn't endeared him to the medical profession and a lot of other people.

Of course what really drove the last nail in the coffin of his public perception was the fact that he was cheating on his beloved and adored and attractive young wife Diana with the unpopular, hated, older and unattractive Camilla. It was seen as a betrayal of the People's Princess (whose infidelity was forgiven for some reason).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The little toe-beans off the to the bottom left nearly killed me. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... you're not wrong, but coastal Spain is still probably going to heavily cater to Brits, and Paris to people from around the world for whom the common language is some form of English. 

Still... you're right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one knows, and in principle it may not even be possible to know. It may also not be a meaningful question; nobody really knows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
