<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2635</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 20:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, oops. I was talking about the SSA officers. Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 19:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't notice that, but they may have. To me, it seems like they did use an existing force- their own. Oig investigations are outside the scope of us Marshalls, for example, so it makes sense that they would equip their armed officers. Whether their officers should be armed is, I suppose, up for debate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 18:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Snopes](http://www.snopes.com/politics/guns/ssabullets.asp) seems to think it's for the organization's oig officers, which are armed as a part of their duties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 18:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Booo!"

"Very well. I promise to eliminate the zombie threat so god-fearing Americans no longer have to live in fear!"

"Aaaaaarghhhhh!"

"Very well. I promise more human flesh than ever before to the zombie voters, and complete protection from the evil hordes for human voters!"

"Yayyy!" "Braaaaaaiiins!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 22:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess any system has its flaws, huh? The US definitely has the same problem, as far as funding for mental health programs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 22:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that just by convention, or does that have something to do with the nature of the medical system in the UK? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 21:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have I been living with you too long, or did that make sense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 21:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is good to question, and also to collect as much information as possible before making an opinion. I hope the good people of Reddit display this much enthusiasm the next time they vote in their respective countries, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 20:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 20:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the same way, in that it's such a minor thing on Reddit, and probably not worth the time we've already put into it. It's been nice talking to you, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 20:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with you, but that's okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 20:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aware of that, and the tutorial is very helpful. If memory serves (and it may not) it was talking about how minor color corrections and changing a small amount (or single?) Pixels *may not* show up on the ela analysis. But such a massive change as suggested in this thread? I would expect to see that show up on the ela analysis. There's also cases where saving the image multiple times can reduce variation, but in the analysis you're seeing the variation that you would expect to find in a legitimate image. 

But maybe that's just me. Feel free to try it, if you want. It wouldn't be hard to Photoshop that same image and run it through the Fotoforensics tool. I'd be interested in seeing what you come up with.

So in one hand we have an ela that's consistent with a real image and we have the original poster (if you do a reverse image search) with the background story and other (unrelated) images from that day. On the other hand, we have people saying that it "looks" shopped to them. Of I were a betting man, I know which one of put my money on. 

Anyway, you're right that ela analysis isn't a smoking gun, but it's a pretty good indication in most cases.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 20:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please enlighten me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 19:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 19:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, [the ELA analysis](http://fotoforensics.com/analysis.php?id=732e6791c6b527f5b817495749324eed69f4402a.395100) looks pretty uniform.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 01:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [According to Wikipedia](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Headlight_flashing), it is illegal in some places.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 00:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And finished prematurely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 21:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gladly. I'm watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 13:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful. Those are the words we're putting on your tombstone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 12:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be specific, they have the same options as other federal employees under the fehb. That means they can choose one of the 300 covered plans, some of which are not affordable to many other federal employees. Plus, they do get access to military hospitals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 04:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The police talked to a woman on the phone that said she was Shelly Miscavige. A little bit of helium and I could probably prove she's alive to their satisfaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 17:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stupid longhorses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 01:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same format and elements in general, or same code specifically? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 18:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she does dig deeper, she WILL find out that you faked your suicide. Whatever positive feelings she had about you then will be completely obliterated by this decision. 

Let her remember the good times. Work to improve yourself, and be genuine. If you do this, you're proving to her that she was right to leave you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 17:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I've gathered on this sub, it's really only bad south of Hillard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mr. Trash Wheel is a browncoat. And provides photographic evidence that our Cap'n is a fan of him, right back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 01:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 02:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they in the same state? Things can get [a little complicated](http://www.dmlp.org/legal-guide/recording-phone-calls-and-conversations) if more than one state is involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 16:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on you! Glad it worked out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 01:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! That's a huge boost. What worked for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 22:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "100% of gynecologists have have called my genitalia 'Perfect, Absolutely Pristine.'" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 01:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 01:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never denied that, nor did I defend the handling of that particular scandal. My point is that if one is a realist, they will recognize that reform needs to be encouraged. That's all- criticism of those acts is not mutually exclusive with accepting what reform does occur.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 16:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can say that about a lot of groups. You can probably say the same thing about your own country. 

Perhaps some would prefer to dismantle the organization entirely. Maybe, for events in the past, that's warranted. But it's not realistic- not in the near future. Perhaps it would be better for humanity if we allowed it to overcome its own past and grow in a positive direction? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 06:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 05:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it publicly accessible? I'm always looking for new adventures with the kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 16:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant username?

Relevant username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 15:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They like to gamble, but they don't like risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 15:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not install your own and run it across systems and a network you control?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 17:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To play devil's advocate (maybe literally in this case), she could easily say that she's her own person and considers former president Clinton to be just like any other past president that has done things she doesn't agree with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 05:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 04:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I get called that a lot :(

edit: oh, you said a**r**tist. I thought you said... you know what, nevermind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 04:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try again. I had to touch up the fishnet stockings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 04:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You're into some weird shit, man](http://i.imgur.com/DUzprx4.jpg). I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 00:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  While fiction about underage character isn't illegal

This is true, but Amazon does have rules about underage characters in erotica. They have rules about actual incest, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 13:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what about the next president, when Congress tries this again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given that, I'd like to see the ven diagram of voat and /b/ users. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 15:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Just looks awkward to me](http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/51jLLUOkE7L._SX351_BO1,204,203,200_.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 13:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, /u/kl0wny! Unfortunately, /u/stackoverload had to drop out. Did you have any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 03:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Big One](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7pPRacG_fz0) by Alan Tew. 

[Appearance in Teen Lust](http://www.thebetamaxrundown.com/teen-lust-1979/), (SFW) largely featuring music by Tew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before it became the theme to The People's Court, "The Big One" was used in several porn movies including "The Opening of Misty Beethoven","Barbara Broadcast" and "Teen Lust" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 03:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 01:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! We've been pm'ing to work out the details </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 19:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll check it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 18:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're awesome, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 17:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be great! I'd really appreciate the assist, especially given your perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 17:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully! I really want to show them that hacking isn't what you see on TV (with the exception of the 100% accurate documentary, [Hackers](http://www.wired.com/images_blogs/underwire/2013/02/hackers_1995_rollerblading.jpeg)), but can be an actual career.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 16:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll check it out! I have to control the simulation, for gameplay purposes, but maybe I can get some ideas from there. Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Setting up a 'hacker bootcamp' for my office's Bring Your Child to Work Day. Not sure where to start. (x-post /r/asknetsec) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 16:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **edit: an awesome and knowledgeable redditor, /u/Stackoverload, is helping walk me through this.**

**edit2: Unfortunately, /u/Stackoverload, had other commitments that called him away from this. If anyone else can help out, I'd appreciate it.**

My office is doing a take your child to work day, and we're doing a 'hacker boot camp' to talk about the importance of vulnerability assessments and common web security issues. Problem is, it's a short suspense and I'm really not sure how to put it all together. 

I have multiple computers available with internet access. I have a web server (remote) I can dump files to. I was thinking about giving the kids a brief orientation about common issues, along with notes and tips as a handout. Things from the very basic levels of HackThisSite- checking the source code for comments, basic injection, things like that. It would be a simple game of capture the flag- first team through three 'levels' wins the competition. 

Now, here's my secret shame. I'm not that great at web programming. I know html and some css, but I don't really have the ability to do anything very complex. Is there a resource where I can get some ready-built code to host on my server? Or anything that I can put together that would be challenging, but not too challenging?

Thanks for any advice/help!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Setting up a 'hacker bootcamp' for my office's Bring Your Child to Work Day. Not sure where to start. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 15:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 15:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it makes you feel any better, many insects are nocturnal so they're more active when you're sound asleep. For that reason you probably don't actually feel it when they fall on your face at night. Incidentally, do you sleep with your mouth open or have nostrils? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 16:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was active duty, but I think the standards would be the same. It seems to me that custody-related issues would affect your ability to deploy, which puts it squarely in [JAG's](http://www.moguard.com/Assets/Pages/15/The-Adjutant-General.aspx?ID=66) realm. Have you contacted them? They may be able to provide advice or other resources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 04:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I missed this one. Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 17:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If reddit has taught me anything, it was Chris. Chris let the ducks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 01:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking Wednesday, being hump day and all. But you make a good point about Tuesday! Thanks for the advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best day of the week to email non-profit association members to ask for volunteers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 22:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really a small business, but a non-profit group. But I think the answer would be the same. 

I need to get some volunteers working towards a specific goal. I'm only looking at those that said they'd be interested in doing that sort of thing when they signed up. 

In your experience, what day of the week is the best day to get people engaged? I was going to do it Monday, but I know I don't feel very eager to start new projects on a Monday. And on Friday, I think people are pretty eager to finish up their work and get ready for the weekend. Starting new things might not be on their radar on that day. 

What days work for you, when you're trying to engage people?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 22:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iANAL, so this is my understanding as a government employee.

That would fall under the realm of "fraud, waste and abuse," which is the term for misuse or misappropriation of government resources. 

You ARE afforded certain protections when reporting suspected fraud, waste and abuse, but only when using the process for doing so (at least as far as that act is concerned). Talking about it to your friends or coworkers and accusing someone of it based on perception is not protected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 04:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, a little of both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 00:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 22:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I installed tinfoil to replace the Facebook app and DISA messenger so I get message notifications. Happy as a clam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 22:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you believe the nerve of that guy? Thinking you know how loud crickets are. I oughta tell him a thing or two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 22:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "No, I said distended *glass*hole!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 14:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But sometimes, it leaks :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 21:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People like [this](https://m.reddit.com/r/self/comments/3zi7qe/my_rlegaladvice_trolls_and_confirmation_thread/) have caused a lot of damage to people legitimately asking for help here. People like OP, in this case. 

You can argue that they at least raised interesting legal questions, but they also drove away a lot of great posters and made it much more difficult for real people to get advice they actually need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 21:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And cigarettes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 20:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't even have to malfunction. If little Billy jumps under the tires chasing a ball, the headlines will still be the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prerecorded emergency broadcast from the 1970s. Would have been played in the event of nuclear war. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 15:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 14:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donde esta el bao, mi amore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 01:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tweet where the shirts were [pulled from stores](https://twitter.com/Walmart/status/717111380663345153) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 13:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.fiverr.com/gigs/reddit/#page=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 13:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good start, but we won't see any real impact until the change.org and WeThePeople petitions take off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 23:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, we do a lot of things with dead bodies that they never consented to. For example, museums and the chunks of dead prostitute in my freezer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 22:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That reminds me; when was the last time we checked on our lemons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 18:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So do you also pronounce jpeg as "jfeg"?? Lol :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 18:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naw, I just screwed up the joke. Not the first time I've done that, lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 17:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was (supposed to be) the joke :) We all pronounce it Scoobah, but if the 'hard g' people were to apply the same logic, the u would have to be pronounced like in "Underwater" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 17:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, same here on both counts! The way I figure it, he made up the word- I'm fine pronouncing it the way he wanted it pronounced.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 17:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Gift," yes. That was supposed to be "gif." DYAC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 17:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when that day comes, we'll argue about whether it's pronounced scooba or scuh-buh.

The people that currently pronounce "gif" with a hard 'g' will probably advocate for the latter.

edit: holy shit, it was a joke. No more pm's, please. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 17:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Autocorrect got me. It was supposed to be gif.

The SCUBA question is a play on that debate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 17:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think... I think we've been watching different Simpson's episodes. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 16:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh? How does it work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 20:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Small thing, but there's a typo in your second image: minuets vs. minutes. Unless you're saying (correctly) that you can register to vote in the time it takes to perform a stately court dance of the 17th and 18th centuries in triple time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 20:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specifically, the [2014 Transparency Report](https://www.reddit.com/wiki/transparency/2014) read:

As of January 29, 2015, reddit has never received a National Security Letter, an order under the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act, or any other classified request for user information. If we ever receive such a request, we would seek to let the public know it existed.

This verbiage has been removed in 2015. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The warrant canary is missing from the 2015 reddit transparency report. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 20:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 16:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I set the microwave for 5 seconds longer than needed. That way, I can feel like I stopped it early and still enjoy fully-cooked food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 01:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been struggling for weeks to get a PayPal appID for my freelance writer's site. I've been through their help files and filled out the fields, but I'm clearly doing something wrong. I'd appreciate a hand with that, if anyone here is willing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 21:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a different interpretation, but that's a problem in and of itself. As you say, correctly, the bill is very ambiguous. But it's the parts that are NOT ambiguous that concern me.

Under the text of the law, a religious shelter could decide to refuse services to a person if it violates their beliefs. That part itself directly spelled out. Perhaps the intent is to protect churches who don't want to marry gay people, but that's not what the text states. It leaves a great deal of latitude for a religious organization that doesn't wish to provide food bank services to someone when it doesn't support their religious objectives. Or, as we already discussed, taking in someone that is gay or transgender. 

But we're both drawing on what 'could' happen depending on the interpretation and text of the bill, and that's one way that it's fundamentally flawed. Perhaps, then, the governor was correct in vetoing it for at least that reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 21:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 21:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How am I not making a point in citing the act? Didn't a provide a specific provision where a faith-based organization (such as a shelter, for example) may legally refuse service to someone based on their sexual orientation? 

I stand corrected on 10-1-1001. But I can't seem to find what that code actually is- the copy of the Georgia code that I was able to find online stops at around 10-1-900 or so. What, I wonder, does the proposed bill allow reference to 10-1-1001? (edit: I see- that was a proposed section that would be added to the Georgia code, which would protect organizations and employees from discrimination suits based on the internal text. Got it, and withdrawn)

We can disagree about whether or not such discrimination has occurred. That's fine and not really relevant to this discussion. But do you agree that a refusal of services as described in the article would be legal under the proposed bill?


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 20:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree! I think that's a gross perversion of the intent of the IRS code. Arguably, it violates the rule against private inurement, which means that a single person (or group of people) shouldn't benefit 'unfairly' from the charity's activities. Problem is that can be really hard to define. But morally it's wrong (IMO) for a pastor to live in a multi-million dollar home while others starve or live in the streets. 

If they're going to be taxes, they should have to prove their contributions to the needy and the poor for their deductions.

YES! I agree. I don't know how it could be done legally, but I wish there was some sort of test as to the societal 'value' of a church.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 20:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "(b) No faith based organization shall be required to provide social, educational, or charitable services that violate such faith based organization's sincerely held religious belief as demonstrated by its practice, expression, or clearly articulated tenet of faith"

That would have protected the actions of [THIS homeless shelter](http://thinkprogress.org/politics/2011/01/18/139396/georgia-homeless-gay-people/) which refused to serve gay people based upon their religious beliefs. Speaking of which, you said:

Find me a homeless shelter that has refused services to gay people and I'll send you to Cancun

Was that a sincere offer? I wouldn't mind a vacation. 

Edit: The proposed bill also reads:

A refusal by a faith based organization pursuant to Code Section 10-1-1001 shall not give rise to a civil claim or cause of action against such faith based organization or an employee thereof or result in any state action to penalize, withhold benefits from, or discriminate against the faith based organization or employee based on such refusal.

Where Code Section 10-1-1001 is the fair business practices act.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 20:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to be clear, are you saying you support those parts of the bill? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 20:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not relevant to this discussion. The issue is that it would have been legal to do so under the proposed bill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 20:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the provision that allows faith-based organizations to fire employees based on sexual orientation? Or the one that allows them to refuse services to gay people (for example, a homeless shelter refusing to allow a gay person to stay even if they have room)?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 20:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a small aside. 

The only thing churches should be forced to do is pay taxes

There's a few good reasons why this may not be the case. The agreement between churches and the government is that they'll basically stay out of each other's way. Of course churches have to follow the law, but it's perceived / desirable that they provide a community service that offsets government expenses. This specifically speaks to the churches (I'm including all religious faiths there) that provide a direct community benefit by having food banks, shelters, and other services consistent with their beliefs. 

Not all churches do this, of course. In my opinion, they *should*, but I don't think the government wants to decide what services constitute a community benefit. I would like to see an acid test of direct benefit to the community regardless of religious affiliation, but that's, like, my opinion, man.

The other more pressing issue is the 'rights' that paying taxes allows a corporation. Remember that a church is legally a corporation- just a special one under the same umbrella as a other charities. Without the special agreement afforded to charities, a church would get a direct voice in the government just like any company would. They could legally influence legislation and endorse a candidate. They could donate money to a particular candidate and support their causes. Right now, they can't legally do that (and yes, it happens. If you see it, you can report it to the IRS and they risk losing their 501c3 status). 

So there's definitely an argument to be made for taxing churches. But if we do so, we have to accept that the government will loosen the restrictions on what they can and can't legally do. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 18:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duh, you're only supposed to use wild west justice against the guilty ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 18:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why we need the "/s" tag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 23:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of examples of the term. [Here's one from the Ohio Supreme Court](https://supremecourt.ohio.gov/rod/docs/pdf/2/2012/2012-Ohio-4861.pdf).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 06:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We didn't want to say anything, but you deserve to know. You still smell like the bread- you've just gotten used to it. On the plus side, that's what we like about you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 00:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also known as [the loophole](http://youtu.be/j8ZF_R_j0OY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 17:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  something something take that bitchez

[Inspirational as fuck](http://i.imgur.com/Wuq34To.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 19:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same result by wearing something around your ankle that looks like a GPS house arrest monitor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 03:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, maybe the baby was born after the apocalypse hit. Because of that, he wasn't infected and didn't re-animate. Of course we don't know much about post-apocalyptic babies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 05:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's consensual and ~~fake~~ scripted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 21:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Spammers](http://www.redditsecrets.com/buy-reddit-accounts). They buy aged ~~Ccoubts~~ accounts so they have credibility when they start recommending products. A popular account would be valuable to them. Just like Red Bull (TM) is popular among people of all ages! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 21:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and once you establish tenancy they have to go through the legal process to get you out of there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 21:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to go to some sketchy areas for business trips. Pretty sure my boss was trying to kill me. 

In some of those areas, I carries a decoy walled and broken iPhone. If anyone were to ask persuasively for my possessions, they would get the decoys and I would go the other direction. Kind of like a lizard with it's tail. 

Never had to do it, but I was ready! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 06:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scientology, like many of the more 'outlandish' cults, have a big hurdle to overcome with new members: they have to seem legitimate and sane enough to keep them coming back until they're sufficiently conditioned to accept the more extreme concepts. I mean, if they invited you in and started talking about space aliens and clams on day one, you probably wouldn't come back. 

So Hubbard combined three things: common sense statements that sound deep until you remember that you once read them on a cereal box, things he stole from other people and his own special blend of moonbattery. 

For example, the UN created the [universal declaration of human rights](http://www.un.org/en/universal-declaration-human-rights/index.html), and defined 30 fundamental rights that we all share. Scientology claims to support those rights and uses that 'secular' message to get into schools. But with a twist. #27 talks about the right "to participate in the cultural life of the community, to enjoy the arts and to share in scientific advancement and its benefits" and "to the protection of the moral and material interests resulting from any scientific, literary or artistic production of which he is the author." Scientology just says that "copyright" is a fundamental human right. Probably self-serving, seeing as their secret church material is copyrighted. 

Or their 'study tech', which is a very flawed implementation of actually successful concepts. They borrow heavily from Montessori education, for example, but misapply it tot he point of uselessness. But they use that to establish and infiltrate schools. 

They often start off with a test called the "[Oxford Capacity Analysis](http://www.xenu.net/archive/oca/)" (which has nothing to do with Oxford), which can often seem legitimate, even through it's skewed to make the test-taker feel like they've done very poorly on the test and in life. But fear not! They have some courses that can help fix those specific problems. 

The basic courses are all pseudo-scientific, but add an element of "wow, you're really special and can do powerful things with your mind if you give us money. And did you know we're trying to save the world?" Once they find someone's 'ruin', they'll exploit that to get them in deeper and deeper. 

You can read a bit in Hubbard's on words [here](http://www.xenu.net/archive/infopack/5.htm), but [this](http://www.xenu.net/) is probably one of the best pages on the topic. This [page](http://www.ezlink.com/~perry/CoS/Theology/index.htm) gets pretty deep into comparing the theology with other systems. It's important that scientology claims to be compatible with all other religions, especially when you really look at the contradictions between them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 04:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, some of the stuff he stole from other philosophies, belief systems and research was pretty good. Until he screwed it up, at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 20:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't vouch for them, but here's one company that provides that service: http://www.imagingforensics.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 20:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but the edge colors (in the ela analysis) are consistent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 20:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fotoforensics is a good tool for this. The error level analysis check shows if different areas of an image have different compression levels, indicating modification. 

[One of these images](http://fotoforensics.com/analysis.php?id=7e8fb53afbd512b77eecc270c619c2617eda9573.18124 show=ela) shows that it's consistent across the image. 

The compatible edges in [This image](http://fotoforensics.com/analysis.php?id=e54a213a3f1016d7f4a0181cf22c810a8c613228.34205 show=ela) is consistent as well, also suggesting that the image is legitimate.

For comparison, [here's an image](http://fotoforensics.com/tutorial-ela.php) that has been digitally altered.

I'm not an expert in image forensics, but this looks legit to me.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 16:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're using the baconreader app, it doesn't parse the site correctly. It opens okay in the browser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 23:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naw, sour cream is generally complimentary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 22:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I now have you tagged as 'once ate urine' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At first glance, I thought Nathan Fillion had a very different bodily fluid adventure. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 17:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 16:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please make an effort to conform to the stereotype in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 15:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to clarify, are you saying that the women were hired and put into positions, but then later fired and blackballed due to their gender? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 13:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because of the weight loss or the kiddie porn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 13:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha, that bald guy with the boxes. adults r so dum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 14:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, thanks for the recommendation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 13:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, this is incredibly helpful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 12:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under the clipart gavel and the notification that the auction has ended, there's text saying that the item has been relisted. There's also a link to the relisted auction, where you can see that one ended without a sale as well. And there's a link showing that it was relisted with the same result. And so one four more times.

Sorry, dude, but no one wants to buy your gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 12:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Porque no los dos?](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/bc/f0/11/bcf011d75f2f39acf22ebe0bfb9b21f7.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 03:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truly, you have a dizzying intellect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 03:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And every time the punk ass kid demands something, the worker looks at him and says, simply, "como deses" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 23:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Original reddit post](https://www.reddit.com/r/delusionalcraigslist/comments/44f9bm/the_gun_is_in_great_shape_that_crack_in_the/) by /u/DonOblivious.

[Original auction](http://www.gunbroker.com/Auction/ViewItem.aspx?Item=540238772) (with the "item has been relisted" rabbit hole) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 20:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now do it in Spanish! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 20:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, like a "little sister" program? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 19:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I closed the window, so don't quote me on that

You can't tell me what to do. I'm telling everyone I know that /u/BmoreInterested said 10.4 cents. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 19:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not bad. I'm really leaning towards a renewable option, and it's good to see that there are some affordable ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 19:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard about that one! I'm very wary of door to door salespeople anyways. I'm always paranoid that it's either a scam or they're trying to case my house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 15:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's [never too late](http://www.capgunstore.com/Paper-Roll-Caps-Super-Bang-1800-Caps-per-Package-30007.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 14:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! This is really great information, and helps me to understand the process/concept a little bit better. I really appreciate your time and the info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 14:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, thanks for the link!

You're right- that's not a bad price. I appreciate you pointing that out. Did BGE increase your rates for the supply (?) portion of your bill? Some people have said that if you don't use BGE for distribution, they charge you extra for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 14:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not bad! I've been seeing good things about ConEdison, too. So you've been with them for a few years? Your price didn't jump up after the agreement expired? 

I heard that BGE charges additional fees if you switch. Is that the case for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 14:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, this is great information! I really appreciate the reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 14:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really the impression that I'm getting. The savings seem fairly negligible, but it's almost a crapshoot with some of the companies after the honeymoon period is over. 

I've been reading through a lot of the older threads, and a lot of people mention that (realistic) possibility, but I haven't found anyone that's posted after the fact with their experience. 

But, yeah, definitely might be wisest to stay put. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 13:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your username.

Yeah, I've been reading through the archives about that. There seem to be mixed reviews, but the most specific information is a few years old. I was just wondering if anyone had done it recently, and if it worked out for them. 

The whole concept is foreign to me. Where I'm from, you had two choices: take it or leave it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 13:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like there's [quite a few](https://www.bge.com/myaccount/choosingsupplier/energysupplyoptions/Pages/My-Supplier-Options.aspx) that service my area, but I'm not sure which of them are good. Some of them seem to have slightly lower rates, but I've also heard that there are some hidden fees that end up canceling out any savings. Math has never been my strong suit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone switched their power/gas from BGE to another company? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 13:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in Glen Burnie, and I just learned that Maryland gas and electricity was deregulated some years back. I moved here from California, and had exactly one option for each. 

Have any of you switched to another company? From what little I've been able to find and understand, it looks like some of the providers are a little bit cheaper. Is it worth the change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without permission, at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 00:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going from memory here, but I think some people believe that was the only legal document because it was an agreement between generally autonomous States. They feel that the creation of a federal government was illegal. Or something equally nutty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 00:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously he's not a free inhabitant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 12:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a scenario that has played out many times throughout history. Have you looked closely at what people in other countries have done when their government fell?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 19:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, there are the [murders, assaults and robberies](http://articles.baltimoresun.com/2012-10-25/news/bs-md-pizza-delivery-dangers-20121019_1_delivery-man-pizza-delivery-drivers-ultimate-pizza) that other drivers probably don't risk quite as often.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 22:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, she [dyed](http://empirenews.net/actress-betty-white-92-dyes-peacefully-in-her-los-angeles-home/) in September. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 15:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/bUNXwFD.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 22:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thanks. Something seemed off about that advice... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 18:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 17:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 17:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 17:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! And good idea, about calling for an uber. I can't believe I didn't think about that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
