<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject513</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the full game, it's messed up for me and everyone I know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, I'll just call him ignorant next time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well a big nerf is coming, its live in CTE. Get those trench fighter kills in while you can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Til how Rogue is spelled  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I really don't like that guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need hard data and numbers to talk about a trend in the sub reddit. Some of us have better things to do than make pretentious people like you an excel spreadsheet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of getting those classes is being powerful. They're supposed to be really good thats the whole point. I think most people around here think a "good" tanker or pilot score should only be like 30-7 and its ridiculous. A good tanker or pilot should be able to use them to change the game and if that means going 90-6 then so be it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he wants dice to nerf anything that people use to do better than him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Players should be allowed to play in a vehicle all round like that if it's how they'd like to play. There are infantry only game modes if you have a problem with it. If someone is patient enough to wait at the spawn screen for another vehicle they're probably good at what they do too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they ever implemented bullshit like that I wouldn't play anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well why dont we add food the soldiers have to eat when they get too many kills too? 

Oh because it would be fucking ridiculous and punish skill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is rouge one considered a prequel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking for a friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone's got to tell you when your idea is stupid  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a bad suggestion that will never happen and its been suggested for years now so why post it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this isn't real life it's a game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's something you have to deal with and it's always been in the game. Get over it and play hard core if you want first person only vehicles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they'd be bad in first person only and get snuck up on all the time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's stop being giant babies and realize a tank is supposed to be powerful  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The gunners are already plenty powerful. Try to approach a tank with manned side guns as an assault and you'll get shredded. Spreading out the abilities and repair of the tank is a bad idea and yet another example of the subreddit wanting to make a vehicle complete shit under the disguise of "team play". 

These ideas would lead to a frustrating experience as tank driver and a frustrating experience as a player trying to take out the tank. Things that make the game more frustrating don't belong in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You going to explain or talk out of your ass champ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once America wakes up it'll come back  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're a riot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a lot of Autism in one place  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 03:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll stay that way until the OSU bots give. I refuse to believe a small community could stand up to this much backlash without bots and scripts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly did you think this comment would accomplish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just fuck off man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been fighting the little shitheads all day I assure you. If one more tells me about the "all consuming void" and its "beauty" I may go find a random teenager to slap on the off chance its them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm angry edgelord teenagers think its cool to ruin peoples work with uncreative bullshit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're older you'll look back at comments like these and really cringe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy middle school tomorrow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stand these highschool void people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup, highschooler confirmed. Probably a freshman no less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bible quotes on reddit? Do you know where you are? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm convinced all "void" users are in high school or younger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Void people are so cringy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're either trolling or ignorant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I had the biggest inauguration crowd since Reagan" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The conservatives brought this shit upon themselves. I'm all for obstruction until liberals get control, just like conservatives are all for obstruction until they do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking forward to watching nothing get done for his entire presidency. The conservative and moderate factions of the Republicans in Congress will make sure of that. Republicans don't know how to do anything other than oppose things and that's all they will continue to do. Trump can issue all the executive orders he wants, come January 2021 they are all going away  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you support Donald Trump you might as well hate me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah between failing to get his muslim ban enacted failing to get border wall funding and failing to repeal obamacare you guys must be soooooo tired of winning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do hate the_donald and its users yes.

They made it clear they hated me a long time ago so don't give a shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and you go into the bathroom you identify as whats so hard to get about that. 

I'm glad most people arent bigoted shit heads like you too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its crazy that you think the issue is that clear cut. A person born a man that dresses as and identifies as a woman shouldn't be forced into the mens bathroom. 

Let people choose what bathroom they use like we have for all of our history, we didn't need any of these laws until the right wingers in NC decided to stick it to those trans people in the cities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really care if they accept me, I view them as vile human beings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they aren't, and donald trump is the supreme shitbag in charge so this should be expected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your response tells me all I need to know.

Just another shitstain on this earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe if they weren't all giant pieces of shit the entire website wouldn't want to mess it up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is more taking out the trash than destroying art </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really think we should let that bullshit subreddit have anything? I don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I don't agree with people being equal but I'm all for equality" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah who needs facts when ignorant bumpkins have opinions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So instead ignorant bumpkins get to elect snake oil salesmen, so much better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You Donald supporters are scum on this earth  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's a horrible sub that should be bashed whenever possible and we will do whatever it takes to keep them off the final canvas  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's turning into a rainbow perfect hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the planes deserve to be a powerful force on the battlefield, like a tank. If unopposed planes should wreck everyone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aka "I'm bad at something so dice should ruin it for everyone else" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My impression from people is that the nerf is very harsh. Get those fighter kills in before this patch goes live in the full game or you won't get another chance. Better get used to the attack plane because post nerf trench fighters won't be worth using </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm upset this subreddit has turned into people essentially asking dice to nerf things that they aren't good at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let the current nerfs to planes work before you start with more "dice pls make planes terrible" talk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People in the game don't give a shit about squad orders man. They really don't. People do what they want and if you're squad leader you put orders where they get the most points.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You people bitch about everything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that, I think the people crying over movement speed need to get good and learn to use it instead of begging dice for nerfs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They Ribbeyrolle is such a disappointing gun. If it killed in one less bullet and didn't have the muzzle flash it could be great  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a lame attempt at an April fool's thread  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you considered getting gud and using a fighter instead of whining?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is /r/blackpeopletwitter set to private? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You should only find normal map servers in the normal quick match option </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really like half of the new maps and I get sick of getting put into server after server of TSNP after picking the normal quick match option. There is a TSNP quick match option, so why can't the standard quick match just search standard maps?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People hate pilots doing well so much that they just want them as nerfed as possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battlefield tracker is broken </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to love the website but its stats are unreliable now. My score fluctuates by millions every day and occasionally whole days get added or subtracted from my play time. The score per minute it shows is very far off and the live tracking feature frequently says I died when I didn't. What gives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you're right but dice has been known to over nerf things. As long as a direct shot on a player still kills it's ok.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been asking for this since November so I'm happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe this is just CTE right now though, I meant next patch in the full game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is the Trench Fighter after the nerf? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading the changes I thought this nerf would turn it into an unusable hit marker machine. Anyone actually used it in the CTE and have input? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah no I'm happy with less random bullshit in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words trench fighters will now be hit marker machines  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh well better get the trench fighter farming in before they nerf it to shit next patch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "doing the right thing" lmao this guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trench fighter wouldn't be spammed so hard if the attack plane didn't suck ass  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I didn't see this was from wholesomememes in my feed and expected it to be typical 4chan bait lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be so broken  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet another person misusing this subreddit to ask dice for an alternative solution to their problem because they don't like the solution thats already in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a guy bad at flying the plane crashing, what's to fix? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of the reason I was rooting for the gamecocks, other than fuck duke, was so some duke fans that voted for this shit felt stupid haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah so naturally its right for the conservatives to respond with a state wide hateful bill, since the liberals did something first. 

These congressmen made this mess trying to stick it to those "damn liberals" in Charlotte and I'm glad they are having to deal with the consequences. I hope that most of them are Duke fans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 1700 kills with the SMLE carbine are proof that there is some auto aim on console with optical sights   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think 70% of the playerbase will never understand the system if implemented in its current form  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gameplayrealism  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because when you write like that no one takes you seriously  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until someone randomly dies from a falling bullet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't the fucking wild west, we shouldn't have to bring guns to a football game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do people with bad ideas always write so poorly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see your point, I just enjoy the trench fighter far too much to advocate getting rid of it. The darts could use some tweaking for sure though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't like the whole "remove it from the game" thing. It's too far. Nerf it sure. But I've never heard of a Dev just removing something from the game that's been there since the start  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fact just don't include ammo 2.0 and go back to the drawing board to make something simpler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Remove trench fighter from the game" get out of here. I was kinda on the same page until I read that. They should remove the heavy tank too by your logic. They just need to increase dart reload time. 

If the trench fighter bothers you badly to be on the receiving end of, then get good with it and watch as you lay waste to entire teams.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this. Now that I've discovered your channel I feel like I can improve my piloting a lot. I'm good enough to slaughter infantry by the dozen but I fuck up my dogfights  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because most of the people willing to wait on a tank are pretty damn good, its nice to have them on your team. If you really want a tank you can wait too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. It will just keep the skilled tankers and pilots from helping their team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd give up that situation to avoid this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may have to spam him hateful things if I saw this happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ammo 2.0 is too complicated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering players in the base game can hardly wrap their minds around the current resupplying mechanics, I see no way the majority of the playerbase ever understands how a system that needs multiple paragraphs of explanation works. I think Dice is giving the average player too much credit in the comprehension department.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're part of the cancer on this earth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This crashes the game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy the coming Russian related impeachment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you guess who those Dumb Hicks vote for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of bounds glitch end of round </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when you are flying a plane in operations and level it out at the end of the round it continues flying off into the out of bounds screen. At the start of the next round, your entire screen will be black and white and you won't be able to hear much as if your character was still in the plane from last round out of bounds. This continues until you die. Can anything be done about this? The end of round glitches/bs deaths are the worst part of piloting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole starting over again aspect just makes me want to avoid the CTE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That will never get implemented I promise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
