<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9704</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My big three were no more interventionist wars (we will see about this with Syria)

Plans for creating opportunity for our inner cities was a big one (Trump 
campaigned a lot on this but I feel like it got missed in all the faux racist hype) I think we, as Americans, should all make it a national priority to help people who need our help within our own borders.

Not being part of our shitty political system, very important. I am not an R or a D and I am sick of their partisan bought and paid for by special interest BS.

Focus on America First, which the inner cities plans were presented as a big part of, was a big deal for me.

I wrote an in depth thing right around the election but the above three were big ones for me. I voted Bernie in the primary because I wanted a Trump/Bernie general. I believed both honestly wanted what was best for the country.

I have to say when Trump said Our country will no longer submit to the false song of globalism I was very happy. 

That's without even getting into how HRC was the human embodiment of our shitty political culture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a President that evaluates facts and changes his position based off of what he learns. I know that makes hyper partisan people uncomfortable, but for the rest of us it is a good thing.

Trump is not a ideologue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On NATO:
I said it was obsolete. It is no longer obsolete, Trump added.

He has progressively come around to supporting NATO after it increased efforts to allow more U.S. and European intelligence sharing on terrorism.

Trump, however, has remained firm on NATO allies meeting their financial obligations and pay what they owe. Trump said he told Stoltenberg that allies need to put 2 percent of their gross domestic products into defense by 2024.

So he is working to improve NATO based on his criticisms...this is a good thing.

Let's check another 'flip flop'..

Export Improt Bank:
It turns out that, first of all, lots of small companies are really helped, the vendor companies, Trump said. Instinctively, you would say, Isnt that a ridiculous thing, but actually, its a very good thing. And it actually makes money, it could make a lot of money.

He changed his opinion based on exposure to more facts, this is a good thing...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just filling time until there is actual evidence.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is something we need to reflect on. Calling it a distraction and blaming Russia is a weird reaction to me to be honest. If you want to focus on Trump just visit the front page of this sub because it is filled with Trump focus, or turn on CNN and it is all day Trump criticism. So I wonder how distracting this article at the bottom of the r/politics heap really is, and enough so to dismiss it outright as most likely being propagated by Russia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'm a Russian internet operative so that's why I don't like the American government working with terrorists.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad, i assumed based on how dismissive you were being. This is a bigger deal than just HRC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I hate Trump so much I am willing to dismiss evidence my government works with terrorists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ok, I am glad you're cool with our government working with terrorist groups.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an American this shit is so fucking embarrassing. Leave Hillary out of the title, our government was working with terrorist groups. 

To everyone saying this is just Russian Propaganda, take your partisan hats off and look at the fucking facts. Just saying Russian propaganda and closing your eyes is the exact response that lets shit like this happen...OMG though Trump is at Mar a Lago again!!!! Outrage.

Get a god damn grip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on Chris Matthews for putting intellectual consistency over a cheap shot at Spicer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 11:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I think if I was saying don't investigate it would only demonstrate I was not confident in my theory. 

In the end as citizens we have the same interests as far as governmental corruption goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there is direct correlation to Hitler betraying Stalin, but damn that is something that is so interesting with historical context. Hitler hate hate hated the soviet union. 

My whole thing with the Russian narrative is that it is completely story driven and none of the connections between Trump people and Russia are all that strange with out having the narrative explained. I am not surprised that business people dealt with Russia, Page worked in Russia so having Russian connections is not that wild. 

The Russian Ambassador being at the RNC convention this summer isn't so crazy considering there were other ambassadors there. Shit the Russian ambassador sat with the Democrats during Trump's join address earlier this year. 

The strongest component of the whole theory is the narrative, which when presented a certain way makes Trump people's connections to Russia look nefarious...when they previously were not. 

If we are going to set a standard that working with Russian people, or talking to Russian people is not ok then we need to expand the scope of investigations way beyond the Trump camp. This is why the evidence the Podesta Group was taking payments from Russia is important, because it provides context to the extent that powerful Americans work with Russians. 

So i do think the Russian narrative is largely media driven, because the story is the most compelling part and it allows for fan fiction on places like this sub to crop up because the story is not evidence driven.

Now that we know the FBI has a FISA warrant for Page since the summer, when we see someone like former DNI Clapper say he saw no evidence even more damning for the narrative. It means he had access to any potential evidence from the summer through January and he saw no evidence...

Schiff also said there was no definitive evidence of Trump/Russian collusion more recently.

I am not saying don't investigate, especially since the investigations only seem to lead to the conclusion that the Trump camp did not actually collude with Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and what would you say to me if i did? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the part that really requires a suspension of disbelief. This is a conspiracy theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently they have been investigating for a long time, don't worry the evidence will show up eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mattis says the strikes were effective, and honestly i trust his opinion on the matter more than yours. I prefer to look at the actual situation without the leaps of faith required for what you are proposing. As an example of a leap of faith is that we would shoot missiles off into a country to kill, what is obviously ludicrous, a media driven narrative. 

The whole point of the comment I was replying to was that the Trump family sold America out to Russia, so the present situation is actually pretty important to a claim like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean? How is this even a response. 

If you don't have an answer that's fine, I wouldn't want to defend such a ridiculous claim either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But who said Trump was eliminating sanctions? The Russian/US relationship is actually pretty rocky right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did they sell the country for political gain again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just think how successful Putin could be at running campaigns. The Democrats spent like a billion dollars on a loss, when apparently it only takes some Russian internet trolls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are getting imports, and because they are not going to be accepting NK coal they are ramping up their US imports. 

But I wonder if they were planning on using the coal they publicly said they didn't want, but then got called out on it? I wish I could have been a fly on the wall when Trump met with Xi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After NK was doing missile tests china banned coal imports (Feb 2017), but because nothing stops on a dime there were still shipments coming in and sitting in ports. On April 7th the ordered it all returned.

part of the win fall for the US also has to do with a storm that knocked out some of Australia's ability to export coal, so two of their suppliers were cut from the chain, one only momentarily, which has lead to better coal exports for the US to China. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not according to this article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Following repeated missile tests that drew international criticism, China banned all imports of North Korean coal on Feb. 26, cutting off the country's most important export product.

To curb coal traffic between the two countries, China's customs department issued an official order on April 7 telling trading companies to return their North Korean coal cargoes, said three trading sources with direct knowledge of the order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To make up for the shortfall from North Korea, China has ramped up imports from the United States in an unexpected boon for U.S. President Donald Trump, who has declared he wants to revive his country's struggling coal sector. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korean ships head home after China orders coal returned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, when you say Zero in the comment, why not focus on making it a numerical 0 so you can save the characters. I never understand why someone would type out a number when they can use the number character.

Just kidding, I hope everything worked out for you and wifey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so this guy has some points defending his position and acknowledging that CO2 is not a main driver of climate change. I am not clear what he meant, he is saying a chart doesn't prove it but the reference is about acknowledging the ice core samples show temperature is not driven by CO2.

I am not sure how he can retort the atmospheric temperature not heating faster when the guy doing the measurements is in the doc I posted. Which apparently there are many versions of, which I did not realize. 

Full quote. I'm going to check this guys theory out. 

The IPCC was one of the main targets of the documentary. In response to the programme's broadcast, John T. Houghton (co-chair IPCC Scientific Assessment working group 19882002) assessed some of its main assertions and conclusions. According to Houghton the programme was "a mixture of truth, half truth and falsehood put together with the sole purpose of discrediting the science of global warming," which he noted had been endorsed by the scientific community, including the Academies of Science of the major industrialised countries and China, India and Brazil. Houghton rejected claims that observed changes in global average temperature are within the range of natural climate variability or that solar influences are the main driver; that the troposphere is warming less than the surface; that volcanic eruptions emit more carbon dioxide than fossil fuel burning; that climate models are too complex and uncertain to provide useful projections of climate change; and that IPCC processes were biased. Houghton acknowledges that ice core samples show CO2 driven by temperature, but then writes that the programme's assertion that "this correlation has been presented as the main evidence for global warming by the IPCC [is] NOT TRUE. For instance, I often show that diagram in my lectures on climate change but always make the point that it gives no proof of global warming due to increased carbon dioxide."[23]


Here is an article by Sir John in 2004 about how we're not doing enough for global warming, which is caused by CO2 emissions. 

https://www.theguardian.com/life/opinion/story/0,,1284281,00.html
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok anyone reading this thread please click the rebuttal links. In the Wiki it says evidence shows the video is wrong, and the word evidence is linked. When clicking the word evidence you are not taken to evidence of the video being wrong you are linked to a definition page for the word evidence. It also says the literature of the period... and literature is linked, guess where it goes. 

The second rebuttal is even better because it provides links to evidence the movie is misrepresenting data, it's just that the links don't work, which the author acknowledges and says to google it. 

So I do not accept these are a rebuttal to my link, someone else posted a link which I will also go review. I hope it's better than this shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did I say this video was the soul product of my research? I say research I guess I should say I have been reviewing a lot of data around climate change and I have found I agree with the skeptics. 

I will check out the rebuttal links I may agree or I may not. At the end of the day my opinion on humans involvement in climate change means very little and I will continue to defend it so long as there are people willing to be such assholes to anyone who doesn't agree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely now someone will find evidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Share Blue as the top post in R/politics. This is a propaganda site.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can appreciate your point of view. I totally disagree but I am OK with that. Just trying your shoes on for a moment, I think the biggest hurdle to jump is that because the climate change is constant and slow people grow accustomed to it. So the messaging of immediacy is lost when people are not noticing incremental change. So if we want people to change their ways it has to effect their daily life immediately, like an invasion would. How can you effect change in that way?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. this is probably the most reasonable comment I've seen yet on the subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Obviously our worldviews are incompatible but hopefully you can see where I'm coming from.

This is my favorite part of honest discussion, disagreements can be fun, engaging and educational. 

I would argue rethinking our economic system is not pragmatic. From my perspective, providing incentives to people's selfish nature is the best way to effect change. That does not mean I do not support spending federal dollars on research, I do. I also support private citizens who are incentivized to fund research for their own personal benefit...which also happens to benefit the rest of us.

I think progress is always built on past progress, or change if built on past change...which is much more appropriately defined as growth. Sometimes growth is hard to predict and often comes from the actions of a small group of self interested individuals. 

Like I was saying earlier, I am not against the development and research of green energy solutions, but I see it is being a democratic and empowering change for individuals...not a climate argument. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK I submit to the will of climate scientists. How then do we stop the earth from warming? What is the ideal temperature and how do we climate science the earth to that temperature? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the storms and rainfall, would you say the climate is becoming more unpredictable?


I think the food point is a good one, sorry for ignoring it initially I should give more time to the reasonable people than the ones who have nothing but insults. 


Food availability will become important because of our rising population, and potentially because of a changing climate. I do think this research should be given importance, I believe Bill Gates new group has said something similar to what you are saying and they are putting importance on it.


I would like to see a democratization of food availability, so that we can have solutions for people in countries that are already starving. Many of these people are also the ones hurt by trying to curb fossil fuels. I would add the case for green energy is super strong when it is described as a democratization of power...rather than the moral climate argument. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright you got me, I work for a major fossil fuel company, well a right wing think tank, that pays me to push this bullshit online. I can't fucking take it anymore. Every time I post everyone who insults me has caused me to change my ways. 

Screenshots incoming to prove it. Fuck this I guess I should get a real job, something for the environment maybe to make good for all the lies I have been spreading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well that's it, thanks for setting me straight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I am not a pseudo intellectual, I prefer internet nobody.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you are designing your sewer, can you predict with accuracy the outcomes of your sewer? I know nothing about this, what are typical outcomes and how accurately can you predict them? I would imagine you can pretty tightly control where the sewer output would be? Do you use formula's developed from observation that allow for accurate measurements and builds? 

Has there been a climate model yet that can accurately predict what the temperature will be? Then what temperature, are we talking ocean temperatures? Surface temps? Atmospheric temps? If it is settled then surely we have a great accuracy with our predictions? How much does me running my car for an hour contribute to temperature rises? whats the formula for that? 

Why do ice core samples show that CO2 levels follow temperate level rises, and why would that reverse? I think there are a lot of suitable questions around human caused climate change.




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot claim the evidence in this below video as my own, but scientists discussing the evidence is below. 

 There isn't a single thing that I design on a daily basis that is based off science that is 100% agreed on yet my designs work because overwhelming evidence says it is an accurate description of physical phenomena and it is incumbent on anyone who disagrees with the evidence to provide evidence of there own that can be reproduced and mathematically expressed.

I am sure you are building awesome stuff based off of scientific evidence, but is that evidence ever presented simply by saying 'science' and you accept that? Because that is what articles like this one are doing, and as the conversation has evolved it has evolved into accusations of denying 'science'...which means it is no longer a conversation. Simply saying 'science' is equivalent to saying nothing in this sense because we are just expected to believe because, well, 'science'. 

The truth is, if we asked scientists to change our climate within ten years to a specific degree...they couldn't. There is much more evidence that sun spots are closely correlated to global temperature than there is that CO2 is. 

If you're interested here are scientists discussing the man made global warming theory.

[The Great Climate Swindle](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=52Mx0_8YEtg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not anti science, this post was not an argument against the science at all. I am saying that people who speak in generalities of 'science' sound dumb to me and that I do not take them seriously. Just leaning on the word science is about as weak of an argument as I can find. Often time I see a moral argument then accompanying the 'Science' argument which I think is indicative of what the human caused climate change movement has become...a moral movement leaning on 'science'. 

I have been researching it a lot lately. The more i research the more I find non scientists arguing for climate change as a human result. If you are interested below is a link to some seriously credentialed scientists discuss the human caused climate change premise. I do not expect to change your mind but hopefully this doc can share perspective of why maybe we should question the 'consensus' of 'science' on the human caused climate change premise.

[The Great Climate Change Swindle](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=52Mx0_8YEtg)

edit, if you watch I would love to hear feedback and rebuttals.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Visual Representation of my comments](https://www.google.com/imgres?imgurl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mathsisfun.com%2Fimages%2Fangle130.gif imgrefurl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mathsisfun.com%2Fobtuse.html docid=8YrXpyRR9Nf3qM tbnid=i4UCWKVzyWzkwM%3A vet=10ahUKEwjTlqKfkprTAhUi2oMKHdyPCbEQMwhJKAAwAA..i w=231 h=115 hl=en bih=894 biw=1280 q=obtuse ved=0ahUKEwjTlqKfkprTAhUi2oMKHdyPCbEQMwhJKAAwAA iact=mrc uact=8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearly all scientists who study this say that climate change is man made and most nations have entered into treaties over it because it is verified and accepted by the scientific community.

The closest thing we have as a list to represent nearly all scientists is the IPCC report from the UN i believe, I could be wrong, but that includes scientists who do not agree with the reports findings. My original points stands when people make general claims about 'Science' or 'nearly all scientists' it is equivalent to saying nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh i see it's not group think, it's a group of people whose thinking you trust. I see the distinction. 


Doubt what about me specifically?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh, yeah just add to those negative numbers lol. Be careful reading it though I would hate for you to break from the group think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  with your infrared RES vote indicator

What is this?

Anyway I do not have an agenda beyond being sick of people saying 'Science' and expecting it to mean something. The more i research Humanities role in Climate Change the less I trust we have as significant a one as people who say 'Science' as a defense claim.

Just another way of approaching your 'agenda' claims, so what? I am a person using this internet forum just like you should I not express my opinion? What the fuck does my 'agenda' matter... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cool, thanks for ignoring it by responding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Even if I conceded you're easily disproven first point and just accepted that the weather was changing due to nature. 

Don't concede anything, how is it so easily disproven? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it hard to take someone seriously when they argue that doubting the climate change hysteria is anti science. Be weary when people use such vague language, because it is a way to not actually say anything at all. There are plenty of scientists who doubt Mankind's role in the earth's recent warming, but do not doubt that there is warming going on. There are scientists who make the case that CO2 levels actually follow temperature levels, rather than precede them like many climate scientists argue. 


By trying to make it a science or anti-science argument the actual conversations around specifics cannot happen. Add on to that that Pruit is saying the EPA should not have the power to enact new regulations without congressional oversight(which I am oversimplifying) but it isn't an argument about 'science' from what I understand. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're almost entirely outsiders, so they weren't in the 'swamp'. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kelly Anne crushed it in the election and obviously she is a data wizard, but she does not help being on TV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me either, I think it is entirely plausible Russia tried to interfere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You said what I mean is, and then changed the meaning of my statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I made my point and do not need you to reiterate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The suspension of disbelief comes when people like former DNI Clapper says he saw no evidence, Schiff says there is no definitive evidence, Morrel (?) a staunch HRC supporter says smoke but no fire. All people with intimate knowledge of the investigation. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 15:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just keep consuming the propaganda, everything will be all right. I'm sure they'll find actually evidence soon. 

It's not projection to ask people to reflect on their bias.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 14:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a grip. I understand that nothing Trump does will ever be positive to some people, we saw the same thing with Obama. But do us all a favor and recognize your bias, I mean the suspension of disbelief required for the Russian narrative is getting pretty wide at this point. 

If you want to speculate on a massive conspiracy between Putin and Trump, that's fine but just know it is starting to sound ridiculous. I mean you're linking a propaganda website... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 14:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SHeCqh_g08Y

Better less edited version: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s3uaf1NFxXc feature=youtu.be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, it is worse than we thought. This is part of a complex plan between Trump and Putin to lift the sanctions on Putin through one hell of a intricate structure. If you want to catch up on the latest conspiracy theory go visit our friends at r/redacted, they have at least 4 or 5 going right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Blaming Trump for the privacy law is not entirely accurate and I would argue you are misrepresenting the debate over the affordable healthcare act, which a lot of Trump supporters did not support the replacement. 

The Syria thing is because many Trump supporters do not want the US intervening in foreign wars, or engaging in regime change. 

You are obviously over simplifying the issues and misrepresenting Trump supporters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schiff actually makes the point that The Obama admin did during this interview.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone keeps focusing on the specific claim from Trump's tweet. Obama did not order wiretapping! It's a lie. This in no way invalidates the fact that we are finding evidence that the Obama admin did in fact spy on the Trump team. 

The tweet is refuted over and over and people act like that means there wasn't spying. It is really dishonest to approach the topic this way I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg Noam don't you realize how much emotional investment people have made in the Russia conspiracy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you were wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John McCain  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the only characteristic there is about George Soros? He does nothing but sit around and be a jewish person? By making this argument you are demonstrating your focus on whether or not someone is jewish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so let's just assume what they meant, based off of what? This is what i mean by applying 'your' (maybe not you, but whoever is doing it) own biases to the statement. 

This is a convenient way to cast a shadow over someone without them actually saying something related to that shadow. It is a low form of discourse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't but some people need to break things down to easily identifiable factors of an individual, like that they are jewish, because when you take a nuanced look and pay attention to detail situations are not so easily boiled down. It is the easy way out of an actual conversation to focus on basic facts about a person, like if they are jewish.

Making judgments based on peoples religion, skin, country of origin, is the lowest form of commentary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that you are over simplifying the situation to be honest. If you heard screams from your neighbors house would you want to know why?

When you over simplify the situation to make your point, you are in fact not making a point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we don't know what really happened yet, so I am not ready to dismiss it just because.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, don't apply your prejudices to other peoples words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Philosophy is based.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the political purpose question, my answer will be different depending on the time frame. If they spied throughout the campaign, even before the DNC leaks I would say they were looking for dirt. I mean who knows, but knowledge is power and intimate knowledge of a competitor is extremely powerful.

Your kidnapping example doesn't fit the situation because there is evidence they were unmasking, we do not know all the details yet but there have been reports that it had nothing to do with Russia. So we have reports they spied, we have a few different reports on the time frame and the contents. So we really need to learn more to know the extent of the Political or National Security reasons. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I am not a Republican or Tucker Carlson, I'm subject9704 and I think it potentially could be a big deal whether it was legal or not. 

Dismissing this as a simple distraction is not an appropriate response from my perspective, because if it was politically motivated it is a major abuse of power. Why not find out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and that is where I see it for the current situation. We need to find out how and why the information was used and we get conflicting reports on this. It could be, no they(Trump team) were doing something wrong and we needed to know what that was or they were not doing something wrong and we wanted dirt. 

I also would like to know the time frame of the 'spying' (qoutes since we don't agree on if it was or not). Was it 3 months, 6 months, a year? This will be important context for whether it was appropriate or not. 

I just hope we get truth, rather than partisan talking points.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I am responding to being told they didn't spy, they did spy.

Spying: work for a government or other organization by secretly collecting information about enemies or competitors.

I did not make a quality assessment, just pointing out they did spy. So saying they didn't spy is erroneous from my perspective. I mean technically our government is spying on all of us, which I do think is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> revealing the name of transition officials who were caught up in legal wiretaps of foreigners is not the same thing as illegally spying on the Trump campaign. But that has not stopped the Susan Rice story from becoming the dominant story on the American right.

The argument seems to be if it was illegal or legal, not that they spied. Even Vox is making the legal/illegal distinction but not questions whether or not they spied.

http://www.vox.com/world/2017/4/4/15177640/susan-rice-unmasking
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would consider unmasking his team's communications as spying. Whether you think it was good/bad or legal/illegal I would still consider it spying...I mean what else would it be?

She admitted to doing it after initially saying the week before she didn't , so I am not sure there is a debate surrounding this. Now as we get into more particulars there may be no evidence she committed a crime, that's another conversation, but it is confirmed they spied. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, just like there was no evidence the trump team was spied on...until there was. I am worried what is going to happen to this echo chamber when the Russian investigation is concluded, where will everyone focus their hate? 

Well anyway keep listening to CNN, i hear the acoustics add a nice harmony to the echo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep hearing from people who have/had access to information saying there is no evidence of Trump/Russian collusion. But this article is focused more on the claim the Russia hacked the DNC based solely on Crowdstrike's report. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with the premise. With that being said, what do you think about Crowdstrike not cooperating with Congress and no one else ever investigating the server? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see how you would think the title is misleading, but the actual article addresses the election claims, the Ukraine army claims and the fact that Crowdstrike is not cooperating with Congress.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it BS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cybersecurity experts who were first to conclude that Putin hacked presidential election abandon some of their claims against Russia - and refuse to co-operate with Congress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol it sounds kind of sad. If you need someone to talk to about whatever is really bothering you I would be willing to listen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> now this is funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, just wondering why you care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, why do you care?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I see he is still an adviser to the President, just not on NSC now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't speak for everyone but I want to see why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel for whoever had to make that graphic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has had many people come and meet with him who did not support him in the campaign, and spoke out against him. Like Trump or not he has done this since the transition began. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a convenient way to dismiss the spying. Why can't we talk about both? Especially since Schiff said there is no definitive evidence that Trump colluded with Russians, even after all these months of unmasking. We can have one big conversation, rather than dismissing the spying stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adults adjust to a situation and make the most of it, children cry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It interesting because if you try to look at it from Erik Trump's perspective it totally has been. They were raised around their company, given jobs in the company and their whole life has been spent working with family. 

Whether you think it is right or wrong, with a little perspective I actually understand why he would say this. And as someone who got my career kicked off with some nepotism I am finding it hard to be a hater. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Defending against Trumps tweet only shows how dishonest these answers are. They say Trump tower wasn't targeted, it wasn't wiretapping. This is pure lying by omission, and in know way means they weren't spying. 

Meanwhile the Trump tweet has nothing to do with questions about how you actually spied, not what you didn't do. They are allowed to change the story and the interviewer just watches. Oh good she said Trump is wrong. 

Fuck man I hope everyone enjoys watching 1984 in 'protest' of Trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never listen to myself. I tend to leave a comment and move on to the next patch of fertile land to plant another comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you sir/madam! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
