<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8719</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's something terrifying living in an abandoned sanatorium (Final) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part One: https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/69p6u0/theres_something_horrifying_living_in_the/

Hi, guys.

In Part 1 I explained what happened in that godforsaken building and how we had to leave Sebastian behind. It's been almost a week since we escaped and until today, I thought my best friend, the guy who had stuck with me since we were teenagers, was dead.

Unable to get the police involved - we would be looking at a *long* time in jail if they knew what we had done - I decided that we were going to take matters into my own hands. My grandfather used to take me shooting when I was younger and I inherited his old rifle when he passed away, and Callum managed to get ahold of a wicked hunting knife.

All that proved unneccary, however, when I heard a sharp knocking on my front door yesterday evening. Callum looked up from his computer (just thought I should mention that he was staying around to plan our trip). I set off downstairs and opened the door.

My jaw dropped. It was Sebastian. "Holy shit" was all I could utter as he stepped through the door, offering a weak smile and slumping into an armchair. He looked like he had aged in the short time he was missing. His skin was unnervingly pale and seemed almost droopy, and he smelt a little off too, but a man who'd spent the best part of a week surviving being hunted by what you guys have labelled a wendigo he didn't look that bad.

Callum grabbed him a beer as I sat across the room from him in awe. I honestly couldn't believe he was back.

We sat quietly by the TV for a bit, before I could muster up the courage to speak. "What happened to you, man?" I asked. Sebastian frowned, and when he spoke there was something definitely off about his voice. It wavered slightly and he seemed to be struggling to speak. "I came back"

There was another awkward silence before Callum started to describe what we were planning to do to rescue him, but before he could finish Seb lunged to his feet with an unearthly bellow. "NO!" the hairs on my neck prickled as he stood there, twitching slightly as Callum and I exchanged concerned looks. "Are you feelin' alright?" I queried. The glare I received was the fiercest I've ever seen in my life. "I'M FINE."

By this point, it was beginning to get late. For fear of upsetting Sebastian further, I offered him the sofa to sleep on and that we all turn in for the night. He nodded and curled up in a ball as Callum and I trotted upstairs. 

Neither of us spoke as we slowly got ready for bed, but we both knew something was wrong with out friend. I wrote it off as just shell shock 
from the time he spent in the sanatorium and fell into an uneasy sleep.

I awoke in the early hours of the morning. I wasn't acutely aware of what woke me until I saw him, stood there in the doorway. It was Seb, or rather it wasn't. Hunched over and leaning against the frame of the door, he wheezed and rasped as his glinting eyes surveyed the room. His gaze locked onto me as the all too familiar smell of copper filled my nostrils, almost making me gag.

I held my breath and lay still until I heard him returning along the hall and downstairs. Then, after an ominous silence, the shattering of glass. The fuck? I jumped out of bed, snatching the rifle from my desk as Callum jolted awake.

By the time I got downstairs, he was long gone, leaving a smashed window in his place. I called the police, clutching the gun in my hands until I heard them pulling up in my drive.

I gave them a heavily edited version of the events of the past week: Seb had mentioned going to some abandoned place, followed by what had happened when he returned. I didn't like to drop him in it but there was something wrong with him and I refuse to believe that it isn't related to what we saw in the sanatorium.

Since then, he hasn't been seen again. But I've heard him. Clicking and wheezing away. Right outside my window.

I don't know what happened to the man I called my best friend. But let this serve as a warning. Places like hospitals, laboratories and sanatorium. They're abandoned for a reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
