<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Organizations including the AFT Union and New York Taxi Workers Alliance publicly announced their support for the protest.

"Our 19,000-member-strong union stands firmly opposed to Donald Trump's Muslim ban. As an organization whose membership is largely Muslim, a workforce that's almost universally immigrant, and a working-class movement that is rooted in the defense of the oppressed, we say no to this inhumane and unconstitutional ban," the NYTWA said in a statement.

"We stand in solidarity with all protesting at JFK #Terminal4   airports across the country. We are a country of immigrants, we stand together," AFT union wrote on Twitter.

The New York Taxi Workers Alliance also joined the protests, leaving Terminal 4 pick-up lines empty.

"We cannot be silent. We go to work to welcome people to a land that once welcomed us, we will not be divided," a tweet from the NYTWA read Saturday evening.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter account retells story of Jewish refugees turned away at US borders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Immigration Ban Is Illegal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Summary and Analysis of Trump Executive Order on Visa Issuance/Screening and Refugees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oxfam vehemently condemns President Trump's harmful and discriminatory Executive Order to slam the door on refugees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 00:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump's Action on Refugees an Affront to American and Jewish Values </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 00:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says Syrian Christian refugees will be given priority </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> St. Louis Manifest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is Carpet-Bombing U.S. Foreign Policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ben Stiller: 'Nobody Wants to Be a Refugee' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It is now two and a half minutes to midnight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indivisible: A Practical Guide for Resisting the Trump Agenda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost Unnoticed, Flat Electricity Demand Is Crushing U.S. Carbon Emissions | Charles Komanoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost Unnoticed, Flat Electricity Demand Is Crushing U.S. Carbon Emissions | Charles Komanoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Environmental Data, Guerrilla Archiving, and the Trump Transition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Environmental Data, Guerrilla Archiving, and the Trump Transition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Prepares Orders Aiming at Global Funding and Treaties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little National Security Benefit to Trumps Executive Order on Immigration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The history of the U.S. refugee program demonstrates that the lengthy and extensive vetting that all refugees must undergo is an effective deterrent for terrorists. Recent research finds that the chance of being killed by a refugee-perpetrated terror attack was [1 in 3.64 billion per year](https://www.cato.org/blog/terrorism-risk-asylum-seekers-refugees-minnesota-new-york-new-jersey-terrorist-attacks
). This means youre more than 200 times times likely to be killed by lightning then a refugee terrorist.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four Reasons Why President Trump Is Wrong to Ban Refugees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CDC abruptly cancels conference on health effects of climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A New Deal to Save Europe | Yanis Varoufakis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Economy for the 99%: Its time to build a human economy that benefits everyone, not just the privileged few | Oxfam GB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So begins the Trump administration under the banner of Groucho Marxism:  "Who you gonna believe, me or your lying eyes?"
There is a method to the madness.  Subservience is humiliating.  Force someone to submit to your power, to deny the truth they see, and they are under your total control.  Today the NPS, tomorrow the World! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> National Park Service apologizes for tweets showing poor inaugural turnout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 02:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I marched in Sarasota Florida (population 53,000).  There were [more than 10,000](http://www.heraldtribune.com/news/20170121/thousands-turn-out-for-sarasota-womens-solidarity-march) of us, starting at the [Unconditional Surrender sculpture](https://www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g34618-d6401028-Reviews-Unconditional_Surrender_Sculpture-Sarasota_Florida.html)  and filling the length of the Ringling Causeway bridge.  We talked to many people who had never been part of a political demonstration before, including a lifelong Republican physical therapist who had had enough and needed to show that she will be part of the resistance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alternative facts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Scott Pruitt, Trump's EPA choice, switch sides and defend his own lawsuits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'The swamp is Goldman Sachs': How the bank is rewarded for putting profits over people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Women's March in Pictures, From Washington to Antarctica </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defiant Voices Flood Nation's Cities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 04:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Republican-style health-care reform quickly becomes a tax cut for the richest of the rich </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Davos Elite Fret About Inequality Over Vintage Wine and Canaps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently the right to life ends at birth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most Americans are one unexpected medical bill away from the street </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leonard Peltier Denied Clemency by Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 01:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump and the nuclear codes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want a president. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Land Rush in Permian Basin, Where Oil Is Stacked Like a Layer Cake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 05:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What So Many People Don't Get About the U.S. Working Class </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mad As Hell: Why the public is so pissed off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Response to Zika Failed Millions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the index, median income actually declined by 2.4 percent between 2008 and 2013 across the 26 advanced economies where data is available, which may help explain the shifting political winds.

Its our response to how capitalism has failed us  and how we need to fix it, said Adrian Monck, a member of the forums executive committee.

The United States ranked 23rd out of 30 advanced economies. In terms of wage and nonwage compensation, it ranked last; in social protection, it came in 25th. It also came in 25th on intermediation of business investment  in other words, the amount of money that goes into productive investments, such as research and development and infrastructure as opposed to share buybacks. (Norway ranked No. 1. Living standards there rose by 10.6 percent from 2008 to 2013 while the economy grew only 0.5 percent.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What to Make of the Davos Class in the Trump Era </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yellow Cab, Long a Fixture of City Life, Is for Many a Thing of the Past </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A journalist who left Venezuela for the U.S. has a warning for reporters covering Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 06:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump promises his Obamacare replacement plan will cover all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 06:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Update: What Trump's nominees said Thursday about science and climate at their Senate hearings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 04:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ailing Vermont Town Pins Hopes on Mideast Refugees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone Donald Trump has called 'overrated' on Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump names eighth Wall Street executive to administration post: Jay Clayton, a lawyer for Goldman Sachs and other Wall Street firms, tapped to run the Securities   Exchange Commission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 17:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Washington Post Needs To Come Clean About Its Russian Hacking Story Fiasco </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Health Care Plan Trump Voters Really Want </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN apologizes to Wikileaks after threatening to sue over commentator calling Assange a pedophile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 04:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Digitizing Radio Unnameable, a Free-Form 1960s Crossroads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 03:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health Care in the United States: A Right or a Privilege </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 02:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surveillance is one-way transparency. It is a tool of control. Secrecy is also a tool of control. Assange lacks what Snowden has always exhibited -- a sense of responsibility for the consequences of his actions. Both acted as pipelines, taking information from the private to the public domain. But Snowden's info flow was channeled through journalists who made ethical judgments about the consequences of wider publication. What Wikileaks provided to the hackers was the honorable cloak of whistleblower, when, in fact, the source was the secret police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump, Palin break with GOP, warm up to Assange </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surveillance is one-way transparency.  It is a tool of control.  Secrecy is also a tool of control.  Assange lacks what Snowden has always exhibited -- a sense of responsibility for the consequences of his actions.  Both acted as pipelines, taking information from the private to the public domain.  But Snowden's info flow was channeled through journalists who made ethical judgments about the consequences of wider publication.  What Wikileaks provided to the hackers was the honorable cloak of whistleblower, when, in fact, the source was the secret police.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump, Palin break with GOP, warm up to Assange </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She Faced Cuomo and Got Clemency. He Got "a Sense of Her Soul." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 05:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She Faced Cuomo and Got Clemency. He Got a Sense of Her Soul. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 05:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study finds EPA and DHA omega-3s lower risk of coronary heart disease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With No Warning, House Republicans Vote to Hobble Independent Ethics Office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 04:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Year-End Roundup: In 2016, The World Passed The Tipping Point Into A Perilous New Era </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite the hype, batteries aren't the cheapest way to store energy on the grid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robots that hire and fire staff could soon be employed by hedge fund </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Q A: The GOP's path to repealing health care law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Do We Go From Here? | Nancy Anderson, Ph.D. | The Sallan Foundation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 02:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How and Why Tribes Are Taking Over </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 16:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 23:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Who is Judy Clark, and why does she deserve to be free?](http://judithclark.org) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cuomo Commutes Sentence of Judith Clark, Driver in Deadly Brink's Robbery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 23:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Serena Williams Engaged to Reddit Co-Founder Alexis Ohanian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 04:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Complaint Board Softened Report on Police Use of Tasers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Environmental activists to protest construction of Sabal Trail pipeline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 15:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Read the full transcript of John Kerry's speech on the Mideast peace process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 04:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the U.S. came to abstain on a U.N. resolution condemning Israeli settlements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 04:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Only Way to Stop Climate Change Now May Be Revolution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 03:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Donald Trump won  and how Hillary Clinton lost: 13 theories explain the stunning election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 16:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Worlds Biggest Hedge Fund is Embedding Its Founders Brain in an Algorithm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 01:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel's Settlements Have No Legal Validity, Constitute Flagrant Violation of International Law, Security Council Reaffirms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 21:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Security Council's Israeli Settlement Resolution: Seven Observations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 21:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health Exchange Enrollment Jumps, Even as G.O.P. Pledges Repeal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge orders unsealing of warrant for Clinton emails on Weiner laptop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Emergency Managers, City Executives Charged In Flint Water Crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Arctic Will Fare If Big Oil Becomes Americas Top Diplomat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 03:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama issues mining rule despite Trumps threat to repeal it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 02:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Oil Age To Soil Age </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 04:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Historian gifts $4M Manhattan property to Native Americans - Jean-Louis Goldwater Bourgeois is the son of the famed artist Louise Bourgeois </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 03:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 00:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In picturing the situation the new administration will encounter this January, John McDonough, PhD, MPA, professor at the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Policy in Boston, compared it to a scene from the original "Ghostbusters" movie.
In it, a lawyer for the Environmental Protection Agency is about to burst open a storage facility containing all the mischievous and malevolent spirits the heroes have rounded up.
"You really don't want to do this. You don't know what's going to happen," McDonough said. "And quite literally all hell breaks loose," he said.
...
While the GOP has enough votes on its own to partially repeal the law through the budget reconciliation process, which cannot be filibustered, to pass a replacement bill they will need at least eight Democratic votes in the Senate.
...
There is one thing that both liberals and conservatives can likely agree on and that is how high the stakes are for Republicans. With a majority in both chambers and a Republican president, Wallner said, "There are no more excuses."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scholars Survey ACA Repeal-Replace Landscape - Plenty of challenges for Republicans in fulfilling promises </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 00:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Julian Assange: Where Is Evidence That WikiLeaks Founders Source Was Russian Hackers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democratic House Candidates Were Also Targets of Russian Hacking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 03:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Hasidim Won the Battle for One Upstate New York Town </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 03:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 03:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now Donald, having benefited from Putin's kindness, will have to do whatever he must to be sure that Putin does not release hacked emails (embarrassing or incriminating) of the Trump campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Perfect Weapon: How Russian Cyberpower Invaded the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 03:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada agrees on national carbon price, but tensions remain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists are frantically copying U.S. climate data, fearing it might vanish under Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Under Water: How Sea Level Rise Threatens the Tri-State Region </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lawyers pointed out that ICE, the federal agent of deportation, receives fingerprints and identifying information for every New York City arrest, whether the city has asked about immigration status or not.

As a result, arrests for being in the park after dark, for possessing an open container of alcohol, or for other harmless activities, which are largely permitted in more affluent neighborhoods, essentially flag vulnerable New Yorkers for priority enforcement by ICE, the lawyers wrote.

The lawyers said police should issue civil summonses instead of criminal violations whenever possible, a conclusion Mark-Viverito agreed with in a statement from her spokeswoman.

Issuing more civil, instead of criminal, summonses will significantly reduce unnecessary interactions with the criminal-justice system and will help thwart ICE's attempts to target immigrant New Yorkers, the spokeswoman said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deportation for infractions makes normal policing dangerous.  Immigrants -- even legal ones -- have every reason to resist to save themselves and their families.  And that resistance could include violence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Broken windows' policing could hand city's immigrants over to Trump, lawyers say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Pruitt is a stenographer for the oil and gas industry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 00:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roberta's Gets Torture Threats After Being Linked to Fake 'Pizzagate' Story - East Williamsburg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Witch Hunt: "Fake News" Software Touted by CBS Smears Naked Capitalism, ShadowProof, TruthDig, Others; Creator Admits He Made Up Who Went on Hit List </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Bigger Economic Pie, but a Smaller Slice for Half of the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plug in for renewable energy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 05:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Immune System, Unleashed by Cancer Therapies, Can Attack Organs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volkswagen challenges Uber, Lyft with new company </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 03:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As they say you cant lose em all.  And here to raise our sights on what we can hope for is an impossible victory (even if, perhaps, temporary) re-awakening what we have always known about  the contagious power of the human spirit.  More than 500 years of repression have not extinguished the  drum circles and sacred fires.   Instead, the circle now widens.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The victory at Standing Rock could mark a turning point | Bill McKibben </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The victory at Standing Rock could mark a turning point | Bill McKibben </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italy referendum: exit polls point to heavy defeat for Matteo Renzi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People Power was crucial in stopping the DAPL disaster from happening.  Profits (called "jobs" or "economic development") will win every time if people are not mobilized to defend their own interests, and the public good.  But mass mobilizations are not enough.  You need strong reasons that other people recognize as just -- like preventing the contamination of the Missouri River for millions of people -- and you need a government that has the will to defend the public interest over private profit.  

We may have lost that third crucial ingredient  when the Trump administration takes over.  But people eventually notice when their government fails to listen.  It may take a while, but the struggle for justice cannot by silenced.  Its message is: We're under attack today, but tomorrow it may be you.  So let us hang together, or we will all hang separately.  

Those who think they can benefit from a government that is not just will learn that they have been suckers.  The principle of Might Makes Right only works if you are supremely powerful.  Everyone else is a loser -- if not today, tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Army Corps of Engineers denies DAPL easement for Lake Oahe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Army Corps of Engineers denies DAPL easement for Lake Oahe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Army Corps of Engineers denies DAPL easement for Lake Oahe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Full Keith Ellison Tape Shows He Was (Mostly) Praising Israel  Not Trashing It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 17:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poland: For Catholics only ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debate: The Italian Referendum, Yes or No ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYT Protects Its Pundit Who Dismissed Trans Rights as Boutique Issue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 17:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders: Carrier just showed corporations how to beat Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hope in a Dark Era: In the Face of Barbarism, Thousands Turn to Democratic Socialism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 16:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medical marijuana in New York can soon treat chronic pain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 16:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medical marijuana in New York can soon treat chronic pain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 16:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why America's labor unions are about to die </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 05:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Divide Between Red and Blue America Grew Even Deeper in 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Two Americas of 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 03:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I understand it, you can't get parole unless you confess your crime and show remorse.  So the catch is that if you're innocent, and have a free spirit, you remain locked up.  Dignity is not denying the truth, no matter what the consequences to you.  Lose it, and they have you -- slave for life, even if you're not in prison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retirement age: Elderly inmate wants to retire from prison job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 03:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retirement age: Elderly inmate wants to retire from prison job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 03:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retirement age: Elderly inmate wants to retire from prison job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 03:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Producing Wind Energy In The Ocean, No Turbines In Sight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cities and States Lead on Climate Change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Ryan just unveiled his plan to privatize Medicare and it's insane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's potential Homeland Security pick has announced his plan and it's absolutely terrifying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 04:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Castro preserved Cuba's national sovereignty. Can it survive Trump? | Samuel Farber </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 03:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 03:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note that Shapiro published this on his web site in February 2016.
During the current Presidential campaign in 2016, a lot of journalists and commentators keep pointing out again and again that Trump is a liar, etc. That may all be true, but it doesnt make a dent in the number of  his supporters.

This reminds me of Jean Baudrillards comments throughout his work (for example, in Fatal Strategies) on the difference between critical theory discourse and what Baudrillard called fatal theory: in other words, the ineffectiveness of critical theory discourse. Since Trump is the candidate of Reality TV (what Baudrillard in his last works called Telemorphosis), of the celebrity culture, of media hyper-reality entertainment, in other words simulation invoking the truth against him doesnt work as a strategy! (we are in hyper-reality where, in a sense, there is no more truth)

Because Trump is already more advanced than the discourse of truth. The only way to bring him down would be to, in some way, out-Trump Trump. More hyper-real than the hyper-real. More simulation than simulation. That is our motto. (to paraphrase Tyrell in Blade Runner) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Casino Owner: seduced to losing by the lure of winning | Alan N. Shapiro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 03:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 00:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does the Republic save itself from a madman?  What if the President lives in a fantasy world of his own creation?  Even if he hasn't committed an impeachable offense, Amendment 25 of the Constitution provides an escape hatch if the President is physically or mentally incapable of performing his duties.

Section 4 of the Amendment allows for involuntary transfers of power. If the Vice President and a majority of the Cabinet (or some other body created by Congress to act in place of the Cabinet) inform Congress that the President is unable to exercise the powers of his office, those powers pass to the Vice President who functions as Acting President. When the President indicates that he wishes those powers returned, he need only inform Congress of this fact and the powers are returned. If the Vice President and Cabinet challenge the President, Congress must decide the matter within a maximum of twenty-three days. A two-thirds vote in each house is needed for the Vice President to prevail.

...
Dr. Lawrence C. Mohr, White House Physician from 1987 to 1993, has suggested that: 
 The presence of a major psychotic disorder in which a president is clearly out of touch with reality would certainly be a reason to initiate the process of presidential disability.  the extent of impairment should be assessed on the basis of adverse effects on alertness, cognitive function, judgment, appropriate behavior, the ability to choose among options and the ability to communicate clearly. If any of these are impaired, it is my opinion that the powers of the president should be transferred to the vice president until the impairment resolves.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Presidential Disability and the Twenty-Fifth Amendment: The Difficulties Posed By Psychological Illness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 00:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Section 4 of the Amendment allows for involuntary transfers of power. If the Vice President and a majority of the Cabinet (or some other body created by Congress to act in place of the Cabinet) inform Congress that the President is unable to exercise the powers of his office, those powers pass to the Vice President who functions as Acting President. When the President indicates that he wishes those powers returned, he need only inform Congress of this fact and the powers are returned. If the Vice President and Cabinet challenge the President, Congress must decide the matter within a maximum of twenty-three days. A two-thirds vote in each house is needed for the Vice President to prevail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Presidential Disability and the Twenty-Fifth Amendment: The Difficulties Posed By Psychological Illness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to winning the Electoral College in a landslide, I won the popular vote if you deduct the millions of people who voted illegally, Mr. Trump wrote Sunday afternoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does the Republic save itself from a madman?  What if the President lives in a fantasy world of his own creation?  Even if he hasn't committed an impeachable offense, Amendment 25 of the Constitution provides an escape hatch if the President is physically or mentally incapable of performing his duties:
[Section 4. Whenever the Vice President and a majority of either the principal officers of the executive departments or of such other body as Congress may by law provide, transmit to the President pro tempore of the Senate and the Speaker of the House of Representatives their written declaration that the President is unable to discharge the powers and duties of his office, the Vice President shall immediately assume the powers and duties of the office as Acting President.
Thereafter, when the President transmits to the President pro tempore of the Senate and the Speaker of the House of Representatives his written declaration that no inability exists, he shall resume the powers and duties of his office unless the Vice President and a majority of either the principal officers of the executive department or of such other body as Congress may by law provide, transmit within four days to the President pro tempore of the Senate and the Speaker of the House of Representatives their written declaration that the President is unable to discharge the powers and duties of his office. Thereupon Congress shall decide the issue,](http://constitution.findlaw.com/amendment25.html#sthash.KDn8DYE4.dpuf)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Claims, With No Evidence, That Millions of People Voted Illegally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Claims, With No Evidence, That Millions of People Voted Illegally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Government won't forcibly remove Dakota pipeline protesters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Has Died in Cuba with Fidel Castros Death? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 02:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fidel Castro (1926-2016): A major feature of Fidel Castros 47-year-old rule was his manipulation of popular support and the creation of a political system that does not hesitate to use repression, and not only against class enemies, to cement its power. | Samuel Farber </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 04:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Dakota pipelines last stand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 06:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 03:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not just property owners, buyers and sellers who are struggling to estimate the potential financial impact of climate change on the real estate market. These risks compound as individual mortgages get bundled and sold as securities. In his April report, Mr. Becketti, the Freddie Mac economist, emphasized how difficult it was to predict whether the bubble in coastal real estate would slowly deflate or suddenly pop.

Will the value of the house decline gradually as the expected life of the house becomes shorter? he wrote. Or, alternatively, will the value of the house  and all the houses around it  plunge the first time a lender refuses to make a mortgage on a nearby house or an insurer refuses to issue a homeowners policy?

...
Coastal mortgages are growing into as big a bubble as the housing market of 2007, said Philip Stoddard, the mayor of South Miami. But this time, he said, there will not be a rebound because the waters will not recede and properties will eventually lose all of their value.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perils of Climate Change Could Swamp Coastal Real Estate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 02:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 21:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans have felt it necessary to speak in code when it comes to race, which points to the success of the 1960s liberation movements.  Until now. Trump discarded code. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: Out of the Shadows of the Sixties Social Movements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 21:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump eases on Paris treaty but aims to slash Nasas climate science budget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 04:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 16:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The appropriate response to Trump is planning ahead.  What would a sane society invest in for its survival and general well-being?  Everyone agrees we need to modernize and upgrade our infrastructure.  But, if don't recognize that climate change matters  (both to forestall the most severe impacts, and to adapt to the climate change we cannot stop) our investments will be wasted and our needs unmet.  Heed the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers: [The entire portfolio of USACE Civil Works water resources infrastructure and programs, existing and proposed, could be affected by climate change and adaptation to climate change. This affects design and operational assumptions about resource supplies, system demands or performance requirements, and operational constraints. Both droughts and floods can affect the operations of these projects. Numerous regulatory decisions made by USACE will need to be informed by climate change impacts and adaptation considerations throughout the U.S., especially in western states.](http://www.corpsclimate.us/index.cfm)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Companies to Trump: Dont Abandon Global Climate Deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 16:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 15:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Michigan law pushed by Ms. DeVos to establish charter schools 20 years ago allows an unusually large number of organizations to start such schools, yet established little mechanism for oversight. Even Republican supporters of charter schools say the law has allowed failing charter schools to expand or replicate.

Last spring, the DeVos-backed group was the chief force behind the defeat of legislation that would have established standards for identifying and closing failing schools, both charter and public, in Detroit, where a flood of charter schools in the past decade has created what even charter school supporters call chaos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Betsy DeVos, Trumps Education Pick, Has Steered Money From Public Schools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 15:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Retreat From TPP Would Empower China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Stunning Reversal, Trump Scraps His Calls to Bring Back Torture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 01:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shows percentage for each candidate by district. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Election Results: G.O.P. Keeps Control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RepressIntern: Russia's security cooperation with fellow authoritarians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 04:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warren to Trump: "despite your campaign promises, you are looking to industry insiders, lobbyists and other special interests to shape Washington D.C. under your administration." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 04:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The appropriate response to Trump is planning ahead.  What would a sane society invest in for its survival and general well-being?  Everyone agrees we need to modernize and upgrade our infrastructure.  But, if don't recognize that climate change matters  (both to forestall the most severe impacts, and to adapt to the climate change we cannot stop) our investments will be wasted and our needs unmet.  Heed the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers: [The entire portfolio of USACE Civil Works water resources infrastructure and programs, existing and proposed, could be affected by climate change and adaptation to climate change. This affects design and operational assumptions about resource supplies, system demands or performance requirements, and operational constraints. Both droughts and floods can affect the operations of these projects. Numerous regulatory decisions made by USACE will need to be informed by climate change impacts and adaptation considerations throughout the U.S., especially in western states.](http://www.corpsclimate.us/index.cfm)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders roils Trump's infrastructure blueprint: 'The plan he offered is a scam' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To resist a Trump presidency, ask: What would the abolitionists do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 20:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 18:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The present energy economy in the US is driven by the low price of natural gas and renewables, and Trump is unlikely to be able to change that. The subsidies that are currently helping renewables were popular enough in Congress to be one of the few things passed during the Obama administration, and the trajectory of renewable prices is such that the subsidies won't be needed for cost competitiveness for much longer. While Trump may revoke some of the rules that make coal less competitive, it's not clear that businesses will feel confident enough that these changes will survive long enough to make something like a coal plant, with a lifespan that runs decades, a reasonable risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive report details the energy economy that limits warming to 2C </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 18:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as Jews are in Israel fighting the good fight with the Arab world as a bastion of American ideals and values in the Middle East, then they are very useful and admirable allies, said Sternhell. Once they are home demanding a multi-cultural democracy, demanding that the country accommodate their religion, their belief and their custom that is a different story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Bannon and Breitbart Can Be Pro-Israel  and Anti-Semitic at the Same Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intensified by Climate Change, King Tides Change Ways of Life in Florida </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mirage of Renegotiating the Iran Deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 12-Step Program for Responding to President-Elect Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 20:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think its about Trump. Trump is just a vehicle, a Mercer family colleague told Politico. Its about wanting to be a player and wanting to beat Hillary, in that order. Because if you remember, they wanted to use Cruz as a vehicle before that. They do want to beat Hillary, but they also want to beat the Kochs and Paul Singer and the Ricketts [other far-right billionaires]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the World Needs WikiLeaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Class, Stupid, Not Race | naked capitalism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 02:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> United States Mid-Century Strategy for Deep Decarbonization </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 02:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 15:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The appropriate response to Trump is planning ahead.  What would a sane society invest in for its survival and general well-being?  Everyone agrees we need to modernize and upgrade our infrastructure.  But, if don't recognize that climate change matters  (both to forestall the most severe impacts, and to adapt to the climate change we cannot stop) our investments will be wasted and our needs unmet.  Heed the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers: [The entire portfolio of USACE Civil Works water resources infrastructure and programs, existing and proposed, could be affected by climate change and adaptation to climate change. This affects design and operational assumptions about resource supplies, system demands or performance requirements, and operational constraints. Both droughts and floods can affect the operations of these projects. Numerous regulatory decisions made by USACE will need to be informed by climate change impacts and adaptation considerations throughout the U.S., especially in western states.](http://www.corpsclimate.us/index.cfm)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ensuring Urban Resilience: Come Hell or High Water </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 15:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 Upper West Side Apartment Buildings Are Dumping Trump's Name </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 23:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun stocks slump following Trump presidential win </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 05:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Labor union anger fueled Trump in Midwest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 05:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Julian Assange gives statement over rape allegations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sarkozy wants tax on US products if Trump scraps Paris climate pact </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sarkozy wants tax on US products if Trump scraps Paris climate pact </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israeli ministers defy Netanyahu over settlement evacuation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 04:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump stock-market rally reflects expectations for new era of fiscal stimulus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
