<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9743</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 07:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happened in Connecticut. It's a pretty common story in the news here. She's suing for a bunch of money, something like 10mil. She won't get that much but she'll win something. The state had issues with the same chimp before the attack, and did nothing to enforce the safety of the public. Sure, she was stupid for trying to calm down a drugged animal, but the state is liable to a degree as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Felt sick, too lazy to go to the bathroom so I puked on the floor and went back to sleep. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 04:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was....[a kid. I didn't want to climb down the ladder from the top bunk, so I leaned over and puked on the floor. Mom came in the next day to a nice crust all over my toys. Had to throw them away.](/spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 13:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS IS APPROPRIATING NEOPETS CULTURE. AS A NEOKIN, I WANT THIS SITE TAKEN DOWN FOREVER. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 08:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when you make a rape joke, a survivor relives in a vivid, Technicolor sound, what was probably the worst memory of his or her life

This shit pisses me off. I don't know who this woman is or what she has gone through, but she has no right to speak for ALL rape survivors.

Case in point: my father was raped (even though as a cishet white boy he couldn't have possibly been raped) by an older neighbor boy as a child. He has struggled with it, gone to therapy for it, and moved past it. It has taken him years of self loathing, alcohol, and hitting bottom before learning to love himself again. He is a survivor. He also thinks rape jokes are hilarious. He made one just the other day about some Game of Thrones character. My sister (somewhat of an SJW, not as crazy as those tumblr types though) called him out on being intensive of rape victims. I just kinda looked at her, confused like, and asked if she realized who she was saying that to.

He also lost his little brother to cancer but still makes cancer jokes.

tl;dr my dad is super chill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 22:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> English was created by cishet white men so definitions don't real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 04:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to elementary school with a girl who was a Jehova's Witness. She didn't stand or recite the pledge because it was against her (Christian) religion. I wonder what these people would say about her... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 13:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait wait wait. So when it's "curvaceous" it's normal to be attracted or seek after a woman based on her size or appearance, but when they're thin it's considered narcissistic? How does that even work?
Also, eating disorders are mental illnesses and do not exist simply because of the "ideal figure." They have been documented for hundreds of years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 07:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shout out to you for handling the anons very well. They go from extreme concern for your well being as an "oppressed trans person" to extreme hostility towards you as an "internalized transphobe." SJW logic is something I cannot comprehend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 13:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really tired and I read this as "Valley of the Dogs: Puppies Outnumber People 10 to 1 in Creepy Japanese Town" and was very confused as to what the problem was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The only thing worse than white men are white women." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 14:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 07:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Squirtle is missing a nose! Quick fix, two black slits and you're all set.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 05:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand why children need these types of cars. My SO's best friend was killed by a reckless driver whose parents bought him a 2003 Nissan 350Z. While driving home from a party, the driver (16) was speeding down a 30mph road and lost control causing the car to slam into a tree. One passenger, my SO's best friend, was killed instantly along with the driver while the other passenger survived. This car crash, along with a couple others, lead to the strict driving laws implemented in Connecticut. 

This article has a lot of information, despite the odd name and inability to direct link:
http://www.mydeathspace.com/article/2008/01/22/Tyler_Priore_(15)_and_George_McLean_(16)_died_when_their_vehicle_struck_a_tree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 17:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your data suggest a strong implicit preference for Thin People compared to Fat People

Difference between strong automatic   strong implicit...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 04:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When drinking wine (cooking ingredient) in some games you lose HP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 04:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion, either the elderly woman or pregnant woman should get the seat.

Another thing about this comic is, Chibiham is taking up two seats, forcing a woman with two children to stand because of her selfishness and laziness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 04:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I thought xposting it was enough. If the artist would like me to remove it so she can respost I'd be happy to.
That being said, you should all check out the intro to her series [here.](http://www.reddit.com/r/fatpeoplestories/comments/2214cv/chibiham_juicy_and_me_preface/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 02:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It shows fat logic and I thought it was appropriate. As per rule 2, I figured this was fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chibiham, Juicy   Me: Ham on the Train [xpost from /r/fatpeoplestories] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 02:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 06:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the post by searching the ugly tag. Nothing else interesting on either of their blogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 20:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: Fat logicians being so mad at other fat logicians they resort to shaming each other on /r/fatlogic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 08:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a petite 5'1 female, the thought of somebody my height being 300lbs is mind blowing. I imagine an extra me in front and an extra me in back. No wonder they're out of breath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 04:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay classy, Connecticut.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 19:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, while she did actually say this the screenshot is clearly edited. First of all, the text is the wrong font and does not line up correctly. Second, the rest of what she said in the tweet is deleted. 

RACIST??? LOLOLOL!!! I love Japanese culture and I spend half of my time in Japan. I flew to Tokyo to shoot this video
(continued in next tweet)
specifically for my Japanese fans, WITH my Japanese label, Japanese choreographers AND a Japanese director IN Japan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 07:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to ask if this was what the Scrubs episode was about, but it happened after Scrubs was already cancelled. Very unfortunate for this to have happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 07:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what state you live in so I don't know the specific laws, but I'm pretty sure they can't just send her back like that. Anchor babies are a thing, as is gaining citizenship through marriage. I'd have your family call a lawyer, get a consultation, see what you can do. If you can't afford a lawyer, there's some that'll do it pro bono (for media attention or in support of the cause) or you could raise money online. 

Best of luck to you and your family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 20:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Police officer caught me breaking the law and reprimanded me for it properly? Fuckin' pig. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 13:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to pay to see their bedroom but hearing it is free... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 13:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a trooper! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 08:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rule 1. Don't be a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 07:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gah, if you go then I'll go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 07:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it, you kinda look like Zico from Block B here. I recently shaved all my hair off as well, I know those feels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 05:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I've forgiven myself for shooting you in the face and making you disfigured, why can't you?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 07:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure why people are so supportive of the girl who is hurting her baby? I mean, yellow isn't handling it the best way but he's got a point.

On a side note, why did dark orange bring up Bree if she didn't do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 04:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tagged as "unintentional bigot." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calories are flavor points. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 07:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 06:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any info on what happened to the 911 operator? I hope he lost his job. Nearly lost my shit when he said they needed to respond to life threatening situations first. Kids taken from social worker and a smell of gasoline? Life threatening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 08:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I worked at a daycare there were very strict rules. I was never to have more than 4 children under my care at a time and I was never to leave them in a room/outside unsupervised. These simple yet very enforced rules could have saved this little girl's life. I'm not saying the daycare is entirely to blame, because this was an unexpected accident, but precautions should be taken. Children get into some extremely dangerous situations while not even knowing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 21:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this at first, but it commonly only happens in the torso area. When I had it I only had a couple sores elsewhere (legs, face, etc.) They were also extremely small compared to some of OP's blotches.

OP, I hope this gets better! It really sucks to not know what's going on with your body. p.s Zelda is awesome, I love your tattoo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 17:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I must have worded that poorly. Of course it's possible for people who haven't experienced an eating disorder to realize it's about control. In fact, I wouldn't have even realized that part if not for doctors telling me. 

What I meant by the "it's really hard to understand" part is more about the experience. Being trapped in a sick mind and creating a sick body is downright terrifying. Anorexics are not happy, every day is a struggle between yourself and the mirror. Glorifying a debilitating disease is an extremely slippery slope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 17:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be 150lbs with a BMI of 27 she'd have to be somewhere around 5'2. A healthy weight for her would be anywhere from 101 to 136lbs.  137lbs to 163lbs would be overweight, and anything 164 or over would be obese. To go from a BMI of 16 when she was 88lbs to a BMI of 27 now is a difference of 62lbs. 

Anorexia is a mental disorder, most mental disorders cannot be cured - only treated. I know from experience that even though people with anorexia go "into recovery," they never truly get better. I find it hard to believe that a person who reached 88lbs bounced up to 150. If she really was anorexic, it seems she replaced that disorder with another. Binge eating is another eating disorder about control, but it has the opposite effect of anorexia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 16:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thing is, unless you've experienced an eating disorder first hand, it's really hard to understand. Media says its about being thin and looking pretty, when in reality it's about control. 

That being said, anybody who tells people who have anorexia or bulimia that they have "thin privilege" needs to be kicked in the fupa. Having a disorder is not fun, it's not a privilege.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 06:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The morbid side of me expected /r/deadbedrooms to be pictures of bedrooms left the way they were before a person died. The actual sub is much less dark, but still sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 02:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up hearing a lot of myths about razors in public/school parks. It was almost as common as a razor in an apple you get for halloween. 

One very popular story told to scare to the kids was that a couple of boys glued a razor in the middle of a slide. As a little girl slid down unaware of the razor, she cut herself from her ass to the back of her neck. I never really found out if the story was real or not, but I sure as hell checked the slide every time before I went down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
