<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9926</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not just leave him on the spot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bitches love wagons!

(I wish) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't this essentially entrapment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using block this. It is very nice. It works system wide so even blocks on chrome, and links from my other apps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously if she didn't have height going for her she would have gotten slept immediately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely love this. Owner certainly has a sense of humor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will take small and sporty over any of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this really the best you can do. Yawn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have bought a 135i if I was a sight impaired midget, with no hobbies lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's where your mom rides </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a time I would have been jealous. This is the closest to a friend wagon to ever hit US shores. After owning a MKV briefly however I can only pity you for all the impending problems you will have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say that all that money should have went to hookers and blow, but c5 money will only get you a peg legged ladyboy, and a key bump of stepped on  bathtub meth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you call a hot hatch with a 50cc engine, and 6 D batteries for a power plant?

A tepid hatch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lot easier snuggling cocaine through south America in this bad boy, instead of the donkeys you were using no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How often do you need to change the newspaper, underneath the hamster powering the engine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the 1990s This car was to the Toyota supra, what Scotty pippen was to Michael Jordan. Today it is a also ran POS, that resides under tarps in bad neighborhoods, bedecked with  cracked wings west bumpers, and faded garish paint jobs. Meanwhile even all these years later, the supra is covereted, and pampered, aging like a trophy wife on Botox, and diet pills. 

Nissan 300z the scuffed up Scotty Pippen sneakers of the car world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is sleepers, and then there is narcolepsy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> E91 wagon is beyond reproach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 11:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great news. Despite being outclassed in smart phones, Sony is still amazing at imaging, and games. I really have a soft spot for them, and will still pay a premium for there products over their rivals. Despite the always quirky Sony software, every product I have ever owned from them has been extremely well built.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taco rice at izakaya naru is bomb. They do the hot bowl with raw beef, and it Cooks right there in the bowl.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would eat while stoned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eggplant Parmesan with [homemade] meatballs  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hawaii. I lease it through TMobile so I can just swap it within the next week or so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish more cops had that attitude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ebony and ivory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that mold growing on her handbag? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly kinda wish I got the s8 instead of the +. The screen is actually big enough for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One person was a jerk to you therefore all liberal arts majors devalue your education? That's a leap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 14:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have giant ogre hands, and it is extremely annoying for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can certainly see some Fringe use cases like you described, however for the most part a dedicated Chromebook with a HDMI out, and USB seems to be so much more useful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would totally get high with this dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much. I will try to help out with some monetary, and canned food donations as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA the switching to Galaxy s8 has cured my coverage problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else having issues with third party rapid chargers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a anker quick charge 3.0 car charger, and a aukey 2.0 home charger. Tried multiple USB c cables, but my phone doesn't want to rapid charge on anything but the Samsung brick. Is anyone else having these issues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want anything for them just to preferably give them to hungry people who cant (easily) afford to buy them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Third world problems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite every reviewer mentioning it, I think they still glossed over how crap the fingerprint location is. Luckily I usually have my phone set to be unlocked by my gear fit so it isn't a huge deal, but otherwise I would be pretty annoyed by it. I mostly use my phone in a cradle in my car that does not face me so Iris, and face unlock are not a option. On average I probably unlock the phone 100+ times in the cradle, so typing a pin every time would be maddening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good suggestion but that only takes ups 5-6 bananas at most.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are talking over 100 bananas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bumper crop of bananas. Is there somewhere to donate them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We keep getting multiple bunches of bananas simultaneously. As much as we, our friends, our co workers, our neighbors, and anyone we can possibly think of to give them away to like bananas we are unable to eat them all. 

I was just wondering if there was a easy place to go drop them off in town for needy people. Everyone can appreciate some fresh local bananas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just tether your phone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of all the technologies that ISPs use to provide home broadband, fiber is by far the most robust. Dsl is limited in its bandwidth, and cable is generally fed with a node system where they will run fiber to your neighborhood, but then divide that circuit amongst many different houses. In my experience with fiber internet (not FiOS, but similar) I have never had a issue with congestion, or packet throttling. 

For years Comcast, and other cable ISPs have used packet sniffers to find people torrenting, and slow them down.  There was a time when bit torrent was consuming over 20% of all the world's traffic. To my knowledge Verizon does not use this practice. 

Kodi functions in a way much different then bit torrent. When you use a stream off of Exodus, you are actually connecting to a server, and streaming directly from it. When you torrent you are connecting to many individual other users with the same file, and downloading from many people at once. 

The thing with Kodi is that is does not have the ability to adjust for current bandwidth available. I have watched the traffic on my router, and in some instances HD streams can be consuming over 20mbps consistently for the entire period of the movie. 

Even though you have more then enough bandwidth coming into your home, your local network may not be able to handle these speeds. This is especially true if you use whatever router was provided from Verizon. ISPs are notoriously cheap with their equipment, and let things linger for years past their prime. I'm not sure what Verizon gives you, but my ISP provided me with a 80211.g router with my 300 mbps package. In ideal conditions it would max out at 50 mbps wirelessly. 

From what you are saying my best guess would be that you are using a router with inadequate bandwidth. To find out for sure try plugging devices in with a cable and seeing if that helps. If you rely on wifi then you should probably get a new router. 

The TP Link archer is very well reviewed and inexpensive on Amazon. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are 100% wrong on all counts

https://www.reddit.com/r/Addons4Kodi/comments/3v8jeg/how_does_kodi_exactly_works_someone_please/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Figures some Jersey cunt would lay into a guy trying to help him out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you very much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kodi is illegally streaming, and contingent on the servers you are connecting to. They are often located in foreign countries, and with the exploding popularity of Kodi, are getting more bogged down. 

They also do not have the same capabilities of Netflix or YouTube, where they can scale down to a lower resolution depending on bandwidth. If you select 1080p it will give you 1080p only. Depending on your device if you pause it, and allow a buffer to build up it may help. 

If you have issues with streaming Netflix, then you can blame it on VZ, but with Kodi it will be hit or miss depending on myriad issues. 

I have 300mbps fiber,hard wired, cat 6, directly into a Nvidia shield. Basically the best possible kodi setup possible. I still will have issues with HDstreams from time to time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A1, top choice doggo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah...

No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The s7e was super chromed out. Glad to see them tone it down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is encouraging. I'm hoping for a bump from my crappy Intel iPhone 7+. 

We will find out tomorrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone even have a passing interest in actually buying Samsung Dex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As cool as it is, I just really don't understand what the purpose of Dex is. If I have a static place where I keep a monitor, mouse, and keyboard why not put a real computer there? Or at least plug my laptop in. 

I just don't see any use case for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats cause you and people you know didn't drive older cars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from my son being born this is the best moment of my life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got a deal $60 per month 300/50 fiber internet, and local channels for life.  

Honolulu

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orchid grey is the same shade of gunmetal they painted tuner wheels in the 90s. 

Not sure what Samsung was thinking. This and the baby blue are really not the most flattering colors. Wish they had a deep red or deep blue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on you. He looks like a good dog, who deserved a second chance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just out there with my v20 for a month and coverage was quite spotty out of town.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The headlights are wide eyed, and glassy. It looks like it is tripping balls on three tabs of acid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's encouraging seeing Mexicans practicing their high speed defensive driving. This way when Immigration officers come after you, you might have a chance to escape.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should really add a couple more feet to the rear door, you weren't using the bed for anything anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't see the point of T-Mobile acquiring a outdated satellite company. They alreadybstated they didn't want to go into fixed broadband, so they wouldn't be able to offer a triple play to consumers. 


Where the head scratching direct TV merger with ATT starts making a lot of sense is if they roll out fixed broadband, and start challeging ISPs in entrenched markets. 

The writing is on the wall that TV services will be delivered over the top in the next 5 years so buying a undiversified company like dish in a dying industry is stupid. Better to wait a few years until cord cutting becomes more mainstream, and buy the spectrum seperately as dish looks to sell off assets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't all those high end hotels offer wifi? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live on Oahu coverage is excellent. I work on Big Island from time to time, and it is pretty bad/non existent in the rural areas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The double edged sword of offering everyone unlimited is congestion. I am dying out here in HNL. I need my phone for work, and all the kids streaming infinite Netflix, is making data unusable. 

I hope that one day they offer a higher tier with higher prioritization. I know that is anti net neutrality, but I need my data.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that is service  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would have been so much better if they stayed 16/9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried a few SP on my S7e. I came to the conclusion that it is impossible to get a good one for curved glass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yeah this guy is legit. So much polish  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry Elon musk will take the wheel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Murdered out chick car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he did it in **NIKE** running shoe. I would rather run a marathon in stilettos then Nikes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T-Mobile isnt bad in decent coverage areas. It needs to improve, on the fringes, down the basements, and in the middle of buildings. This article totally missed the point, that while it won't work with 5g, your phone will work at all which is major.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Case came in but no phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty good graphics! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That feeling, when you sold a kidney, plasma, semen, hocked your ps4, went down on a guy from Craigslist for $200 and you are only half way to raising enough money to getting this POS back on the road.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I gathered talking to CS and in store rep they will give you trade in value for your phone (inflated on s8) then the balance remaining (up to a maximum $650) will be paid back to you in instalments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't magnetically close so they are annoying, and don't provide good protection.  Skip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm over here tabulating how much the guy would have to pay me to take possession of that POS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is pretty spendy for a s10 IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T-Mobile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you paint it to resemble barneys rotting carcass, or is that that the way it came? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty annoying to have to wait. I don't see why they couldn't ship them.with the phones through the carriers. Last year it was late June when I finally got mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any difference in functionality between this and the sport version? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the clear cover snap closed, and can you interact with the phone through it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a Optimus prime themed vibrator </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just 3 more $19.99 payments, and you can get your front suspension back out of the pawn shop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4,000 lbs of rust, and 90sness held together by a paper thin coat of shit Toyota paint.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad that you didn't block your LP. 

This way when they issue the Amber Alert for a scion tc with my little pony stickers, we can notify the proper authorities, before you can strike again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does the 86 stand for, how many times you lost a race, how many HP under the hood, or how many guys your GF blew in a row, while she told you she was spending the weekend at her mother's.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck my guests. If they are over on Sunday night chances are they want to see TWD too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you actually own reel to reel, or is that just a prop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 0 regrets leaving NYC's #1 most expensive real estate market, for Honolulus #3 most expensive market </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as you feel comfortable in your own skin that is all that matters. 

 is sexy to me so you are 

Don't let the assholes on here tell you anything different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 08:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made it 10 minutes then realize it went another 45 minutes to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/LCwIVXT.jpg 

Voila

I'm sure everyone has seen a bowl of pulled pork, what matters is the bark.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The risotto dish is mind blowing for a no stir dish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it is that big you will have less bark. I personally like Multiple smaller ones  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lazy man's pulled pork. 18 hour sous vide, 2 hour electric smoker. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New this is the kind of car a gay hairdresser would drive, now it is the kind of car a high school drop out taco Bell worker would get repoed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the personal injury lawyer representing the family of the dead pedestrian never sees this photo. You should put some spikes on your stinger, so at least they don't suffer as much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isnt it's natural habitat on a flatbed getting towed to a transmission shop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still doesn't do it if you have YouTube red.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get about the same results listening to spotify </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hobbies include biking, cooking, building, and working out. Living in the tropics means greasy sweaty hands all the time.  Thereare some materials that thrive in this environment, and some best left stuck inside all day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. My point was that recent advancements such as apt x, and Bluetooth 4have really improve the signal strength, and bandwidth/sound quality. To have the potential of double that is exciting. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that the only vegetable on the plate is butter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those sweet potato fries look killer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (casserole) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much of a good thing IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get a lunch combo with almost as much as this out here in Hawaii. It is probably slightly less expensive then this ran you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes there are chunks of bananas in the waffles, along with pumpkin pie spice, and brown sugar. 

When you have a week to eat 30 lbs of Apple bananas. Everything has bananas in it. (Sips banana smoothie).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] when life gives you bananas make banana waffles. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 13:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be interesting to see what they can do. I got the airpods recently, and the range is unheard of. I was washing my car about 60-70 feet away from my phone, and had one or 2 drops, over a hour long podcast. As recently as last year my bluetooth devices had a hard time getting from my pocket to my ears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He LIVES for hiking. Luckily we take him often, and he is in good shape for a old man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The headlights look like they got depressed, after caught a glimpse of the rest of the ugly body.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many supreme bricks, and Yeezy boosts is this worth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The jalopnik nutswinger starter pack. 

http://rs258.pbsrc.com/albums/hh256/rza45/nutswinger.gif?w=480 h=480 fit=clip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like a evidence photo after they extracted a car from a lake with a guys "missing" wife in the trunk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the ussr never fell this would be like driving a S Class to you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
