<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4909</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 03:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen to The School of Greatness podcast. Learn new skills, perhaps get a certificate in accounting, graphic design or something useful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 03:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, it's good to see that this thread is working. This is inspiring! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Vent/Get Used of IT: Fear? How do you embrace and move on from fear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 02:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another Vent/Get Used of IT: Fear? How do you embrace and move on from fear?

I've been on a roll these past week(s?) (emotionally). I've been watching The School of Greatness YouTube Motivational channel videos/ Lisa Nichols videos. I've been practicing positive thinking and I have 7 days down of my daily gratitude journal. The positive thinking is working a bit, but I definitely have a long way to go.

I've also been looking for sublets to rent until I can put myself together and find a full time job/apartment (my first). Even so, there is still this paralyzing fear/anxiety that makes me back out at last minute whenever I get contacted about renting a sublet apartment. When this fear/anxiety overcomes me I get so SCARED (pseudo stomachaches, trembling, and wanting to burst into tears). Like I don't know what to make of it.I have been feeling this way for five or six months. Like this fear isn't motivating fear and I don't know how I can turn it into motivating fear.
Like a part of me still doesn't want to go through with it. A part of me is still attached to this place/this situation. I've had motivating fear several times before in my life. By motivating fear I mean that fear that makes you feel afraid but there is a bit of excitement/drive because you WANT/HAVE/NEED to do. This fear is something else.

Part of the reason for this fear is if I do get out of my living situation, I have no one to depend on if I fall/fail. I don't like that feeling. I know I should just count on myself, but I am not there yet. 6 years of depression make you believe the lies you've told yourself. Hence why I'm practicing positive thinking/doing gratitude journals btw the next step is affirmations and visualization. Not there yet, but I will be. Basically I don't have support or a cheerleader, someone on my corner. Most of my life I've been independent and responsible but also cold and untrusting, I don't want to go back to the cold/untrusting parts. I know I have it in me
to be the person I need to be. But how do I get there? I also know I am giving too much power to this fear. But this fear means something, this fear is important for some higher power/spiritual, necessary reason.

I can't nor want to repress or ignore this fear (I don't think these are solutions). I want to turn it into something I can use. Something productive/motivating (like turning it into something good). Like can anyone relate? How do you embrace and move on from fear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 05:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
