<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3122</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really is like being held hostage by someone who is becoming increasingly erratic as their demands aren't being met. It's like a new nightmare I can't wake up from every day. It's having a real, negative impact on my mental state.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, he had a stretch where he won two out of three yusho with a 12-3 in between. The trouble seemed to be, in addition to the concerns you mention about hinkaku, that his losses in that 12-3 tournament were to lower ranked wrestlers early on the tournament (one Yokozuna was absent while the other dropped out mid-way). That's a much stronger case than two jun yusho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most important part of what you said, to me, relates to the ways in which a robust safety net makes international trade feasible in personal terms. That sort of safety net is becoming increasingly infeasible in our political climate, however.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the vote went his way this evening. Good for him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kisenosato On Path To Yokozuna </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 10:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe it's really happening! With the terrible day I've had, I can't help but feel Kisenosato and his impending victory is a harbinger of good things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm piggybacking on the top comment to point out that HIV isn't even a huge issue for childbirth like it was for this lady. They have drugs to prevent transmission of HIV in the womb. If you're thinking long term consequences, that's something to keep in mind as we'll.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible he doesn't remember you by name? That's the only case I would think you're likely to be able to get some sort of change in the decision. I know most of my students by face, but I'm not great with names and I teach large course sections. 

If you're certain he knows you by name, I think you're SOL.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 02:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite being a Russian puppet, Trump occasionally makes some astute arguments. His identification of the EU as an instrument of German trade domination is spot on. The Germans derive substantial benefit from the low value of the EU relative to a hypothetical German-only currency. That, coupled with their refusal to share the wealth with Southern Europe, will lead to the demise of the union. 

This insight is lost, however, in the rest of his inflammatory interview.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 23:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The NHK announced said something about Kotoshogiku having sore knees, but I think you are closer to the mark in terms of explanation. It will take a miracle to hold on at this point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget about the straight-to-SyFy version called "I Am Omega" starring Mark Dacascos. It was like watching a slow moving car accident that you wanted to stop but couldn't. 

Spoiler: A woman gets sexually assaulted by a non-zombified corpse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally just made a whoop of joy in my office. My assistant came to see what happened. Walked away shaking her head... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 04:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I show tablets like this when I discuss the history of accounting with my students on the first day of class each semester. I have a museum's photo of a tablet which is supposed to be inventory records for beer production. The frat guys love that one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 20:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not wanting to have them is one thing, but intentionally changing your body so that you can't without notification may constitute a type of fraud or misrepresentation that could adversely impact your divorce settlement should she decide to divorce you. I'm not chastising you despite how it sounds in my previous post (though I think it's a shitty thing to do, it's not my choice). Consult a lawyer to make sure your pre-nup will hold up to your getting a secret vasectomy before you inadvertently cause yourself trouble.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 20:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope your pre-nup protects you from fraud and misrepresentations because it sounds like that's exactly what you're about to do to your wife: misrepresent your ability to have children and commit fraud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You leave Buzzfeed out of this! They should be working for Gawker...the U.K. Press is where Gawker learned from in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 17:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be the exception that proves the rule. "I like women so much that a man has to be THAT attractive to entice me in any way!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 06:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first episode of the second series of Vicar of Dibley includes Liz Smith in one of the funniest few minutes of television I've ever watched. The bit when they talk about potentially hosting the Olympics in Dibley is the bit I'm talking about. Rest In Peace! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a Gen II synth, that's why he seems that way. The Gen IIIs, like Romney, are better functioning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't about sexuality at all. It's about honesty.  By leading you into believing she enjoyed sex with you, she basically set things up to be crushing for you at some undetermined later date. It's like she set a time bomb under your relationship by lying to you. 

Don't let her get away with saying it's because she is bi. It's because she's a liar! Keep focusing on that whenever anyone tries to defend her. Best wishes to you for getting through the holidays after being betrayed like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This had some potential but your lack of story telling panache made it hard to follow and filled the payoff. Give it 6 more editing minutes and help us help you with karma! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 23:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two things:

(1) This is really the top rated comment? What a bunch of pedantic jerks you all are. 

(2) This misspelling is the best thing about the story because it lets us know that the person writing it is probably telling the truth. A liar would have researched the term.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 09:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in this position. We have three top journals, one published by Elsevier. Ignoring it would be career suicide regardless of how bad an actor the publisher is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 18:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that's what I like to hear...someone disengaging from nonsensical arguments! 

I always love to see Mr. Rogers, no matter what he's doing. Thanks for bringing a smile to my face! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is hilarious! It also raises an important semantic point which is probably worth discussion. The title is so silly, however, that I think it will be ignored by many people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with many people here in thinking I didn't hold professors in such high regard. A few professors stand out as being especially brilliant. Most professors, however, simply don't have a chance to demonstrate their expertise given that they teach mostly required courses which aren't their specialty. For example, you could have a French Revolution scholar teaching European history or Western Civ. That professor gets one day out of the term to show off. It's not enough to make an impression most of the time. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 01:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a joke. You know, when people change the words and then put "fixed that for you?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 22:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the Russians have spoken their view on the Clintons, right? I'd fix that for you but I am not savvy enough to use the editor on my phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 21:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I sang mostly Catholic funerals, the music tends to be very traditional. There is a range within the traditional category, but funeral music tends toward the somber by default. I e sung a few odd requests and turned down others based on the rules of the parish, but I can't say any of them were happy. The closest to happy I did was Always Look on the Bright Side of Life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 21:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon and Uber! Both are run by shitty people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> */r/gaybrosgonewild submission history </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like this one bit! No robots can be assholes more efficiently than we can?!? What a crock! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first one wasn't memorable in any way. I suspect that means it was an elderly person in my home parish with whom I was unacquainted. A funeral for a very old person is a much milder affair than, say, one for a child or even middle aged person. There's generally little surprise, so the family tends to be relatively calm.  These funerals take on a much more celebratory feel with family and friends coming to pay their respects rather than mourn deeply. None of this is to say that people aren't sad...they are. They just aren't as overwhelmed by their sadness. That makes it easier to witness and, consequently, easier to sing. 

More simply put, a person's age matters. Someone dying at 65 these days can be described as tragic. At 85, it's "their time." At 105, it's "they cheated death out of 20 years!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 01:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Eagle's Wings is definitely a crowd favorite. I imagine there are geographic preferences, as there are definitely ethnic preferences. As for Bagpipes, there are a separate clique.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read my other response to this question. It's not that simple.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See...I wouldn't even attempt to perform a service for a relative. It's too much. I have a lot of respect for those who try.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't gotten that, but that doesn't mean people don't ask for it. I changed careers before people if that generation got into their "funeral years." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 21:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like 12 hours max for funerals if you factor travel time, but yes...that's about right. Of course, you're doing what most people do by ignoring the inputs to the work. I practiced regularly to stay sharp, went to university for four years to study my craft, and took years of expensive voice and piano lessons before and after university to build up basic musical skills. I also worked hard to network and maintain relationships in order to have access to work. Additionally, I have the sort of demeanor that you would expect from someone who works in the service industry rather than a more "artistic temperament." I also engaged in other musical work, like holding a regular church musician job and teaching student to supplement that income. 

Basically, this isn't a job that just anyone can do, let alone do well. Frankly, it isn't even a job that most musicians can do. People won't tolerate a bad funeral musician for long, so there is constant pressure to be on top of your craft. The money is a reflection of the circumstances of the job and the low supply of competent, temperamentally suitable people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the same way in my writing. The big picture plot is brilliant, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could like this ten times! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Networking is critical. I, like you, started off singing a few. Then I talked to all my organist friends to let them know I am available if they need a sub or singer. I wouldn't go through funeral homes, but you could try that route. 

What matters is that you have a solid voice, good reading skills, and that you're reliable. It's doubly good if you can play piano and/or organ. Once you are known to have those things, networking and announcement of intent are the missing links.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. It'd be like I'm trolling the attendees one last time. They'd see the humor in that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a college professor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very different sort of service from a Catholic funeral. But it makes sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've shared a few elsewhere, but those are ones I've done. I don't know them all off hand, but I can share a few. One I declined was "Come Sail Away." Another was "Bring Me to Life." A third was "Everyone's a Little Bit Racist" from Avenue Q. 

You can see the pattern, perhaps. Either they are songs perceived to be about death or songs perceived to be either about the deceased or inside jokes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, people come with those requests all the time. But they tend to be much more reasonable than you'd think. Lots of old church hymns or songs with religious overtones get requested. 

Some gems? First off, these are all from secular services. I haven't done a lot of those, but I've done a few. The absolute best was Always Look On the Bright Side of Life, complete with whistling. Second best was Bob Marley's. Jamming (I played jazz organ). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow...that's a good one! I've already texted that to my friends and exchanged a few joking comments about it. "Grandpa Joe was a good man...wait, why is he doing the limbo down the aisle? Tell that magician to cut the crap!" "Is this your prayer card?" "What's that behind Grandma's ear? Is it...oh wow. A silver dollar! I just knew she loved you, Tommy!" Those are just the sort of jokes we might rely on to help soothe us in difficult moments. 

Oh man...thanks for the laugh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to check that out. Sounds interesting as a premise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think religious ceremonies are more comforting while non-religious ceremonies are more celebratory. That's a blanket statement so I know you can find examples to counter my view, but that's the main way I view the difference. 

I want a religious service when I pass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of fell into the job, actually. I am Catholic and active within the church, so I was known to priests. I also know Catholic rituals well, an important consideration given the volume of service music involved. I was also known to local musicians as someone who can sight read music well. Most importantly, I can sing and play at the same time. Sometimes I did one or the other, but other times I did both. It was a convergence of skills that made me qualified for the job. 

As for how I did it, I feel like my other comments can give a more complete impression of how I did it than any response I could write here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even think to mention singing multiple funerals on a day, but clearly that happens more often than I'd like to think, particularly in large urban parishes. We'd get coffee and gossip in between funerals, me and the other musician(s). 

Thank you for your kind words, in any event.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a lovely story. I'm glad someone from my field of work was able to give your family a moment like that. Even if we shelter ourselves from the emotions, we all like to think our work makes a difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have that sort of voice. More importantly, Catholic Churches don't allow that sort of thing. Still, I live the thought of a 103-year-old man or woman being carried out to the strains of "Highway to Hell!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put a list elsewhere in the comments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put a list elsewhere in the comments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of incompetent people who work as church musicians. It's a travesty, but churches aren't always meritocracies when it comes to such things. I'm sorry your funeral experience suffered for someone else's incompetence. 

Complaining after the fact, however, can help change things. It won't change the service you had, but it can help save people from future issues.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tell people I'm the only musician they know who gave it up for reasons other than money. If you're going to be a pro, my unsolicited advice is to get ready to hustle. It takes a lot to build a steady music career, but it can clearly be done if you're willing to be flexible and work anything that comes along. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. What's that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to think some things are still sacred to people, death among them. I truly believe that I haven't been scammed because people don't want to sully the memory of their loved ones with such behavior. I almost always sang in churches...even mobsters, who I've absolutely done funerals for, have a healthy fear of God. Working for God gets me a bit of deference, therefore. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes...I sure did. But some songs I still love despite the repetitions. The Ave Maria is a personal favorite despite how often I've sung it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to do altar serving for funerals and weddings to! I wasn't even aware of what was going on, however. As a kid, I just went through the motions. It didn't even occur to me to point that part of the funeral service out, but yeah...that's screwed up that we put kids in that position so young. 

I want to say I didn't chuckle at the dramatized version of your story in my head, but I can't. It's clearly tragic for the family, but also something directly from a Cohen Brothers film. You either laugh about it or cry about it...I almost always choose laughter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one with the wailing (or keening, as someone told me it's called), threw me for a loop. I sang the closing hymn kind of choked up. On a relative basis, I find deceased mothers harder to sing for since I get song so well with mine and hate thinking she will pass away someday. Very poorly attended funerals also bother me more than the huge ones because I feel sorry for the deceased. It got harder as I got older and more aware of my own mortality. Most funerals aren't of the cosmic tragic variety, however. Seeing how much people live their 80-year-old grampy is more sweet than bothersome. 

I actually find weddings to be harder to do on average, personally. Seeing so much happiness stirs up a lot of emotion. I've rarely gotten through a wedding without a few tears. I don't have coping mechanisms for that like I do for funerals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our ideas of crazy may diverge a bit, but the craziest one I recall was somebody asking me to sing "Proud Mary" because they thought it was a good encapsulation of the deceased person's life.   There were other contemporary tunes, but at least those made some sense in context. But "Proud Mary?" Nope!

Honestly, requests don't get very crazy simply because of the timing of the choice. People are generally grief stricken, so you generally get either music planned by the deceased, a fond memory of a single hymn, or a family that leaves the music up to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds horrific. I know the looks you are describing. They are the hardest to deal with for me as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do what you have to in order to cope. That strategy probably wouldn't work long term, but I'm glad it got you through the tough ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no...they handle payment on the day generally. Caterers probably get paid at least partly up front, but musicians don't. The presence of a funeral director to coordinate payment, however, means that issues are rare. A caterer wouldn't have that luxury, generally speaking. So that episode probably happened in real life...probably more than once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really awful. I'm very sorry for your loss. I'll light a candle for him at mass this weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I did, however, get a request for the Dolly Parton version of "I Will Always Love You." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
