<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9189</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the Actual aim of NASA? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here are a few signs the guy likes you but is just too scared to tell you:

1. He seems to be around a lot.

Maybe he goes to your coffee place just about every day. If you work together, he might find himself near your desk or sitting near you at lunch. Maybe you see him at the water cooler more than anyone else.

A good sign that he likes you  but is too shy to tell you  is if he tries to be around you all the time and doesnt steal the spotlight. Hes trying to figure out how to make his move.

2. He goes out of his way to be nice to you.

He doesnt necessarily go over the top, but he does things a good friend would do, even though you don't consider each other good friends.

He'll save you a seat. He'll grab you a coffee or a donut. He'll share his snacks or his lunch  anything he happens to be munching on (I know this sounds silly, but when guys share their food, it means something).

He is always polite and respectful to you. And, most importantly, this feeling of warmth resonates from his body.

3. He always smiles at you and breaks eye contact.

The truth is he cant help smiling at you, but he does his best not to show it. He desperately wants to stare deep into your eyes, but he's afraid you wont want to do the same.

4. He always gives you his undivided attention.

When you two are chatting, his focus is entirely on you. This happens even when youre in a group. Id bet hes looking at you even when youre not saying anything, but he probably tries to hide this.

5. He compliments small changes to your appearance.

That new haircut. That new dress. Those new shoes. That new bag. That new shade of lipstick. Whatever it is you've discarded or added, he's likely to make a comment on it. It's his way of showing you he notices you.

Of course, he may not compliment you as often as he'd like. But he definitely will give you a sincere compliment on occasion. Which  let's be honest  is better than most guys.

6. He doesnt ask you out  even though you suspect he likes you.

Sometimes, the nicest guys are the shyest. They don't see themselves as being the aggressive type, so they have a difficult time doing things outside their comfort zones.

It's a shame, really, because a little bit more confidence would make their lives so much better (and theyd probably get more dates).

Some shy men will find it in them to do what needs to be done, but others will miss out on amazing opportunities. Traditionally, men are supposed to court women, but this doesnt help the shy guy.

If you like him, be the one to make a move. You really don't have anything to lose.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a backup plan or windup plan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you dont get a job, whats your backup plan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
