<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3443</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms14652 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using a satnav to get to your destination 'switches off' parts of the brain that would otherwise be used to simulate different routes, reveals new UCL research. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even Pokemon Moon and Sun are "3D overworld". Yeah, everything is in 3D, but you cannot move the camera, the camera is not always behind you, and every section goes on rails. It is basically the classic pokemon game with fixed camera 3D. 

It feels more like a classic pokemon than Ocarina of Time, for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the fact that a game is open world, doesn't make it "open". it is true that in WW you can sail around and get some stuff, but most of the main stuff goes on rails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main difference is that english nationalism expands itself to be a "british nationalism". There is nothing wrong with english nationalism as long as they don't want to impose their "nationalism" over the rest of the UK.

* When Theresa May denounced Nicola Sturgeon for playing politics with the future of our country

This is what I mean. For english nationalism, their country is the UK. They don't acknowledge different views on what the UK is. If you disagree with them, "you are playing politics with the future of their country". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right, sorry. The game is like 5 years old, I thought it was DS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  BotW almost feels like a franchise-killer because it so perfectly nails everything that the early Zeldas aspired to be. 

Same was said about OoT, which IMO is still better than BotW.

In any case, the author of these videos loves "openness", choice, backtracking; and he often complains when dungeons are linear. So he was bound to love this game.

There have been excellent Zelda games which have been sort of "on rails", such as Wind Waker, which was also an excellent game.

If they do a game similar to MM, I really hope it won't have any sort of time travelling / limit time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~RF4 is a DS game, not 3DS.~~

RF games, as harvest moon or stardew valley, are games that you love or "hate". I also don't like those kind of games. But I don't think it is a bad game. It is just not my style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am annoyed there are no real FF for 3DS. It is my favourite saga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, I did not. I already gave up. still getting the same error.

please if you fix it, tell me how it goes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Conor was fighting in the FW (so UFC 194 or before), the official and ceremonial weigh ins were the same. Fighters used to make "official weight" during the ceremony.

During 205, the official weigh in was during the morning, and during the afternoon it was the ceremonial one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK I didn't now. I thought it was only council / local ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but there were plenty of people from outside of the EU, who've made Scotland their home, live and world here, who were not eligible to vote last time.

Non EU people which have made Scotland their home are very likely to be british citizens (unless they want to spend their live with the uncertainty of visas), in which case they could vote.

EU people rarely have british citizenship because it is not required for us. After Brexit, it will be very different, and you will find plenty of EU british citizens.

By the way, commonwealth people were also able to vote. Which means someone from Canada or Cameroon was also able to vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used the word tribe before in a way to describe how romans used to run their elections during the republic. (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Roman_tribes)

S/he just got it wrong and is using the word in a strange way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The whole point of Scottish independence is to draw a line around a landmass and declare that everyone inside that landmass is a new tribe, members of whom will receive the benefits of that tribe. The OP wants to have the benefits of being able to vote in another referendum because he feels he should have some say in the matter without being a member of the tribe. 

You don't understand what a tribe means in the context I was using it:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Roman_tribes

There were almost 40 tribes in rome.

It is just a way of clutering people based on background / job / social status / ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But once we've left the EU, why should people from EU-Europe have a right to vote in an indyref, but people from non-EU Europe, or America or Angola not? And if they should get a vote, for how long will this 'Scottish referendum voting rights' rule be grandfathered in as a special right if you're from the EU-27 forever more, should indyref 3 happen in 2030?

Indyref1 franchise was very clear:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scottish_independence_referendum,_2014#Eligibility_to_vote

Not only EU could vote, but also commonwealth people, meaning someone from Canada or Cameroon, who was resident in Scotland, could also vote.

At the same time, someone born in Scotland but resident in London or a mediterranean beach was not able to vote.

Basically, the objective of this franchise was to let almost all the resident people to vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SNP has sent me 2 letters about the situation of EU citizens in Scotland. They are already "pushing us". I think it was a nice letter, by the way, just after Brexit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 12:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During 2017 I have only played 2 games so far:

1. Pokemon Moon

2. FE Awakening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any tutorial for using SVM (or any other similar method) and OpenCV? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 12:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been using opencv for a lot of years already, but most of the thing I have done is just image processing and some 3D reconstruction.

When I need to "find stuff", I use img proc to clean my image as much as I can, and then some algorithm to find the shapes I want to find (faces, corners, lines, color, background / foreground).

I want now to take a step forward and use SVM (or any similar method) to help the classification. Obviously I will do some sort of initial image processing, but then I want an algorithm to help me.

I just wonder if anyone can point me to any good tutorial about how to do this.

Thanks ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 12:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, I expect to be in Scotland for a long time (I hope, unless I am deported or something very bad happens), and my girlfriend of 4 years is from Scotland (born and bread, as you would say), so if we have children they are very likely to be born here, and I want to have an input on the future I am leaving to them. As the Tories seem keen to frame it, it seems I won't have any input at all, about my future, or the future of my children.

Secondly, what does exactly a vote represents? As I said before, people seems to think it is some kind of "part ownership". This thought is actually very modern and populistic (like your sentence "what nationality me and my chilndren will be", which is extremelly populistic. Using "childen" in any debate is a cheap shot, it is like saying "we should ban porn, think about the children). The romans were way more practical about what a vote means (more than 2000 years ago). You voted with your "tribe", and you represented your tribe. Even if I leave Scotland in X years, there will be another person, some other EU migrant, in a very similar condition to mines. The point of the franchise of Indyref1 was not about "who I am" but "who do I represent".

There are almost 200k EU citizens in Scotland, and you cannot just silence them, because their "tribe" is very likely to be in Scotland in 20 years, or 50 years, 100 years or 200 years. I am not voting "for me". I am voting for what a EU citizen in Scotland would vote.

Scottish people living elsewhere were not able to vote. Would you rather let them vote, even though a lot of them don't plan to set foot in Scotland again, instead of letting to vote people who is already living and established here? Does a "scottish expat" living in some beach in the mediterranean who will never visit Scotland again be able to say what nationality your kids will have? Because that's what the Tories want, by the way.

The tories let EU citizens to vote during Indyref1 because they knew most of us would vote no (EU uncertainy and all that), and now they want to remove us from the equation because they know most of us will vote yes. That's like the opposite of what democracy should be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could vote during Indyref1. If they don't let me vote I will be very annoyed and feel that democracy failed here. Scotland has always been an example on how to define a voting franchise, I could also vote during the last  elections to the Scottish parliment, while as far as I know the only ones EU granted are the local ones.

I already think it is very stupid that I can vote in my original country, but not here. Is this stupid idea people have about their vote being like their "part of the ownership" of a country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Being let loose in the calm courtyard with very little in the way of forced tutorials was such a great way to start the game. 

The problem is that new players don't really want that. Even if open worlds such as GTA, they want some direct marking telling them were to go.

I have a 3DS and I frequent a lot the 3DS subreddit here in Reddit, and there you can see how frequently new players complain about Ocarina of Time or Majora's mask, because they don't know what to do. The idea of "go out and explore" is kind of gone for the new generations. They want the game set in rails, and instant gratification. the idea of just roaming around without increasing the % of complete game is not something they like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Thankfully they went back to that approach with Breath of the Wild. 

I am playing now Zelda: Link between worlds, and it follows the same scheme. There's no tutorial, and you need to move and explore around for a bit, where they show you a bit of the world, until you get new items to explore new areas.

I cannot remember any Nintendo game with a set tutorial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Mario64 aged poorly.

There's something that happens with videogames, and that also happens with other forms of art, like movies, fashion or music.

When the piece is initially released, everyone is shocked because it looks or sounds amazing. There's a period then when other pieces of art "improve" it, and the game (or song or movie) sounds or looks dated, and people says the "it aged poorly". But when there's a final step when the piece becomes an atemporal piece of art, and you enjoy it based on what it is.

Music is a very common example of this. If you listen to Led Zeppelin 1, the sound is incredible amazing, and if you compare it with nowadays production, a lot of people will say that they prefer vintage all analog production. There was a period, though, when everyone started to use digital for everything, that people said it sound aged.

My opinion of Mario64 is very similar to this. When I play it nowadays I think it is a unique piece of art. Yes, you can get games in your phone with better graphics (but not better art design). It is not only how it looks, but how responsive the game is, how the enemies move, the design of the levels, the classic music.

No one is playing it nowadays expecting something ground breaking, but even then it surprises you.

This is the same for every game with was really well made. I replayed FF8 recently and I got the same feeling. After the first 5 minutes of "this looks really blocky" you start to appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was a tuf finalist with 3 KOs in the house. They always get more leverage. Another example of 0-2 and not cut is Khalil Roundtree. Also from TUF.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah yeah we called it "Recopa" in Spain. Barcelona has a lot of them 8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 11:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cup winners never played CL, there was the "Recopa" for cups winners. I don't know if this is what you meant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 10:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here i am. Unable to unlock mines  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 10:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, it is not. Every poll out there is giving the same results  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am surprised Jouban was so rocked by that punch which seemed to hit his forehead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks I think I will do that, if I can find the game anywhere to buy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in theory it was now, but with the 2 missing fights, maybe it is in 1h? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brexit yes or no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> always excited to watch fight lives (on tv I mean, instead of waiting to the next day).

Watching a fight live (on tv) it is way more exciting than watching a repetition even when you dont know the result </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard apocalypse is more "playable"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played OoT in my n64 back in the day, and for me it is the best game ever. 

I played recently MM in my 3DS (one of the reason I bought it), and i don't know. Even though I finished it and spent around 50 hours, i don't think it is a master piece. I wonder what my opinion would be if i played it back in the day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classic question, iv or apocalypse ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. They were games meant to be played in a big tv, plus the n64 was amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pokmon is perfect. Most of the time you're just walking around capturing Pokmon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chandler clean though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 3ds can play ds games though. They knew plenty of 3ds users would buy them. As far As i know the switch cannot play 3ds games  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5" with 720 at least. Every shitty phone has at least a 720p. I have a shitty Chinese phone with 5" and 1080 which i bought for like 120 pounds. And the battery is amazing because it is 4000mah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Heiko Westermann

he was good/decent in betis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't the second leg in Barcelona? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EU loser here. I did vote for indyref1. If i cannot vote for indyref2 I'll be very angry and write here a long post.

In any case I hope the situation of EU people is somehow regularised after Brexit. I have all my life here. I cannot just "leave". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is also my home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. I pay 420 for a studio at the bottom of byres rd  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was she saying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thery will never do this. It will fragmentate the userbase, which is the last thing game makers want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think a new version would be about the internal storage and the battery life. 

plus better cpu and gpu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep. The difference between Eddie and Cowboy was crazy:

http://media.gettyimages.com/photos/opponents-donald-cowboy-cerrone-and-eddie-alvarez-face-off-during-the-picture-id456161938?s=594x594 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is very sad, but the only way to enjoy most of the DS gems are to going to /r/3dshacks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sorry to break the circlejerk, but I disagree. And I have a 3DS and I love it, by the way.

First of all to consider the library of the DS part of the 3DS is not fair. If we do that, then the PSP is the best handheld ever (it could play all PSX games) (no idea about if the Vita still can).

Just by comparing the 3DS to the other Nintendo handheld systems, it has a weak library. I would the 3DS library is similar to the GBA, but weaker than the GB or the DS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might eat my words but this is easy for Joe. it is also surprising that in theory madadi is 1 inch taller than Joe, but Joe here looks 1-2 inches taller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will do it. They did it with the 3DS, they will do it with the Switch.

There is a point where just getting better hardware is more cost effective to source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worst thing is that now hereis says he can beat him, bite the mouch piece and go all in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait for the "New Nintendo Switch" in 2-3 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the 3D gameplay

Link between worlds is not really retro style. The world I would say is fully 3D and very well drawn. The only thing is that the game view is top bottom. Just because it is the newest game I would say it is the one with the best art and best design of characters.

It really never felt like a 2D game to me, and very often the camera moves around and things like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any of them, they are really disconnected games, and they are not story driven. I mean, the overall story is very basic, usually the sub-plots are more interesting.

I would suggest you start with A link between worlds, only because it is the newest one, and the mechanics and everything are very refined, and I am sure you will like it.

Ocarina is the best one for me, best game ever, but its mechanics are almost 20 years old, so for some people it is a bit of hit or miss. Same with Majora's mask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v543/n7645/full/nature21420.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA study confirms that using biofuels to help power jet engines reduces particle emissions in their exhaust by as much as 50 to 70 percent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 years? More like 5 or 10. During the next 2 years after article 50, only the terms of the break up will be discussed. In this case it is very simple, UK citizens won't have access to EU health. There won't be any "building agreement" during this 2 years, but only how shared resources will be split , such as debt, or EU facilities in the UK and things like that.

After the UK is cleanly out (so 2 years later), then they will need to go around Europe knocking on doors trying to get an agreement with different countries. I expect this to take 5-10 years. 

In the case of the EU health card.. it is not really a big problem. Travel insurances are cheap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time a LePen went to the second round 10 years ago, he lost 80/20 against Chirac, who was at that point extremely unpopular and sort of corrupted  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 seasons before that. The last 2 with Rijkaard we won nothing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last season Rijkaard finished 17 points behind Madrid. First season Pep he won 3 titles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey sorry, yeah it is sold to the other redditor who asked for it a few days ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He run for DOF during the elections Laporta won, but he lost. He wanted to appoint Lillo as coach though ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't have Bara DNA, he is the DNA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember that it is not the first time that LePen qualifies for the second round. In 2002 his dad did too. There Chirac got a 20% and LePen a 17%. In the second round Chirac got a 80% and LePen a 20%.

LePen was completely smashed even though at that point Chirac was super unpopular and was related to corruption cases.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary Clinton never had a 80%. 2 months before their GE she had like a 45%, and Trump had like a 40%. It was a big gap. And by the way, she won the popular vote on those terms, more or less.

I dont know if you know how the french system works, but there are 2 rounds. First one free for all, second one for the 2 most voted ones.

At the moment Le Pen is leading the polls with a 26.3%, she is, as you know, similar to UKIP. The second one is Macron, which is leading a brand new party, with a 25.3%, this party is very similar to LibDems. Then you have Fillon (sort of Tories), with a 19.2%, then Hamon (Labour) with a 13.9%, and finally you have Melenchon (far left) with a 11.6%.

it is very very likely that Le Pen and Macron will go to the second round. Both parties are "fresh brand new". Le Pen's is not that new, but it is the first time they are in this position.

There's no way that their Labour or far left will vote for Le Pen. So in the second round Macron can expect something like a minimum of a 50.8%, and this is ignoring the fact that a lot of Tories will vote for him (the same way a lot of Tories voters in the UK would vote for LibDems instead of UKIP). Polls actually give him around a 70%, while LePen will have a 30%.

In any case, even if Le Pen wins the second round, with an initial 25% she won't be able to form a government.

BTW, betting agencies give first round to Le Pen with a 4/6, but second round to Macron with a 8/11 (second round for Le Pen is a 5/2).

There will be a lot of hysteria once Le Pen wins the first round, saying she won the elections, while that is false. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do you recommend to buy screen protectors and cases? I am based in Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Redmi 4 (Prime). The screen protector I am using kind of shatters very easily. Also the "case" that came with the phone is kind of useless. It is very thin, silicon-like, but I don't think it offers much protection.

I have seen that there's stuff on Amazon and ebay, but I wonder if there's something out there you would recommend (like an specific case or screen protector).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Polls give her a 20-25% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  BBC: WILL GEERT WILDERS BECOME PM?

This is just shocking. You'd expect them to know more, at the end of the day, they are the BBC.

It is basically the same situation with Le Pen. There's is no chance in hell she will win the second round, and even if she does, she will never be able to form a stable government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't know if the others were juicing or not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry :( 

I didnt post it for the joke btw, it just came to me after it, and I thought it would be funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 100% he will coach Qatar for their WC for a fuck tone of money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We all knew that negotiating with a group of 27 countries, each with their own wants, is going to take a lot of time.

This is something I think the UK never understood about EU. Your political system behaves like an absolut power that changes every 5 years (basically this is caused by the way you give seats). Politicians rarely negotiate. They win elections, and then they decide what to do.

On the other hand, in most EU countries, government is shared by 2-5 parties. There are even governments with no party control (like Belgium for 2 years, Spain for 1 year), and countries in minority without any alliance (like Spain now). This means that EU politicians are very used to long negotiations, trades, and giving up a lot of their key points just to reach an agreement. EU politicians are very used to give up things. UK politicians are not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the UK doesn't seem to understand is that:

(a) The UK is leaving EU, not the other way around. EU is already busy managing nearly 500m people. Why should the EU take the first step? It doesn't make any sense. The EU is not making TM wait. The EU is already busy with some other stuff.

(b) when Article 50 is invoked, what will be negotiated are the terms of the break-up. Nothing more, nothing less. The UK thinks they will "negotiate" with the EU and talk about trades and things like that. That's not going to happen. Only the break-up terms will be negotiated, which will be basically about debt, eu people in the uk, british people in the eu, shared resources that will need to be reallocated, and money floating in projects that might extend more than 2019. From the moment article 50 is invoked, to the 2 years deadline, the talk will be only about "how we break this".

(c) only after 2 years and when the UK is fully out, then, and only then, the UK will be able to negotiate with the countries about trades and all that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are horrible news for Espanyol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pep Guardiola says he will never return to Barcelona: "Never again, my period at Barcelona is over." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much is he paying you for this promo ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing fight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ??? This weekend we lost against Deportivo after a non existent penalty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We got shafted by ref / PSG in a game in the early 90s. When they had Weah.

The thing is that that Barcelona team sucked (Busquets was our GK), so no one cared  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An MD can have a PhD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick question, do you have a PhD ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's this one in Coatbridge where Paul Craig trains, no? There are direct trains between Edinburgh and Coatbridge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea about Edinburgh, but there are a few in Glasgow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the Scottish people already decided during indyref1 that we can vote.

Based on your opinion, I'm glad I'm living in Scotland and not England. I prefer people more welcoming. 


Also, i don't plan on leaving Scotland any time soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because this second referendum is directly related to the UK leaving the EU while Scotland voted for the EU, it makes perfect sense for EU citizens to vote now in indyref2, even more than indyref1.

I am a EU citizen living in Scotland. I have been here for a few years and i want to stay here even more years. The UK wants to deport me while Scotland wants freedom of movement. Why I wouldn't be able to vote? 

In any case, EU citizens in Scotland are a minority, around 200k people out of 5.5m , whatever we vote won't really change anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he beats Bisping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What makes that difficult for them is that the last one is recent enough that changing the terms looks so obviously like crude self serving manipulation. 

Exactly my thoughts. Changing the franchise when the previous one only happened 5 years ago (if the new one happens in 2019), makes no sense and it would be disgusting.

They let the EU citizens to vote in he first indyref knowing fine well they would vote for remain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We could vote during indyref1. If we are banned now it would be shameful, and I hope the SNP doesn't accept those conditions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm sure the SNP has enough polls and research to justify taking a "get tae fuck" approach.

Basically there are around 200k EU citizens in Scotland, who during Indyref1 voted NO for obvious reasons, and now they will vote YES for obvious reasons.

I am a EU citizen in Scotland, and I have already received 2 letters from the SNP pandering to our group.

I votes yes, by the way, and I will vote yes again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I voted yes during indyref1, and I will vote yes again, but this is a mistake from SNP. It is too early.

They like to think that because of Brexit a lot of people would have changed its mind, but it is not true. In my workplace most people votes No, and not a single one has changed their mind.

It is like Brexit in this subreddit. We think that because the pound dropped a 10% and EU doesnt offer a good trade, a los of leavers would vote remain if asked tomorrow, but the reality is that every poll out there indicates a very similar results to Brexit1.

if the SNP wants to win it, they need to make a long term plan for 10 or 15 years.

The main difference here are going to be the EU people, who voted en masse for a NO and now will vote for a YES. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, swap one of them for Diaz.

I have to say during the second fight I could hear some of my neighbours shouting at 5am. I didn't expect for UFC (or McGregor) to be so big in Scotland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I voted yes, and I will vote yes again, but I think this one is coming too early, basically because I think it will be lost again. Similar to what happened in Canada. There there were 15 years between referendums, which I think it is much better.

People's opinion doesn't change that fast. It is a common mistake we do when we lose something, we think that we are still right, them wrong. It is like brexit. If you go to r/uk with the pound dropping, no trade with EU,... it seems that people would vote en masse now for a remain, but every poll out there seems to say that the results would be very similar.

SNP thinks that they were "right" and the others "wrong", and that because of Brexit and May a lot of "no" voters would swap to "yes". Where I work there are a lot of no voters, and not a single one has changed their opinion, not a single one. They give you exactly the same reasons.

I think the SNP should have waited at least 10 years between referendums, "educate" the people and teach them the "yes". This is what they have been doing in Catalunya for more than 30 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also McGregor vs Diaz 2 only 6 months after the first one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to buy a Vita recently, and it is IMPOSSIBLE. I couldnt find a single shop that sells one, not even games, not even a stand, nothing. It is like if the console doesn't exist.

I enjoyed my old PSP a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was impossible for me to like the Oracles games because a lot of the stuff you have to do seems very random and the fact that you have 2 maps in one forces you to remember a lot. I don't know, I didn't like the 2 maps thing.

I had to check too many times a guide to know how to follow... This rarely happened to me with A link to the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played OoT back in the day when it was released for the N64. It is the best game I have ever played.

I don't want to play it today because I feel some of its amazing stuff might look dated and I want to keep that feeling, "best game ever".

Some of the stuff the game did, like day night cycles, free roaming, kinda open world,... were unique and shocking back then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 11:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially because at that time there might be a lot of rain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 11:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like her. She was working on a take away before being MP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 11:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was working on a take away before being MP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example : http://www.americatv.com.pe/deportes/movil/futbol-mundial/zidane-y-dura-critica-sus-jugadores-derrota-ante-valencia-n266461 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has thrown them under the bus a few times. Everything has been in his favour since he took the job. We will see if he is good handling them once things go bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The years of Ramos in Madrid have actually been the best in Bara's history  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always the same. I guess you're new here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Betis robbed. It was a red for keylor navas in the 23 and penalty from Carvajal to Sanabria in the 39.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of his rotations only work because he has stellar players. I suggest you watch his old games with Castilla.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah we all saw six times the ref taking the balls in his hands, running half field, and throwing it into PSG net, and then signaling for the half field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know why you are downvoted, because this is a fact. the ball never touched Ter Stegen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't know whether Enrique is a good or shit manager.

IMO Lucho doesn't add anything, but he doesnt remove anything (like Tata, I think he had a negative factor). He is neither positive nor negative. So basically, the players are the ones doing everything. I think the same about Zidane by the way. They just keep the players fit and a bit motivated. Tactically none of them are genious, and they read the games very slow. Sometimes this is the kind of coach you need. Del Bosque was like that, and he won everything.

Pep on the other hand was a genius, and even Rijkaard was a net positive factor, except the last 2 seasons when he lost control of the team, but during the first 3 seasons you could see Rijkaard was very important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some random facts:

- First time Suarez scores and Barcelona loses. Every other time he scored Barcelona scored or tied. This happened in a bit more than 70 games.

- Bergantios has scored 4 goals in La Liga during his career. 3 of them were to Barcelona.

And finally, to UEFALONA fans, the corner kick that ended in Bergantios goal, was not a corner kick, because Ter Stegen never touched the ball. it hit the post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pokmon moon. Around 50 hours in. Almost finished. No idea what I'll play next, probably Zelda because it's still available in the shops  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 12:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can see pictures here: http://imgur.com/a/69580 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started with the Boston fight night, siver Vs goat. The day mma changed forever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Artem spars every day with the unanimous GOAT and has sent him to the hospital a few times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If every time they watch the tv they bang theory walls or put notes through, then their behaviour is borderline harrasment.

I'd tell them to call the police if they are so annoyed, but if they keep hanging my walls I'd call the police myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 12:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a dB logger. They are cheap. When they complain show it to them and they can see it's under the limit. If they say "but it was above before you just turned it down " tell them it's a logger so that is a lie. 

If they keep complaining tell them you are going to contact the police for harrasment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 10:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barcelona </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He ignored the question and asked someone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spanish PM has an interesting opinion about Brexit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a big L though, keep that in mind. That is the reason why I am selling it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am spanish myself, and this is my fifth year in Glasgow. I have tried plenty of spanish restaurants here, and none of them really convinced me. I am not expecting a 3 michelin star place, especially not for tapas. But I don't know, everything was kind of disappointing. Nothing really taste "home made", and everything tasted like from frozen or almost ready.

What I suggest is that you cook the paella yourself. It is really easy to cook. The total cooking time takes like 1 hour, but the steps are really easy.

If you want chicken paella, it would be something like this:

- Get some sort of big pan. If you don't have one, a pot will do it. A pot will result in a more watery rice, in spain we call this "arroz caldoso" instead of paella. But it is equally nice.

- Put olive oil. I recommend to put A LOT, without going overboard. a thin layer covering the whole pan. If using a pot, because the surface is smaller, a bit more.

- Once the oil is hot, throw in pieces of garlic. I would say 1 per person, until the garlic is a bit golden.

- Then add your chicken. Whatever you feel like you are going to eat. With or without bones, it doesnt matter. Just put it however you like it.

- Get 1 tomato per person, and grate its inside. You dont want any skin, just the inside. So just split in half the tomato, and grate through the soft part. Once it is all grated. throw in with the chicken. Shake and move everything, probably lower the fire. Once the chicken is golden, and the tomato is kind of gone, it is usually the right time.

- Adding your veg. Standard paella uses bajoqueta y garrafon, this is some sort of big white beans and green beans. You won't find this here. so use whatever you feel like eating. long green beans work very well (chopped into pieces), as do artichoke hearts, peppers or garden peas. Shake everything together, and let it cook.

- Once you feel it is cooked, it is the same to add the rice. You need to know your rice (how much water per rice portion), and this is something you will master as you repeat the recipe. In Spain we use "bomba rice", which you can buy in supermarkets here, but it is uber expensive. Unless you are rich, I recommend just long rice. In my experience, a mug of milk is something like 3-4 portions of rice, but use any measurement you are used to. If I put a mug of rice, then I usually put 1 mug of water. But as I said, this really depends on the rice, so initially I would suggest going for like 1:1.5

- Just after the rice and water, add the spices. Big supermarkets sell a "paella mix" sachet (or tube) which works quite well. Try to get that. Otherwise it is really a mixture of saffron and paprika. But I recommend just buying one that is done.

- Now add half stock cube (chicken).

- Because you likely added cold water, put the hob up, until the water bubbles, then keep a medium point for the hob knob.

- something very important, dont move the rice! people tends to move everything while cooking, but if you shake the things around, the rice breaks and becomes like a paste. Just make sure carefully that the rice is equally distributed, and let it cook, dont ever touch it again!

- wait until all the water from the surface is gone. Then carefull move some of the rice around, to see if there's any water underneath. If you cannot find any water, then it is done! otherwise let it cooked it for a bit more.

- remove the pan from the hob, and let it sit for 10. then eat it! Something common is to add lemon afterwards.

The most important thing about paella is to remember that everything is cooked in the same pot, in different stages. but always in the same pot. first meat, then veg, then rice, layer by layer. I have seen people or places cooking the rice in a separate pot and then putting all together, no!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/jkblPD9.png

This is exactly what I bought. It was sold by Amazon from TNF shop, so  it would really surprise me if it is fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 40 sounds fine, but I cannot drop it anymore.

This afternoon at home I will take pictures. I hope that apart from buying a jacket that was too big, I did not buy a fake one! Although in that case I wonder if I can complain to amazon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been in this subreddit for something like 6 years. You dont know how many times i have been asked about this.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 12:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game is a shame. A game between us is really important for both fanbases. You cannot do a friendly game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 10:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2 computers where I can only use Edge, it crashes every 20 seconds ! "Recover page".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give me an example of a young fighter with a lot of fighting years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The strange this is that he got the visa for TUF, but then he had problems like 2 months later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The celebration of Barcelona's sixth goal generated a tiny earthquake or tremor in the city </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought it from amazon. I removed the tags. I dont really know the process to send it back. I have never done it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they will wait until past the local elections </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their reach is identical, which is the most important factor IMO, and this is very good for Jose if he is going to fight someone who is primarly a striker. Mendes hit him mostly when he was feinging a TD.

Apart from that, Jose has won against taller fighters (Korean Zombie, Kenny Florian). I don't think it is going to be a problem for Jose, because he has never been a head hunter. As said, I think he will stay in the outside and eat him with leg kicks, and then try to conter once max moves in.

I just see Aldo in a completely different level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  laughing stock

You are not the laughing stock because any football fan knows how it sucks. Those making fun of PSG are not football fans, so you can ignore them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cannot blame the ref when you lose 6-1.

In any case, when you have a team going mental searching for goal during the 90% of the game, with so many times the ball being in your own area, penalties are going to happen, always, it is just statistics.

The person here to blame is Emery. The first half was a DISASTER. But then in the second half, with the 3-0 and against the ropes, they did the right movements (di maria in) and PSG actually had the best opportunities there. But then for some freaking reason he got complacent, thinking the 6-1 was impossible.

If you have a lead of a 4-0 and players as good as Draxler, Di Maria or Cavani, you should always go for a trade game, instead of parking the bus badly. When PSG went to trade, they scored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maia's TD technique is not your classic wrestling technique (like Woodley's, for example). He doesn't really need to shoot for the TD, he just needs to initiate the grappling, and considering how stationary Woodley is, that's not difficult.

Maia's stricking is not amazing, but his defence is decent. Remember that he fought against Silva during his peak.

The only question here is if Woodley will be able to connect and KO Maia. it that doesn't happen, I am sure Maia will take him down, and sub him. Remember Woodley vs Rory in the ground. Woodley's BJJ is not that amazing, and he couldnt stand up against Rory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same way each fight has gone for Aldo except the one against Conor. Aldo will keep the range, eat him with leg kicks. People undervalues Aldo after the fight against Conor. They seem to forget all the other fights, including his fight against Frankie.

I don't see anything Max can have against Aldo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is a good time because you get good deals! Like the one I bought, its marked price is 120, and Ive got it for 70. It is just a black jacket, so next winter it will be fine. The problem is that it is just too big for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last season, though, the one Barcelona lost against Bayern 7-0 because we had no coach... Madrid failed badly too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Benzema was also there. I would be more likely to blame Mourinho for those years, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 11:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who voted yes during Indyref1, and who will vote yes again, she needs to wait longer. There's no need to rush it, and every poll out there seems to favour the NO.

The second one is the last opportunity, like what happened in Canada. There won't be a third, at least in our life time.

Just wait, and let's see how Brexit goes. The Tories and Brexit are a ticking bomb, there's no need to rush it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 11:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have watched that fight a few times, and the performance from Rory was masterful. His combinations to T-Woodley were amazing. T-Wood look like even scared. He was just moving from corner to corner, while Rory was stalking him.

Why I think Rory wins easy:

Rory's stricking is not as good as Wonderboy, but it is much better than Woodley (woodley basically has a super punch, and that's it). Rory has a super long reach (76"). He is not going to knock you down, but his combinations and kicks are amazing. Rory is not a counter fighter, he is a stalker, but he really never commits.

Rory's ground game is much better than T-Wood. He finished that fight on top, easy. He kept T-Wood down for like 2 minutes, when T-Wood was desperate for knockout. Rory made T-Wood quit. I think TWood style is just perfect for Rory.

Also, and I know that what I am going to say now is not popular, because people here follows the famous "fighting years". But T-Wood is 34 years old. He is a very old champ. Only 1 year younger than GSP. On the other hand Rory is 27.

I know that people here only follows the "fighting years rule" (Which IMO is kind of bullshit, there are a lot of counter examples, see Bisping, Overeem, Werdum, Frankie Edgar or even Nate Diaz). People with super long careers that peaked late (or kept their peak until late).

When you are 27, like Rory is (or I think he was just 25 against Lawler) you recover much faster. I can only speak for my experience, which I know it is "just my experience". But I love sports and I have been practicing them for a long time. I am 31 now, and when I was 27 my athleticism was just much higher. As a 31 year old male, after every traning season I need like 30 minutes of stretching, and my whole body aches the next day. I remember when I was 27 I could go to train and then party. I cannot imagine how it is going to be once I am 34. In the last 2 years I have been developing pains in my hip, and sometimes I cannot train at all. I doubt T-Wood is "fresh". If you see pro athletes his age, after training they need to spend 1 hour in a ice tube, and that's in sport where some sort of recovery peds are allowed (like in the NBA). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 11:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's still unknown if Rory's nose can hold up.

Tyron Woodley couldn't hit him a single time. Rory can pressure him, he doesn't care about the TDs, and he has better ground game. He finished the fight on top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 11:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cardio is very related with size. It is easy for Mighty Mouse to have good cardio when he only weights 125 pounds (tops 135 during the fight). I wouldn't say that MM has a much better cardio that some of the fighters in his same division. For example, I wouldn't say he has a better cardio than Joe Dodson.

IMO we should pick fighters that have a much better cardio than everyone else in the same division. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 11:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They had someone called Pipita Higuain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iniestazo 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it would be interesting to see if split D benefits champion or challenger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 12:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'd argue that it's the opposite in the UK. Any former Prime Minister get such vitriol poured on his/her legacy. Everyone wants to blame them for the worlds ills and anything that didn't go 100% in their time. 

My little experience with british politics is that your politicians will rarely take any blame about anything, and they will usually blame others (until now this was the opposition, like now the Tories blaming Labour for anything, or Europe).

I have watched sometimes the "questions to prime minister" or when someone ask about something like "Why X region is under funded" the answer is usually "they got less money with labour".

Obviously the "blame the previous party" is used everywhere, but not to that extreme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 12:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Opinions about Thatcher today aren't nearly as strong as they were when she was in power.

It depends who you ask to. She was a very polarised politician within the UK. Some regions used to not care about her, some regions hated her deeply.

Those regions that didn't care much about her, which is mostly south England (so the most populated area of the UK), nowadays kind of accept her. That's why you read "good stuff" when she died, because most of the media is based in London. On the other hand, regions that hated her in the 80s still hate her nowadays. Just ask in Scotland.

The problem if you are from outside the UK (I am spanish myself) is that if you check the british media you will mostly check London centric media (BBC, The Guardian, and so and so), which doesn't really represent what the people in Scotland, North Ireland or North England might think. Like if someone wants to check what's going on in Germany will probabli check Spiegel, for example, and for obvious reasons their views doesn't represent the whole Germany.

I guess in the USA it is kind of easier, because you have big newspapers in different cities. Like you have the NYP, LA Times, WP. Just checking LA Times and NYP you get very different views on the same subject. In most european countries most of the media is based in the same city, and represents a very centric view. In Spain, for example, most of the "national" media is based on Madrid. Thus if you want to read about the spanish royal family you will think Spain has a positive view about it, meanwhile if you go to parts far away from the center, the opinion might be drastically different. But foreigners rarely check "local news". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers discover that male baldness shares a substantial biological basis with numerous other human phenotypes and may deserve evaluation as an early prognostic marker, for example, for prostate cancer, sudden cardiac arrest and neurodegenerative disorders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 11:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unrelated to pipes. If it was near the sea it could be sea water with a bit of processing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tap water is safe in Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Brendan always with the phone? It looks horrible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel really bad for all these fighters. They are all basically being shafted for "money fights", in a lot of these instances the money fight is not even generating that much money (see Bisping vs Henderson).

Holloway for example. Now he is getting his title fight, but it was probably 1 fight too late. Khabib and Ferguson both deserve it in the LW. Maia in the WW. Romero or Jacare in the MW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Damn! One of this days science is going to find out that we are robots, not joking.

I guess it depends on how you define what a "robot" is. When people thinks about "robots" they think about mechanical platforms which move and think. Ultimately the objective of a humanoid robot is to be as similar as possible to a human, from every point of view. So if you think that way, we are already robots. A big branch of robotics is about "bio inspired" systems, and they take as much as possible from biology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you very much, your answer is perfect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paper: http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/02/28/1615290114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One in 5 residents overuses electricity at neighbors' expense. Household electricity use falls by more than 30% when residents are obliged to pay for their own personal consumption. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paper: http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/02/28/1609194114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who suffer from obsessive compulsive disorder (OCD) are poorer at learning about the safety of a stimulus than healthy volunteers, which may contribute to their struggles to overcome compulsive behaviour, according to new research from the University of Cambridge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about song / style / drums </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So today I was listening to this:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jSFsrmLhC00

which is a very jazzy video game soundtrack (transport tycoon).

And I really love how the drums join in around 0:19. It is like they are off by a beat, but a I love how it sounds. I wonder if this is characteristic of some jazz style, and if you could point me to more stuff like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 10:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: http://robotics.sciencemag.org/content/2/4/eaal3735 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A japanese research group has developed a molecular robot consisting of biomolecules, such as DNA and protein that can start and stop its shape-changing function in response to a specific DNA signal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 10:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 09:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Local shops have no chance against IKEA and the likes.

The selling prices they offer are just impossible for a local shop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He got the belt and the money. Nothing left for him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with what you say. Wonderboy did nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is very good. Main and co main of course, but then I want to see Duffy and Luque again  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right. I got it wrong with the other swedish guy he beat in the first fight in the house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ryan Hall

He also had an easy win against Teymur. I wonder what's Hall's ceiling. I think we will never know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr Jones has spent all his live in the UK. He speaks the language, he knows the locals. He has a market, he knows the neighbours, he has a network established. He knows how Ms Theresa likers her flowers, and same for everyone else. He also knows whats best at any given time in the UK because he knows the seasons. He has established a network with providers to get the best possible deals. He knows what's the "hit" this year. Neighbours trust him thus he can go to other people gardens even when they are not at home. He also provides a good work and people are happy with him. Neighbours recommend to each other the services of Mr Jones.

Mr Smith doesn't know anyone. He can barely speak the language. He has no network. He knows nothing about UK gardening. He knows nothing about british seasons. He doesn't know how Theresa likes her garden. People won't trust him when they are not at home. The only thing he can do is going around the houses and dropping a piece of paper with his contact number.

If Mr Smith is beating Mr Jones in a market he completely controlled, then... there's something wrong with Mr Jones. Not everything is about money. In fact people go rarely to the cheapest option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mum closed her shop once IKEA appeared. You've got there in IKEA locals selling the same as she was selling, but with a fraction of the salary, because they are young and they don't need to keep a family afloat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually end cycle AAA games are the best ones. So I am very hyped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will ignore your first paragraph and just imagine that you failed to convey your words into thoughts.

The EU has all the mechanisms the UK needs to control EU migration. It has them now, it had them 10 years ago.

If the UK wants, it can, for example, (a) force any eu migrant to get a private health insurance instead of using the NHS, and (b) set a threshold of "sufficient funds" and reject applications based on that. This can be done within EU laws and most EU countries are actively doing it. Under EU laws your freedom to roam only lasts 3 months. The EU is already giving to the UK tools to control the freedom of movement.

The Tories will never do this because it would acknowledge the fact they can solve the problem themselves instead of blaming EU. The UK is the only EU15 country which decided not to actively control EU migration, the only one. The Tories were in power since 2010, they had plenty of time to change it.

So yeah, the EU doesn't need to give the UK a "breather", because such "breather" already exists, and this is what the EU is telling to the UK. The problem is that then your newspapers are telling you something different. I suggest you start to read about Brexit reading international sources like any big germany newspaper (most of them have english editions). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed the fight while it happened for the suspense. But I am not going to watch it again, ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And it's hard when your opponent won't engage AT ALL. 

He was not really engaging. The few times he tried to engage he took the lead. Like the only TD he scored. He could do that every round. WHy he didn't is a mistery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People already forgot that his fight against Rory was also a snoozefest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I'm glad Wonderboy lost and I wanted him to win both times. He lost both fights as far as I'm concerned. 

Same here. I wanted him to win both times, but I am glad he lost. His fight against Rory was also a disaster. He always stays super far away, so far away that no one can do any damage. His "I am a counter fighter bro", is bullshit. A counter pouncher is someone like Bullet Shevchenko against Holly. You need to bait, stay in the pocket, and counter. Wonderboy was running away every single time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Thompson is a great counterstriker but man is it boring watching him do that shit for 5 rounds.

We have watched 75 minutes of Wondery which were pure shit. It was only interesting when he was in the receiving end.

The "I am a counter puncher bro, what do you expect" is bullshit. Every time Woodley blitzed in, he just ran away instead of dropping his feet and trying to counter. he was also always very far away from Woodley for Woodley to do anything. If you want to counter, you need to offer something, a bait. Feinting from 2 meters away is bullshit.

I don't want to bring Conor here, but he is an example of a guy who is mostly a counter puncher, but that he "offers" something to punch. In most of his counters he actually receives from the other guy (like the famous 13s with Aldo), but he makes sure he makes more damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that the last round was a 10-8 is complete bullshit. Here is why:

Imagine that round in reverse, the first 15 seconds you have the blitz of Woodley, the following 4:45 nothing happens. Would you still give a 10-8 for that? No, it was a 10-9.

That said, I think Woodley won, but just because I am a "pride - let's bleed fan" and I think he did more damage.

Also, I think scoring should be live. People say that "but if they know they are winning they will stall". Well, by the same reason the other guy will go harder. This is like football when a team is winning 2-1 or whatever, and the other team always blitzs at the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before writing such a long comment, I suggest you read first. The person I was replying to wondered why there was racism against the poles, but not against the french, to which I just said "because there are more poles". If there were more french people, then people would complain about the french people.

The EU has the mechanisms in place to control migration, which the UK NEVER USED. When the UK complained about it, the EU said: "there are already mechanisms in place, why are you not using them?". Plenty of EU countries are using them. For example, to move to Spain you need (a) a job, (b) a private or public health service (and this is not the eu card, that is only for tourism and does not cover in case of residence) and (c) sufficient funds for themselves and family members. Spain can reject any EU application based on this three points, and they do, and all this is within EU laws. Not only that, but Germany (for example) banned countries from the A8 (this includes Poland) until 2011.

So instead of complaining about the EU and the fact that they never understood the problem (when the french knew there was a problem before you did, and that's why they banned east europe migration for a set of years), you should really study the matter, and wonder why the UK never used any of the mechanisms it could use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are several studies that show that inmigration has near a 0 effect in wages. The idea that "if they leave, there won't be enough people to fill the jobs, which means they will need to offer a higher wage" is false. Why? Because if they are in such big numbers that they would have an effect on wages, they also have an effect on production and consumption. If you remove "them" from the equation, maybe then your local tesco only needs 6 lanes instead of 7, which means that the job they leave doesn't need to be filled.

There are several studies, by the way, which show that inmigration has a positive impact on economy growth, which drives wages up.

The bigger drop in wages in the last 80 years (so, from WW2), has been caused by economic crisis (like 08), which are completely unrelated to inmigrants, and very related to politicians, big companies and greed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is because poles represent a 15.7% of the total migration (including non eu), while France represents a 3.1% and Spain represents a 2.8%. 

My point being that I don't think people are racist against them just because they are from Poland, but because they are the most numerous, by a big margin. There are 3 more times poles than irish (which are the next one).

It is worth remembering that many EU countries opposed Poland joining the EU (leaded by France) but the UK was strongly lobbying for them, and that most EU countries banned their free movement for a set of years (except the UK). So it is very hypocritical to blame them for anything, when the UK government basically said "come here". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he missed weight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wasn't him fighting 185 or something like that in Sambo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is liked for the hordes of Russian fans. Simple as that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Because HR became an industry in its own right

08/09 world crisis was their lottery moment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We had to do something like that for my call centre job too.

I used to work in call centers from 03 to 07 or something like that. Before the 08 crisis everything was different. During that time frame I worked in like 4-5 call center jobs. In every case the interview was like 5 minutes long, with maybe a mock call which would last 1-2 minutes. That's more than enough to see if someone can work there or not.

Plus, in a call center the need of teamwork is 0. It is an individual job. You sit in your cubicle for 4 hours straight without any other human interaction, just answering calls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and any competent interviewer would know if someone isn't right for the job in the first 5 minutes.

Yup. The main reason is because after the 08 crisis HR adquired a lot of power and money within companies. Before they used to just handle CVs, now they make you build castles with sticks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HR adquired a lot of power after the 08/09 world crisis because big companies let them do the purging. Thanks to that most HR departments have increased their budget, and also their power.

I started to work in 2003 (it was in a call center while I went to uni), and back then the job application process was way easier (that doesn't mean getting a job was easier... although it actually was, but just because the economy was better). You just sent your CV, and based on the CV is where they did they big purge, if they liked you, you got the interview, otherwise you wouldnt usually receive an answer. I am not saying this is the best way to do it, but at least it was the most efficient. I used to use a website to find jobs, and the website used to do everything for me. I only had to submit my cv to jobs, which was as easy as writting this comment. The following days, any interested company would phone me to set up and interview. That is how I managed to get 5-6 jobs between 2003 and 2007 or something like that. HR department back then was "transparent", they just handled the application and the contracts. The decission process relied on the "bosses" or the people who would directly supervise you. A 1 minute "mock call" was enough to see if a person would be able to work in a call center or not. You dont need to build a bridge with sticks.

Nowadays, because HR has more power, they also do a lot of the decission process based on bullshit metrics which are impossible to measure in a stupid exercise, like "teamwork", "openness" and things like that (you tell me how important teamwork can be in a callcenter, where you are just answering calls in your cubicle for 4 hours straight without any other human contact). Nowadays, when you submit your CV it is very strange to be rejected. They will make you go through a team interview and all that crap, which is just a waste of time. I would rather them reject me based on my CV than reject me after a 4h exercise. In "well paid" jobs, they even make you go to a hotel for 1-2 days, with loads of stupid exercises. This usually requires you to ask for holidays to your current employer.

This is because while before HR would just send the CVs to the respective team, now they get to decide who has the good qualities, and later on the supervisors would decide.

It is a lot of shit, and sooner rather than later companies would realise how much money they waste in this stupid process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When you play on a hilly map you just force yourself to use less fun options, that doesn't make them any less lackluster.

not really. you need to be more creative. you still use a lot of trains. you need to plan very well the whole map. and you can still build bridges or tunnels. It does require you to use all the forms of transport. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TT was my favourite game as a kid, back in the day when I had my 486 and I was around 10. I loved the music, and the art. I could play it for ages.

My favourite thing was how the time went on, and new ways of transport were added. Updating the train network with the last model, or the planes, was amazing.

I always wonder how such a complex game could run in a 486, while nowadays more advanced stuff seem to struggle to create similar complexity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That wasn't a particularly viable way to play the game. Immediately building up an industrial rail network is the way to go, and you'll be rolling in money before long.

This really depends on your initial map. If it had a lot of flat land surface, then yeah. But those scenarios were boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  lackluster

I strongly disagree. It all depends on your map. If you play the standard, then yeah. If you play on one with a lot of islands or mountains, then planes or ships are the way to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. This is more like railroad tycoon (which was also an excellent game. I still remember when I had to connect italy to switzerland, and I built a bridge over the alps) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> imagine that the round was in reverse. The first 20 seconds the blitz, then 4:40 of nothing. would you still give a 10-8? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you but the rules are the rules.

I'd go back to Pride rules, and I would already give the first one to Woodley.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
