<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8379</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you kayaked on the Charles? I like to kayak in places I go, because you get a quiet and really different view of the place from the water.

The Harbor Islands too. Fun day going around out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunshine state shuns solar as overcast New York basks in clean energy boom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See if you can buy them from an installer. I know an installer on the project I just did with my city had some SunPower they needed to purchase. They might break up the set?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump Administration's War on Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Anti-Vaxxer Illness Worse Than Zika </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have convinced themselves that federal grants are some kind of gravy-train for scientists. You know, academics are making coin on this, supporting their lavish lifestyles....oh, wait...

I have heard this argument though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a really old piece. Have you noticed that Michael Pollan has been distancing himself from the food nonsense lately? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gets better. They (OCA) are lobbying now to remove vaccines from animal health care. It's unfuckingbelievable. https://www.organicconsumers.org/news/nosb-testimony-gmo-vaccines-organic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not only expensive and stupid, it's cruel. http://inthesetimes.com/article/6330 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is about the 4th similar post on this lately. It's like it's a conspiracy to tweak skeptics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize this was a local thing until I went away to grad school. I missed this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamas science diaspora prepares for a fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you talking about? I think public schools are an important investment in our kids and our future. 

But if you are gonna teach kids nonsense--like there's an invisible sky guy who created all the animals in 6000 years, you are hurting children with misinformation. And I don't want my tax dollars to pay for that. 

If people want to pay tuition for that nonsense--they are freely able to do so. But you are not using my tax dollars for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Channel 5 just covered it. A few dozen pro-Trump and anti-Trump. Apparently hand gestures were exchanged.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stealth homeopathy article makes it into PLOS One where it will probably remain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's more on the drama here: https://www.facebook.com/robert.saik/posts/10155133965150879 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cargill Proudly Partners with Non-GMO Project - The Farmer's Daughter USA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. But my understanding of charters is that they still have to follow some of the public regulations. I was just reading this piece on vouchers yesterday that said that again:
Vouchers are different than charter schools, which are fully public schools that are privately operated, often by nonprofits. Charter schools receive freedom from some state rules and school district oversight in exchange for demonstrating higher-than-average student achievement, the terms of which are outlined in their charters, or contracts.

Maybe this varies by state, though. Here's the link (warning, autoplay audio--I hate that): http://www.jsonline.com/story/news/education/2017/03/21/tensions-rise-vouchers-pick-up-traction-across-wisconsin/98177206/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surveys have shown that a disproportionate number of EV owners also have their own solar. This is the case for mine too. 

And the program I bought my car through also had an option to source with wind power.  I know other people who can't do solar choose those options as well. 

You don't buy these cars on a whim. You have to think things through. And if you are doing it because of environmental issues, it's likely that the same folks make green energy choices when possible.

That said, part of me wants to tell Trump that EVs can run on coal, just so he supports them. And then charge 'em with my solar panels anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a remarkable backstory. I had no idea how that happened. Thanks for bringing that. 

Yesterday I was musing on twitter about the possibility of public schools being hurt by the upcoming voucher press. I do not want my tax dollars to go to private schools that do not serve of all our kids, and teaches them nonsense like creationism. 

Michael Gilbert, "Field Director, Mass. Association of School Committees" replied to me: "in MA we have a Constitutional prohibition to sending public tax dollars to private schools - would take long process."

I am relieved to hear this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Incomplete List Of Complete Bullshit Websites - SciBabe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to revive Massachusetts first language </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lamar Smith, unbound, lays out political strategy at climate doubters conference | Includes "writing legislation that would punish scientific journals" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A flash mob dance. I'm in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TOWANDA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, no, my choice. No worries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I did editorialize. I wanted to emphasize why I brought it over, and I wanted to set the tone with the "kudos".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and so rare. I thought it was worth celebrating someone who did the right thing, and publicly stated it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I understand this. But I lean with a friend who pointed out that a counter-demonstration shows our trans neighbors that we have their backs on this. And that's important too. 

It's possible to do both.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to kill off a blog: Why yeast free isn't the answer | Food blogger admits to Dunning-Kruger. Kudos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will drop everything as soon as someone posts a sighting of this. Can you take a pitchfork on the T?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's saying that it's a larger issue of medical privacy--not just genetic mutations. And yes, plenty of people do hide pregnancies. Your employer does not belong in your medical records--there's too much potential for misuse and abuse. 

Finally, it could discourage patients from seeking preventive care.

If you get wanted to get treated for depression, or maybe some new genetic risk will be unearthed for depression, you might not choose to because your employer would have access to that data. Or maybe you don't want to know about your BRCA1 or APOE status--some people don't want this info. You should have control over your choices for your health, not your employer. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why antioxidants aren't as healthy as you think </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Discriminate Against Mutants Like Me | x-posted at EverythingScience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Discriminate Against Mutants Like Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you hold on to these things? Does it make you feel like it gives you secret knowledge? Does it make you think that your special knowledge gives you some kind of control? Is it because it's more exciting than your real life, and you get kind of a thrill out of it? 

I was hanging around with a group of folks at one point who really wanted there to be global upheaval. Things weren't going that well for these folks in real life in the new economy, and they thought that after the upheaval they'd be top dogs because of their secret info and bunker-building skills. It also gave them kind of community. Nutty community, but community. I can see why people seek this out. 

I think it's probably not the conspiracies themselves, but you and your existing therapist need to get at why this gives you a feeling of power, or whatever it is. There is also plenty of debunking out there. You need to think about why you can't accept it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, what? Electing anti-vaxxers has consequences?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please put that on a sign for the march.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, that's awful. And so unnecessary. 

I wonder how much that treatment cost--aside from her life, of course.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I March for Science, I'll March for Equity, Inclusion, and Access </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Are Looking at the Face of a Man Who Died 700 Years Ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby born with extra legs thriving after surgery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tweeted @311, and they got back to me. I had checked the calendar and there was nothing and the list of groups looked truncated. But it's working now. 

Go here for calendar: http://www.somervillema.gov/events Choose "Commission on Energy...".

For agendas and meeting notes, now go here:  http://www.somervillema.gov/event-documents

The minutes haven't posted in a while, though. I know they start each meeting by checking the last ones. So they have them. I'll still mention that at the next one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parks, People and Power: Building a Movement for the Mystic Greenways </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sigma Xi: March for Science - Bus Trip from North Carolina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been really impressed with the folks who are donating their time and their significant expertise to these important community issues. 

And in my experience they act based on thoughtful analyses, principles of fairness, and the greater interest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm...looks like that's kind of borked on the new city website. They are (almost always) the 2nd Wednesday of the month, 7pm, in a room upstairs at the TAB building near Davis. 

I'll bring that up at the next one. One of the agenda items is "any other business". I'll ask about that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Trumps N.I.H. Cuts Should Worry Us | Varmus: "Speak up" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll spread the word. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Environmental Spending Cuts Could Cost Republican Districts Billions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not on the Climate Change and Energy Use commission, but I go to the meetings. I like them. It's nice to be in a room where people are actually acting on the realities of the future climate.

And I like to hear about the reports and programs that are underway. 

BTW: you don't have to be on a commission to go to the meetings. They are open public meetings and you can just go as an interested resident. A bunch of people turn up at the Climate one in a pretty regular basis. And if you decide that it is a group you'd like to work with, you'll know about Commissioner resignations when they happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good one. Very thorough yet concise. 

And thanks for participating in government commenting. It's so awful to watch cranks get in there and leave stuff that would get kicked out of YouTube as commentary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You, the people: Why you should consider joining a city board or commission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Rep. Capuano: Democrats need to listen, compromise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, what can you do to force people to align with people who deny science? I don't understand how this is supposed to get resolved. Maybe the acupoftwodayoldcoffe can proffer a solution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making Solar Big Enough to Matter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> electric car programmes found most owners charged their batteries immediately after returning home from work. That coincides with when energy demand is already at its highest point in the day, which has led the company to trial time-shifting the charging to miss the peak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because this piece is from 2010.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People march for a lot of reasons. You can't control why people show up to a march. But it's easy enough to read the mission statement.

The March for Science champions robustly funded and publicly communicated science as a pillar of human freedom and prosperity. We unite as a diverse, nonpartisan group to call for science that upholds the common good and for political leaders and policy makers to enact evidence based policies in the public interest.

As long as you can agree to this, you can bring whatever else you want. I even got a UKIP guy to agree to science-based policy yesterday. https://twitter.com/RogerHelmerMEP/status/843862134043922432 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Critical thinking instruction in humanities reduces belief in pseudoscience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super! You stay in your state, I'll be in DC. I'd be delighted for it to work out that way. 

I can very clearly comprehend that people are tone trolling. It's 100% clear. That's because we have evidence. I love evidence. It makes it very easy to stand on. 

I don't know who you think you are marching against, but if you don't grasp evidence you might be the one I'm marching against. 

But if you are against all the things the march is for, please, feel free to keep your feet up. 
The March for Science champions robustly funded and publicly communicated science as a pillar of human freedom and prosperity. We unite as a diverse, nonpartisan group to call for science that upholds the common good and for political leaders and policy makers to enact evidence based policies in the public interest.

But I stand for these things, even if cranks will be attending this too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charge electric cars smartly to take pressure off national grid  minister | UK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You prefer Rational Wiki? http://rationalwiki.org/wiki/Tone_argument

You're the one that didn't know what it was--I'm sorry if it's embarrassing to you to not be up to speed on internet culture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's not what happened. Look back at how this started. I didn't say anything about the tone trolling until the 4th comment--which specifically stated it was tone trolling. 

We have the evidence. Don't let the door hit you either. Buh-bye. 

And I'll still be at the march.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, no, it's a well-known phenomenon on the internet. http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=Tone%20troll

I'm so glad I could help you learn! See, this turned out to be worth it after all. You have new knowledge now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm still standing after all this time...  

You don't seem to understand how this works. But your attempts to pretend I'm not still standing are adorable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to have missed the point. I am defending myself, and I am still here. 

If you're chased away by assholes in comment sections, you are of no use. 

Glad to help you out there!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, I'll be cited! Will you take away my poster at the march?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Handle what? I'm perfectly capable of rolling my eyes back in my head when I get tone trolled. And that won't keep me from the march. Which is exactly the point of all this. 

Thanks for playing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please--dig. When you find nothing, what are you gonna do next? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't find tone trolling to be helpful either--why don't you take that on if you are looking for something to do. 

But if I'm gonna get tone trolled, you are gonna get snarked back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait--you started out calling me arrogant on a "high horse", then came after my "tone", and you are surprised to get called out? 

Buh-bye. Don't let the door hit you on the way out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No--I stated a fact, sorry to disappoint you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston Skeptics in the Pub: Dr. Ann Neumeyer on Autism: The story and the controversies | March 27 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your concern about my tone. Women love it when people are concerned about their tone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for reading and recognizing the context. That's rare, and I appreciate that :) . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aiming at scientists who think sitting on their ass is the way to make change. It is not. 

And there's dispute about whether backfire is as big thing: https://www.poynter.org/2016/fact-checking-doesnt-backfire-new-study-suggests/436983/
A new paper, however, suggests the "backfire effect" may be a very rare phenomenon. 

But that said, I am not aiming at cranks with this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand on scientific evidence, and the consensus of the science on the issues. I don't see how that can be considered crank.

But if you show up with your anti-vax posters, your anti-GMO posters, and your chemtrails posters, you are a crank. And I'm going to call that crankery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am the author, thanks for reading. What crankery do you adhere to?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I will be participating in the March for Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Green energy in a coal state: the struggle to bring solar jobs to West Virginia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find Kahan's work perplexing. Ok, you can measure things. What do we do with that? 

And for me the issue isn't that lots of people are misled by marketers about these foods. Team organic has big marketing money. What bugs me is that the left claims the mantle of standing with science (because of climate), but then abandons that when it comes to this issue. And they pressure the left politicians as a result. 

It's the hypocrisy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BTW: thanks for pointing me to the IMDB record. When I went over there, I saw that it only listed men. I was livid. I fixed it. 

I appreciate that you drew my attention to that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Electric cars have arrived. But what about electric motorcycles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 13:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there's some footage of the question section. But you have to follow this guy who takes a pee with his camera running first. 

https://twitter.com/dc4reality/status/842928160358514688 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The state still owns a number of copper engraved plates by Paul Revere, and new prints of this one and a couple of others were made a few years back. I have this one in my house now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll ask.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An open letter to the Center for Biological Diversity  re: March for Science | Can sciencemarch unite groups? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not with the team of scientists involved. I don't know if they'll bring up their fundraiser. In case they don't feel comfortable with that, I'll just leave this here: https://fundly.com/chestnutchallenge#updates/blog/update-58971

Disclosure: I'm a donor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debunking a Myth: The Irish Were Not Slaves, Too </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh. Well, he's on a hot mic. So you will hear it from his own mouth.

But I don't want to publicly disclose it. It builds up to that in the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am told they are in that phase of looking for distribution. But I am under the impression it will get to a streaming service eventually.

If you can find it locally, though--do go. I'd love to hear how it plays in the wild. The audience I saw it with was pretty friendly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I thought it was done fairly. But I don't think he liked it. 

I am reluctant to give you the spoiler for that. But...there's a striking moment of clarity about his motives. How's that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's gone now. I hope you saved it for posterity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen this--it's really well done. As I noted in the comments there: 
The best part, though, is watching cranks like Jeffrey Smith reveal themselves for the nonsense peddlers they are.

Worth your time if it appears near you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much do you know about the natural variation of pre-blight chestnuts in the wild? 

I'm wondering if gene editing can also later help to add back some of that diversity to the population.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYT wants comments: Will You Attend the March for Science on Earth Day? x-post from r/MarchForScience/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't have room, but I wish I could have added that I'm marching with my best friend from grad school from 20 years ago, as well as new people I've met on twitter. 

And I'm wearing my park ranger hat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYT wants comments: Will You Attend the March for Science on Earth Day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vaccination debate flares on NSW north coast after seven-year-old contracts tetanus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists Brace for a Lost Generation in American Research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science and medicine leaders say Trump budget would be dire for U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just watching that video from Houston Science March that talked about how many jobs locally there are in STEM. They say they got their data from Bloomberg. But maybe somebody has a pointer to the actual data?

Calling /r/HoustonScienceMarch/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video: March for Science - Houston - We Love Science! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Math. It was an incredibly good investment--if you are in a state that is doing incentives right. I haven't paid an electric bill in 15 months, and now also stopped buying gasoline because I can charge my electric car. And the system will pay for itself in under 5 years. Very few investments in your house have that kind of return. It paid back 51% in the first year (because the current tax credits are so big the first year, later years it will be SREC income which will accumulate more slowly).

PS: the utilities suck, I love not paying them anymore. 

Also, I'm a biologist. Climate change is real, and will have massive impacts in ways a lot of people don't really grasp right now. The environment loaded the gun, but the math pulled the trigger for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps budget is everything scientists have been fearing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we should tell him EVs run on coal....and then just charge them with our solar panels anyway...

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, outside consultants are expensive. Chuck Benbrook wanted $100,000 for doing review work. https://www.geneticliteracyproject.org/2015/10/13/foia-10000-charles-benbrook-offered-ramrod-independent-anti-gmo-research-australian-activists/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monsanto had a response to this: http://monsantoblog.com/2017/03/14/monsanto_did_not_ghostwrite_glyphosate_paper/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's not just that it doesn't work. It's that there could be real harm from this. Imagine some numbnut using it on children. Those poor kids could get 3rd degree burns--through no fault of theirs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Age of Reason Got It Wrong: Understanding Social Conflict Through a Brain Science Lens [04/03/17] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shedding light on solar potential in all 50 U.S. States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, what?
such as test subjects being administered higher dosages than the product recommends 

It's water. 

I..er...sigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Group Is Trying To Replace The Most Anti-Science Members of Congress With Actual Scientists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, yes. 

http://www.cbsnews.com/news/autistic-boy-dies-during-exorcism/

http://www.syracuse.com/news/index.ssf/2014/01/mom_kills_two_children_during_attempted_exorcism_in_maryland.html

Sometimes it appears to be mental illness-driven, certainly. But there are some religious-based ones that go wrong too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fake news plagues scientists, too </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, we have another one now too. 

https://echa.europa.eu/-/glyphosate-not-classified-as-a-carcinogen-by-echa

Or the less nerdy Reuters version: http://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-eu-glyphosate-idUSKBN16M1KM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be a nice gesture to talk to the manager--tell them you appreciate that they've got the charger. Ask them if they mind if you charge in off hours. 

I did this at the local Nissan dealer to understand their local etiquette. (It's not the place I bought mine.) He was actually hilarious. He said there's a tesla guy who keeps hogging one of the chargers at night, but if I found there was a problem with abuse to let him know.

I also need to charge only rarely. I think you'll be fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My city's on board with the desire for EVs. And we have some. We have a number of chargers in good public locations. 

But I was at a city meeting just last week. The problem is that we don't have the budget for new vehicles of any sort, not what kind they are. These are big ticket budget things that require lots of discussion on priorities. 

Also, Trump is threatening to take away stuff from us because we are a Sanctuary city. So these won't be at the top of our list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice to see. There are rarely consequences for nonsense peddlers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what I hear from German friends. But she's been a good leader for a long time already, so your argument is invalid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angela Merkel seems to be doing ok.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 60+ Organizations Join March for Science, Network of Satellite Marches Nears 400 Globally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, ok, downvote that. I haven't paid an electric bill in 15 months. And I also no longer pay for gasoline because I charge my car in my garage instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told them to fuck off by strapping solar panels to my roof. And I was part of a program in Somerville to get more neighbors solarized--now 115 additional people told them that. 

Be the power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An interview with Bill Nye: 'Respect the science!' | on ScienceMarch: "Yeah, Ill be there. The idea is good." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists are conspicuously missing from Trumps government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be easier to do research on whether Pauline Hanson is safe. They'd find out that she's not. 

Or, find out if diseases are safe. Same outcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I bought the WizGear for $8. Perfectly happy with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Behind the Quiet State-by-State Fight Over Electric Vehicles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this is a curious conclusion. But the whole report is just so poorly sourced it's an embarrassment to the UN. You can't cite fake tribunals as evidence for anything, ever. Next you'll have anti-science cranks of all sorts holding chemtrails tribunals and anti-vaccine tribunals as if they are legit. Or some climate deniers put climate scientists on fake trial. 

That's a terrible example for the UN to set. 

I was reading a piece about [Pruitt and the EPA](http://www.vox.com/science-and-health/2017/3/10/14871696/scott-pruitt-climate-denial), and it includes this point:
The dispute is over the *authority of the referee*. 

Diminishing the sources of legit information has harmful consequences in lots of ways. Opening the UN to that sort of nonsense has unfortunate downstream effects. The IPCC got into trouble for using "gray literature", and they really should have learned from this. 

But the resulting misinformation harming the most impoverished is the truly most awful outcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Week at Sea with Canadas Alt-Right </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just spotted this really nice counter to that, I wanted to save it for future reference: https://thoughtscapism.com/2017/03/09/no-the-un-did-not-dismiss-pesticides/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted it to r/science but it was removed. In that post before it was disappeared, someone did tell me the study was paid for by Monsanto.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every year, scientists try to help people to understand this fearmongering. Here's another attempt: http://appliedmythology.blogspot.com/2017/03/organic-might-not-mean-what-you-think.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Claims like that require evidence. What's your evidence? Or is that just a wild conspiracy theory? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible these groups would know about available clinical trials too--which might be a way to do this properly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not a review, it is a meta-analysis with new assessments and conclusions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scientific paper itself is here: [Many shades of grayThe context-dependent performance of organic agriculture](http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/3/3/e1602638.full). Open access.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Organic food not automatically better, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just reading that paper. It's here, if anyone wants to see the full monte: http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/3/3/e1602638.full

I love how they talk about the need for better plant breeding for organic systems. You know what kind of better breeding would be great for organic systems? Bt eggplants, for one. Bt corn. Blight-resistant potatoes. 

But no, let's not use things that would actually help reduce the need for pesticides because...um...because what?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saving GINA: Is Genetic Privacy Imperiled? | DNA Science Blog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are 2 other good pieces that picked up on this:

[This Development Should Matter to Anyone with Genes](http://www.esquire.com/news-politics/politics/news/a53776/house-republicans-genes-bill/)

[Saving GINA: Is Genetic Privacy Imperiled?](http://blogs.plos.org/dnascience/2017/03/09/saving-gina-is-genetic-privacy-imperiled/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In mine, I want to take their money with some quack product and use it to fund science education and outreach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Resisting the Suppression of Science  NEJM | x-post from r/skeptic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Resisting the Suppression of Science  NEJM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MMS and the Fake Clinical Trials  #3. An Experiment Designed to Get the Results They Wanted | Myles Power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inventing the Charles River, talk by Karl Haglund | Historic Somerville </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "reddit ecologist"

I am roaring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House GOP would let employers demand workers' genetic test results </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Speaking up for science: A perspective from the Boston science rally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, GMO haters were doing fake stuff long before Trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What we have is evidence that the author is, in fact, a modernity crank. And does not understand the reality of food production. I'm sorry this disappoints you. You are not required to buy Phillip's book--although you would benefit from reading it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Do Prestigious Hospitals Sell Snake Oil? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They actually cited the fake "Monsanto Tribunal" as evidence in this thing. It's sourced almost entirely from activist gray literature--which is really a bad idea. That's what got the IPCC in trouble and they had to stop doing it. That stuff isn't peer-reviewed and it's distorted and cherry-picked.

The author was described by a science writer as a "modernity crank". More here: https://twitter.com/Leigh_Phillips/status/839308914705379328 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it doesn't matter why I thought the Women's March was impactful. And that's exactly my point. Maybe I have 14 reasons. Someone else had 8 reasons. Someone else had 21. And maybe all of our outcomes are different. But even with that--the overall visibility, alignment, discussion generated, and spurring ongoing efforts was worth it.

If you are trying to shut off people's reasons for marching to generate a tidier message you prefer, you are micromanaging.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people call it "quackademic" medicine when these academics do it. 

I love [this description of it](http://scienceblogs.com/insolence/2013/02/27/the-cleveland-clinic-foundation-mixing-cow-pie-with-apple-pie-in-pediatrics/): 
As Mark Crislip once put it, If you integrate fantasy with reality, you do not instantiate reality. If you mix cow pie with apple pie, it does not make the cow pie taste better; it makes the apple pie worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that amusing? You are presuming why I did these things, which may not be what you said--but it still all sent the message you got anyway! 

And yet--the one that I found most impactful was the Women's March! So maybe micro-managing the messaging isn't that effective.

And yes, the failures of Occupy are something to note. Do you think their message was too diffuse? What should that have been? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are we all supposed to have a restricted list of things? Whose rules are those? 

I'm sure I went to the Women's March, the Sanctuary City rally, the NoBanNoWall rally, the Science rally, and the Planned Parenthood rally for some different reasons than other people in the crowd. 

Seems to me it's a Venn situation. I'll share some of the same reasons as some people, others are more personal to me. But so what?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UN experts denounce 'myth' pesticides are necessary to feed the world | Cites Monsanto Tribunal as evidence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring on the gene drive. A guy from MIT has a project that could help. https://www.nytimes.com/2016/06/08/science/ticks-lyme-disease-mice-nantucket.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, no, they are terrible on plant science.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside The Internet's War On Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope most people involved with the march will say that we'll use evidence to make decisions on science topics.

Most topics that are controversial aren't really controversial on the science. So standing on the evidence is always a good place to rest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Washington on Prospect Hill - Take the Tour at Home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medicine with a side of mysticism: Top US hospitals aggressively promoting alternative medicine offerings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Single-molecule sequencing and chromatin conformation capture enable de novo reference assembly of the domestic goat genome](http://nature.com/articles/doi:10.1038/ng.3802)
Nature Genetics, March 6, 2017 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NIH and USDA scientists publish goat genome sequence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think policy will matter--but even if federal mandates go away (and they might now) the states may step up. 

Our state plans a fleet electrification,among other things: http://www.mass.gov/governor/press-office/press-releases/fy2017/gov-baker-signs-electric-vehicle-promotion-legislation.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be willing to switch to this for my next ride. It's not ready now, but it will be by the time my current Leaf expires. 

And I support the idea of using vehicles more--the ZipCar model shows this can work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Secular Coalition is a bit more focused on non-religious aspects of legislation--such as opposing religious exemptions on vaccines, keeping creationism out of schools--but as a result they come down on the side of reason and evidence: https://www.secular.org/

Also, NCSE: https://ncse.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> scientist-petting-zoo

Heh. Like it. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why NCSE Is Marching for Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Not All Relative | Can a devotion to cultural tolerance lead to the triumph of alternative facts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a neat idea--but I would go broad with this. Invite cartoonists to do posters. Invite local science-aligned groups to do posters. Invite some local science teachers/classes to do posters. 

Invite the public health department. 

Don't make it all wonky.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very true. I fly in to DCA because I don't need to rent a car then, as well. I can hop right on the train at the airport and get into the city.

There are a lot of hotels in the area, they do a lot of conventions so I've stayed in a wide range of them. All perfectly adequate. 

But the key is close access to a Metro station.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Peter Kareiva was at the Nature Conservancy, he spoke about GMOs on multiple occasions, and favorably. He also called out some nonsense by other advocacy groups. 

He's gone back to academia now, and I haven't tracked them lately. But I had been giving them money. 

Another alternative is to look for a local group near you, working on related issues. There are a few around my area doing great work on rivers, wildlife, green energy, and they stay out of that stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Wolfe: Aussie anti-vaxxers funded flat earther's tour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fluff At 100: The Sweet History Of New England's Sticky Spread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't use it. I never have. I still think people who are unaware of this shouldn't be misled. And this is why we have consumer protection laws. There are possibly some vulnerable people--like the elderly, or those who don't have the mobility to get out--who should not be taken advantage of.

I'm just a softie that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 15:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My CPA was asking me for additional business expenses this week, and he was laughing that I don't have gas receipts any more. And with my $0 electric bills (solar panels), I got nothin' he can use. 

I didn't care. 

There's a lot of free charging that I sometimes use around my city when I'm out doing an errand--and because the free parking is sweeter than the electrons. But even if it's free to us, it's possible to calculate the value of that in power costs. And my Chargepoint receipt also gives me the ICE equivalent. https://www.screencast.com/t/EvcVohjgcI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 15:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a consumer protection issue. I think you are right on the misrepresentations. If the tax is being calculated on the wrong basis, they may also be skimming off the top of that, which would make the revenue department very, very techy. 

Might try the Consumer Affairs hotline? http://www.mass.gov/ocabr/

Alternatively, you could contact a local beat reporter like the "5 Investigates" team and they might be interested. Then they would track down which items are legit charges and which are not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump has set the US up to botch a global health crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, those maps. Sigh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House proposes steep budget cut to leading climate science agency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, that irked me too--but the paper is paywalled. I haven't got a copy yet. One will turn up eventually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmmm...solar margaritas....

I shall ponder this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, in MA the SRECs are approved by a state agency, traded on the SREC market, and we get checks from SRECTrade for this. That's the particular piece at issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right--the path of our production that flows into our house for our use (if we make more, then a utility bill credit), is not taxable. We never see cash for that, it's purely mathematical/paper value. 

But the SRECs we get for each MWh of production--issued by a state agency, traded on the SRECTrade market, for which we get big checks--that is a different beast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
