<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1510</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 07:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Haha that is really awesome! The new episodes pick up where the first one left off. The whole thing is a continuous story, but each episode will focus in on one aspect of it to some degree. The I talk more about it in the [kickstarter](https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1152912515) if your curious.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 06:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks ILikeMyBlueEyes!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 06:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot WiglyWorm! Yeah, I have had too many people ask me to work for little or nothing to ask anyone to work for free for me. A friend of a friend was asked to direct a major artist's music video, which had a $300,000 budget, for free. He did it. Maybe in that case it is worth it for the exposure. But it is definitely messed up they couldn't dedicate at least some of that money to pay their director. 

Edit: changed something I realized I wasn't 100% sure about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 06:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, what? crazy name. No, but I am intrigued.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 06:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks StopDropNFrag! Heres hoping the kickstarter succeeds! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 06:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And thanks so much for contributing! That is really awesome! It means so much to get support from people that want to help get more made! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 06:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks intianmidgetninja!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 06:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I did most of the 1st one myself. I had a voice actor on this one and a lot of people giving me notes. If it gets funded on Kickstarter I will have some more people to help on the new ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 06:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was inspired to make this film by a few things, cordyceps mushrooms which infect and control the minds of ants, causing them to climb up as high as possible so that when the mushroom finally bursts from the ants head the spores are spread as far as possible by the wind. Secondly, "parasitic ideas" - such as ideologies designed by cults or oppressive regimes explicitly to weaken and control the holders of such beliefs, and the callous mechanization of corporate bureaucracy. sprawling bureaucracies in super massive organizations can have so many moving parts and conflicting interests that no human maintains real control. 

I talk more about this stuff in the [kickstarter video](https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1152912515/operator) if your interested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 06:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for backing crecentfresh! It's really awesome to have people support it and help it get made! Very much appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 06:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, excellent! Thanks TheRealQU4D! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 06:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks GosuGian! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 06:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot Sam3104545! thats awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 05:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, yes. From time to time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 05:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Phantomass! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 05:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks nekolabelle!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 05:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot motherfailure! Nice name haha. Anomisa was pretty great. Kaufman is a genius. I am really glad he has gotten to make so many movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 05:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks h_word! What is the H word?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 05:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is recorded like any other folly, except you try and move the sound source around a 3D Mic dummy head in real time to match the motion in the video. Then once it is recorded properly i onto the left and right channel, you can pretty much mix it as you would anything else. 

They have also created software, in the form of plugins for Unity which is a game development software, that allows you to move the sound in space after recording it normally. I haven't used this much but I heard a demo that was pretty impressive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 04:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks TLG160! Yeah, the new episodes are a lot more character driven. I have some great ones lined up should the kickstarter succeed, one friend who is a regular on the Howard stern show doing amazing voice impressions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 04:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot lipman19!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 04:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAhaha, always glad to make someone lose their lunch in the name of scifi horror. Thanks hyperintelligentcat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 04:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for backing ICanCountTo0b1010! Really hope we make it! Means a lot to have people watch it and then want to help get new episodes made.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 04:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, exactly. Anyone who successfully resisted the parasite got killed by the company. Thanks for watching! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 04:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. haha. I would totally be into that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 04:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for backing Inertial0811! Very much appreciated! And glad you don't think all the work was for not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 04:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's based on the actual cost of producing an episode. Which includes materials, actors, crew, (I will be hiring a few professionals and don't want to ask them to work for free, all of them have rent to pay, one has a kid) space to shoot, cost of making and shipping rewards, ect. There is a budget breakdown near the bottom of the kickstarter page if you want to take a look.  

About the currency, no I am in the US. 

Edit: clarity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 04:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot Gengar11! Yeah, it made it onto the front page and was the top post on r/videos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 03:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot Ajeh! That is really awesome. And very much appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 03:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fixed! Thanks for letting me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 03:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks ducktards! Glad to get past your lack of interest of stop motion. I like to think I am making stuff for everyone and not just for people who like animation. Most of my favorite films are live action. I think I pull from them more than most animation.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 03:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Chopsteryo! Glad you liked the pacing. I haven't posted in r/movies. Do you think they would be receptive?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 03:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot thedersy1!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 02:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for backing Hunt270! That is really awesome and helps a lot! if you meant physically also, are you in Los Angeles?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 02:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks brick124! Hopefully the [kickstarter](https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1152912515/operator) works out! I am really excited about the new episodes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 02:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot 2711gamer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 02:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much Drifty_Canadian! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 01:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats awesome Redmarz! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 01:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also! Thanks so much for backing! Thats really awesome. Every bit goes a long way to getting this thing made.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 01:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black Mirror is awesome! I saw the white Christmas episode 1st which just totally blew my mind. I made Operator before seeing it, but, I am really into making stuff that uses scifi to ask a very specific question about what the new technology will mean to people. Which I think that show does a great job of. So I certainly want to follow its its footsteps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 01:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAHA! Thats great notabook! thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 01:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anyone wants to see animation tests for the new epsiodes(I have gotten way better at stop motion and puppet making the the last 2 years) or hear more about what I am doing with the series, here is the link to the [kickstarter](https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1152912515/operator). I am really excited about where the new episodes go! 

No pressure to contribute if you dont want to. If you do want to, and are excited to see more Operator, everything helps and there is a long way to go to fund episode 2. We would be extremely grateful!

Also, I promise to never to copy write the concept of stop motion. Haha. I love reddit so much for attacking those guys. 

Edit: fixed link
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 00:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Mydubs! Yeah. I love the 3D sound. Its freaky. I was never into 3D video, or surround sound all that much. But I really thing the 3D sound adds something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 00:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for backing! I really means a lot. It can be tedious work, haha, but I do really love it when it starts to come together. And there is some stuff in the new episodes I am really excited about and I hope people will like!

Edit: Grammrrmar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 00:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do love THX1138  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 00:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha. Yeah. Sometimes it really feels like that. Thanks Afrothunderz! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 00:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much 2cool4life that is awesome! I really hope people see the quality of the work and want to support it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 00:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks grodisattva! I considered that for a while and wrote a script. But then decided it really belongs in stop motion, so I am making it into a stop motion web series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 00:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot 2cool4life! Nice user name! haha. Yeah, its not easy. It's why I have launched the [kickstarter](https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1152912515/operator) with the hopes I can switch to making new episodes full time.  

Edit: Hijacking because a lot of people have asked:  The new episodes pick up where this one left off. They follow people who escape the initial infection and some people within the power structure of the corporation fighting to control it. I talk some more about it in the kickstarter if you are interesting in hearing more about where the series will go and what its about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 00:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Headless_Snowman! I can't wait to get to work on the new episodes. I take the creepiness a whole lot further. And have gotten quite a bit better at animation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 00:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot ProvostP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 23:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot for the sub! Twice! haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 23:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! they are about 10 inches tall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I spent 8 months making this 7 min stop-motion short about a man being attacked by a bio-mechanical parasite. I was inspired by reddits amazing reaction, so I spent the last two years (between working other jobs) writing 15 new episodes. With reddits help I am finally ready to start making them! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 23:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nibbler, Ruslan Kadiev, digital/drawing/painting, 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 06:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Constantine Demon by aaronsimscompany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 06:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Constantine Demon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 06:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MATTA by Doug Q </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 06:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monster by Disse86 (dennis, no last name) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 06:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 04:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't agree more. I almost stopped a few times but glad I watched the whole thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trash Aliens by Bjorn Barends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 22:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bobby Yeah is a BAFTA-nominated stop motion animated short film written, directed and animated by Robert Morgan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 22:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turn, Ron Garret, Francis Bacon inspired abstraction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 22:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legless, Ron Garret, Acrylic, 2010 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 22:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brilliant animation build out of soundscapes recorded in DTLA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 21:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Butterger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 20:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bearphin charging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 21:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 21:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kept laughing even as I saw it trail off into nothing. haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL exposure to platinum can turn snails into their evolutionary decedents the slug. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 19:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DUCTTAPED AT YOUR MURDER TRIAL? YELL AT THEM WITH YOUR MOTHERFUCKING EYES! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 07:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 22:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats weird. Still works when I click it. http://fantasygallery.net/blanche/Queen_bee-by_Pascal_Blanche.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They are so happy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 22:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creepy Mr Burns - B Barends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 21:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> prints_ -- Tears [Future Pop] (2015) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 21:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> QUEENBEE by Pascal Blanche </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 21:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 11H by Thomas Alen Kopera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 21:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SHARKMAN By the amazing Sebastian Krger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 21:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turtle Penguin - by IdentityResults </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 21:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dave Correia -- Sphere of Hallucination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 20:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunday Smiles by LennartVerhoeff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 20:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> prints_ -- Ghosts [FuturePop] (2015) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 20:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 20:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Werner_Herzog! Ok, I thought because its all made by one group it wasn't. But you would certainly know better than me Werner_Herzog. Thanks for the notice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 08:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome man thanks! lots of good info. I had heard it called net art and had made some myself a while back but wasn't sure it was the accepted term as its not something I all that involved in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 08:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Thanks! The site I found it on had basically no info. I was wondering.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-rex in the desert sky [Dino Art] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 07:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White Blush - Ghosts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 07:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Auke Ijspeert: A robot that runs and swims like a salamander </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 07:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazing hallucinogenic short. Lots of amazing roto with animation. Like what scanner darkly was doing but much better IMO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 06:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Robot -- Robot Koch   Cerebral Vortex - Vortex Cookies (Peter Robot Remix) - 2012 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 06:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> STOP IT! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 05:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 01:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Switch off robot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 01:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early Mechanical Body Suit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 01:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-drone rifle lets people shoot drones out of the sky without firing a bullet - See more at: http://www.healthnutnews.com/anti-drone-rifle-lets-people-shoot-drones-out-of-the-sky-without-firing-a-bullet/#sthash.gEkJLEdG.dpuf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 01:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 01:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Camel? But yes. Agreed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Y F Wang - forest different - Hands reaching out of mirrors towards a women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 01:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A collection of trippy interconnected interactive pages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 00:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wave Vortex, Arizona. HARUN MEHMEDINOVIC [1500x1000] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 00:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love Birds, Chad Keith, Pencil, 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 00:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chillin on the roof like a boss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 00:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 23:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 23:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmmm... Maybe i'm wrong, but in my mind 'evolved to' doesn't necessarily imply forethought or intention. That makes sense to me as one reading of it, but my reading of it is "evolved to the current state in which'

Edit: I am in complete agreement about evolution not having an end game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> smile by BBarends on DeviantArt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 23:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 22:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be clear, I do not believe in designed. Evolution all the way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Robot -- Catharsis [Electronic] (2015) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 21:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 21:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My apologies. Should have said 'evolved to carry'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 21:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, its sad. That's why I decided to post it. Otherwise I totally would have if I got the chance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that elephants skeletons are designed to carry weights under them, not on top, and many Elephants end up with deformed and broken backs as a result of years of long hours spent carrying tourists around. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 21:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 21:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made me do the same and I am 100% sober </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Orwell Lived Here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 21:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walking Upside down on ice underwater. Mind blown. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 20:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wave Vortex, Arizona. HARUN MEHMEDINOVIC [1500x1000] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 11:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Benjaminm Obrien - Along the Eaves "translational procedures and machine listening" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 11:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wordclock -- Concept 2.1 [Industrial Drums] (2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 11:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 07:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People temple is a really excellent doc.  I highly recomendnit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! its only funny once. But pretty good the 1st time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
