<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1702</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erik Prince related perhaps  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Senator Warren to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Senator Elizabeth Warren:**

"What I think a big debate in Washington is about, is who is government going to work for, is it just going to work for the top, or is it actually gonna work for the rest of America?..."

"But the Russia thing, I put in a totally different category...That's the one that should not be partisan.  I don't care if you're a Democrat, if you're a Republican, if you're an Independent, if you're a Libertarian, I don't care: You should care whether or not Russia finagled our election, or otherwise, is calling any of the shots in Washington."


"Everybody should care, so let's start with what we absolutely know, for sure:"

"We know that the intelligence community of the United States of America said, Russia hacked in to American systems in order to influence the outcome of the 2016 election. **Pow!**"

"We know, for sure, that the FBI has an active and ongoing investigation about the ties between Russia and the Trump campaign and Donald Trump. **Wow!**"

"And we know, for sure, that top Trump aides, as you have just talked about, have been fired, because of their ties, their undisclosed ties and connections with Russia. **Now,** for me, that's is enough to say, we've got to have an investigation."


"We need a special prosecutor, with strong subpoena powers, and We need an independent commission, and All of us should want that. This is not about partisanship, this is about patriotism."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Senator Elizabeth Warren talks with Rachel Maddow about the need for a special prosecutor and an independent commission investigating possible Trump campaign's cooperation.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warren: Turn heat up on Trump Russia case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Farewell To Bill O'Reilly From Stephen Colbert And 'Stephen Colbert' Who Mocked Bill For 9 Years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Farewell To Bill O'Reilly From Stephen Colbert And 'Stephen Colbert' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Farewell To Bill O'Reilly From Stephen Colbert And 'Stephen Colbert' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 11:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was removed for being *off-topic* at politics subReddit...

**MTPDaily:** Chuck Todd and conservative radio host Charlie Sykes discuss Bill O'Reilly impact on American politics -- and how Fox News moves forward without him. Duration: 6:55 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> O'Reilly Out: Chuck Todd Suggests, While Literally Replaceable, Conservatives Have Lost An Influential Leader and Voice of Authority, haha! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pope Totally Failed Today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out like Flynn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Chuck Todd and conservative radio host Charlie Sykes discuss Bill O'Reilly's* **impact on American politics** *-- and how Fox News moves forward without him. Duration: 6:55* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> O'Reilly Out at Fox: Who Fills the Vacuum? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The pope shook hands with Bill OReilly the same day Fox fired O'Reilly for sexual harassment... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even a handshake from the pope couldnt stop the inevitable.

Fox News has officially dropped Bill OReilly after sexual harassment allegations prompted protests outside network headquarters and a mass exodus from advertisers in recent days.

But amid the outcry, the accused predator is vacationing in Italy, where he briefly met Pope Francis on Wednesday.

OReilly sat in the VIP section during the pontiffs weekly general audience in St. Peters Square. The general audience is a free, public event that thousands of faithful attend every Wednesday. The VIP section where OReilly sat is situated beside the stage and is only accessible with special tickets distributed by the prefecture of the papal household.

Greg Burke, head of the Vatican press office and a former Fox correspondent, told Religion News Service he did not facilitate OReillys visit. But he did not specify who 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill OReilly Meets Pope Francis The Same Day Fox Fires Him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Sexual Harasser Gone, One More Needs To Go! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bye Bill, you'll never do it live again! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's over, he's fired! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's over  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill O'Reilly Out at Fox News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New accuser+Protest+Damning report of inside Fox sources ready to replace you+Intense media backlash to all three=You're fired! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Nearly half of the respondents in a new poll think Fox News should cancel host Bill O'Reilly's primetime show amid a sexual harassment scandal.* 

A Morning Consult poll found 46 percent think the network should cancel "The O'Reilly Factor," while just 22 percent think Fox News should keep the show on the air.

"Among those who watch the show, 23 percent said they think it should be canceled, compared to 58 percent who said it should be kept on the network."


"The poll also found lower favorability ratings for O'Reilly. The Fox News host is viewed favorably by just 30 percent of Americans, down from 36 percent in a poll take earlier this month."

"His favorability rating among those who watch his show has fallen to 73 percent, down from 80 percent in the earlier poll."


"The poll was conducted from April 13-15 among 2,201 adults. The margin of error is 2 percent." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll: Nearly half think Fox News should cancel O'Reilly's show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Nevertheless: The Story of Riley Martin*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a virile tapestry: *Musculature!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howard too shocked to appropriately react to Ronnie's sex
limo, more later </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It took a whileyears too long, in factbut Fox News finally appears ready to fire longtime host Bill OReilly over the blowback from sexual harassment allegations accumulated over the course of his career at the network. The news of the popular hosts coming departure comes from the Wall Street Journal, which cites anonymous sources that Fox News is preparing to cut ties with its biggest star and that a final decision on Mr. OReillys fate could come as early as the next several days." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It took a whileyears too long, in factbut Fox News finally appears ready to fire longtime host Bill OReilly over the blowback from sexual harassment allegations accumulated over the course of his career at the network. The news of the popular hosts coming departure comes from the Wall Street Journal, which cites anonymous sources that Fox News is preparing to cut ties with its biggest star and that a final decision on Mr. OReillys fate could come as early as the next several days." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Appears Set to Fire Bill OReilly After Sexual Harassment Accusations Pile Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The OReilly Factor Is Also Making Waves Across the Atlantic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hanzi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is The *Howard Stern* Show lovers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Maddow:**

*John Archibald, columnist for the Birmingham News, talks with Rachel Maddow about the newly re-scheduled election to fill Jeff Sessions' old Senate seat, currently held by Luther Strange whose appointment many see as inappropriately tied to disgraced former governor Robert Bentley.*

New Alabama appointee Governor has moved election up to 2017, from Bently's 2018 planned race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political favor backfiring on newly appointed Alabama senator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F.U. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today's Guest: President Donald Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must have seen what I just posted before! https://i.redd.it/dvang57kbfsy.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox News is planning to sever ties with Bill OReilly, the popular host who is embroiled in a sexual harassment scandal, according to a new report.

The Wall Street Journal reported late Tuesday that sources close to the situation reported a final decision regarding the host of The OReilly Factor could come in the next several days.

Wall Street Journal is owned by Rupert Murdoch, who also owns Fox News.
The report follows earlier reporting by CNN in which sources said OReilly and the network have begun discussing his exit from Fox News </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox News is planning to sever ties with Bill OReilly, the popular host who is embroiled in a sexual harassment scandal, according to a new report.

The Wall Street Journal reported late Tuesday that sources close to the situation reported a final decision regarding the host of The OReilly Factor could come in the next several days.

Wall Street Journal is owned by Rupert Murdoch, who also owns Fox News.
The report follows earlier reporting by CNN in which sources said OReilly and the network have begun discussing his exit from Fox News </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News planning to sever ties with Bill O'Reilly over Sexual Harassment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News planning to sever ties with Bill O'Reilly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill and Donald are Two of a Kind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Murdoch owned Wall Street Journal reporting about the Murdoch owned Fox firing O'Reilly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would give him a chance besides Fox? There's nothing lower in standards and no brand would take this fired sexual harasser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Dude, I *served* with Howard Stern. I *know* Howard Stern. Howard Stern *is* a friend of mine. And Bill O'Reilly is *no* Howard Stern! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No satellite broadcaster either, no more *syndication*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From primetime to podcast...independent podcast? Like a website? Sure, anybody can have a website  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reaction to a reaction of the salient issue  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Radio won't even touch this guy after this dismissal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beck had some interesting takes on Trump during the election, but ya they are all bad and liars  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New accuser+Protest+Damning report of inside Fox sources ready to replace you= You're fucking fired  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New accuser+Protest+Damning report of inside Fox sources ready to replace you= You're fucking fired  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure Glenn is still underwater, and he also hates women having free choices  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, Fox is a joke, but O'Reilly has a particular undeserved authority </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He would never talk to her, not even hello, except to grunt at her like a wild boar." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill NO TAKE CANDLE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unnamed Rich People. Three is good  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He would never talk to her, not even hello, except to grunt at her like a wild boar."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be creepy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the message on it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He getting dropped thanks to this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women's Rights Group 'Ultraviolet' Flies Banner Over Manhattan Ahead of Protest: "Fox: #DropOReilly, The Sexual Predator" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/amp/news/bill-oreilly-protest-droporeilly-plane-banner-nyc-fox-news-995074 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women's Rights Group 'Ultraviolet' Flies Banner Over New York City Ahead of Protest: "Fox: #DropOReilly, The Sexual Predator" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women's Rights Group 'Ultraviolet' Flies Banner Over New York City Ahead of Protest: "Fox: #DropOReilly, The Sexual Predator" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya it's never about the actual problems. But the reaction to the problem from the public should make them react, or act like they care about the problem, and fire Bill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, thing. It happens  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you check it out? Picture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fuck it, we'll never do it live" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With only six days remaining in Bill OReillys vacation, the pressure on the Murdoch family to decide the embattled commentators fate is intensifying. Three sources with knowledge of the discussions said that, while no final decision has been made, the Murdochs are leaning toward announcing that OReilly will not return to the air. Sons James and Lachlan have been arguing that OReilly needs to go, say these sources, though their father, Rupert, has resisted that outcome.


The prospect of dumping OReilly  once unimaginable  has gained steam this week due in part to street protests outside Fox News headquarters and advertiser boycotts on OReillys air. One network insider said Fox executives are alarmed by the severity of the ad-revenue decline. Its worse than Glenn Beck, the insider said, referring to the advertiser revolt that helped derail Becks Fox News career in 2011. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sources: The Murdochs Are Turning Against Bill OReilly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Hollywood Reporter:


Bill O'Reilly used to leer at an African-American Fox News clerical worker and called her "hot chocolate," according to attorney Lisa Bloom, who helped the woman report the harassment to the network's hotline.

The woman worked for a different broadcaster in 2008 while this was going on, but The O'Reilly Factor host's office was near her desk, the attorney claims. 

"He would never talk to her, not even hello, except to grunt at her like a wild boar," Bloom tells The Hollywood Reporter. "He would leer at her. He would always do this when no one else was around and she was scared."

Bloom says she spoke with three witnesses who knew the woman at the time and confirmed she was upset and stressed at the end of each workday. 

"She was afraid if she told him to knock it off shed get fired," Bloom says. "Now thats she's aware this is all in the news, shes decided to phone in a complaint to the Fox News hotline."

Bloom is also representing radio personality Wendy Walsh, who says she was forced out of the network after refusing O'Reilly's advances. 

An April 1 New York Times story revealed explosive allegations against O'Reilly, including that during his tenure at the network at least five women have been paid off to keep silent about harassment. In the story, Fox said in a statement that "no current or former Fox News employee ever took advantage of the 21st Century Fox hotline to raise a concern about Bill OReilly."

So far at least this woman and Walsh have taken advantage of the line  and, soon, another woman is also expected to call and report harassment by the anchor, according to Bloom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The Hollywood Repoter Reports:*

Bill O'Reilly used to leer at an African-American Fox News clerical worker and called her "hot chocolate," according to attorney Lisa Bloom, who helped the woman report the harassment to the network's hotline.

The woman worked for a different broadcaster in 2008 while this was going on, but The O'Reilly Factor host's office was near her desk, the attorney claims. 

"He would never talk to her, not even hello, except to grunt at her like a wild boar," Bloom tells The Hollywood Reporter. "He would leer at her. He would always do this when no one else was around and she was scared."

Bloom says she spoke with three witnesses who knew the woman at the time and confirmed she was upset and stressed at the end of each workday. 

"She was afraid if she told him to knock it off shed get fired," Bloom says. "Now thats she's aware this is all in the news, shes decided to phone in a complaint to the Fox News hotline."

Bloom is also representing radio personality Wendy Walsh, who says she was forced out of the network after refusing O'Reilly's advances. 

An April 1 New York Times story revealed explosive allegations against O'Reilly, including that during his tenure at the network at least five women have been paid off to keep silent about harassment. In the story, Fox said in a statement that "no current or former Fox News employee ever took advantage of the 21st Century Fox hotline to raise a concern about Bill OReilly."

So far at least this woman and Walsh have taken advantage of the line  and, soon, another woman is also expected to call and report harassment by the anchor, according to Bloom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Bill O'Reilly Accuser Says He Called Her "Hot Chocolate" and Leered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I said. I love the Howard Stern Show. I ain't complaining  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Joy-Ann Reid contrasts the Donald Trump White House explanations of its priorities for deportation with reports of arrests for deportation of mothers of American children with no criminal records.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Real Donald Trump Deportation Plan Seen In Arrests | Rachel Maddow | MSNBC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Letter Signed by over 450 Sexual Assault Victims Demands Fox Fire OReilly: Protest Planned For Today 1:30 EST at Fox HQ NYC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Sucks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baby, if you dare, won't you meet me half way there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wah Wah! You cry either way, Wah Wah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She sounds goood! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Wrap:**

A womens group plans to lead a protest outside Fox News headquarters in New  York City on Tuesday, complete with a plane and a banner.


UltraViolet, which is an online community that seeks to fight sexism in corporations and the media, commissioned a plane to fly with a banner over the Hudson River, which will read Fox: #DropOReilly, The Sexual Predator.


The group also plans to hang posters around Midtown Manhattan, which ask, Have you also been sexually harassed by Bill? 



Fox News has a problem with sexual assault  and its bigger than just Bill OReilly, said Shaunna Thomas, co-founder of UltraViolet, in a Monday statement. Fox News needs to prove to the public  and its advertisers  that the era of covering up sexual assault is over. That means  firing Bill OReilly immediately and conducting a comprehensive and independent investigation into sexual abuse at the network  firing anyone involved in, or complicit in covering up, those crimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sexual Assault Survivors to Demand #DropOReilly at Fox News HQ Protest Against Bill O'Reilly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women's Group Protesting Fox to Drop Bill O'Reilly over Sexual Harassment Accusations: Today at 1:30 p.m. EST outside Fox News headquarters in New York City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women's Group Protesting to Fire Bill O'Reilly for Sexual Harassment: Today at 1:30 p.m. EST outside Fox News headquarters in New York </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who? Me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Blows! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except they say it is bad before it happens, excessively! It doesn't matter that Scarlet Johansson was one of the best interviews this year, or if it was the worst, they decided it was the worst before it happened and therefore they sound ignorant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Says the user who posts polls on Reddit, when Reddit is a poll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Whenever there's a negative, you say *trolls,* Robin." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The group, UltraViolet, will fly a plane banner over New York on Tuesday that reads, "Fox: #DropOReilly, The Sexual Predator.""




"In the past few weeks since The New York Times reported that O'Reilly and Fox News have allegedly paid $13 million to women who claimed that he sexually harassed or verbally abused them, several groups have boycotted and called for advertisers to drop The O'Reilly Factor."



"Ultraviolet has called for a boycott, and later published an open letter to 21st Century Fox CEO James Murdoch to fire O'Reilly, which read in part, "We are sexual assault and domestic violence survivors and their loved ones, writing once again to ask you to rid Fox News of its culture of gender-based abuse.""



"The group now has a protest planned for Tuesday, to be held at Fox News headquarters in New York, which includes a plane to fly a banner reading "Fox: #DropOReilly, The Sexual Predator"

The protest is set to begin Tuesday at 1:30 p.m. EST outside Fox News headquarters in New York.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women's Rights Group to Fly Aerial Banner During Bill O'Reilly Protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joy sits in for Rachel Maddow:

*Joy-Ann Reid reports on the questions about the legitimacy of a Turkish referendum election and the authoritarian power grab seen in Recep Tayyip Erdogan's win, none of which stood in the way of Donald Trump making a congratulatory phone call. Duration: 3:57* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump ignores oppression in congratulatory call to Erdogan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, that's a classy sidebar for a naked birthday party  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point it does not matter who complains about who Howard interviews, this place will complain and complain about complaining and complain about complaining about complaining.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Forget About Collusion! I think I saw Putin at the White House Easter Egg Roll... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Washington Post:


Antiabortion advocates are on a roll right now, and theres less and less standing in their way

As part of the 'March for Life,' thousands of abortion opponents from across the country gathered in D.C. and marched from the Washington Monument to the U.S. Supreme Court with renewed optimism from an administration expected to move forward with antiabortion policies. 


President Trump just scored a political base victory by signing a law that allows states to withhold federal funds from Planned Parenthood and other facilities that provide abortions.


But the real movement on abortion is happening in the states. There, antiabortion advocates are on a roll, passing some of the most restrictive abortion laws ever. And with the winds shifting in Washington in favor of conservatives, some antiabortion advocates are banking that the ultimate prize  ending legal abortion  could be within reach.


There are now 17 states that ban abortion after 20 weeks, when antiabortion advocates argue a fetus can feel pain. In the 2017 state legislative session (which for many states isn't halfway over), five states have passed major abortion restriction laws, and 28 legislatures have introduced legislation banning some or all types of abortion.


Like it did last year, Arkansas is leading the pack. It has passed a flurry of antiabortion laws: One will require doctors to look into a woman's pregnancy history to make sure she isn't getting an abortion based on gender selection. Another will let husbands sue to prevent their wives from getting a second-trimester abortion. And the state banned the most common abortion procedures employed in the second trimester. (Similar bans have faced legal challenges in Kansas, Oklahoma and Alabama.)

A new law in Arizona will require doctors to resuscitate a fetus if it's born alive in an abortion procedure. It will also be one of the only states to require clinics have certain lifesaving equipment on hand.
Shortly after Republicans took control of the state House, which Democrats had held for nearly a century, Kentucky became the 17th state to ban all abortions at or after 20 weeks. Doctors also have to do an ultrasound on a woman who wants an abortion. Kentucky also just signed into law a bill taking away federal funds from Planned Parenthood, with a provision at the bottom that it would go into effect once Trump signed Thursday's bill.
Wyoming, which hasn't enacted an abortion restriction in nearly three decades, just signed into law a requirement that doctors offer a woman an ultrasound and an opportunity to listen to a fetal heartbeat during abortion counseling.
In Utah, abortion providers will soon have to counsel a woman wanting an abortion about a medically unproven procedure to undo it. (Despite the fact the top gynecology organization in America does not approve of this method, bills allowing for counseling about it was introduced in four other states.)


That's a lot of movement on abortion in a few months. But antiabortion advocates have actually been on a roll for six years and counting. Since Republicans swept control of a majority of state legislatures in 2010, states have enacted more than 350 abortion restrictions. In the 2016 state legislative session, some 14 states made it harder to get an abortion.





Antiabortion advocates have been so successful at restricting abortions that lawmakers are now coming up with some creative and eyebrow-raising ways to push the envelope.


A proposal that recently passed the Kansas state House requires a woman to receive her abortion information in black ink in 12-point Times New Roman font.


In Alabama, lawmakers are debating a constitutional amendment to ban abortion completely.


Since they haven't been able to stem the tide legislatively, abortion rights advocates have successfully been playing whack-a-mole through the courts. Many state laws banning abortion before or at 20 weeks end up getting held up or gutted in court, or GOP governors veto them to avoid such a fate.


With the landscape in Washington shifted to the right, however, court challenges might not be as much of a roadblock for antiabortion advocates.


Even with newly sworn in conservative Justice Neil M. Gorsuch, there are still five justices on the U.S. Supreme Court that have upheld abortion rights, including recently striking down Texas abortion clinic restrictions. But if some of the court's liberal or swing seats opened up during the Trump administration, that could change. Antiabortion advocates think it's feasible we could see a court in the next four to eight years that would be amendable to reversing its landmark 1973 Roe v. Wade decision legalizing abortion.


Elizabeth Nash with the abortion rights research group Guttmacher Institute says there's an arms race in conservative states to pass increasingly strict abortion laws in hopes of being the trigger for a tidal wave of abortion bans.



Keeping up with politics is easy now.
One of these states are looking to be that state to enact the law that ends up at the Supreme Court and overturns Roe v. Wade, she said. That's what we're watching for.


Four states  Louisiana, Mississippi, and North and South Dakota  have laws in place that would immediately ban abortion if Roe v. Wade were overturned. A January report from the Center for Reproductive Rights calculates that abortion could quickly be illegal in 33 states if given the option.


In a 60 Minutes interview shortly after getting elected, President Trump seemed okay with that: Well, theyll perhaps have to go  theyll have to go to another state, he said of women who would want an abortion under that scenario.


Antiabortion advocates, like Mary Spalding Balch with the National Right to Life Committee, say the ultimate goal is ending all abortion: We still have a long way to go to achieve full protection of the unborn child, she told The Fix last year.


The trend is in that direction.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good old news.fastcompany...um, I don't know...but they put the tweets and stuff into a story first so..good for them, this has more details too: http://www.refinery29.com/2017/04/150266/fox-news-oreilly-protest-womens-group </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, I'm not around so I'm relying on you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://facebook.com/events/125820131294053/


The protest is set to begin Tuesday at 1:30 p.m. EST outside Fox News headquarters in New York.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://facebook.com/events/125820131294053/


The protest is set to begin Tuesday at 1:30 p.m. EST outside Fox News headquarters in New York.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you provide the appropriate flushing out for what I simply stated.
 Besides Wendy Walsh, there are at least 7 women providing a situation where job was offered then sexual advances then no job. In the nytimes article and previously reported in court cases and witness testimony and reporting years back. Sure, more information is welcome as reporting and investigating continues, at this point I trust the stories of the women and the reporters reportings of the sexual harassment. It's not one story or one case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://weareultraviolet.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill O'Reilly offered several woman career furthering job opportunities at Fox News. Bill O'Reilly came on to these women, said sexual things to them, and wanted sex with them. Whatever the exact form, he made sexual advances and was rejected and the women were not given the career opportunities. Bill O'Reilly mixed his job and his employer and hiring, in with sex stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this will catch you up on the story: http://www.msnbc.com/am-joy/watch/o-reilly-faces-investigations-after-settlements-922387011504 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the info was on this page from the start, and in the article. You should take it up with the writer at Variety.com, I should have redone it, but alas I don't think it's worth reposting..you can't change title after posting... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If people don't know that he's a sexual predator or why a women's group would be protesting him, they probably wouldn't be here, and besides, they should definitely look for more information if they didn't know what was meant. It could be a better title, more sensationalized and/or more details, but alas, I went with the article's title and just added the detail of the group's name. I agree, but this sub encourages clicking inside so I think it's okay, I don't know that it is worth re posting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sexual assault survivors are planning to protest Bill OReilly at Fox News HQ
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Katy Tur on Twitter: [Jon Karl: Is it time to say finally that POTUS is never going to release his taxes? Spicer: "We'll have to get back to you on that](https://twitter.com/KatyTurNBC/status/854041489202085889) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reporter Jon Karl to Sean Spicer: "Is it time to say finally that POTUS is never going to release his taxes?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "On Tuesday, April 18th, Ultraviolet will lead the protest with survivors of sexual assault demanding that the network fire OReilly in light of recent sexual harassment allegations. The group will also deliver a petition they say has been signed by more than 140,000 people calling for the network to fire OReilly. In addition, the group has commissioned a plane to fly around Manhattan with a banner reading FOX: #DROPOREILLY, THE SEXUAL PREDATOR."

Website: https://weareultraviolet.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are Ultraviolet: Womens Group to Demand Fox News Fire Bill OReilly at New Protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The peaceable assembly by sexual assault survivors and their supporters, spearheaded by the group UltraViolet, will call on the network to fire its Talking Head-in-Chief, Bill O'Reilly, in the wake of a wave of sexual harassment charges against him. Over 140,000 people signed a petition calling on Fox to can their man. The protest will take place in the streets as well as in the skyUltraViolet has commissioned a plane to fly around Manhattan with a banner urging Fox to drop O'Reilly." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sexual assault survivors are planning to protest Bill OReilly at Fox News HQ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It goes over the facts and a couple developing new pieces: 

**One** of the reporters who was reporting previously on the case, says Fox has intimidated him and he's pursuing a complaint. 

**A lawyer** points out that Fox News may be in legal trouble for claiming the sexual harrassment case settlements as compensation and that that may have misrepresented info to shareholders.

**And Lisa Bloom,** Wendy Walsh's lawyer for her sexual harassment claim against Bill, says there may be two further investigations from two additional investigators into the sexual harrassment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill O'Reilly implied to several different women they would have more opportunities at Fox News. Then, he tried come-ons with them, was overly and bluntly sexual with them, we do not know all the details, but we know he made unwanted sexual advances, and we know these women did not get the further job opportunities. It is likely there are more graphic situations and sexual harrassment cases we do not yet know about. But simply, being rejected and then not advancing the women is enough for firing him, his prior moralizing persona would agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Everything is PC!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some surprising self-awareness from Mariann from Brooklyn, her calls would be much better if she chilled out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Joy Reid and her guests discuss two new investigations being launched in the wake of FOX paying five women $13 million after they accused Bill OReilly of sexual harassment (which he denies). Duration 10:55* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OReilly faces investigations after settlements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PYONGYANG, North Korea (AP)--
"And in Pyongyang, where war would mean untold horrors, where neighborhoods could be reduced to rubble and tens of thousands of civilians could be killed, few people seem to care much at all."



"On Sunday, the city's zoo was crowded, playgrounds were full of children and families strolled along downtown sidewalks speckled with the falling blossoms of apricot trees. At the city's annual Kimilsungia flower show  held to celebrate Saturday's 105th anniversary of the birth of North Korea's founding ruler, Kim Il Sung, and the purple orchid named for him  thousands crowded around the displays, many using cellphones to take photos of friends and family."


"In a country where the propaganda is all-encompassing, and where the same family has held power for three generations, every display mixed bright flowers with reminders of Kim Il Sung or the nation that his grandson, Kim Jong Un, now rules. So there were dioramas of Kim Il Sung's birthplace, photos of him meeting foreign leaders, paintings of new housing developments  and models of missiles."



"And there was Chong Ok An, a retiree pushing her way through the crowds with her family."


""We're not afraid," she said. "As long as we have Marshall Kim Jong Un we can win any fight.""


"Her response reflected the phrasing of North Korean propaganda, as well as the reality that every person here has heard talk of war for decades. The Kim family has entrenched its rule by portraying the country as being relentlessly under siege, leaving its people unable to distinguish between daily hyperbole and the reality of an increasingly tense situation."


"The same unending hyperbole has affected South Koreans as well. They have heard North Korean warnings of their destruction for so long that the threats barely even register."


"While interest in North Korea spikes immediately after a missile launch, within hours internet search traffic is again dominated by TV comedy shows, taxes and real estate." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Its important to acknowledge that at no point has any court of law delivered a verdict against him. But the sheer number of accusations; the prominence of the women who have leveled them; the absence of any categorical denial (let alone apology); the mindboggling sums of money involved; and OReillys feeble excuse for settling  his children?  indicate that, failing a terrific explanation, theres fire as well as smoke."


"**If thats true (and the Murdoch family has wisely hired the law firm Paul Weiss to investigate), theres only one way forward: OReilly must go."**


"Firing him is a huge step, but the Murdochs own history leaves them with little choice: In July, they established a precedent, terminating Ailes (with a $40 million spoonful of honey), based on similar accusations."

"That precedent could be critical in determining how they move forward. Not firing OReilly would lead to accusations of hypocrisy."

"Adding pressure to the Murdochs is their recent history with scandal, most notably the biggest one ever to strike their company, when reporters and editors at Londons News of the World were accused of wiretapping celebrities and other figures."

"Three years after phone-gate, they must convince investors that theyre their own men; that they can successfully guide their company into a future that may last even longer than its decades-old past. They must reassure prominent female employees (theyve promoted such top-level women as the Fox studios Stacey Snider and Emma Watts) that the old boys are no longer running rampant, whatever one might think. And they must win over shareholders who are increasingly under pressure to invest in corporations that are ethically as well as financially sound  especially those with access to the public airwaves."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the Murdochs and Fox News Should Fire Bill O'Reilly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Its important to acknowledge that at no point has any court of law delivered a verdict against him. But the sheer number of accusations; the prominence of the women who have leveled them; the absence of any categorical denial (let alone apology); the mindboggling sums of money involved; and OReillys feeble excuse for settling  his children?  indicate that, failing a terrific explanation, theres fire as well as smoke."


"**If thats true (and the Murdoch family has wisely hired the law firm Paul Weiss to investigate), theres only one way forward: OReilly must go."**


"Firing him is a huge step, but the Murdochs own history leaves them with little choice: In July, they established a precedent, terminating Ailes (with a $40 million spoonful of honey), based on similar accusations."

"That precedent could be critical in determining how they move forward. Not firing OReilly would lead to accusations of hypocrisy."

"Adding pressure to the Murdochs is their recent history with scandal, most notably the biggest one ever to strike their company, when reporters and editors at LondonsNews of the World were accused of wiretapping celebrities and other figures."

"Three years after phone-gate, they must convince investors that theyre their own men; that they can successfully guide their company into a future that may last even longer than its decades-old past. They must reassure prominent female employees (theyve promoted such top-level women as the Fox studios Stacey Snider and Emma Watts) that the old boys are no longer running rampant, whatever one might think. And they must win over shareholders who are increasingly under pressure to invest in corporations that are ethically as well as financially sound  especially those with access to the public airwaves."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Fox News and the Murdochs Should Fire Bill O'Reilly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're waiting for more controversies they can blame on him so they can say, this or that evil thing Trump did is resolved by *Spicer's you're firing.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am Joy Reid:


*Sean Spicer faced possible firing after making a number of gaffes about the Holocaustbut Joy and her panel see Trumps methods in his madness.* *Duration: 9:24*

To be fired or not to be fired? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Spicer: pure Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck it, we'll do it live </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 12:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same feeling, but he said so, so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Bill, bored on vacation I see  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess cut the list of Trump issues and just focus on your Ways and means point is good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 1973 President Richard Nixon uttered a line that has since reverberated through the American psyche: "People have got to know whether or not their president is a crook." Well, we know what he said.


(Wait for laughter to subside)


But what you may not know, is that Nixon was not talking about the Watergate scandal, but about his decision to give into public pressure and release his tax returns. 

(Gasps)

Since then, every single American president has done the same until Donald Trump.

(Booing)


And the irony is, that our current president has more conflicts of interest, his businesses profiting, nepotism, foreign ties, than any of his predecessors.

(Applause)

Section 6103 of the Internal Revenue Code gives the House Ways and Means Committee the ability to requisition tax returns and release them when it serves the public interest and it is inarguable that seeing his taxes is in the public's best interest. Three Republicans from Texas on that committee, including Chairperson Kevin Brady!
(Gasps)

They can release Trump's tax returns and we need you, we need you, you (points finger) to put pressure on Mr. Brady. Failure to do so is an abdication of your civic duty.

The American people have got to know if their president is a crook.
(As they try to pull the microphone away from you scream:
Show us his taxes!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had seen it and experienced whether I believed it. I can't stop laughing at this article, at this thought "Hey, heads ups, that Donald Trump pooped his pants story is fake." And it's not that it's dumb, it's just so absurd and perfect for every reason   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact is, that awhile ago, their was a specific email specifically about Bill O'Reilly to stop degrading her story and Bill O'Reilly persisted and this upset her right as she was deciding whether to stay or leave, so it seems that it was a factor perhaps not the only factor but a factor, certainly she was upset about the environment specifically about Bill and certainly she left. It don't say Kelly published this email  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 1973 President Richard Nixon uttered a line that has since reverberated through the American psyche: "People have got to know whether or not their president is a crook. Well," he said, "I am not a crook. 

Most Americans don't realize that Nixon was not talking about the Watergate scandal, but about his decision to succumb to the demand to release his tax returns. 

Since then, every single American president has done the same until Donald Trump.

And the irony is, that our current president has more conflicts of interest than any of his predecessors: whether it's bribery scandals in the Philippines, nepotism scandals in the White House, Mar-a-Lago doubling its membership fees, or any number of outstanding lawsuits against him for  possible violations of the emoluments clause of the American Constitution. 

It is imperative that the American people can be assured that their president, that Donald Trump, is not a crook

 and, it is impossible to do that, without seeing his tax returns.

Section 6103 of the Internal Revenue Code gives the House Ways and Means Committee the ability to requisition tax returns and release them when it, quote: serves the public interest." Considering the longstanding precedent, and all of Trump's potential conflicts, wouldn't seeing his taxes serve the public's *best* interests?

There are three Republican congressmen from Texas on the Ways   Means committee, including its Chairperson Kevin Brady. They have the power to acquire and release President Trump's tax returns and We need you to put pressure on Mr. Brady, and the others, to deliver what the president swore he would release months ago. Failure to do so is an abdication of your civic duty.

The American people have the right to know if their president is a crook, show us his taxes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
