<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1320</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 02:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a position I hear often from some in the paranormal community.  I sort of get the concept.  It's a very interesting method of believing something is real.  My only retort to that would be how many letters do you see in this picture?  How many C's ?http://imgur.com/a/YJuMD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 02:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e2RioksC9Kc and https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ovIrMEZ-GiY  and https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0O_1_vEomBk. The organization http://www.sep.moonfruit.com ( Listen 1:11 , 1:14,  1:23 , 1:25 ,  ) Day 3 of Day 5. Steve Mera and Don Philips arrived at my house Jan 21st to conduct a week long investigation about the events happening in my house from 2012 - 2015. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 02:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> field?  there's a field?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 19:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bench mark it guys!  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uBte7PDEmTc same house. 

My hand was no where near the recorder.  "why" comes immediately after I said I'm laying down trip wire and voice recorder.  After "why" comes a quick "no". Pause it in Audacity and loop it 00:09 thru 00:15" seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 19:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bench mark it guys!  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uBte7PDEmTc same house. http://www.coasttocoastam.com/pages/parapsychologists-declare-home-has-poltergeist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 19:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bench mark it guys!  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uBte7PDEmTc same house. http://www.coasttocoastam.com/pages/parapsychologists-declare-home-has-poltergeist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 18:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you'd like that to be the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVP "WHY" - Haunted House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 18:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/JQhRXWwggBI
EVP at 00:10. "WHY" then a quick "No" at 00:13 seconds. April 2016. Days before the movers arrived I placed voice recorder and trip wire in the hallway of my home.  I wanted to see what if anything the spirits would say as a result of me moving, taking down beds, pictures, and etc.  This is one snippet of that encounter. EVP at 00:10. Then a quick "No" at 00:13 seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 18:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/JQhRXWwggBI, re listen again after hearing this video.  I try to get the EVP's during a natural setting. because these spirits speak about current events. They interact.  In this instance I'm just having a recorder, capturing their commentary.   This video is the perfect example of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVP - "They'll Walk Through" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> April 2016 - 1st Voice recorder 3:16 "They'll walk through...."  then 2nd Voice recorder is located on opposite of the house (lower level) at 7:05 "They'll Walk Through it..." Best with headsets, even better with Audio Galaxy, re-looping.  https://youtu.be/7nRXcrsqdg8   EVP at 5:34 "MY STUFF"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Attack - Poltergeist (True Account) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 05:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overall. 4 years. The "Keith" EVP weirdness was discovered in May, after I moved out of the house.  Where over 30+ "Keith" EVP. Where found on several of the listening devices around the house. Both cam and voice recorder placed in various place caught "Keith" "Keith"  "Keith"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVP: "Keith" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 21:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/tD8GVmCi7C0
Female voice at 00:04 "Keith"   Male voice at 1:32 "Keith"

https://youtu.be/BmkMoc1plIU
00:12 seconds "Keith"

The female voice has whispered "Keith" in my ear while sleeping.

One does themselves a service by comparing the "Keith" above NEW House to the "Keiths" below at the old house (Move Out Day)

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a83qZ1uOwXI

my name is Keith BTW
http://www.nwnews.com/index.php/local/news-features/12586-the-haunting-in-bothell-paranormal-researchers-from-uk-investigate-infamous-house </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 20:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm alone in my home. There are no investigators.  My name is Keith.  House is empty besides me.  The series of "Keith" specific EVP stems from my 4 year stay at this house.  

http://www.nwnews.com/index.php/local/news-features/12586-the-haunting-in-bothell-paranormal-researchers-from-uk-investigate-infamous-house

Other KEITH evp'S
Too many to be a coincidence and shows that an spirit attachment does exist.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tD8GVmCi7C0

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BmkMoc1plIU

Videos above are NEW House
Video Below is the Old House
Move out Day

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a83qZ1uOwXI


Mind you most of these evps are caught on multiple devices, at the same time, devices spread out and some device are video equipment not voice recorder.

ALTHOUGH NOT REQUIRED AS SOME EVPS are LOUD]  5:32 " test that" 5:37 "EVP", murmurings.  7:09 "Yeah" 7:58 audio interference.  10:33 "Breathing" 10:51 "Go Ahead" ??  13:22 "EVP" 13:37  "Yeah" 16:46 "Yeah"  20:11 Audio volume flux. Interference.  20:37 significant mic bump. Mics on frig BTW. 20:48 breathing.  26:00 "Yeah" Weird Interference at 30:24. and 30:44.  34:14 "Keith"  35:45 "Keith"  (the spirits are in the Kitchen) 35:58 whisper "What Ever"  36:08 "Keith" and 36:09  "Keith"  37:00 interference noise. 37:31 "EVP"  37:43 "Keith" and "37:45" two voices are saying "Keith" now almost back to back.  Could this be the attachment process?  37:49 electrical audio interference.  37:58 "Keith"  38:03 "Keith" 38:09 "KEITH !"  the loudest "Keith" so far.  38:30 "Keith"  40:14 "Help Me" , breathing noises. whispers. 40:50 "EVP" GET READY HERE IT COMES.  43:07 "Keith"  43:12 "Keith" "43:18"  Keith"  43:25  "Keith" 43:33  "Keith"  43:36  "Keith"  43:41  "Keith" 43:46  "Keith"  43:49  "Keith"  43:53  "Keith"   43:55 "Keith"   43:58  "Keith"  44:09   "Keith" 44:12 "Keith"  44:18  "Keith" 44:22 faint Keith.  44:24 faint "Keith"  44:51  "Yeah"  45:00 "whispering, and dialogue , chatting, whispers can be heard".  46:16  faint  "Keith" 46:37  "Keith" faint.  46:53 "Keith" ??   47:05  "Watch Out!"  47:15  "Yeah"  48:20 "EVP"   48:51 "Keith" 48:53 "Yeah" 48:57 "Keith"  49:00 faint "Keith" 49:12 , 49:14  "Keith"  weird noises at 51:00 and beyond.  51:58 "EVP??  Keith???" as i make rounds to lock the house up.  53:50 "Keith" a Keith is uttered even after I leave.  and then at 53:53 a sudden "Keith" can be heard. 54:39  "Keith" Knock at 55:20  House is empty.   55:47  "KEITH !!!!!" can be heard.  Remember the house is empty.  Movers and I are on our way to the NEW house. Walking around noise can be heard.  Loud noise upstairs at 57:05.  PAY ATTENTION....The ice machine/i.e.frig cuts off at 57:20. Its possible the spirits didn't know that was coming.  As u can hear them clearer. 57:22 "Keith" 57:23  "Keith"  57:30  "Keith" 57:32, 57:33 "Keith"  57:39  "Keith"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Female, Male EVP. (1st one comes at 00:04 seconds) best with headphones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 22:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tD8GVmCi7C0
Summer 2016 post Bothell House - Female voice at 00:04 "Keith"   Male voice at 1:32 "Keith"


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 06:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 00:12 Keith,  best w/headphones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington State 00:12 seconds "Keith" EVP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVP at 00:12 seconds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 22:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://soundcloud.com/user-423872078/keith-evp

both audio and video

https://subject1320.box.com/s/ooyhlrb85aejkq9egnaqn59t215e7lst

30 minute to be shared soon.

oh my name is Keith BTW


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 22:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The GA team were divided into two teams A team (Zak and crew) and the B team (B roll) as it is called.   Suffice to say the B team was better.  My sentiment of Zak and crew is a matter of public record. But in the end it was a blessing in disguise.  Because there lack of thoroughness allowed me to contact other, more experienced teams(experienced in malevolent haunting) i.e. world renowned Steve Mera parapsychologist of the UK. and Chief researcher Don Philips. They came and busted the case wide open. Yielding powerful results.  Hence the "Im a Mirror" evp above and much much much much more.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0O_1_vEomBk
and
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zhA-tqf19Es </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NO "EVP" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 18:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have no interests in promoting your work then you are not advancing the science, knowledge and understanding of Parapsychology. If there's one thing I notice that sticks in my craw about both Paranormal and Parapsychology is how silloed you individuals are. And more sad and shocking is how much you take pride and relish in the fact that you are private, cut-off, wont share, won't dialogue with others with identical interests and understanding. 

A physicists at UT(Austin) will communicate and share his/her info i.e. publication with the physics community for both opinion, objectivity and possibly the new discovery and advancement of the field which is to ultimately seek the truth about life itself.  

Here you are on Reddit giving me beef, lecturing me on how you never heard of Steve Mera. I now know why you haven't heard of Steve Mera. You're too dam private.  This is either gross malpractice, or ego. Or both.

The perfect example from a professional point of view of how the left hand doesn't know what the right hand is doing. Build a web site. Write an article and share it among colleagues.  Adopt a best practice method. In short come out of the cave and into the 21st century.

Ex.
[Einstein gave a series of lectures in 1915 about his new theory, which was to become known as the General Theory of Relativity, including a new equation to replace Newton's law of gravity, now known as Einstein's field equation. The complete theory was finally published in 1916, although physicists and mathematicians like Karl Schwarzschild and Ludwig Flamm were starting to publish solutions to his field equations even before its publication] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 05:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I get you're a wanna be parasychologists? There are mall cops and their are police officers. Fire fighters and volunteer fire fighters. I see which category you fall into. You have no publication. You have no case log,  or case history. It's 2016 and u have no Web site. I heard of self made men but this is new.

For someone calling themselves a scientist you carry alot of subjectivity. 

Even Einstein wrote publications.  You? You got this space. Hmmmmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 21:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You worked in this field?  Under what name?  Whats your real-name?  Whats your web site?  What work related material have you put out on the paranormal?  30+ years?  U must have a book? A journal? A web site.  Google the names provided and educate yourself on S.E.P/Steve Mera.  Why so disgruntled over a potential colleague baffles me.  And lastly just because one doesn't know someone doesn't mean there not legit.  Reveal your name. Your work and I'll be sure to mention you to Steve. I'm curious as to what work you put out. 30+ years. You got's to have something.  Weird you're on reddit but thats another story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 17:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no clue why a ghost would "I'm a Mirror"  I think its a riddle. Might mean its a portal? A doorway? A reflection of us?  Thats a good question. One I was hoping to entertain here (which is why I bought the info to this community).  What does it mean when an entity says "I'm a Mirror?"  Thats a great question. I'm open to theories, intelligent theories, intelligent thought experiments. No mirror has ever been broken in the house.  Mirror in general are viewed as doorways so maybe its related to that.  Maybe it means you guys will never catch me because "I'm a Mirror"  I'm a reflection of you. Its quite unusual and I think it means something.  Im googling the term now to see what I come up with. Maybe there's some sort of historical reference.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 17:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No what it said is you do dont read.  hence the PDF report. https://subject1320.box.com/s/93o3vk8o5i52225lpb686rudo9ikwfg3

Read but dont weep my friend. The above initial report is from Week 1 visit.  What does mean to you and this community.  It means I'm going to do my best to share every video, every audio gathered thats been certified as being legit.  i.e evidence. 
427 records (1st trip)  Not even counting the 2nd trip.  So grab some pop-corn, pen and a note pad and lets talk Paranormal baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 00:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You're presenting your "case" as if you get evidence every single day. I'm not buying it.

No thats how you're interpreting it. Im not getting evidence every single day. if you'd read you see the date says April 2016. Which coincides when S.E.P was last here. I moved out of the house in May. May 9th to be exact.

I'm sharing with you and you I mean this forum the evidence after its been reviewed, compiled and analyzed.

It takes days, weeks, months to review audio and video file.  You best your last sight saber the fact that you're seeing it hear means its been 100% vetted.

do yourself a favor and get caught up on all the facts!

Not guesses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 00:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know this case is phony?  Wow  you used the word "know" so certain are you as Yoda would say. U mean you hope its phoney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 22:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know whats super funny, super sad about this whole mini debate between you and I?  You're inability to admit when you're wrong. When Albert Einstein realized one of his equation(theories) was wrong he openly admitted to the world it was his greatest mistake. His biggest blunder, Even by admitting his greatest mistake via publication he gained greater prominence and respect from both skeptic and believing community.  He grew intellectually.

It takes a BIG man to admit when there wrong.  And what's even more sad is what does it cost you to admit being wrong  What prevents you from saying you know what I wasn't there, Zak and GA was.  They left with nothing, maybe something chose to not present itself while they were there.    Maybe what GA shows on TV is a little too simple. I mean any paranormal investigator worth his/her weight in gold will tell:  99% of investigations yield 0 results. .5% yield inconclusive. The remaining .5% are true mystery cases.  Let Ghost Adventures tell it  theyre batting a 1000. Every time. Several teams have come in, spent greater lengths in the home, other teams with far more experience, far more longevity in the field than GA. Teams before and after GA. S.E.P  uncovered a lot, at the very least they uncovered something. You saying something is not there, that its all a hoax is like a Dr trying to perform open heart surgery by peeping through a key hole.  Youre swallowing the opinion of man who buys his hair gel in bulks.  His verdict is supposed to be gospel?

Instead of attacking the messenger and proving you can be. #1 Zealot for Zak Bagans why not ask thought provoking questions?  Why not analyze whats been put forth. Obviously Im not afraid to be scrutinized: look whove Ive invited into my home? - look at what I've put forth?  And if that don't suit you then exercise your God given right to just ignore it. Ignore it and allows others with interests to chime in.  Thats a lot better than trying to be the Barney Fife on Redditt message boards.
I display my credentials openly. I've yet to hear from you and from other skeptics on what makes you the judge and jury on whats paranormal and whats not?

If you are the expert then take a page from Albert Einstein. Admit when you're wrong and just let it end with that.
If not. Be you. And I will continue to be me which means expect more info. More evidence. After all this is a paranormal community.  Not the world is flat community.

[Pretty sure the implication was that these two nuts were spray painting their walls with fake burn marks and attempting to drum up attention. Fortunately, the clients found a bunch of "researchers" who want attention as much as they do.]  Your conjecture and innuendo amuses me.

"...Well it proves one thing, Mr. Hooper. It proves that you wealthy college boys don't have the education enough to admit when you're wrong. "

Quint Jaws Movie
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 22:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No actually its called due diligence.  When you capture 500 GIGS of video and audio. It takes months to comb through.  Slowly but surely it gets done.  Then its checked, re-checked and double check.  Couldn't help you obvious ignoring of the evidence already provided.


Put a blind fold on. ignore the source. pretend it was you who found it and you'd be saying thing Im saying.

Don't shoot the messenger. Dissect the message.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 21:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> see you at the next evidence release! No whats funny is how you're putting so much emphasis on a comedian within the paranormal community.  They didnt say the case wasn't real. They said they just didnt find any evidence "while they were there." And if there such a low caliber team (as you you say the laughing stock of) then how can you expect them to find true evidence to begin with. In all actuality its a blessing they didnt.  Had they did you'd be singing the same song LOL. Wise up due. Increase your P-IQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 20:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why you want to know? As if you'd read it?  LOL

so much is coming in the next few weeks and months. Fall/Winter 2016 will be information over-load about the findings of this case. It wont even be fair debating you come then.

we've dotted our I's and crossed out T's  so get ready
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 19:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you are so in love with Zak its seriously showing.  U want this case to be fake. u cant refute or offer anything intelligent about teh evidence provides accept to say Oh Zak found nothing.  Nothing doesn't equate to fake or hoaxing.  Heck you might be even be on the GA payroll.  Instead of vouching for Zaks skills as an investigator why not ascertain some true research?  Why not broaden your horizon. if not. ignore a post you dont believe in.  Zaks fan club is a few message boards over. proceed to right please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 18:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude you should really get off Zak B nut sak.  #1 GA never said it was a hoax or fake. They said they found no evidence.  Paranormal teams investigate establishments all the time and MOST of the time (not like how the portrays) they leave with nothing.  To label something or hoax you have to first catch them in the act.  You literally have to see someone hoaxing or planting evidence. I wish you would get that through your dense little head. Stop drinking Zak Bagans Kool-Aid!.  If your interest is really paranormal then you'd know and understand Ghost Adventures is a TV show. They dont even make up 1% of both the science and paranormal community.   The minute you wake up and understand that, trust a whole new world is going to open up for you.

GA investigated the house for 7-10 hrs
S.E.P investigated the house for 2 weeks. 360+ HRS

Do the math

http://www.coasttocoastam.com/pages/parapsychologists-declare-home-has-poltergeist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 16:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xztHjWBKqzg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 05:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there are a lot of people in here not sincerely interested in the paranormal.  the idea that it exist urks them.  Not I though. Obviously </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 05:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow !  very interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 02:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 85% of all audio/videos still haven't been reviewed. More to come. But yeah...creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVP: "I'm A Mirror" Washington State Poltergeist case. Voices caught on 2 diff devices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 01:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uBte7PDEmTc  2:10 "I'm a Mirror" and 8:26 "Im a Mirror" i do a strange reaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haunted House EVP Captures: April 2016 Steve and Don returned to my house for Part 2 of their investigation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 00:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 23:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fascinating.  I know exactly what you mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 17:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen apparitions and have had activity while alone in the house, but usually its when my GF had just left and vise versa.  Minimal activity has always been foot steps. Pacing back n forth and etc.

http://supernaturalmagazine.com/articles/living-with-a-poltergeist-an-interview-with-keith-linder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 20:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.coasttocoastam.com/pages/parapsychologists-declare-home-has-poltergeist  and https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_xt7GiGhlrs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 20:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really?   thats interesting!  What ever came of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 08:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :26 seconds in a strong Keith whispers out of nowhere.    
Voice is not me. But my name is Keith.  Voice sounds female </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVP at 00:26 seconds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 22:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://soundcloud.com/user-423872078/keith-evp-at-0026-seconds

EVP at 00:26 seconds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the theories being talked about is some sort of portal door was opened. Why, How or by who we may never know.  Weve only been able to reach two of the previous tenants.  Parapsychologist Steve Mera theory is a Poltergeist infestation has in an indirect or direct way attracting other entities to the home.  There does appear to be a correlation in some cases, the rarest of cases of demonic and Poltergeist cases being either the same or similar. One begets the other.

Another theory is the spirits in the house are tied to the land.  We have EVPs were the vocal responses say they move from house to house. 

The vocals talking above, one of them is called Ray. We have this on about 5 other EVPs. Rays the subordinate. The one bossing him around so far remains unnamed

These two are who I feel could possibly be demonic or minion.

Its clear by the EVP there watching me. And this confirms I was followed. 

All is quiet right now except for the bed shakes, poke and prodding while sleeping and the feeling of being watched.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attachments. Steps for getting rid of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 07:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XyiS22Wn1cw

A lot of bed shakes, tugging, pulling, crawling over me while sleeping. Poking and prodding. Middle of the night I got up and placed a voice recorder in the hallway, outside my bedroom.  00:17 weird noise,  Whispers, Murmuring, voices, at 1:57,  "Ray?" 2:08   "Keith" at 2:12,  other whispers, murmurs, 2:19 "EVP"  3:53 "Keith",  6:03 another "Ray!"  Ray quickly responds at 6:04. 6:06 thru 6:08 conversation going.  6:06 accent voice "You Like?" accent voice sounds like "Chew like" weird dialect.  6:46 "EVP",  23:10 "SEE HOW HE STOOD UP,?"  EVP coincides with me getting out of the bed.  Murmur and whisper then "Fast" 23:31. [Is he implying I got out of bed fast?]   23:41 a response of "Yeah" 26:36 "How are you?  or Hello?"  I turn off recorder and leave the NEW house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
