<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1935</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never had this response from a chugger. Are you politely telling them no, or are you being a dick about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on the code. The DCMA has some passages about bypassing DRM, so while copying a CD is not illegal, copying a BluRay is, because it uses some propriety DRM code. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of all companies, Nintendo were one of the few companies that kept their back catalog alive. For instance, Super Mario Bros has been available for NES, SNES (All Stars), Gameboy Color (Deluxe), GameBoy Advance, DS through backwards comparability, and Wii, WiiU and 3DS through VC. I presume the Switch will have a version soon enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, fuck people who collectively bargain. Life is suffering and collective bargaining is only something corporations should do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reagan was a fucking hypocrite. He was the head of a trade union, making life easier for millionaire actors who already had it too good. When President he let Hollywood write its own rules. As soon as a trade union he had no stakes in was in trouble (a union who mostly voted for him, because he presented himself as pro union due to his role in SAG.

If we are working in 'could haves' we can spend all day speculating and each inventing our own narratives of how he saved money or lost money. If we are working in cold hard facts without any speculation, all our quantifiable knowledge says he lost money. There are still teacher unions and police unions in the US, who do strike so his actions didn't completely kill public unions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you think letting a company go under, then rebuild the entire company from scratch would be cheaper? Even if the drivers don't see any payments, management won't let that happen without some golden parachutes. Then the process of rehiring will be vastly expensive again because first you need to hire new management, before you hire any new drivers. Plus there will be no public bus services in this period. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reagan firing all the flight controllers is exactly what I was referencing. It took weeks before normal services resumed and it ended up costing far much money than simply meeting the demands would have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fire and rehire imo

Historically, this will almost always cost more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More importantly, people shouldn't take drugs and drive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It kinda makes sense. You want the best version of your game available. Why would you sell both versions. You are competing with yourself and undercutting your own price while you are at it. In the end the consumer gets the shittier version of the game and because it is older, it might have trouble with modern hardware.

That said I've noticed I've gotten a lot of enhanced versions of games for free (Skyrim, Whispered World, Darksiders) and even if the price is increased on these special editions, they are still usually a lot lower than the cost of the original game, new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That too.

Plus it makes sense in other ways. You probably don't need a pen tester on full time. And if you did, there is no guarantee they would find a majority of exploits. Some people have a different way of thinking, which is why outsourcing works great in this capacity. You could have consultants come in every so often and do testing for you, but what recourse do you have if they say they found nothing.

Bounties are generally a good model for this sort of work, especially if you are in an industry with high levels of hobbiests doing the work anyway, whether it is to pirate stuff or create homebrew apps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are people who make a career out of finding exploits and collecting bounties. If no one else is collecting bounties on Switch 'for the greater hacker good' or whatever, someone will fill the gap. Heck, he will probably be a homebrew insider. You probably only need one or two people to actively work on it to see the benefits.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm no Tubs fan, but as cover?

I mean he had a pretty big opportunity and took it. And that opportunity allowed him to charge more for his services. That doesn't seem like he is trying to cheat anyone. That sounds like career progression. If I was a chef and I was asked to work with or cover for some prestigious European Michelin rated chef, I would use that to renegotiate my compensation. That's not sinister. That is how things are suppose to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, so we are back to public money should only be spent on things that benefit you directly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Tubs covered for Chris Evans](http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b01n0w56). At one stage Evans was the highest paid radio personality in the country, so there must be some interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These aren't screens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly this. If you are honest, we all knew this would be coming. The license fee was dreamt up as a per household charge. People started using their computers and laptops as televisions. This was really just a loophole around paying. RTE followed suit by putting their content online, but at that point they probably should have said that the license will apply to internet connections too. Now they are just catching up with themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well tell me, do those headrests play an important role in creating and promoting Irish culture? Are they providing a national service? Do they provide jobs (yes they pay a fuck tonne for 'talent', but they also hire Irish directors and actors, crew and pay Irish artists for their music on radio)?

What, the headrests do none of that? So are you saying it isn't a public service set up for the benefit of the Irish people? Okay, so I guess they have nothing in common then.

Look, I think the RTE is as shite as the next man does. I'd say I watch RTE maybe once a month, probably less. I do listen to the radio a bit more often while driving. But I also think the Irish arts are important. Gabriel Byrne (Bracken) and Ruth Negga (Love is the Drug) both got their start on RTE. Without RTE you won't see Irish actors on TV or drama's set in Ireland. If you do it will be twinkly eyed simpletons chasing leprechauns.

Our health service is in need of a big shake up or even be rebuilt from the ground up, but I won't ever say we should get rid of hospitals. Same for RTE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you will only pay it once. So if you have a TV, or internet connection you will pay. Calling it an internet tax makes as much sense as calling it a Playstation or a VCR tax just because some people had TVs and used them for games or videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pedestrians do pay road tax. The money from motor tax isn't allocated to road maintenance and money spent on roads comes from general taxation. You also pay for schools you don't attend, welfare payments you don't receive and salaries of politicians you didn't vote for, civil servant pensions you won't benefit from.

It wouldn't be tax if it was spent on only things you wanted, it would be called wages. It is a public service and whether you use a public service or not, you are still generally charged for it through taxation.

You can complain about the quality of a public service and demand change, that's fine. But you can't stop paying money for schools or hospitals because you think they're shit. You vote for people and tell them they need to change things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So VAT already exists on those services and goes elsewhere on govt spending.

The reason we have the post office collect license money is to keep it out of the hands of the government. This is suppose to stop it from being a government mouth piece. In theory, it also means that the government can't decide to 'cut funding' if they don't like something said on the radio or tv.

Adding to the price of TV might be a bit much. If you consider that a TV can last you 10 years, that would drastically increase the cost of the TV. People would just go north and buy TV's there, or buy them second hand.

A flat fee added to a SKY and internet bill might be a way forward, but there is also the chance of 'double dipping'. If you pay for a Sky subscription and an Internet subscription you will get charged twice. And it doesn't cast a net over the older population of Ireland who don't use subscription TV or Internet but watch RTE everyday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 10:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's obviously misrepresenting the situation. The license is for the content on RTE's site, not for having an internet connection. The same way you aren't paying a license for having a Sky cable box. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 10:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Not according to Howard Zinn](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XUBYI97cUgU). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 10:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a reason for that. You know when you see a movie with tanks and fighter jets and accurate uniforms? They are all borrowed from the US army, at no cost, on the condition that they get to approve the final script draft.

In movies like Black Hawk Down, they had to write out a character because of abuse charges laid against him and the army didn't want anyone less than 100% hero in the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assassin's Creed was an open world PoP. And I don't think it would work. Prince of Persia's platforming is puzzle based. It wouldn't be great by having puzzles you can just walk around. AC solved this by having tombs, which were essentially PoE puzzles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have to ask you're not invited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then at every industry or press event they have to here the same questions over and over again. Look at Valve and HL3. That game was never announced and there was never anything solid worked on, but nearly every interview people ask about a game that has never existed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What games disappeared? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it was written entirely by a 28 year old playwright Stefanie Preissner. And I think the idea was that the main character was a trainwreck and not your typical 20 something Dublin transplant from Cork. I'm sure shows you mentioned probably helped greenlight it (although apart from starring girls living in the city, I don't think Girls and Broad City have much in common) but it is relatively original. The main character has a pretty good job and is really good at it. In those other shows, the characters are usually failing at work.

I understand why you didn't like it, but I would disagree that it panders to 40 somethings. I only brought it up because it is one of the few shows that RTE have put out for the 17-35 age bracket.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more to do with their background than religion. And it's not to stop it, it is to ensure that people have a paper trail to say they aren't discriminating.

Without it the scenario would go something like this:
Auditor: I see that everyone who works here is Catholic. Are you only employing Catholics?

Employer: Well only Catholics applied. They were the best for the job.

Auditor: Can you prove that?

Employer: Can you prove otherwise?

With the rule the employer can say they interviewed 8 protestants and 12 Catholics and they can give reasons why they hired and on what basis.

Industries in NI have a history of hiring people from only certain backgrounds. The police force was almost all Protestant and so was Harland and Wolff. Before they could plead ignorance or say well that's who applied. Now they have numbers and can back up their hiring policies.

Is it the best way to fight discrimination? I don't know, but at least now it is easier to spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What or who do you think it pandered to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you managed to make a completely unrelated to Ireland post about Ireland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If RTE gave even a modicom of decent home-grown productions then, i might, think about paying.

RTE has a demographic problem. They make great TV if you are in your forties or beyond. They don't have much for younger people. Their version of First Dates is actually pretty good, but I would like to see some unmissable homegrown original content. The last show for young people was Can't Cope and it was generally well received, as was their prostitution docu and that Asking For It doc. They could go a lot more experimental over people in their twenties getting drunk in Coppers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's coming off the back of discriminatory practices. Previously employers would hire only people from one side. If they were challenged they could say it was a coincidence and they didn't know that all the people they hired were protestants. This ensures employers are aware so they can't shrug their shoulders when someone challenges them for hiring people mostly from one side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen so many people on here complain about advertised speed and then moan even more when they are told to get those speeds they would need a wired connection.

You have internet going through the air. That's a goddamn miracle. A wire to your machine shouldn't be a big issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so weird too. I mean I get complaining about internet. He made some bad assumptions that he should have had the foresight to think of, but lets say he had a brain fart. But quick access to an ambulance? Come on, he can't be so blind to not realise this would be an issue. Forgetting the shambles our health service is in, it's not like they will build a hospital just so his kids don't have to wait 30 mins in the off chance they need emergency medical attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have been Humble Bundled before. I imagine if you wait long enough there will be an AC bundle again and it should have most of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unity had launch issues which I think is why people hate on it. It also has a shitty story and also did nothing to move on the modern day story.

It did have time leap segments so you could play in different time periods and were a bit similar to the tombs from the early games. They were fun. But as a super fan of the series, Unity is at the bottom of the barrel with AC3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Connor felt more like a soldier than an assassin. Plus his role in the revolution was so big, there is no way he'd be forgotten by the history books.

Connor working with Haytham was cool but it took long enough to get there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the chronicles games are pretty tragic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always tail from the rooftops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think AC3 failed because of a boring story and having far much new things to do. It was better than its predecessor in every way. The free running evolved and had the mud game twist was really clever. But there was so much hunting lodges, homestead missions and  other bs.

Mechanically AC4 is pretty much the exact same game but with the focus on the naval element but the missions were more fun as was the protagonist and story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could be wrong but the reason KOTOR was set in the past was because the writer of the games hated the Star Wars universe and he wanted to distance Kotor from the Jedi equals good, Sith equals bad world of Star Wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, the EU was only ever Canon until they got in the way of the movies. The first EU entry was immediately thrown away by events in Empire. The prequels wrote off a lot of the EU too. When a movie was being made they rarely took any precautions not to step on EU properties. What Disney have done is wipe the slate clean so they can start their own EU that actually does stay in step with the movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen A Few Good Men? That's the whole point of the movie. You can't just follow orders. You are suppose to protect people and you need to know when you receive an order you shouldn't follow. Nicholson speech is basically safekeeping too. He's saying shut the fuck up, we do things are way and if you don't like that Fuck right off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In would call someone like Stephen Colbert a comedian, but I don't think he has ever done stand up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say Monopoly is a good game when you play by the rules, just quicker. Generally the winner is decided early on in the game. Going from there it is just grinding other players until they are out. But where is the fun in that? When a player is out they sit on the sidelines and watch others play. Why play a board game with friends when the goal of the game is to stop others from playing? A game with elimination probably shouldn't go on longer than 15 minutes after the first elimination. At least in a game like Clue, by the time players are getting eliminated, most should have a pretty good idea who the killer was, so you are in end game.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> House rules aren't the worse. The worst is people who think they are great Monopoly players. There are a few things you can do to make your luck go a little further but the best Monopoly strategy is being the banker and cheating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you would rather the government decide which food you eat, and what house you live in? 

No, but if the price of food went from 10% of my income to 30% of my income, I'm not going to sit back and think it's all for the best because 'free markets'. I'm going to ask why did this happen and why was it allowed to happen. 

How would you react if you found out that the reason you have to spend all your money on food now was because some rich people from different cities or countries were buying all the food and then only eating 2 out of 52 pieces they bought a year or sometimes not at all. Or if rich people were buying it because they know everyone needs food and if they wait until people are really hungry they will be forced to pay more for it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can guarantee no on will care. Netflix is going through huge growth right now and by the time you finish your show, they probably won't correlate the two.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People need things like houses and healthcare and food and water. Should these really be things that are bought and sold for maximum profit? Or should they be considered a social need and treated as such? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Netflix Originals used to be gold standard watches. Then they had the Adam Sandler deal and it started going downhill. Even their TV shows aren't all that great anymore. For every Stranger Things or Better Call Saul, you have two or three Hemlock Grove's and 13 Reason's Why. Don't get me started on The OA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Wouldn't it be the same film with a different language setting?  I've noticed some films and shows have dual audio, but they don't appear as two different shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new system is to help with recommendations. I don't particularly think that any of the Resident Evil movies deserve more than three stars but I will still watch them. I'm an atheist but I like watching Christian movies for their smaltzy reality and morals but God's Not Dead will and Heaven is Real will never get better than a single star. Good, thumbs up; watchable, thumbs up; bad and watchable, thumbs up. Anything you don't want to watch, thumbs down.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a letterboxd account then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it leads to situations where only super wealthy people and retirees can live in cities and you need to start busing in baristas from the suburbs or rural areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 13:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be related to or friends with the head of the hospital. Worked for an Aussie friend of mine. Was under the knife in less than 48 hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More restrictive laws won't stop people drink driving 

That's not the fucking point of laws. Laws against stealing and murder haven't made those issues obsolete. Should we get rid of them? The law is there to punish people when they are caught doing shit like drink driving. It is a deterrent for some, but it is mostly so there is actual recourse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way the law is written though says you an only go the limit if it is safe to do so. So technically if the conditions are wet you can be caught speeding by going 80 on an 80km/h road because you were suppose to adjust. Same for these roads.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which you need to learn as part of your driving test, yet OP doesn't and a lot of people probably don't. Maybe we need to retest people every 5 years or so.

There is a plan in place to review all the roads and give them a limit based on the actual road and not the road type, but I get the thinking behind this. You are driving but missed the sign, you should have a general idea what the limit is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple use to be the worse for this. They even managed to push an iPhone reference into Fanboys, a movie based before the iPhone came out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most consoles are sold at a loss or with thin margins. It discourages third parties reverse engineering the system and selling it cheaper. This means there isn't shoddy knock offs of their product on the market, which makes them have a better quality build. Also they don't need to compete with shoddy knock offs or Chinese counterfeit products. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they? Nintendo make electronic entertainment. They hire trucking companies to do haulage. Why would they move market? Let the trucking companies invest in their industry.

Sometimes companies move into a new field to help their current business but it is rare. Amazon moved into logistics because it was the way they were going. They also moved into cloud storage for similar reasons. And consumer branded goods. But they are really the exception. I think the Kerbal Space Program people moved from marketing to games to keep a programmer on staff. But these moves are rare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America has one of the best freight train infrastructures in the world. [This article](http://business.time.com/2012/07/09/us-freight-railroads/) from 2012 says 40% of intercity freight used trains. I can't imagine that going to shit in 5 years, especially considering the investment mentioned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually overtime has been pretty important historically. People would look at their take home pay and felt they could count on padding that with OT. It meant you could get a chance to save for leaner times or Christmas or holidays.

Something happened in the last 10 years though. Our blue collar and service jobs started working less or part time hours, while jobs that didn't have OT or '[banker hours](http://boingboing.net/2016/06/16/the-winners-in-todays-econom.html)', are working longer hours. So now if you work in an office you will probably find yourself doing far more salaried time that is over 39 hours a week, while people in shift work are trying to fight for extra shifts, or just something that isn't a zero hour contract. Oh and in the same time the price of C-Level or Executive Level work went up at a ridiculous rate.

Obviously Ireland isn't as bad as the US but our rights have been slipping. Obviously I would prefer everyone to get a fair base wage without overtime, but I think they have a right to argue. Imagine they looked at their means, were sensible and only bought a house and car they could afford and now they are being told even though they did everything right and planned within their means, now they might miss mortgage payments because the specific extra revenue they were told was available to them no longer is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy the bluray? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 12:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youtube runs at a loss and for some reason it pays its creators. Instagram or Twitter don't pay their most popular users. I think YouTubers are living in a golden age and don't realise how good they have it. I can't imagine in 10 years YT will still be paying users. I imagine the model will change, slowly at first but more rapidly. And there is not really anything YouTubers can do about it. Depending on income from YouTube won't last forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you serious? Literally at the very start of every movie: *A long time ago* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Wars isn't set in the future, Lord of the Rings isn't set in the past. Clearly the person who created this image hasn't got a fucking clue what they are talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So wages should be a race to the bottom?

I think a driver on a tough route could have it worse than Gardai in a nice suburb on a desk. It's all relative. 

Also, have you ever driven Irish roads? Is the average Irish driver really the standard you want to hold bus drivers to? Because most Irish drivers are shit and at least bus drivers need to retrain every so often. If you get points on your license it is not like they make you take the test again. If you complain that a bus driver is driving dangerously, corrective action will be taken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spotted the Pinkerton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Driving a bus and being responsible for 60 odd passengers doesn't take 'low training'. And their training is irrelevant. Jobs are usually priced on supply v demand, not how hard it is.

If the whole city grounds to a halt because you and your team don't show up to work, your job is probably more important than lets say if all the banks decided to shut down for the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turns out it was [Sapphire Ruby](http://bulbapedia.bulbagarden.net/wiki/Berry_glitch) on the GameBoy Advanced. 

Still cool though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They had a real sneaky patch for Pokemon Blue and Red where if you traded with a patched version of the game, the traded Pokemon would install the patch.

EDIT: [It was for Ruby Sapphire, not Red Blue](http://bulbapedia.bulbagarden.net/wiki/Berry_glitch) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DLC is planned until August of 2017. Looks like they will be working on this game a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't buy games, unless you want to play that game. Great rule. I will choose to live by it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everytime I watch that I want to visit Paris. I don't think any other movie has ever made me feel that.

Except The Lizzy McGuire Movie. I watched it drunk and booked tickets to Rome as soon as it finished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The price of living in Ireland is pretty high, while wages are relatively low in comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I'm going to have to disagree with you. Snow White does not fit in the same aesthetic as some other princesses. I can't imagine Maleficent going to the same store as Belle, I can't imagine Triton hanging out with the Prince in Cinderella. I can't imagine Sebastian the crab spending time with Iago. 

I mean I can because they do in House of Mouse and other shows often, but they still look mismatched, the way Mickey and Dumbo are but they still can inhabit the same world in Roger Rabbit type scenarios. You'll notice in the Princess toy line they use slightly different drawings and models so they fit better. There was a controversy when they made Merida more 'feminine' to fit this world.

I think we will both have to agree to disagree. I know animators are pretty limited to watch they can do with the female characters regardless, because they have to keep them '[conventionally pretty](https://every-flavored-bean.tumblr.com/post/112569173199/every-woman-in-every-disneypixar-movie-in-the)' so they all look like a wig change away from each other anyway. To be fair, the blog post contains Inside Out which I think actually had pretty decent character design.

I don't know. I guess with animation everything can be weird and wonderful so it is disappointing to see things looking the same, to me anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Batman was running a lot better after the performance update after episode 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Batman was released mostly on schedule. Walking Dead 3 released 2 episodes at launch, so if you think a month or a month and a half between episodes, they are still on track. They could have just sat on episode 2 for a month and a half I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because you are only looking at it from your own perspective. Sure you just want to play it all at once. That's a single perspective.

From Telltale's perspective they have a longer development time, early episodes fund later episodes, they can work on a story longer, they can segment the episodes into teams when working on multiple games. They can take player feedback and incorporate it.

Some of the reasons for episodes don't benefit Telltale now they are a bigger studio, but Jurassic Park was released all at once and is considered one of their weaker games. I don't think The Walking Dead would have all they hype it did if it was released as one big entry into the series. Also episodes kinda work for the games they release. Story heavy games that are mostly people talking can be fatiguing. They would be hard to play in 3 hour bursts. Making games the length of a movie works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 10:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's libellous. Of course it is up to you to talk to a legal professional if you want to peruse it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 10:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, people want to shout compo culture when in fact there are plenty of legitimate claims. If a security guard is grabbing you and shouting at you that is completely legit reason for compensation if you have done nothing wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 10:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Well no one is sure, but after mention of North Korea Sony ran with it and made The Interview a movie people wanted to see. It was most likely former staff.](https://www.vice.com/en_nz/article/who-hacked-sony-pictures-two-years-later-no-ones-really-sure) And very unlikely it was DPRK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say most of the human characters in Big Hero 6 and Moana (with the exception of the hero himself) would easily sit alongside Elsa without looking like they stick out.

Pixar is different and hasn't quite fallen into the sameness trap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well fuck. I wish I could choose which taxes and public services I got to pay for too. But I don't, only multinational companies get to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually that is the exact problem. Supposedly they want all the characters to look somewhat similar because they want to do cross promotional princess stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are essentially charging us for owning a car

They are essentially charging us for buying thing

They are essentially charging us for working

They are essentially charging us for other people getting sick

...I could go on. Welcome to living in a first world nation. You get charged for public services, sometimes through income, sometimes through VAT sometimes through paying for shit you don't use because people see it as a plus benefit to society. You know there are people who will never go to Newgrange or Phoenix Park but the OPW still gets a slice of their tax pie. If you don't like how it is run, you get to vote on it. It's slow and shitty and doesn't always work but no one has come up with a better democracy yet, so you are stuck with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. And how does a license fee in any way infringe on neutrality? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 13:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Google or Netflix providing a service for Irish people specifically and operating under a government remit of the type of content they provide?

Just stop. RTE have existed for decades and for most of its history it has been in the position where almost all households have been required to pay a license, even if that household exclusively watched BBC or videos or DVDs or played Playstation. 

In recent years they moved the content online and despite broadening their content availability, they didn't change the license fee requirements. Maybe they should have to include people with broadband speeds over a certain speed. Whatever. Now they are finally catching up with the change they made to availability so that the license fee, which has always existed, finally covers their new availability model.

You can rant on and on about Google or Netflix or Net Neutrality (by the way, you need to look up what that means again, because net neutrality is about favouring certain traffic over other, nothing to do with taxation) but Google and Netflix aren't public services. You pay tax on roads you don't use, services you don't use and some goes to counties you have never visited. When Google start doing things specifically for the good of the Irish people they they can charge me. Our government already gives them huge tax breaks for 'job creation' so in a way we are paying for them.

Nothing has really changed in how RTE collect the license. If anything they fucked up by putting their content online without saying that people still need to pay for it. Probably because they were under the assumption that most households with broadband also had a TV and license anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course you can, but why would you without a receiver i.e. a TV. The TV is capable of picking up RTE, whether you want it to or not. Like your laptop. It's not a huge concept to get your head around. There has never been an excemption for people who just don't watch RTE. Now they have added a new way to access RTE (quality aside) why would people who don't use the RTE player be exempt?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RTE should fund only the thing I like.

Seriously, I agree that most of the content on RTE is not to my taste, but I also like the idea of seeing serializied content starring Irish actors and using Irish writing talent, film crew, etc.

You are looking through a demographic lens. RTE doesn't do much for content for the 18 - 35 demo, which also happens to be the most tech savvy users who know how to get content elsewhere. RTE needs a shake up. Dropping it all together is a mistake and could kill a large portion of the Irish Arts industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 11:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While Disney designs are getting boring. They are sticking to a simple aesthetic so every character looks normal next to each other. Elsa could easily hang out with the Tangled characters and not look strange, but put Aladdin next to Cruella DeVil and you can tell they are from different movies. The worst aspect is that this is moving into other studios. Even though it is a different studio, and time, [these characters from the Little Prince](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/d5/d5/ca/d5d5ca2b37f841f32fdf505cd7dfb9f7.jpg) could easily hang around Avondale and look normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about instead of complaining when people get their day in court, councils stop doing shit that could get them sued? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TVs, monitors and laptops are still sold on inch sizes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a tv, a satellite dish and a subscription service and you never even tuned the rte stations in, you would still need to pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well before the excuse was that there are no caveman living n ireland. The will assume every house has one. Even the smaller laptops are 12 inches. Gonna be hard to escape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like water charges.... Oh wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have. And it explains why the first Death Star has the flaw. It doesn't explain why did they build two more without fixing it.

It also brings up other questions. When they discover that there is a potential weakness Vader and Tarkin talk about how they don't want to use a weapon that could be used against them. But then they do anyone and act like they aren't aware of the potential flaw.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
