<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2714</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Both arms tonight, I'm too fucking stressed to live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 03:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 03:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been on Reddit for 3 years, I've been here first :P  
Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 03:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ I'm 21 and I still fucking cut myself haha I'd love to finally fucking die  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some common household objects that people have used to committed suicide with </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 03:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this on 2meilr4meirl and haha true I ain't even trying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 03:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 03:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I see. Thanks for explaining, I hope things are better now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 03:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How an earth can you pierce your heart with that?  
Wouldn't it stop like at the ribs or muscle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 20:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep,  they physically itch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 10:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True,  my arms usally get really itchy though  so I'm not sure what to do about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 10:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was quite helpful,  he's very thoughtful and it was a bit hard to start of with but when I started I just kept getting more ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's very supportive. 
I still have the urge though and I don't know if it's going to go away but it's a lot less strong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not gonna lie, my arms are still really itchy but I don't want to do it nearly as much and it has helped, but I don't know if it's going to completely help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My boyfriend got me a colouring book to see if it would help with my urges to cut this is what I done. It calmed me down but I still have the urge to do it but not as much </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does it feel like to die? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 14:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in last thoughts,  what happens like moments before ect... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 14:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey what was your thoughts leading up to it?
What do you think happens when we die? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this song.
My favorite version is by a band called Pallbearer,  they are a funeral doom metal band. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do suicidal people get up the courage to do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like do they do anything beforehand or do they do it even when a little bi.t scared? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 18:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha just got into lesson at that point  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got overwhelmed, most likely gonna do it again today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 17:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do this graze hurt more over time then my cuts do  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 12:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god...OH GOD.
That's only been around for me for the last couple of years,  getting pretty bad but I can't imagine living with this for that long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even when one of my parents will next has an appointment just to let them know?  
Hmm I'll look into it, do you think they will ask about my mental health if they do see? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have to go to the Doctor on the 22nd of Nov for The Implant, but I have fresh cuts on my arm from self-harm, used to be in the mental health services and am not willing to go back, but I do want to know what they are likely to say. (UK) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what they are going to say. Both arms too, but they arent bad at all, just a few. You can see in my post history. It doesn't help that the Doctor rang me a week ago to see how my mental health was as the Police Safeguarding Team sent him a letter to let them know about some of the stuff they found on my phone, which was stuff like self-harm and suicide methods.  
I straight up lied to the Doctor when he asked how it was. I said that I was interested in it and that I was fine, hardly had any thoughts like that and weren't planning to harm myself. Luckily they are only superficial, but there's no way I want to go back to therapy. I know I'm gonna do it again before I see the Doctor though. What are they gonna say?
Also, can they tell my parents? I'm 21 but I still live with them and we have the same Doctor Surgery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have to go to the Doctors on the 22nd of November for the Implant, but I have fresh cuts from the last few days. (UK) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what they are going to say. Both arms too, but they arent bad at all, just a few. You can see in my post history.
It doesn't help that the Doctor rang me a week ago to see how my mental health was as the Police Safeguarding Team sent him a letter to let them know about some of the stuff they found on my phone, which was stuff like self-harm and suicide methods.
I straight up lied to the Doctor when he asked how it was. I said that I was interested in it and that I was fine, hardly had any thoughts like that and weren't planning to harm myself.
Luckily they are only superficial,  but there's no way I want to go back to therapy. I know I'm gonna do it again before I see the Doctor though. 
What are they gonna say?
Also, can they tell my parents? 
I'm 21 but I still live with them and we have the same Doctor Surgery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 17:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure,  I think it's because it's superficial and there's a quite a few in the same place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 17:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listening to it for hours and when I'm not supposed to like in lessons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 12:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah ok, I'm in the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Few on right arm. Can see a couple of old scars too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 12:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 12:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You UK or US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 08:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, what do you mean by low frustration tolerance?  
I do get a bit frustrated by small things, when sometimes I'm ok with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 07:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only 21, but my longest has been a year but he was extremely controlling.  
This relationship I'm in is only 8 months, but we're still going incredibly strong and he's very supportive of me, and we are not breaking up anytime soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 07:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's staying, it was just a talk on how my self-harm affects him, he said he's not coping with it that well and it does hurt, but he did know about this in College and he's willing to help.  
He's got me a colouring book and some pencils I can use when I want to, and he also said he complety understands if it doesn't work, but he wants me to at least try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 07:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wrong, he said yesterday that he never wants to leave me, he could tell I was getting way too stressed about losing him.  
It was a chat about what I can do so my self-harm doesn't get too bad and how I can stop, but thank you for the help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 07:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scratching, picking at stuff, not eating a lot, and music.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think my boyfriend wants to leave me and I'm freaking the fuck out, I can't handle this at all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 10:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We met in College and we started dating 8 months ago. I was doing well at the start of the relationship but my mental health has gotten worse, I've started self harming again, for a couple weeks a couple months back, stopped and I just started up again on Friday. 
I can get a bit snappy or moody with him and take things the wrong way but I'm always fine within a few minutes and I do take responsibility for my action.
I've never tried to manipulate him at all, we've never had a proper argument,  but he has been trying to get me back to therapy for months.
The thing is, I'm very stubborn and I don't take care of myself when it comes to my mental health. I've been making excuses to why I don't need therapy or why I don't have the time. Also the last time I started cutting around the same time I tried to kill myself by jumping up the Clifton Suspension Bridge but got pulled back, so he's now worried that's going to happen again, but I hardly have those thoughts anymore and self-harm helps loads.  
He's said that it's a bit draining which that I can appreciate, he said yesterday he doesn't want to leave me and he said a few weeks ago that he wants to spend the rest of his life with me, but this morning he sent me a text saying that we need to talk about everything. I'm seeing him in less then an hour, he sent me that a couple hours ago but I only relised what that meant a few minutes ago, and now I'm terrified about what's going to happen, I've been having such bad chest pains.
He's also been texting back shorter replies then usal for the last few days so I kept on asking if everything was OK,  he said it is he's just having also hard time coping with this but I think I fucked up everything again, I really don't want to lose him,  there is no way I can handle that at all, that might be the last straw.
Sorry for babbling but I'm freaking out and thanks for reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got a blade now. Few on arm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 00:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relapsing again. And has anyone else thought it's more painful when you relapse compared to last time you did it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 00:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'm doing it again, on my arms because it's cold. 
I did do it a couple months ago for a bit but stopped, longest I've ever gone was before that for 10 months.  But it's so much more painful then I rerember. OUCH.  
My boyfriend is going to be so mad though, he knew about this before we started dating (8 months) But I didn't think I'd end up here again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I listen to a lot of Metal, and I've discovered a few new bands.  
I've been listening to Mastadon and Paradise Lost recently, with some Chimaira. I've also heard of Twelve Foot Ninja a couple of days ago, they seem pretty good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 14:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been in a relationship for 8 months, it's a great one, but he says I tend to drain him by not getting help and he'd rather I not self-harm, but he said that he's not going to tell me to stop either.  
He does think I also need therapy ASAP.
I do tend to get a bit too snappy or moody too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how would suicide by rubber bands work in this case? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 08:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/9301230  
I'm unsure on how it would of worked or carried out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm more into Black Metal,  but Necrophagist and Today Is The Day are good bands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh? 
I've never gone that deep with it but I prefer doing more then deep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I'm gonna start with sharpners again but I've never gone to razors  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest I've been harming myself in various ways on and off since I was 12, with cutting being the most satisfying. I'm 21 now,  I've posted here with cuts before, and I'd rather not go back to therapy again.
Luckily I've never gone that deep, and really only with sharper blades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More scratches, no blade as of yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 13:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So fellow emos, if you had a metal sharpener but no screwdriver, what the plans be for you? :3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 12:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 08:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. I like cutting, it's fun, yes it helps me deal with stress, but I do really like the feel of it and the blood drips afterwards, it's good.  
And it's cold now, so I can now do it on my arm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scratches on arm with pin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 12:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red mark caused by scratching with key </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 08:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not, but my boyfriend plays it a lot, like nearly every day.  
We were on the collections screen and we were playing a game where I had to choose a random champion and he had to tell me the name and damage.  
He got everyone right, apart from Zacs Damage, but he says that doesn't count cause it's a hybrid, and I keep annoying him but saying he got it wrong xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 19:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, I think the word is Condition of the building, some of ours are still quite old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 11:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, UK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 12:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always come back here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 12:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UK here too, I'd love for guns to be legal here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this on the bus to College. Our kinda room  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 02:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 23:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the same way. Me and my sister nearly got hit by a rock, and my siter freaked out and I was more like "Meh."  
There has been many times where I've walked into traffic or been in any danger, and I've not reacted or someone has had to do or say something.  It's usally me walking into the road when a car is too close and my boyfriend stopping me or pulling me back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 20:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this stops me from crying full-stop, have a drink, I tend to down one. I don't have any other advice apart from that, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 10:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm one. No-one knows what I go through, I keep it all inside.  
The only noticeable symptom is mood swings and my lack of appetite, and the fact I sometimes snap a little.  
My parents think I'm fine, my boyfriend has a glimpse but he doesn't know how it goes, and the people at College don't have a clue, but they do know I can be a bit moody at times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 10:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I'm terrible at making descions. Takes me like 10 minutes to decided what to eat for or where I want to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 08:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we should be allowed to, but it depends on the person who's asking, as in severity on thought, if they're just asking because they are curious, how long they've had them, have they sought help ect.
Oh, and if there is any hope of them ever getting better, cause there's fuck all for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 08:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 08:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...morbid curiosity. :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 09:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But how do people put pressure on the carotid?  
Is it to do with the knot or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 21:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, what's an air embolism?  
What does that have to do with this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does hanging compress the carotid artery and how do people do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 08:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 09:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could keep at it, I just get a bit frustrated.  Could be a good suprise and to be honest that depends on my mood. Like I could be talkative but other times I just need some alone time or I can be unsociable. Luckily people know that and they respect it, they just make sure I'm ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 08:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest I used to love Fallout 3, it was my favorite game.
I've tried playing it before, but I can't get the controls right, I've always been a console gamer.  
To be honest, I do think I'm getting worse again. The thing is, I don't realize I am until it suddenly hits me that I was not like this a few weeks ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 08:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you re-direct your thinking?  
If I'm worried, it will not go away.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 21:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just checked his work schedule,  I actually forgot he was working tonight, oops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to keep myself from thinking irrationality/overthinking and worrying when my boyfriend is taking ages to reply? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 21:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to overthink stuff a lot, I always see the worst in a situation and I percive things happening when they are actually not. Sometimes my boyfriend plays a lot of online games (League) and they can carry on for a while, like around an hour.
There are times where he can take more then that to reply and I can start overthinking stuff and today is one of those times, but I'm worried with the more texts I send the more I'm pushing him away, I'm already terrified as I am as losing him as I already am.
Can anyone help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends how long the solution would take and how likely the problem is to come back.  
I have given up on getting better, I was in therapy for 4 and a half years and I had a LOT of up and downs.  
Got discharged...good health lasted for few months...then went downhill. And I'm now going downhill but I don't think therapy will help again, and I have no time anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people do not understand. Hence the reason I never, ever say anything about my mental health. I only post about it on Reddit.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 08:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend made me a powerpoint of all the stuff we did together for my birthday. I tend to watch that, or make a list of everything we did together, or send him a couple texts on how much he means to me. I've never brought this up either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 16:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes no sense  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 09:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I get it, so this isn't dangerous in the slightest?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 09:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean no messing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do people only kill themselves using a ligature/garrote? Don't they need to suspend themselves of something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 09:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 01:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I eat at the very most most of one meal and a couple snacks.  
I'd eat even less but then my parents would ask.  
I've never had a decent appetite even when I was a youngster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 01:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thanks :)  
What do you mean by grounded out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this behind an unlocked cupboard at College, is this safe? Can anyone be fatally electrocuted by this and how? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 01:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 01:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curios, do you mean a plug like one you plug in or a socket?  
What plug was it?  
How did you do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 01:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about in the UK? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 13:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds interesting, there's another one I've heard which is good, called Nembutal.  
Say it was OTC meds, or various prescription meds, or even the 2 mixed together.  
Or even Eucalyptus oil by itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is right, it IS fucked. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 13:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If someone took an overdose but took some anti-emetic, what would happen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 12:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would they still throw up or would they just feel unbearably sick?  
Effects? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 12:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the same so I don't talk about it.  
Or I'm scared of pushing people away.  
I thought it's better to hide it anyway, my family can get over-protective with some stuff and there's stuff I won't tell my boyfriend because I don't want to worry him about this stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's getting to the point where I have no motivation to take care of myself and other thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 12:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My eating has always been off, but it's gotten worse. I only eat like at the most 3/4 of a full meal a day, with maybe a little snack.  
My family thinks my eating is doing alright, but they don't know how little I eat, they think I eat at College. I have lost some weight, but they have noticed my jeans are getting baggy.
I don't want to shower or get dressed or wash or brush my teeth.  
My sleeping isn't that good, but that could also be part of my PTSD. I also have BPD but I thought this was more suitable here. I can't concentrate enough in College.  
I don't socialize that much, but I do have people that let me when I want to.   
I'm thinking of suicide every day, it can vary in how intense it is.  
Luckily I know how to act so no-one gets worried.  
I don't actually get depressed that often, I more get frustrated or upset, but there are times where I cant reconigze or know what I'm feeling, or if I feel at all. Times where I feel numb, or nothing feels weird.
I'm meant to get my ID sorted so I can start drinking, so it can help. But I can't even get that sorted.  
I'm not normal, I don't do anything right, I don't really have any actual friends. People would do so much better without me.  
I have no purpose, and it would be better if I wasn't here, but I'm too fearful to go through with it just yet. Hopefully soon.  
I can't take this again, I hate myself so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 09:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/watchpeopledie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 09:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much every day, at least once a day.  
Also you might like /r/sanctionedsuicide  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are most hangings so successful? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 01:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 00:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be VERY inconspicuos.  
Ah I see the problem, I'll look into this.  
Very easy to hide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 23:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm interesting,  how many bands and what strengths? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 09:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really, how does it work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to stop thinking my boyfriend is going to leave me when there's no evidence of it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 09:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how to stop this, but I'm getting worried my boyfriend is getting sick and tired of me.
I KNOW he's not, for christ sakes we've just opened up a joint bank account, but I can't stop myself from thinking like he is and I don't want to mention it to him in case he thinks he's doing something wrong or that I'm being too clingy.
Help please?

Oh, and there's the very few times I've split while thinking about him, it hardly happens but it's really annoying.
Thanks for reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can the carotid artery be compressed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 20:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, the most effective way to do it and if they are by themselves ect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 01:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was FUMING. Nope, she was gonna call the Police but I ran away, I saw her talking to the guys in the toll booth though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 00:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She grabbed me and pulled me of a barrier of a bridge I was climbing.  
I was just wondering what would count and what wouldn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 23:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been times where I've expected to die, but the last time I got stopped by that stranger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, what's your defition of a suicide attempt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gone to places with the intent of dying but I've not done it because of fear, and being stopped a couple times.
I've tried hanging myself,  but I stopped because I can't either do it because of fear or I can't pass out.
I'm not sure what the definition would be, what do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can i find links to suicide hanging videos, preferably where they don't use rope, but any material including rope is good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the most common things used to hang yourself with besides rope? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 22:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 11:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here, even in lessons, I just hide it behind my hair and in my hoodie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 08:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And another thing,  shoelaces would be too short. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can someone hang themselves with a shoelace, wouldn't it break? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 08:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't see how people could die with a shoelace, they are far too weak. (The shoelace, that is.)  
Wouldn't it break?  
I don't see how it could compress anything either or put enough pressure on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 12:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to keep it to myself.
I'll mention it in passing to my boyfriend and we've had a couple of chats about it but I keep it to myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This rap song describes how hard it is to work and do it for a 40+ years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 10:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 15:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mind explaining the method of blood letting?
Like what you use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 11:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how painful that would be if swallowed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The lunacy of the modern working life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 23:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if I'll get appointments, I have to miss a whole day of College as it's an hour coach drive, but at the very least, an hour and half with public transport.  
I'd rather do my work and find my own way with dealing then missing work and getting left behind and failing the course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I have no time for therapy as I'm at College 5 days a week, my bus is at 8 and I get back at 6.

3rd comment saying this.  
I have tried that, it's not that effective for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 16:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why it happens, I hate it when it does.  
I just really hope it will never happen in front of someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 15:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot to mention, I have no time for therapy as I'm at College 5 days a week, my bus is at 8 and I get back at 6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 15:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been doing it off and off for many years, and my family has found out I used to do it last year and made me stop cold turkey.  
I started again for a few weeks but I'm too scared of geting caught so I'm figuring out different ways, and I have no time for therapy as I'm at College 5 days a week, my bus is at 8 and I get back at 6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 15:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm, I'll try it. And cutting is my favorite but I'm too scared of getting caught  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else has those times where you are just really upset and crying for no reason? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 01:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had that today, for the past 3 hours. On and off.  
The thing is, I have NO IDEA why.  
It's so frustrating and I wish I knew why.   
Oh yeah, and I keep getting more panicky and my physical health has started going downhill too. 
And I just want to send a massive message to my boyfriend saying sorry for being this fucked up but I have no idea what he would say.  
Sorry and thanks for reading.
Edit: I've also lost so much weight, I've lost a stone and a half in like 4 months, when it took me a year to put on a stone. I weigh less from when I got discharged from hospital. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 01:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do mean physical, and I'd rather do this my own way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any "invisible" or a method which doesn't leave marks form of self-harm? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 09:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's illegal here.
I always have a sharpener blade on me but I don't want to be done for assault as there's no proof he did those things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm near you, but my College doesn't have counselling anymore, we have PLAs instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the guys that did something to me is at the same College. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 14:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea what to do, I can't really stand up for myself. When I've resisted to people before they have just gotten really violent.  
He's seen me, he's waved to me. The next time I saw him, I sped-walked away.  
I've sorta shut down and I feel tense, as in my muscles are all tense, and I keep looking over my shoulder. I didn't think he'd be back. I just feel really numb, but I have a feeling this isn't going to do me any good.  
I know he has some sort of learning disabilty, so he might not even understand even if someone tried to explain it to him.  
 I don't really have any friends that I could hang around with, but I could just go up in the LRC for my lunch, I don't eat lunch anyway, and music helps me loads. 
This is just me getting my thoughts into order, they are a bit racy at the moment. And I know my sleeping is going to get worse now.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 14:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I'm not pregnant,  I was just interested. 
Thanks for the info  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 09:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I freaking HATE funerals.  
They are a waste of time, just a reminder that the person is dead and a whole service to "celebrate" their life.  
What if they were a terrible person?  
What if they didn't want their life celebrated?  
I'd rather be cremated, funerals are expensive and I would't want one.  
I do like graveyards, they just seem so peaceful and relaxing.   
And if I did have a funeral, I'd want this song to play as one big last FUCK YOU to myself.  
[Bobaflex - I'm Glad Your Dead]( https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4XO-8SmOQ84)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 08:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been wanting to try it, how is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A tiny little scratch on arm. I know I've been doing it on my legs, but I'm getting desperate to do it on my arms again as it feels way better but it's still hot, and I nearly did it but stopped myself. Can see very faint scars. Sorry for babbling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 00:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
