<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1121</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks like something out of Space Quest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Woke Alf!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the point is that every time a muslim commits a crime, the whole religion is blamed, even if it wasnt a religiously motivated crime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a VHS player was typically called a VCR.


how quickly we forget </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bradley whitford looks so old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://thedigitalbits.com/columns/my-two-cents/022417-0100

In addition, 20th Century Foxs Senior Vice President of Library and Technical Services, Shawn Belston, was also on hand at the Wexner event last night. He confirmed that all of the trims removed from the original cut negative (in the mid-1990s, to create the SEs) still exist as well. (Thanks to Bits reader Chuck P., who attended this event, for his firsthand report.) So what does all that mean to you?
In summary: When George Lucas says that the original Star Wars no longer exists, its a little like Obi-Wan telling Luke that Darth Vader killed his father; hes speaking truthfully from a certain point of view. From any other point of view, however, its silliness. The point is, while it is essentially technically true that the 77 cut negative no longer exists in its original state, it is also technically true that it could be re-built if so desired. All of the needed film elements still survive and have been preserved

EDIT

basically, 20th century fox says that all of the removed bits of star wars remain in their original form in their vault, or something to that extent.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mean, I doubt he went and physically edited the original negatives of the film.  that'd be a very impractical way to do things.  SOME of the SE changes are irreversible due to damage to the film (some of the shifting in shot composition is to crop out damage to the negatives), and its likely that a restored version would have to digitally replicate some of the transitions, possibly re composite the effects...but the original negative still exists, it is still restorable   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have found the current season of the Simpsons to be a lot better (pretty good overall), but for sure it's lacking in its heart still. 

They still try to make it about moral choices? But cram too many plot lines and gags per episode for it to work. The best new episodes are ones with more limited focus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We produce practical, factual content to delegitimize Trumps presidency, embolden the opposition, and empower the majority of Americans to fight."

how is that any different than breitbart over the past 8 years?

factual, practical content

that alone makes it better than breitbart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shareblue is a legitimate website. I mean, its biased and not a good news source for unbiased news, but its not the conspiracy trumptards think it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which foreign policy experts?

Bombing syria without congressional approval is certainly bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spiderman, X-Men, and the dark knight trilogies have all showed that superhero movies dont all need to have the same tone, and can differ stylistically while all being superhero movies.  GoTG, even though its a bit more hip than other marvel movies, ultimately falls back to the same feel of the avengers by the third act (first two acts are great). The movies are all a little different in the MCU, but mostly the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it looks like it is good stylistically, with good humor.  Unfortunatly, it looks super CGI (as in, it looks like a cartoon), which is not a look i love in live action films.  The characters sometimes have that weird weightlessness that films get when they overuse CGI. 

But it sure looks better than the last thor movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they couldnt really do CGI in 1977. wireframes sure, but not full fleshed. there was a plan to do a stop motion jabba, but they had to abandon the plan due to the cost of doing so (that and the scene sucks and slows down the plot needlessly)

EDIT
for reference, the scene was included in the comic book version of ANH, but there was no description of jabba (since they lacked the money to do the stop motion). He looked like [this](http://cdn2us.denofgeek.com/sites/denofgeekus/files/styles/article_width/public/swjabba.jpg?itok=5wwk2QhS) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...?

the jabba scene isnt in the theatrical release at all. It was restored in 1997. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I'd like it to be restored and included in future releases, but mainly just because I dislike the color correction and that one jabba the hut scene </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im sure the printing press is the teacher's lounge printer the morning of the test </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the worst star wars movie of all

no.

Look, there is a lot of room for improvement, sure. There are aspects of the way Lucas did things in the OT and the PT that I miss in the new movies.

But the cinematography and dialogue in TFA blow episodes one and two out of the water, and definitly give episodes 3 and 6 a run for their money.  The acting and directing of individual scenes is better than in the PT, even the pretty good Episode 3.

How the fuck is Leia still in a rebel alliance? They won the war she is the government, but Disney's marketing team realized rebel characters are more popular than government ones.

yeah, thats poorly explained (and requires some combo of books to get a better idea to the political climate of ther galaxy) but it isnt like rebellions that topple huge empires do so without a ton if messy stuff for decades. It isnt explained well, but it isnt far fetched either. 

they gotta phase out all the old white men from the original cast because thats what Disney is all about.

i mean, the movie isnt about the old characters. its about new characters. 

Marvel and Disney's message is anti-western and anti-white

oh grow the fuck up and get out of my fandom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats something only we care about, no one outside of the most dedicated star wars fans care  (and the despecialized editions are good enough for most people who DO care) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sure, but all were critically acclaimed, which should count for something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mean, whole foods has a huge bread and bakery section, which are always packed with people buying bread. so while they definitly push GF things like the whole 30, they clearly profit off of gluten lovers.

but still, you have a good point. breads and pasta definitly make me bloat, and i sometimes get a little sick from eating too much of that kind of shit, but I have a celiac friend and its nothing like what he gets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I oppose the death penalty, except for people who use their phones in a theater.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> texting during the movie is pretty low, you should be ashamed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Wars wasnt great due to its FX alone. It was the marriage of genres, making a movie that felt (at the time) both fresh and nostalgic, that made it such an icon.  If it had just been the FX, it would have died in time, like other blockbusters.

That said, the saga is in trouble if moving forward is all about nostalgia and appeasing fans, and not looking at what actually made the original so good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Han and Leia know (according to bloodlines), but it wasnt common knowledge beyond that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For as much as I didnt care for the way he acted in the movies (or perhaps the way he was told to act...), he has great screen presence in the role, and is able to nonverbally convey a lot about Anakin. I like the scene in Episode 2 where he tells padme he has to go to tatooine, and him returning with his mothers body. I like him looking out the jedi temple windows in episode 3, I like when he finds out padme is pregnant.  All in all, Episode 3 is pretty good from his end.


Him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem confused </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 04:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My weekends don't cost the taxpayers millions of dollars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 04:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is literally doing something he said he wouldn't do. He is doing something he criticized Obama for doing, and he's doing it every weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I support our country. Hence why I don't support trump  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats a bad idea. For one, political situations change all the time.  You could get into office saying "i wont vote for war", but change your mind if international circumstances change.  You could promise one thing, but gain new insights once briefed on the issues by other officials. 

FORCING politicians to keep their promises means they cant react to the ever changing political climates in the country.  it could also limit a politicians ability to negotiate with other parties and deal with incremental changes. 

Imagine a republican promising to cut x amount of the budget.  then imagine that there is some kind of disaster requiring funds. you would have him forced to still cut the money he promised under different circumstances </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can't (literally) touch/measure a soul, but you can measure consciousness (to some extent), and I think a lot of people would define it that way.  We can be fairly sure that a tree inst worried when it sees a guy with an ax (not that a tree can see, but you know what I mean). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rachael (blade runner) as a german expressionist painting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a lot of places pride themselves on absurd bloody marys, but this one is over the top (and impractical).  So, I dont think anyone could argue that this is a common bloody mary.  Cheese curds, bacon, pickles, olives, sausage, several inches of shit is "normal" for an absurd bloody mary.  This is not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who needs coffee when you start every day with a healthy dose of the tragedy of Darth Plagueis the Wise.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1). Flavor. the flavor of potato chips is very salty. overwhelmingly so, compared to a regular tortilla chip.  Potato chips would not be conducive to guacamole or a lot of salsas, because they would overwhelm it with salt.  A potato chip is best enjoyed with either a mild dipping sauce or none at all.  If you have a good dip, it will be wasted by the potato chip.  Tortilla chips taste mild (like a tortilla does) but generally hold up to dips without overwhelming anything

2). texture. A potato chip is weird and thin, and will get soggy with a wet salsa.  I am not sure where you are getting that they are sturdier. compare Lays to your average tortilla chip.  Even thin tortilla chips are more solid than a potato chip, and will do better when dipped in salsa.  Most tortilla chips are rather thick and will do better with good amounts of guac compared to the potato chip

3). nachos.  I dont want to imagine potato chip nachos. the tortilla chip is more versatile due to its sturdiness and more mild flavor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait guys I messed up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats have been calling for military action against Assad since 2013

Its worth noting that its democrat officials calling for those actions, and its far less popular in their voting base </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They support Muslims for the way they treat women

We support people's right to practice any religion in peace, including islam.  Where have you seen liberals supporting the right for anyone to treat women poorly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> were a lot of liberals saying that we needed to take down assad without first getting congressional approval for an act of war?  Or that we can't investigate it first.

Most liberals I know (myself included) have mixed feelings on the subject, where it seems pretty obvious that Assad should not be in charge, and is a bad guy, but are worried about further destabilization in the region, and dont want to be involved in a full scale war without a real good plan on how to resolve it.  Remember the last time we went to war with a country who our leaders and news insisted was committing crimes against his own people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unless this was a well coordinated ploy to get us to THINK he isnt a russian puppet...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if Trump, Mattis, McMaster, Russia, etc all signed off on this then it was for good reason

People said the same thing with WMDs in Iraq, but that turned out to be a load of shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's absurd is thinking a well bred dog should cost $150

and thats why buying from a breeder is not a superior way to purchase dogs.  

vet insurance

oh arent we fancy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well they are all fantastic, so if there are any specific collections you recommend, I'd love to hear it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it baffles me how everyone is against Pam on that decision. they had 2 kids, not a ton in savings, and Jim did not take her desire to not move to Philly into account. Had jim lost his job, or if the money they sank into athlead had resulted in nothing, it would have been really bad for their family.  Forming a startup with 2 young kids (their oldest was what, 4?) is a hugeeee risk, and I cant blame pam for not being gung ho about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> disasters is a lot of fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you have a list of assets you were using?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm baffled that clerks got NC17 initially -_-

In general, the MPAA dislikes movies with swear words and movies with LGBT themes, so unfortunately i am not surprised.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> since its all owned by disney, Im bummed they didnt use the actual star wars soundtrack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah, I like this better than the older ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats absurd. My family's first dog was ~$100 (approx $150 in 2017 dollars), mostly covering vet fees from the pet store. They had good jobs at the time, but three young kids.  By demanding a price so high, you are limiting it away from anyone on the lower income end of the scale, especially those with children. 

I mean, dog food, dog supplies,etc all add up, but are (or can be) affordable. vet visits can be a pain in the ass, but wont break your wallet unless your pet really got hurt (which is hopefully fairly rare).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it would also significantly increase the cost of buying a dog to require it to come from a breeder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sure. He did what many people considered impossible, and the movie IS good.

But he didnt bring anything new to the material, no deeper understanding or symbolism or further commentary.  He presented it exactly as it was in the graphic novel (except with sex scenes that drag on, slow motion fighting, and a different ending).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> love is like a virus

thats a bad analogy but okay it works

flying shoe is like a virus

that analogy does not work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My vague understanding is that full breeds tend to be less healthy overall than your average mixed breed, and few breeders are looking to sell mutts. 

Without shelters, we would have to expect that every single person would be neutering their dogs.  That isnt going to happen. Most people will. Most people should. But there will always be some percentage of people who wont, and shelters and a culture of pet adoption (be it craigslist or a shelter) is important to make sure pets dont die needlessly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss being a kid and picking out a movie from the video store while ordering pizza or chinese food nextdoor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my girlfriend is from southern Illinois, and their family frequents "family video".  I mean, their internet and netflix/hulu accounts still work fine, but I personally like the ritual of it, and that they carry movies that are not on streaming services.

Also, "family" video has a much  better porn selection than netflix... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but a more talented creative team would have been able to convey the same points in a slightly shorter timeframe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, watchmen is good.  

However, it is good because the comic is good. Snyder sticks very closely to the source material, so the depth is not of his doing. In fact, it is shallow in that it seems like snyder had a surface level appreciation for the graphic novel, but due to the high quality of the source, created something quite good.

The expendables has substance if you view it as a semi parody of the kinds of movies the actors involved typically star in.  Its silly over the top fun.  The Avengers was well written pseudo serious action, but not particularly deep.  The great source of watchmen makes it deeper than either, but Snyder had little to do with that.

EDIT: if you watch watchmen, watch the directors cut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not to my knowledge. She first mentioned it after law school,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as much as the spacefight in episode 1 was just stupid, i loved the design of the ships.  really, the design of everything in episode 1 was pretty coolio </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone who's heard of it thought it was a bit odd and nobody thinks she's a Native American.

she never used her belief in her native american ancestry for personal gain, as far as I can tell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people just mean that white people, as a whole, have no distinct culture (ie, you have american culture, british culture, itallian culture, etc.)

I have heard a few fringe people argue that white people have no culture in regards to music, since most pop music is appropiated from holder african american music (many forms removed at this point).

but yeah, this is not a mainstream argument </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> things are predictable because stories are predictable. If it is well told, knowing that Luke Skywalker blows up the deathstar in the end doesnt ruin the journey there.  However, if a movie falls to cliches AND is predictable, that sucks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant find it (it was a roundtable with all of their contributors) but I will post an article showing what would have happened if the polls had been 2% different https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/what-a-difference-2-percentage-points-makes/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the data said hilary, but it said several close races were likely to go in her favor, which gave her a high chance nationally.  the polls were only off by a few points in a lot of those, but a few points was enough to skew a few states in such a way that she lost the EC.  The postmortem by 538 was pretty interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people hoping that the movie would lead to an increase in asian-american representation in cinema are free to not see it.  It wasnt my personal reason for skipping the film (bad reviews and not a ton of familiarity with the original), but you cant be mad at people for choosing to spend their money elsewhere  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I know japanese americans who care, since they never see japanese people in english language movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> while there is a $100% chance this Einstein actually encountered this, I did have a size 0 friend in college who had a lot of awkward moments with "body positivity" tumblr types who bashed size 0 women as not being real women.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where are you from?  Because for overall cost of living to be that low, itd have to be a pretty small town lacking in other things.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rent is stupid expensive

compared to a large city, rent in mke is affordable if you have a roommate.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stuck in waukesha, never going in to milwaukee?  sounds depressing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its a pity. I went a few times post remodel and loved everything about it, but it was far too expensive for me to go on a weekly, or even monthly, basis.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "virgin" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was from the podesta hack?  My memory was that it was from a Brazile-podesta email chain...


though yes, technically not Clinton being hacked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donna Brazil was interviewed by the Daily Show a few weeks back where she said that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "diversity day" is one of my favorites. I know most people kinda dislike season one compared to other seasons, but its all fantastic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but that would have meant JJ abrams watching any star wars media other than 4 and 5... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Can Pull Money From His Businesses Whenever He Wants  Without Ever Telling Us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mean, there are ways to get discounts on windows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, good meme kiddo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Biden would have given clinton a run for her money, at the very least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She didn't cheat in the primary debate.  All democratic candidates were given answers by Donna brazille. Clinton is the only one who got hacked.


It's a shame they never hacked trumps server.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any website can collect and sell data.  Wtf are you talking about.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has empire ever been shown in a regular theater? 

Art is subjective. I believe that empires unwatchable quality was the point behind the installation. But I'm not an expert on the subject. Most pieces shown as art installations are simple in technical aspects.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but it sounds like the root of the problem is bad writing, not diversity.  the comics would still be bad if they had no diversity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "empire" isnt a movie though. It isnt meant for cinema exhibition. its an art installation. It is meant for museaum exhibition. Itd be like criticizing a painting for not being like a comic book.  They are incomparable mediums  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can you give a few examples?  Most indie films tend to skew shorter (closer to 90 minutes, maybe 2 hours).

My only thoughts is that slower pieces (say, manchester by the sea) are totally different in appeal than epics.  They have more time to breathe, and can be deeper in their character study, give some time for reflection while watching, but even MBTS is just about 2.5 hours, maybe less. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marvel is suffering due to too many events, crossovers, and an increasingly convoluted storyline. They are suffering due to bad writing above all else.  Diversity isnt the reason of this bad writing, it just happens to be happening at the same time.

For example, Miles Morales was great back when it launched. great writing, great characters, great take on the world.  However, the recent stuff (such as the spidergwen crossover) is pretty lame.  

On the other hand, I recently started the most recent iteration of hawkeye, and quite like it (that likely counts as pushing diverisity, since it stars a woman in a traditional male role, and one who is a feminist as well). 

The writing would be bad, regardless of if they had a diversity agenda or not.  

it seems your issue is with the politics, not quality, of marvel comics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't like Empire because it's like the most boringest

this is no ones opinion. Its much faster paced than ANH at the very least.

Regardless, TFA could have used a little more dialogue to help set the universe. This scene runs far too long for what it says (and the dialogue just isnt great in much of it), but aspects of it should have been included. More lines about the nature the state of the universe, and the mythology of the world, would have helped immensely (think back to ANH)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we get a little bit of that in the movie, but it could have been done better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for sure, its too long and wordy for the way the movie was shot, but 3/4 of this could have worked just fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, the first transformers wasnt high art by any means, but it was a goofy, fun action movie that took itself the right level of serious vs not serious.  the second one was one of the worst movies ive ever seen in theaters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> new building opened on farwell and Greenwich (i think)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same thing to do after any breakup

drink </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bummer :(  I always liked their food, though I couldnt go much because its just out of my price range </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its great that YOU have the correct definition of an SJW (which i first saw feminists using on tumblr to bash keyboard radfems advocating death to men from behind the safety of the computer screen), but right now being anything more than slightly left of center makes you an SJW in the eyes of the internet. Saying anything in support of any minority group, you get accused of virtue signaling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess not, not if he's eating out every night. If he can limit it to 3 days a week then sure. He should be coming back with something like 3.5k every month.


My point was, people do it. It's rough, but possible if the job is the right move  (or if you just want to live in LA).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly we found a good deal. Right building at the right time. I had a friend on the block at 850 or so a month, but that's same ballpark. It was a great location, sometimes sketchy past 3am, but generally fine.

Certainly better than my last LA apartment by McArthur park -_-  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. But at 60k I think he will find something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I WAS off of Lexington (Lexington and orange). Two bedroom 750 each

Edit: 2014 - 2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rice and beans as a diet.

My rent was 750 a month in hollywood. Bills brought it up to a little under 900 total, 1000 when you count food. I walked away with a little over 1.2k a month with a call center job, more when 8 had good months . It's hard but not impossible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be fine. You'll have to save a bit to hit the standard of living you are used to? But I've seen people live in LA on. 25k/yr. Some less.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a recruiter, not 100% sure what that linkedin post is about. What I imagine it is is about dealing with subcontractors, especially in the tech field. We get a lot of resumes written by their vendor company (not the job seekers themselves), which leads to fake resumes that the candidate can't speak to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's totally relevant to the story though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> from /r/foodporn: limp, stale fries and burger on tortilla chips and a dry bun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOOGLE how to snap crakle and pop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the argument is that trump is used to working from the golf course, making deals, taking calls, etc, while obama just did it to relax.

Of course, Obama also golfed with members of congress (republicans and dems) and world leaders, so I dunno it there is any actual difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always try to think of cities I have lived in, and do some layout to see if I can emulate it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
