<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2165</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 05:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How common are people who read this much? I'm at ~30 this year (not counting rereads) and that's been sort of taxing. But for me it's probably just poor time management (video games, "platinum" age of television). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 05:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shame there! I think this has to be the best way to expand your vocabulary. Usually my phone is nearby, makes it easier. If not, I have strategic pencils in coats and drawers to jot words down for later.

This week's stars: quiddity, telos, plenipotentiary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say what you will, I'm always happy it doesn't fall into one of Toronto's main architectural categories: "brutalist concrete" or "boring-mixed-use-glass-facade". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drone-tato? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the feeling...I just replaced my S3 (2012) for an LG G4 (2015). I feel like I finally joined the club where all my photos don't look like they were taken on a potato.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely get the "like-minded" aspect. I wish TIFF's website was easier to navigate. Just give me a calendar with all your films and times and one button to buy a ticket. Blargh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 17:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it worth the 14$ for old movies at TIFF? I could see if it were an old 70mm print or something, sure, but it seems other theatres drop the price a bit when showing classics. Curious if anyone has been. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 05:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Building one store isn't the same as retrofitting 69 stations, and networking them together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 05:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're on the Spadina streetcar occasionally. Saw them catch two people without any PoP once. Doesn't seem like a pleasant job. Lot of under-the-breath cursing at them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Construction workers, period. It was only a few times over ten years, but I refused to do specific jobs with specific people because I was aware of their recreational activities that they brought to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like if the driver's can be subjected to random screenings, they will make the case all employees in the union will have to undergo it, in the interest of fairness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to think (but I could be wrong) that if I got on a bus and my driver used meth, I would be able to tell :-p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell which one of us they're calling dumb! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shouldn't no. And if you have the urge, stay to the right with your hazards on and get off at the next exit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 12:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youngstown, NY appears to be my nearest choice :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 12:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who drives this section frequently, I agree completely. Definitely have to have your head on a swivel, on both sides of the equation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 11:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do the readers the inspectors carry allow you to pay, as well? In the instance you are standing beside a broken machine when they check? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 11:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Honest Ed's pass for 2017 will have a wrecking ball smashed through it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 11:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What pricetag do we think "affordable housing" will start at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 11:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was almost upset about the Parliament cut-off, but you're pretty accurate. "Oh you're on the Danforth? How's the Greek food? What do you mean east of Greektown? You must mean Scarborough..." Also, Blogto basically writing "here be dragons" over the area in all their posts doesn't help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 10:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does New Belgium have distribution in Ontario, do you know? I could really use a couple bottles ahead of their Toronto show on the 30th ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 10:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't realize how bad it was until I skidded up to an intersection a couple hours ago on Walmer. Seriously, speed limit minus 10 until you see some salt on the roads. I had a guy pass me in the **oncoming** lane for having the gall to obey the limit on Spadina. People are idiots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 07:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And decent lights. Thank you to those cyclists who at least put something on their bikes, but please, brighter is better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want burgers? [Dangerous Dan's](http://www.dangerousdansdiner.com/) is an institution. Their burgers are in no way healthy, and that's a good thing. Onion rigns are great there, too. Want a more ridiculous burger? Try [Holy Chuck](http://holychuckburgers.com/) and if you take the challenge, prepare to hate yourself. For a quality hamburger in a nicer setting, try [Allen's](http://www.allens.to/). They use fresh beef and you get get your burger medium rare, if that's your thing.

Others have mentioned the AGO, and it is great. You can go skating at Nathan Phillips Square for your increasingly-more-mandatory picture in front of the Toronto sign. I'll also suggest [Casa Loma](http://casaloma.ca/), which is gorgeous and lit up nicely for the holidays. And if you are in that area, [Big Crow BBQ](http://www.roseandsonsbigcrow.com/) is one of my personal favourite places.

Enjoy your stay!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 07:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Rotana Cafe find a new home? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 07:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know how many people used to frequent the place, but the Bus Terminal Diner, at Coxwell and Danforth is open again, with new management. The menu has been updated, and the food is 100% less greasy than it was. Still affordable, but modernised and clean.

Very excited that this location didn't become a Starbucks or Rexall or pre-condo empty lot. Apparently the building owner really wanted to keep it a local business.

From what I was told, they're still in soft open, from about 8am. If you're in the neighbourhood, come on by and show some support! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Also](https://youtu.be/vB02gj9Pfn8?t=4m38s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never run into the problem personally, but you can always ask the guy/gal how the job is, just in conversation. Hours, traffic, etc. Then ask about pay and "compensation", if others do it, so on. And make a decision that way. That'd be my plan. Especially if you're going to see the same people weekly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 11:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they aren't talking about new trucks are they?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 03:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My app just updated, and I thought I was going crazy. Went to settings and there is no way to change it. I would love to have an option to put it back where my dominant hand is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 02:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sucks. Our driver (not the line-wide announcements) came over the pa to tell us
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I was on the train behind you. I think they were holding to let trains pass? Or work cars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 13:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first time I read the first three books, maybe around middle school. Reading them again (in parallel with s/o, a first-timer) I am *definitely* noticing quite a few things my 13-year-old self missed. Or at least missed the significance of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 12:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations and enjoy the ride! My personal favourites have been the City Watch books, and the Death books I have read. And the Moist books. Also The Witches can be hilarious at times.

....basically there are no bad Discworld books. Please enjoy responsibly, and make room on your shelf for all of them in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 12:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I meant by "legal-ish", yeah. I guess it would depend on the workplace whether or not *any* THC results in a firing? As someone who doesn't smoke, I'm not up on the details. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what are your qualifications? And how long have you been there?

Let's not pretend someone get to waltz in to any employer and just be handed 6 weeks paid vacation. At my current job it will take me 10 years to earn that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 14:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all fairness, the dickish comment was followed by an actual answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 14:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume it's all the cheap booze (hello from Canada!). And now pot is legalish to make thing all better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Penelopeiad, Margaret Atwood** Grew up reading Greek myths and the voyage of Odysseus specifically, so I really liked the idea of a different perspective on events. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 07:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a choice between leaving early and being late, it is a no-brainer. Same thing if you drive. Snowing/raining? Leave earlier or eat it in traffic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 20:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so literally nothing has changed. Thanks for the update. So long, Stinktown  :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 20:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been noticing lately, almost as a rule, that any license plate starting with a 'C' drives like they just polished off a 2-4 and their foot is glued to the accelerator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 16:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we add some more pedestrian crossing opportunities? The amount of people, especially elderly folks, I see playing Frogger on Eglinton worries me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 16:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming soon: "Starting in the mid-1.5millions" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 16:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I left Oshawa, 8 years ago, a bus wasn't even an option to Bowmanville if you weren't taking GO. Is there really a better way now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 16:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And pay those parking enforcement officers all their overtime to ticket the hell out of people who can't read a parking sign! I mean, it isn't just 905ers, obviously, but while we've got the pitchforks out, can we do my thing too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 16:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who works construction in southern Ontario, I'm trying to find a way to politely tell you where to put the "temporary worker" idea :)

But seriously, as an example, OHL (international contractor) built/is building the 407 Station on the TYSSE. I can tell you there were just as many fuck-ups, extras, changes, corner-cutting and general nonsense on that site as there were on the other stations being built by PCL, Ellis Don and Aecon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 10:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could reply more often to recommendation threads, but either the requests are way too specific ("a hard sci-fi series with young adult relationships and squid monsters where the protagonist learns something") or way outside my wheelhouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 14:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To quote my s/o: "Oh yeah, I fucking love a Christmas Market."

Thanks for the suggestion :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 14:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what this week is going to be for me: confirming what the internet tells me by phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 13:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll look into it
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to hear! That's one of the main reasons we chose it for this trip. Worried about whole towns shutting down! Only problem has been last minute (one month's notice) reservations aren't the easiest to make... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Visiting over Christmas, looking for advice regarding Christmas Eve/Day specifically </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due to unexpected vacation days, we are coming down from Toronto for six days. Hotel and flights booked yesterday, reservations and planning itinerary has begun. We've both been before, and will again, but the holidays provide a unique challenge.

Obviously many things will be closed on the weekend, and I was hoping for some help sorting out what is open, possibly with an emphasis on Christmas events/attractions. But really open to any singular suggestions.

Failing all else, we'll just be wandering the city, but some specific destinations would be wonderful. Anywhere transit reaches.

Music, food, drink...there are no wrong answers in brainstorming! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 14:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is accurate. Several of the employees I have spoken to manning the Presto gaps are on light-duty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 15:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Birkenstocks left out at Bonnaroo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Securing my new vacation home, I see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Casual racism towards aboriginals in Australia is very common, in my experience. Saw a lot of them not well off while I was there, and the amount of "Yeah, that's a bloody abo' for ya" comments I heard were disturbing. (getting ahead of the downvotes) And yes, I know it isn't everyone, but it was a damned lot more than I've experienced in North America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 04:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its only smellz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 01:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I plan my visits to the Wren around whatever their food special is. They post some delicious, unholy creation on their fb every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 15:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked them. As others have said, I would consider the books, especially the first one, to be a tribute, more than a ripoff. Quentin can be insufferable, as can some other characters, which almost put me off, but I just finished the third book recently. Don't regret it, at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 15:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so glad I wasn't the only one. It sounded like the author I just enjoying sending up/paying tribute to coming-of-age fantasy books had done the same with Da Vinci Code/Indiana Jones tropes. Disappointing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From their map, it looks like the creators live/play in the west end. Still more east end representation than blogto!

(plus The Only and Muddy York)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, most people would be too confused by logarithms to be mad... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like doing the same thing between heavier reads. Not that some graphic novels are light reading (looking at you, Alan Moore). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finished **Stories of Your Life: and Others by Ted Chiang** yesterday, jumping back into **Norwegian Wood by Haruki Murakami**.

Also reading **Trees (TPB Vol 1 2) by Warren Ellis** and **Bridge of San Luis Rey** (fits nicely in my pocket on transit). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 07:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently reading an extremely annotated version of *20000 Leagues Under the Sea* where they lay out all the things the original English that were misinterpreted. Verrry interesting to see the comparison. Would be cool for *Monte Cristo* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Stories of Your Life: and Others** by Ted Chiang

Great collection of short stories that explore concepts near and dear to fans of science fiction (first contact, the singularity) in a new way, including some not-so-sci-fi stories that are equally enthralling. 

Found unexpectedly in a second-hand store, prompting me to set down, unfinished,

**Norwegian Wood** by Haruki Murakami

Following a student in Japan in the late 60's through his life and relationships. Not a lot happening poltwise, but I don't really care because the characters and landscape is so interesting.

Should be back into it this weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the first story in the collection, *Tower of Babylon* roped me in. I had been meaning to buy the book for some time, and the announcement of "Arrival" made me pull the trigger. The instinct to jump to *Story of Your Life* was there, but I'm glad I didn't

I am still floored by how much world-building he managed to fit into 28 pages. Felt better realized than some trilogies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im currently about halfway through *Stories...* (reading *Seventy Two Letters*) and I have to say I am really enjoying his work, so maybe I'm your guy.

Some of his characters sound smart, I think, because they *are* smart. Two hyper-intelligent post-humans are going to sound a bit different than the crew from Workaholics. Same goes for a genius mathematician, world-class linguist, etc.

As to the stories being uneventful, you may be right. In the case of *Understand*, you may naturally want to see how Reynolds will change the Earth, make it better, but that isn't what Chiang wants you to think about. You may want a more action-packed battle between the two of them, but that isn't the way they function anymore (I thought of the scene in *Hero* where Donnie Yen and Jet Li fight a battle in their minds before ever moving). In *Story of Your Life*, maybe we naturally want some grand conclusion to mankind's first meeting with extraterrestrials, but who's to say it will work that way? I absolutely loved his take on our first "Close Encounter". Looking at the practical problems over the fantasy. But it could absolutely be seen as boring.

On a slightly different note, I don't know if others may agree, but his writing reminds me of Borges a bit at times. I can't put my finger on why, exactly. Maybe Borges told his stories through magical realism, and Chiang tells similar stories with science fiction. I see similarities and would welcome a discussion one way or the other, if only to flesh out my own viewpoint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 11:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. This is the book in school I felt was most forced upon me. I didn't get the allure. When it came to Dickens, Shakespeare, and every Can-Lit author, I came to enjoy and understand their books. Wuthering Heights just seemed like a reason for our English teacher to watch her favourite movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty cool. Thanks for delivering :-p I guess you need to be fairly flexible. Good site to watch.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently reading *Stories of Your Life: and Others* by Ted Chiang. Some great short stories, kind of a technical/hard sci-fi. Have nearly missed my subway stop several times I was so engrossed. Apparently the new movie *Arrival* is based on *Story of Your Life*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I don't say this often, but I would love some proof of that. That sounds highly unlikely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some options we looked at for the holidays that were much cheaper than TOR--VAN: Mexico City, Havana, Reykjavik, pretty sure Texas was on the list at one point as well. Canada is expensive :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This *would* give me an excuse to finally crack open my nice-looking, never-read copies. Would probably take some structuring though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 13:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read The Color, and it's been a while since I read Creepshow, but isn't there a similar story about...something green...maybe I should come back after I google it.

edit: found it

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Weeds_(short_story) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 09:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're probably excited about being magnificent and crepuscular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 07:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go for it. Book one is a pretty easy read. Book two (probably my favorite in the series) is pretty different, as the world and characters start to fet fleshed out. Definitely try the first two and see how you feel, if you get invested in the characters and destiny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that was part of the point of the book as a piece of propaganda, no? To show people in these occupied areas that they could fight back. That the invaders were just men. It's been a while since I read the backstory of the story, as it were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had some version of these that were small, square books. I cannot remember the publisher, etc. They were thick little squares and every other page was a picture, black and white, showing the action.

To this day, for some of the "classics", this isnmy only exposure :-p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 07:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *always* want to get technical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 06:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Jays fan who blamed our offense initially, watching the Series has been an eye-opener. I didn't watch Cleveland at all during the regular season, so I had no knowledge of the pitching staff before the ALCS, or how lucky we were not to face a full game of Bauer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 05:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching Cleveland in the Series has made me accept them as a great team. Turns out I was a little biased during the ALCS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 05:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or bust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 05:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably less common with books than movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 05:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I have omitted that one from memory, thank god. Was there not also a scene, maybe in Pacific Vortex, where he played a "fop" to get close to a closeted villain character? That was awkward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 05:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a kid, my grandfather had a lot of Clive Cussler's paperbacks kicking around, which I would read on weekends at their house when the weather prohibited wandering through the ravine out back. This continued until my teens, the last one being Atlantis Found. Trying to reread some of them, ten years later, was really disappointing. Mostly because of the obvious formula he uses for his novels, with just the villains and mcguffins changing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest it to just about anyone, but John Scalzi's *Old Man's War* series is a great sci-fi read. 

The main character of the first couple books is definitely not "grey", but a lot of the overarching plot deals with whether or not humanity is doing the right thing in the way they are approaching colonization/expansion in the galaxy. I think the books hit on your other points more strongly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, they're going on **The List**. Hopefully sometime around 2021, judging by the ever-increasing length of **The List** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I read *Kraken* first, and it wasn't like many books I had read before. I very much enjoyed the discovery of a "world beneath the world" type of thing, like Gaiman's *Neverwhere*. I moved on to *Perdido Street Station*, which seemed to have a steeper learning curve to it's world, and was a little more difficult to get into. *The Scar* was my favorite of the Bas-Lag books, but I can't recall if it would help to read them in publication order, since they aren't sequels, but set in the same world (edit: the novels follow each other on a timeline, but the characters and storyline are mostly separate).

Based on this conversation, I plan to dig back into Mieville's work when I finish my current book. Reading about his books again makes me remember how much I enjoyed them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 10:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much is carried over between the Maddadam books? I understand it's the same world but with different characters perspectives? I read *Oryx and Crake* after finding it secondhand and enjoyed it. But I didn't find out it was a trilogy until a month ago, somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 10:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why, but *The City and the City* is where I fell off the Mieville train. I loved the Bas-Lag books and *Kraken*, but stalled on that book for some reason. Maybe time to give it another go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 09:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a pretty cool tie-in for the movie/series. Don't think Stephen King has cash flow problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 07:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ka Ka was great when we were working on the Bridgepoint reno. ~5 bucks for meat/veg/rice takeaway. No skimping on portion size. Always packed in there as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 18:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read somewhere (it was either in 'Crash' by JG Ballard or 'Rant' by Chuck Palahniuk) that the only reason roads/traffic works is because everyone just decides, as a group, to follow the same rules. Any group of people, small or large, decides to just do what they feel, it messes the whole system up. Obviously more eloquently put by the professional writer.

So when you have, for some quick examples, motorists ignoring bike lanes, cyclists ignoring stop signals, and pedestrians crossing wherever and whenever they want, it compounds the problem. Gets hard to police all these minor/major infractions effectively.

So help me if I was empowered to write tickets, this city's financial problems would be a distant memory. I'd be Oprah friggin' Winfrey, and you, and you, and you get a ticket.

Of course, I would go mad with power and start handing out tickets to people standing on the wrong side of the escalator, putting their bags on transit seats, and using sob stories to get at my pocket change. 

...I lost track of where this comment was going some ways back. Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 13:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully it'll help me get a better grasp on his style in a more "normal" setting. Enjoying it so far. Then maybe a break before "Hard Boiled Wonderland...", which I found second hand the other day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 13:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So very accurate. First cat reference just popped up. Waiting for "Historical flashback", those are my favorite.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe some short stories, to wet your beak? Any of Neil Gaiman's collections (Smoke and Mirrors, Fragile Things, Trigger Warning) I recommend all the time. Stephen King comes right after that (Night Shift, Skeleton Crew, Everything's Eventual)

If you like sci-fi (my genre of choice) I'd recommend John Scalzi's Old Man's War series (space/action/adventure), or Ben Winters' Last Policeman books (impending apocalypse/noir mystery). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's true, the boring parts still stick with me. Now that I've finished it, I'm glad I have, though the process was excruciating at times. And I feel like the extra attention and effort I had to put in left me with a better knowledge of the book. Three months later and I could probably bang out the basic plot without missing many scenes. I can't say the same for every book I've read this year, over a similar timeline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say the surreal/magic moments (In 'Wind-Up Bird Chronicle', anyways) were more subtle than Pan's Labyrinth, but equally as rich. Good comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here I thought 3-4 months was bad. Glad to see I wasn't the only one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel exactly your pain. There was a point 2/3 of the way through "Chronicle" that I almost threw it out the window. I made a post here this morning about these exact feelings, and by-and-large the feeling is that there isn't a point, and we should just enjoy the ride :-)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished "Chronicle" a while ago, am onto "Norwegian Wood as we speak. I actually just made a semi-frustrated post about Murakami [this morning](https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/59o4xj/the_windup_bird_chronicle_cuts_confusion_and/) and since you're reversing the order, would love your input when you finish (some possible mild spoilers in the post, don't click yet!) if you feel inclined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your right about common points. I see the characters in "Wind-Up Bird" and their analogues in "Norwegian Wood", even in the early pages. Confused young man, disappearing (to an isolated setting) girl, militaristic young man, amoral political man, awkward/regretful sex etc. No cat yet....

 Clearly you enjoyed his writing enough to stick with him 

There was definitely a tipping point, about 2/3 of the way in, where the book was either going out the window, or back in my knapsack. Curiosity beat frustration that day.

I do enjoy how the "magic" aspect seems to casually slide into what is otherwise a fairly normal narrative. "I climbed down the well to chill with my baseball bat as usual and wound up in this weird dream motel where shit is going *down*." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely surreal in parts, but very relatable, both the characters and their relationships. My first 'magical realism' experience, and I didn't really know what to expect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think when I stopped expecting a 'point, or even a hint of one, I started enjoying it more. Going into 'Norwegian Wood' with that attitude is helping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
