<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8617</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is so interesting.. have you read the email conversations in the guthrie folder? they seem to be quite friendly towards each other. not sure what's going on. can someone explain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 06:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i feel the same.. this is not supposed to happen with pork sausages. with fresh porcini from the woods maybe but not sausages! seriously! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not sure what recipe OP followed but I love the recipes the "cooking with dog" show does: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F1mvYnRJX70 

PS: no they are not cooking a dog!
PPS: they are also adding an onsen tamago, which i think is essential to gyudon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 07:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am just guessing that this will also be the price at the 76 on wilshire and 26th street. that one always is the most ridiculous in my neck of the woods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 07:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> more like 90 cent hike... when i left for work today i passed cloverfield and olympic gas stations with 3.35/gallon tonight coming back was 4.24/gallon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 02:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> such a great movie. I have been in absolute awe after the movie was over. saw it in the theatre. I still think Gyllenhaal should have gotten an oscar for the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 01:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all beet juice and whatever else came out of that fish ;) (i added some gin) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 00:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks again for the inspiration! So tasty! I posted the result here: http://www.reddit.com/r/food/comments/3a3c5o/gravlax_curing_result_i_wish_i_had_better/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 00:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as promised the result: http://www.reddit.com/r/food/comments/3a3c5o/gravlax_curing_result_i_wish_i_had_better/ 

It is actually really good! I think I might need more Gin next time and probably a bit less salt. With the sour cream and dill it tastes fantastic though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
