<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4153</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is some weird stuff homie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WITNESS !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once told my buddy to order his burrito with "carne de verga" wich translates to cock meat burrito. I laughed, the cashier laughed, the cook laughed. It was good times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  http://imgur.com/a/nhZtJ

I totally did, here it is again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/nhZtJ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe because he has trouble being STRAIGHT to the point.. no ? inappropriate ? I'll go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MBD is a bitch, good for you for raising them. I haven't fed my dragon roaches in years, ever since the gf and I moved in that was the line. And I respect it hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen some tips and tricks for this. you cut out the bottom and fix a wire mesh bottom with putty. Than the original bottom underneath that. kind of like how toasters have that bottom to catch crums. But it's such a hassle breeding crickets, and I just don't have the space or time for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A waiter once treated my girlfriend poorly because of where she put a coupon in the billfold. I left 25 cents in the wine glass. Maybe he was having a bad night, but she didn't earn how she was treated. and she still wanted to be nice to him and leave a decent tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It ends up making the end of the experience awkward, and I try to be a fair person so i can't just not tip or tip poorly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's totally where it starts, I owned a California king snake when i was little. Learned about death from mouse and Cal King. First time I saw one get pounced on i was maybe.. six. Dad looks to me and says "never assume your the snake mijo, some days your the snake, some days your the mouse, that's the way the world works," </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, nothing like seeming him stalk from a high branch and pounce on a cricket making a break for cover five or six days after the fact. Really satisfying, and he always looks so proud of himself. Holds his head up as he chews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scene where the buzzards attack the war rig in Fury Road </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> made a post about how tipping is stupid and we should just pay servers a decent wage instead of passively handing out our dollars because of an old bullshit system.

I guess tipping makes people feel good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie is crazy underrated  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 300 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> upvoting matters ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a lot of respect for them. They are pretty feisty for an insect, they do not go quietly. Accept for those first couple that didn't grasp the gravity of the situation in time that get chomped off of the bat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I inherited a leapord gecko and owned him happily for a few years. awesome animals. I try to make my dragon feel like he's in the wolds of australia. Although i totally support the roman theme XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The incredible thing is the two or three crickets that prolong the inevitable. They slip into the cracks of the wood and hides i've provided and live out the next few days surviving off the kale and collard greens i leave for the dragon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think about that all of the time, I once watched a woman at the pet shop where I bought Moco powder up +60 crickets and toss them into a terrarium with 9 hungry baby bearded dragons. I could not imagine the horror of being dusted with white powder along side so many strangers, taken to a cage with 9 monster anxiously awaiting us to be dropped in. And they were, they were hopping around the glass, they knew it was feeding time. Than dropped 15 feet into some desert environment as the slaughter and chaos surrounds me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cockroaches are more rich in calcium but the gf hates the idea of roaches in the house. So you can powder them before you toss them in to give your lizard all of the nutrition it needs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk to the crickets i've stored just before I powder them with calcium and toss them into my bearded dragon's cage. Didn't notice it was bad till the gf and I got a place together. She was sitting there sipping her morning tea and I said something like. "Bath in the ceremonial powder, prepare your self to do battle with my beast, I've named him Moco, remember this name and know that you are not long for this world," (Moco is spanish for booger, or snot) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly guys, and like a girl complaining about how they are involuntarily celibate. Mostly nerds, that smell bad, with shit social skills blaming their loneliness on woman and "normies".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good, that was one train wreck of a subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brain says "listen, we've been hurt before we don't want to get our ho-" Than my heart interrupts with "YYAAAASSSS !!," </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the /r/incel group. it will make you lose a little faith in humanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It totally makes it more acceptable for what ever reason
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what ever it is it makes me paranoid. i trust the guy and everything but i still keep my password's forgotten to this day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A while back I received some high power 1,000 yard binoculars as a gift. I'm an avid hunter and target shooter so they were used often. In oregon it's not uncommon to live in an apartment complex that is 100 -200 yards away from the nearest neighboring apartment complex. Due to regulations you can't shoot a deer within city limits unless it's right on your property and i'd been eyeballing this same buck for over two weeks. It made it's way to a apartment complex +60 yards away to nibble on some flowers when I noticed that the woman who lived in the second floor of the apartment complex had her blinds open and was walking around butt naked. Older woman with short dark hair, maybe in her 40s. Pretty fit for her age, I was maybe 20 at the time so naturally I looked for longer than i should have. I still feel a little bad about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What's the creepiest thing you've ever done ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if someone has your IP and the right software they can totally make something happen. I needed something fixed on my computer once and couldn't figure it out. A friend had me install this program that allowed him to control my computer from his house a few cities over. I un installed it and searched my computer for any traces after it was fixed. But i still keep my webcam unplugged and the search history wiped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a vegan father in law. Can't take him anywhere, bring some carrots if it's so damn hard for you to find a vegan friendly option you like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Toothpick - Biting Elbows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> technology, every other day something comes out that i can't believe i lived to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> found one of my dad's old porno mags, unopened in the plastic with the price sticker still on it. It cost him $15 collars, every now and again I look at the members price of some sites some times as low as $1 and I scoff at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why is that instinctively the first place we go ? XD 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7u3uhKxNPNg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What argument would a cold can of pepsi solve ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a perfect example. This is what the vast majority of us going to experience. At least from the heterosexual POV, this is still hot, good stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Millionaire - Queens of the Stone Age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i once watched an young woman maybe 17 -18 backing up in a grocery store parking lot. She was headed straight for one of those things that is able to push a row of +20 shopping carts at once. I could have stopped her. I should have stopped her, but instead I watched her tip over fourty shopping carts and a power pusher over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the dip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What song makes you feel cool ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the dip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> move out and don't stay in touch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was walking back from a small mini market with some snacks and beer to enjoy with a few friends back at my apartment. We were almost home when this guy hanging out on his porch asks the million dollar question "Aye, where you from ?" Now I had already had a drink or two in me at the time. So i answered foolishly with something like "Just rode my moose here from alberta ese, looking for work but you guys don't hire mounties here," so the guy take his beer and smashes it across my face. I drop my groceries and knock him back onto his porch and hit him in the face till he stopped trying to fight back. He might have given me an ugly scar on my face and hand but i think I rearranged his dentistry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the worst that you've ever hurt a stranger ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she any way attempts to hurt me or a loved one. I like to deliver equal opportunity ass kickings. No racial or gender bias here. Or if she hurt some ones pet maybe ? Or if she pulled a lethal weapon during a small scuffle with a stranger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an avid airsoft nerd. Some guy was selling an airsoft gun for a great price. He flaked on our first meet up and than apologized like crazy and dropped the price down till he was practically giving it away. Than i show up and he tries to rob me a gun point with the airsoft gun he was advertising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> little hands make me feel bigger
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> included in the house bill means I don't have to worry about it. At that point it's legitimately not optional and taken care of by the establishment as the end total of the meal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doug (Ben Affleck's character) is put up as a good guy by the movie. But he had no objections robbing banks and armored cars at gun point. He only really objected when his accomplices began to get sloppy. Not only does he hold his love interest at gun point, but he builds a relationship based on lies that eventually gets sexual. he's a bad guy that does illegal things, but the movie doesn't villainize him enough for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More glove companies should produce gloves in XS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up just how small that number is. I bet the don't even keep track of the domestic violence that takes place just over this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girls read porn for what ever reason. I picked up a few silvia day novels to see what they were into and step my game up. They're basically just cheesey porn flicks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amatuers are the best. Air brushed fake tittie bimbos getting plowed by mondo cock mongoloids almost never depict what the rest of us experience as sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stockholm syndrome, when you're taught from an early age that this is what your community and god himself wants you'll choose what ever. Muslim countries do persecute woman for not wearing the garment. Ignoring that is kind of weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right ?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, screw that guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at a shooting rang e a while back, there was an obvious noob with a new pistol a few lanes over taking pot shots at a small target way too far away for him to hit. We had a larger target a little closer and we were getting decent accuracy. He calls me over while we were paling around, loading up a few mags. He asks me if one of us could give him a few quick pointers on how to fix his accuracy. He's waving the gun around with his finger on the trigger as we talk and I ask him to stop. He tells me that the gun is not loaded he ch - BAM !! He puts a hole right in the ceiling next to our heads. I tell him to put the gun down and get the range master to help. He bought a gun and had zero clue what he was doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the scariest interaction you've had with a stranger ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in many places that i visited in manchester, and england. They got along fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Richard Brake playing Doom-Head from the Rob Zombies flop "31"

The movie in it self was just a campy slashler flick that wasn't really good at all. But everytime doom-head was on screen you got this feeling that the actor wasn't acting. And that was just how he carried himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is your notch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Town, only do lethally illegal things if your accomplices are fair, smart, and trust worthy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm also not the only one. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q_vivC7c_1k

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm polite, respectful, understanding if it's busy, and forgiving of mistakes. I've never caused a scene over any meal. I'm just a coupon person, a dealer, haggler, and over frugal person so that i can take my hard earned cash and spend it on things that matter. the tipping system is stupid system and bad for everyone involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not know this..  time to tinker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hell, i tip %10 %15 if i'm feeling generous. if they were bad at their job they get squat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in all honesty, i just wanted to take some servers down a peg in a way that doesn't earn spit in my food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also google is a thing so...

https://www.google.com/search?q=federal+minimum+wage ie=utf-8 oe=utf-8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not in california, read the title again. also fight so that slave labor is illegal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that may have been the case when you were working there. But that's not the way it is now. they make the same as some one working a carls jr and they do not recieve a tip for the same working conditions. I could and did afford the bill that was given to me. I did even leave a tip. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fury Road... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mom called me a son of a bitch once. I responded with " at least we agree on something" before closing the door and contemplating whether or not i'd survive the night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do i have to worry about every kid who shops at hot topic ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A guy decided that he needed some smoke, he left a party shitfaced. And hit the car of my first love doing 80 in a residential area. She is now six feet under feeding the worms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People like it fine, went to england and some guy asked me if i thought he was a hobbo for leaving him my change for the meal he served. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd wish for the nails of every person who has ever shamed some one for farting to be immediately and painfully ripped off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why bother, money hungry vulchers are just going to down vote it into oblivion. Along with every other sympathetic soul to scared to say what we're all thinking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not obligated to leave a %1 tip. In california you are mandated to pay your employees a minimum of $11 an hour. She wasn't even incredibly attentive, and got several rolls wrong. I've got three jobs that stand the test of anything a server goes through and not one is deemed "tip worthy". And the few times I ever got a tip in any job I took it with gratitude regardless of size. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A while back i felt like treating my parents to a meal at a local sushi restaurant. Bill comes out to $96 bucks and all ive got in my wallet was $100. So I pay for my meal and leave the change. We're already in the parking lot when the hostess follows us out and asks why we left such a small tip. I said that's all i had and she says than i shouldn't have come at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not mandatory, you poured me a shot of jack that clocks in at $8. Why are you looking at me like I owe you another $2-3 ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Servers of reddit where the minimum wage is equal, why are you so tip hungry ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And don't say that raising the minimum wage to equal of other jobs would raise the cost on food and drink. Because I live in a state where that is the case and it does not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Servers of reddit, how would you change the tip system in the US. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always hear from other states that the minimum server wage is shit in other states. But it never comes up on a ballot federally. Why don't you get on it so i don't have to pay $12 for a shot of jack or $70 bucks for a sushi night when the bill was $59 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]Servers of reddit in the US, do you want the same minimum wage as everyone else ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to smoke all of the time, recently moved into university housing and they have a really strict policy on it. I've seen a few friends get kicked out of housing for it so I stopped for the time being. Love it though, very relaxing, and it nukes alcohol in terms of enjoyment and versatility. I'll pick it up again when i move out for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea, but not exceedingly. The rush and gameplay is totally worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People say say you can't buy woman. False, you can totally buy woman. Legally, illegally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
