<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9748</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is hard! I do it because if I don't - I have nothing else. No reason to be. Yes, I love being a mom and a wife and a friend but writing is MY SOUL. 
I try and set aside what isn't working and think up a new story - that usually gets my passion going again for what I love.
But ... occasionally there are those lows in my writing where I think OMG, this sucks. Or some times I get editorial feedback where I have SOOOOO much to fix in a manuscript and the challenge weighs me down. 
Those days are where I ask myself this question: Why am I a writer? And I can think: I should just update my resume and get a real full time job with a regular paycheck!
 Well, every time I think them  I remember how I sat down in my grief over losing my mom and wrote my debut novel without knowing anything about writing a book. 
And I remember how it came from my heart and came from the deep places inside me where I most love, where I most hurt. 
And I know that no matter how much I think I suck at times  I KNOW THAT I AM A TRUE STORYTELLER. And this is what I was born to do. 
So that is how I get by.
Oh, and a supportive husband...and some good beer :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, people are surprised at the lines I cross (in grown up fiction). I think I get my demons out! I also, believe it's very gladiator-like. I get all my violence out in writing. Probably why Gladiator is my all-time fave movie with Russell Crowe! That scene where the gladiator chick is sliced in half? I LOL LOL LOL. Super fun, as it's not real. So I like to write that stuff too! My son is an amazing writer but loves video and photography more - he is creative all around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I may look sweet and innocent but read my books and heh heh heh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn! I hope not! Although it was decades ago. I also I never wanted him to read my first thriller for grownups and he did (just last year) and NOW he just bought book 2 - which is waaaaaayyyy dark and tortured. I told him NOT to read it! LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
