<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2699</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP launches religious attack against Rep. Martha Jane King </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Montana Supreme Court says citizens have a right to trial by jury before the state can take private property in civil forfeiture cases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicago cop arrested on charges he sex trafficked underage girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Contra Costa County Halts Fees for Parents of Juveniles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 17:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Civil lawsuit: Jeremy Mardis suffered immensely after barbaric shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 15:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Campaign-related clothing leads to voter's arrest in Bulverde </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 19:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santa Ana to pay marijuana dispensary $100,000 after video appears to back police harassment claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sledgehammers don't vandalize Hollywood stars, people vandalize Hollywood stars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Officials: Voter error, not conspiracy cause ballots to flip from Trump-Pence to Clinton-Kaine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mississippi woman appealing district courts ruling that her nearly 100-day incarceration in county jail, without being offered bail or an attorney, did not violate her civil rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 18:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bat-wielding suspects like Deborah Danner are good target for shooting because NYPD trains on them at firing range, cop union boss says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 22:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta love the way he kicks with his shin while stepping through and looking away. Sure he'll try to write this off as unintentional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 17:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goes without saying that targeting cops is despicable, but as a matter of rising stats I'm not sure their data makes sense. The total number of cops killed in ambushes this year is 12, and 3/4 of those tragic deaths came in two incidents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An arbitrator has decided the city was wrong to fire Minneapolis police officer Blayne Lehner earlier this year for using excessive force and ordered the city to rehire him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Illinois Youth Prison to Reopen as "Life Skills" Facility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 19:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ferguson effect? Chicago police release video of beaten officer who didnt pull weapon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 19:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DC woman's charges dropped after body cam video released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cleveland police officer on restricted duty after driving through field, crashing into shed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSU student says Trump supporter assaulted her, made lewd remarks while filming her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 16:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saginaw County Sheriff Denies Driving Seized Muscle Car, Won't Explain 56k New Miles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 17:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 19:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone seems to be skipping over the bigger picture here, which was that she had the choice to shoot the guy BEFORE he began smashing her face and is regretting her decision not to in hindsight. Nobody's saying she wouldn't have been in the right to shoot him in the midst of the attack. But instead we're getting a dangerous defense of a shoot-first mentality, which can obviously be problematic, even if it might prevent some terrible incidents like this. Seems like there's a different tactical approach that could have led to a less rapid escalation of the situation and made it harder for the guy to so quickly isolate a single officer. Again, there were 4 cops.

Also, how about the other cops? Why didn't they shoot this guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Columbus police officers will be allowed to review body camera footage before they file reports or make statements under new rules the city agreed to with its police union </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 15:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least four officers respond to this dude and they can't stop him from smashing her face repeatedly into the pavement until she's unconscious? There's a bigger problem going on here, and it's not "we couldn't kill the guy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officer fired, charged with manslaughter after child's death in patrol car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two safe injection sites proposed for the Seattle area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 22:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coroner identifies second person killed by LAPD in weekend shootings as 16-year-old boy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 22:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former chief of the Altavista Police Department has been sentenced to a year behind bars after being convicted of using department money to buy pills and then covering up the scheme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bail Reform Proposed To Help Poor Defendants In Santa Clara County </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The DEA just cut opioid production by 25 percent for next year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 02:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police chief explains Bridgeports problems: people have abandoned God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 23:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawyer: 15-Year-Old Girl Pepper-Sprayed By Hagerstown Police Won't Face Charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 23:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ga. deputy fired for racist Facebook posts, targeting black motorists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 22:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 22:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they are still immune to criminal charges, apparently. Even if they point a "loaded firearm at the head of an innocent and compliant person, with the safety off and a finger on the trigger," which is "not constitutionally permissible," according to clear precedent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge denies bond for fired Jackson cop accused of lying about being shot by black man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police Detective Who Threatened To Kill Teens And Plant Drug Evidence, Is Suspended, Not Fired </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 22:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TASER plummets 14% after losing NYPD body camera contract </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 22:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drug informant nets $1.5 million for undercover work over 31 years, records show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 22:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Generally I think it's wise and commendable for a marginalized population to show an interest in peacefully protesting against an oppressive one. I'm guessing these high school football players might fit the profile of people who are likely to be mistreated by police. Police can counter if they want, but it ends up looking petty and not having the same power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anybody would question their right to do it. But the wisdom of fighting this PR battle against a bunch of high school football players is another issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Jefferson Parish deputies are refusing to work extra detail shifts at Bonnabel High School football games after a majority of the team took a knee during the national anthem during last weekends football game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Department announces $20M for police body cameras </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police in Beaumont arrest man with "grenade." Officers were able to deploy a Taser to subdue suspect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 23:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mans truck held in limbo by the feds a year after they found five bullets in the cab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dallas Police Lieutenant Calls Police Brutality A Growing 'Epidemic' That Must Be Addressed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Englewood Cliffs dips into civil asset forfeiture fund to pay police overtime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 14:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Orleans City Council considers eliminating bail bonds for minor offenses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 23:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Florida inmate begged for help, guards gassed him to death, suit says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 15:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New report shows Iowa law enforcement agencies seize cash, vehicles and other private property from at least 1,000 people a year without proof the property was acquired as a result of a crime or was being used to help people commit crimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 22:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Bronners pledges $660,000 to marijuana legalization efforts in California, four other states </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 23:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US House considering bill to rein in ability of the IRS to seize bank accounts and other property under so-called civil asset forfeiture laws. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 21:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicago cop indicted in 2013 shooting captured on video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 21:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYPD: Revealing the Truth About the Millions We Seize Would 'Lead to Systems Crashes' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 20:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hefty portion goes back to cops and prosecutors who litigate these cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYPD arrests man for having a pocket knife, seizes $18,000 for forfeiture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outstanding police work by Louisville's boys in blue. This will surely help everyone involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FDA tells doctors: The money youre taking from pharmaceutical companies may be clouding your judgment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 17:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad how being born into an impoverished neighborhood starved of jobs, quality education and opportunity leads people to sell drugs, which leads them to get arrested, which makes it impossible to get a job, which leads them to sell drugs, which leads them to get arrested.  Sad how that cycle inevitably includes violence and often ends in death. Or we can be mad because we assume this guy accepted a government handout -- even though having a criminal record usually makes that impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 17:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This whole article is some shit, just regurgitating the "he had it coming" narrative fed to reporters by police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Jersey ACLU Challenges Law Enforcement Asset Forfeiture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 17:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston Police Body Camera Pilot Program Begins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indiana Supreme Court: No money bail unless a defendant is dangerous or a flight risk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 23:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police seized $171 from a N.J. man. It'll cost him $175 to get it back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 17:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time, Norfolk shows reporters body-cam video of a fatal police shooting. But it still won't be made public. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 17:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muskogee childrens charity refuses $28,280 donation from local atheist group </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 17:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
