<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5867</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So much stress and pain, I don't see the point in continuing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 05:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 20 year old guy who is just about to start my second year of college and about to continue a program that I hate and only doing it to please my mother.

And I was expecting to enjoy a nice summer vacation without much stress, only to discover that my parents are breaking up and that we're losing the house. So for the entirety of my summer, it's been the stress and shock of that, plus moving, and dreading going back to school.

The only way that I can find to deal with everything is to cut myself. I used to hide my scars, but after awhile, I decided to show them in a stupid way to get sympathy from my mom, only for her to either ignore them or joke about it.

The only thing that was stopping me from taking my life this summer was thinking about my few friends and my sister, and ignoring the thoughts by watching YouTube videos   movies. But my mom took away all of my movies and lowered the internet, so I can't watch anything on it. 

I've been feeling depressed for the majority of my life and right now, I feel like everyone would be better off and happier if I wasn't in their life at all.

Sorry for the long post, I just don't know what to do anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eli Roth Presents Terror Tram Announced for Hollywood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't allowed to go trick or treating or do anything related to Halloween since my parents were extreme Christians and the day "celebrated the devil". It wasn't until a year ago, I got to carve a pumpkin for the first time. Like OP, I love Halloween now, but I feel like I missed some great times by not enjoying the fun of the holiday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 09:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that nothing that happens in the game happens in any of the books. Since Madness Returns and the game before it are made as sequels to the books, that might explain it.

Plus, since the company that made the Alice games; Spicy Horse, are based in China, I think those levels are based around China and Japan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 10:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here with me. I haven't gone to the event, since I'm a broke college student in Canada, so there's no way I can get to Orlando or California.

But every year, I look forward to watching the mazes and scarezones on YouTube. And until I get the funds and transportation to get to either park, going to HHN will remain high on my bucket list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 20:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1: Not having enough money for a $60/80 game, plus I have a huge backlog of games.

2: Doom. I love the series, and I'm a sucker for bloody violence.

3: Probably Five Nights at Freddy's: Sister Location. I'm a big fan of the series, and the games are pretty cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DIY Pumpkin Spice Coffee Syrup recipe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 22:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's like all the other Telltale Games, they usually will just have the season pass on the physical release for whenever they release the next episodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 12:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rest of the album can be found [here](http://imgur.com/a/2UZ5L) (if you haven't found it yet). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 20:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I want to play a game." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 20:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOG stands for Good Old Games, it's a website where you can buy older PC games. You can add the games to Steam using the "Add non-Steam game" option, but it won't have any achievements or anything like that. They just give you the installer for the game and you can install them onto your computer, but you don't have to download anything other than the games to play them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBC interviews Neil Gaiman about The Sandman Overture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 18:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
