<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7666</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GoodReads kicks off April's 'Reading Without Walls' challenge to get you outside your reading comfort zones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything you use a lot, really. 

--------------------------------
The reason that the rich were so rich, Vimes reasoned, was because they managed to spend less money.

Take boots, for example. He earned thirty-eight dollars a month plus allowances. A really good pair of leather boots cost fifty dollars. But an affordable pair of boots, which were sort of OK for a season or two and then leaked like hell when the cardboard gave out, cost about ten dollars. Those were the kind of boots Vimes always bought, and wore until the soles were so thin that he could tell where he was in Ankh-Morpork on a foggy night by the feel of the cobbles.

But the thing was that good boots lasted for years and years. A man who could afford fifty dollars had a pair of boots thatd still be keeping his feet dry in ten years time, while the poor man who could only afford cheap boots would have spent a hundred dollars on boots in the same time and would still have wet feet.

This was the Captain Samuel Vimes Boots theory of socioeconomic unfairness.

"Men At Arms," Terry Pratchett </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the benefits of not being Christian is that I can eat my chocolate bunny now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, the *author* likes the movie better than the book. Or at least he's said there were parts and themes in the movie he wished he'd thought of when he wrote the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forrest Gump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the last couple years several people announced publicly that they were making a point of reading all non-white-male authors, which predictably caused the Internet to explode. A look at some of those articles and the books mentioned might provide some direction.

https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2015/feb/20/i-only-read-non-white-authors-for-12-months-what-i-learned-surprised-me

http://flavorwire.com/429473/why-i-only-read-books-by-women-in-2013 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl with Swan by Evoca1, in Thornton Park neighborhood in Orlando </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'American Ninja Warrior' ready to roll at Daytona Intl. Speedway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like in movies, it depends on the story. I've known the general plots of many classic works and still enjoyed them. Reading "Gone Girl" wouldn't have been nearly the experience it was because it was written with the intention that twists and turns would be revealed at a certain pace.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alpha male military testosterone-dripping shoot-'em-ups. Pretty much the exact opposite of romance novels but with the same problems of cookie-cutter plots and replaceable covers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to lie, I'm 51 and I love YA books as much as I do any other type, provided that they are well-written and they entertain or inspire or amuse or engage me. Books written for the YA adult market aren't, I think, any more likely to be badly written. 

YA books, if they have anything in common, are not quite as complex as "grown-up" literature since the writers assume their target audience has not yet had the experiences that grown-ups have had. But they can be just as affecting and meaningful.

My two favorites weren't YA when they were written, as that genre wasn't a thing yet. They were (and are) science fiction. "Ender's Game," by Orson Scott Card, and "Jumper" by Stephen Gould. Both later made into subpar movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm ahead I do. If they're a little ahead and merging would be awkward, or if me speeding forward to get ahead of them would be obvious and dickish, I slow or hold steady to leave space. 

And hold, and hold, and hold... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monument Valley. Something about the elegance and bizarre Escher-ness of the design appeals to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm on the highway and there's a car in the merge lane next to me and I slow to let them in and they wait till the last possible second to move over, even when it's fairly clear I'm waiting for them. 

No idea why this irritates me more than other traffic issues, but it always does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy to see it happening. Just thought about it because I got an unexpected "whoa, nice beard" compliment from another bearded dude when I stopped to grab breakfast this morning (I was caught off guard and stammered a "Thanks, you too")  and it occurred to me how rare that is when I hear women complimenting each other all the time.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going for a romantic walk in the rain would be a lot tougher if the raindrops all screamed on the way down. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men of Reddit, have you ever complimented another man on his appearance? How did it go? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'm looking forward to seeing what you post! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Return of Captain Mysterio"? I guess since it was the only Doctor Who anything in 2016, but that was a weak episode.

On the other hand, I'm seeing a lot of things I liked, and I honestly don't know which graphic novel I'd go with. Paper Girls is great, Monstress was great, but Vision was unexpectedly amazing (Ms. Marvel and Saga are perennial favorites). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  evannarehood

Hashtag might get their attention, the @ definitely will. But check the hubs' Instagram page, some might have specific preferences about what to use when.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some Instagram tips:

Follow photographers who inspire you, and like and comment on images that catch your attention with a little more praise than just "Nice!" Social networks work better when you're social, and every photographer loves it when people notice elements of their work. Heck, if they did something you envy, tell them so and ask how they did it. I've gotten some great tips that way.

If you see photographers posting similar images to the ones you take, pay attention to who follows, likes and comments on their work. Go check out THEIR feeds, and like or comment on some of their posts (if you feel like it, don't fake it). Some of them may tap your name to see who you are and see something they like. If your pictures are similar to Photographer A, then fans of Photographer A may like yours too and that's an easy way to let them know you exist.

Post regularly. 

Use hashtags. There are hashtag generators such as https://displaypurposes.com/ or the Focalmark app, and you can save sets of hashtags you use often in a textfile on your phone to copy and reuse. Put your hashtags in a comment, rather than the main post. Less annoying to people to scroll past. Since you're a landscape photographer, make sure you post location hashtags.

Use hashtags or @s for photography hubs to possibly get your work featured, such as @world_shotz, @capturelandscapes, @wonderful_places, etc. They may regram your image and tag you -- and they will almost certainly get more likes for your pic than you ever will -- and it gets your name and work out to a larger audience. Here's a list: https://brianventh.com/2016/04/instagram-feature-accounts

Keep your feed focused. This was tough for me, I went back through and deleted a lot of images that weren't about my photography, but you want this to be your portfolio and not what you had for lunch. (Unless you're a food photographer.)

Remember that you're not after numbers of followers, likes or comments. You want dedicated fans, ideally ones that will buy from you or least tell other people about you. One fan who buys a print is better than 10,000 likes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Publishers and media companies also greatly underestimated how much they had pissed off consumers right as this technology was available. I remember the articles about CDs and how even though they cost much less than an LP to create, ship and store, they still cost more but don't worry, they price will come down. This was, of course, a lie. Plus more and more stories were piling up about  companies making record profits while stiffing artists, etc., so by the time IRC and Napster and Grokster and LimeWire and all the rest popped up, few music lovers had any loyalty to the companies. And the companies, rather than deciding they should find a way to get out in front of this move, fought hard against it and pissed off even more people.

I don't advocate piracy. But man, if there were worse ways to respond to it I can't think of any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. It finally broke me of my lifelong habit of collecting comics by character. I had been a Spider-Man fan since the early 70s and faithfully bought his books wherever he appeared, and while I was already getting very tired of the increasing numbers of BIG EVENT CROSSOVERS THAT CHANGED EVERYTHING AND SOMEONE SURPRISING DIES this was the story that finally told me there was no point in getting invested in a long-term character in a hero book.  Why care about the latest love interest? The next editor might decide to retcon them away because he doesn't like them.

I dropped a lot of books after that, books I had been buying largely out of habit and completeness. I don't power through a lousy story arc anymore, waiting for a good creative team to come to the book. Now I just find good writers and artists and follow them instead. Turns out I'd rather read a good story about a character I've never heard of than a crappy story about a character I like.

"One More Day" wasn't the only reason, but it was the most blatant one and a big tipping point for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite is still the one that says "you wouldn't download a car" and I just think dude you are making  some big assumptions about me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found someone checking out Arlin Graff's cheetah in St. Petersburg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is it about anti-piracy promos that make me want to go download an entire season of something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's got its own annoyances, never fear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now, the first Ms. Marvel trade is #8 in best-selling Marvel graphic novels on Amazon. The rest of the top 20, with two or three exceptions, are all Old Man Logan collections, Black Panther collections, Deadpool related, or Star Wars related. The first three Ms. Marvel collections all made the NYTimes bestselling graphic novel list. 

I don't think there's any question Ms. Marvel made them money, especially when you add in whatever the digital sales were. And if they could get critical acclaim at the same time, hey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I'm never away from my desk long apart from the one walking break, and I'm salary so I rarely work only 40 hours anyway. If they can call me on weekends to solve problems, they can deal with me taking a stroll.

Also, our company is good at encouraging exercise, health screening and proactive healthy activities. Hdealthier employees means fewer insurance claims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And soon. I was tested and diagnosed with it, got a CPAP machine and not only do I wake more rested, my wife has mostly stopped wanting to murder me. Best thing we've ever added to the house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's Quiet Uptown" from "Hamilton." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get up from my desk and move around, at least once per hour or so for a quick walk to the bathroom or somewhere nearby, and once on a 15 minute walk around the building to pretend I'm exercising. If smokers can take a break to kill themselves, I can take a break to try to avoid it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, I'm sure we'll find something else to blame on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thor's numbers are relevant because a) the story was about Marvel sales, not DC's, and b) the new Thor is outselling the last Thor book, so clearly diversity didn't hurt that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, someone looked at the numbers and analyzed them instead of picking an easy scapegoat? That's suspiciously like journalism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captain Marvel was doing well just before this, though. The book under Sue McConnick was growing a loyal group of fans and selling pretty well, I thought. Then Secret Wars mixed that up and Civil War II just ruined any good will casual readers had for her. I still don't understand why anyone thought it was a good idea to take a character who's SLATED FOR A MOVIE and work so hard to make her unlikeable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captain Marvel was doing well just before this, though. The book under Sue McConnick was growing a loyal group of fans and selling pretty well, I thought. Then Secret Wars mixed that up and Civil War II just ruined any good will casual readers had for her. I still don't understand why anyone thought it was a good idea to take a character who's SLATED FOR A MOVIE and work so hard to make her unlikeable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss Jarts. There was never a purer, more focused version of childhood Darwinism than yard darts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which childhood toy did you hang onto, or hunt down again later? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it started running down about the time they killed off the Ultimate Universe and combined the two, another weird confusing mess of an event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. Say, did her book, which had great stories and character arcs, start suffering around the same time they started shoving her into the Avengers and then pulled her into Civil War II? No reason, just curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terry Moore, Stjepan Sejic, Fiona Staples,  Charles Vess, Sana Takeda, Paul Chadwick, John Cassaday.

There are other artists that definitely influence what I buy but if it was work on a book whose writer or subject matter didn't interest me I'd keep walking. The people I listed above tend to only work on the kinds of projects I like anyway, so instant buy.

Also, looking at the list, I seem to like comics artists known for drawing realistically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect she's peeved about her successful comic becoming the image for complaints about sales tanking from "diversity." Ain't her fault, Marvel dudes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say, Marvel, remember two of your best-selling, critically acclaimed books of recent years, "Hawkeye" and "Vision"? Know what I liked about 'em? It wasn't just the writing and the great dialogue and the amazing art and the way they weren't afraid to take new looks at very old characters to make something fresh and new.

It was also because both books were allowed to have complete, years-long story arcs to tell their stories. 

STOP WITH THE CROSSOVERS. They were annoying enough when they were every summer, now they're all year long and not even fully plotted out. Crossovers get you short-term bumps, but they aggravate the long-time readers that are your solid base.

Crossovers and events and hero deaths with zero meaning because you know they'll be back before the next movie and retro-reboot-redos on editorial whim that ensure there's no reason to ever get emotionally invested in a storyline because by next year it might never have happened are why I largely stopped reading hero books at all. Now I follow writers and artists I like, I've given up on character loyalty. Or company loyalty, for that matter.

I really liked "Hawkeye" and "Vision," though. Maybe try some more like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I really wish Febreeze made a room fogger. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice work! I think it can be hokey when it's overused -- do we really need another scarlet rose in a black and white scene? -- but when used well it really pops the image and guides the eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure I made it past book 10. I enjoy good sex scenes in books and I liked her characters, but the scenes were getting more and more gratuitous and frankly, if I want to read erotica there's better out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Snake Woman," by Tes ONE and Pale Horse, in St. Petersburg, FL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savor the books that you want to savor. If you're in a book that speaks to you, angers you, delights you or otherwise pulls you in so that you linger and reread and make notes or just aggravate everyone around you talking about it, there is no good reason to deny yourself that pleasure. (Your friends may disagree.)

If a number count is important to you, zip through other books in between the really good ones. Unless every book you pick up affects you that way -- and good on you if you're that lucky -- you can always run your numbers up around the ones that encourage you to linger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to do that with all my street art pics. Sometimes it's more of a pain than others :) But I like the way it gets the emphasis on the art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still enjoy them -- just as I enjoyed Parker, even when his publisher started using larger text on his later books, I assume to disguise how sparse they were -- but while I enjoy most of his books, I do feel a bit unsatisfied when he hits a passage that really, really needed a little more detail for empact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything not interesting enough for Buzzfeed to steal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another: "Game of Thrones." Granted, there's a lot of main characters, but I lose interest when the story is on anyone besides Arya Stark or Tyrion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ending of every Flash episode, ever:

**Barry:** I can't do it! I'm... I'm not fast enough!

**Literally anyone else, possibly including the bad guy:** You can do it Barry! I believe in you!

**Barry:** I did it!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it was "Buffy the Vampire Slayer" and "Angel."

I liked Buffy the first season or so, then started getting annoyed by her from then on, but we watched because the supporting cast was fantastic. (My wife and I had nothing against the actress, and we loved it when she got to play different versions of herself, but Buffy in her right mind was getting insufferable.) 

Angel we never particularly liked so we avoided his spinoff show till friends convinced us to give it a try. It helped that the other characters were making fun of the same things about him that we didn't like, so we stuck with it.

Also Ted in "How I Met Your Mother," but someone already mentioned that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a  big one for me. Love everyone on that show except for Ted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What show do you watch despite your dislike of the main character? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He lightens up a little on that after he starts dating Anya. They let him mature a little bit after "The Zeppo," and after "The Replacement" he finally starting acting like a goofy man instead of an entitled goofy teenager. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I loved BtVS, couldn't stand the Angel character; too broody, too anguished. But we watched all the BtVS eps and needed more, so we gave it a shot.

In the very first episode the other characters make fun of Angel for being broody and anguished, and they keep doing it. We liked Angel better in his own show (still not a favorite). But we loved the supporting cast and as others have already commented, this show has some of the best character arcs, the best seasons, and one of the best show finales ever. Well worth watching.

Season 4 still sucked, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scalzi, to me, is the science fiction version of Robert B. Parker, author of the Spenser mystery novels (among many others). 

You buy 'em for the ideas and the dialogue. You're not going to get a lot of description and you may not get a terribly complicated plot. You will get witty characters who get things thrown at them and you watch them deal with it. That's pretty much it.

If you enjoy this style, you'll love his work. If you don't, you won't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three, counting the candle part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can be two things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Space Rainbows" by Ricky Watts, in St. Petersburg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am incapable of seeing a big candlestick without instantly judging it on its suitability as a murder weapon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome. He does like his Dobermans.

But I can't stop looking at the face on the girl in the one I posted. I'm a decent artist but I can't even imagine how to get a face 25 feet high to emote like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spent a day and a half just walking around the area, marveling and taking pictures. I had a list of some I wanted to see but I kept getting surprised by unexpected street art everywhere I turned. Just amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to an article about the murals in the area, "Girl with Doberman" symbolizes the anguish Evoca1, his sibling, and their dogs endured when their parents battled through a bitter divorce. The kids and dogs were pretty much ignored, and the dogs kept getting in trouble and had to be muzzled. The girl depicted is actually his sister. "So his point is that no matter what youre going through, you need to nurture your pets and your children. Nothing should take precedence over that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's at 1246 Central Ave, by the Central Arts District.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Girl with Doberman" by Evoca1, in St. Petersburg, FL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish I had known decades ago in high school to only make friends with weird names so I could find them more easily on Facebook now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I wrong or do they show a picture of Buffy standing off against Glory when they're supposed to be talking about Anya's introduction in the video?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed it in his other readings, though. Again, I'm a big fan of Wheaton. And his reading voice does sound, to me, a lot like my own, which may have something to do with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But when, exactly, has he bullied or banished anyone with differing or unpopular views?

He has responded to attacks. He hammers people off his comments page but not because of their views, but for how they are stated, and he explains this. 

I disagree with your initial opinion that the Hugos are useless now, and I'm unaware of any times Scalzi has blasted anyone solely for conservative views. Can you name any? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to upvote posts I comment on or comments I reply to, unless I'm arguing with them. I think I've downvoted maybe three times in four years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked up the habit -- I may have even seen it in an LPT post here -- of not saying anything if I answer a call from an unfamiliar number. After an awkward second a human will say "Hello?" but a robocall will hang up.

If it's a human, I have fun avoiding any version of the word "yes," sometimes with very convoluted responses. ("It seems to me, at this time, to be quite possibly so.") I don't give out info. And I end each of these calls with, "Please remove all of my information from any and all databases available to your company. In the U.S., anyway, they have to.

The one that really bugs me? "Hi, is this Carol"? "I'm afraid you have the wrong number." "Oh, I'm sorry, but maybe you can help me. Have you heard about this great new service..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an explainer from the AP: http://www.news-journalonline.com/news/20170329/what-death-of-broadband-privacy-rules-means </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I admire the result, but that is way more work than I'm going to put into a nighttime snack. I barely put the effort into evenly spreading peanut butter. I salute you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, no. Scalzi may have his asshole tendencies -- as he has said himself -- but I doubt I could last ten minutes in a room with Beale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I kind of want to see that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any movie title can be improved by adding Jim Hensons in front of it. Jim Hensons Reservoir Dogs. "Jim Hensons Caligula Babies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PB J for me. Can't beat it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Night owls of Reddit, what's your go-to late night snack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of them? My wife and I were both game and curious, but after all these years we've ended up pretty vanilla.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which authors keep you awake? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're serious about the coffee shop, consider finding an existing one that might enjoy having shelves of books in it and working something out with them.  

Other than that... if your residence allows it, try finding as many places to store books as possible. Stack em up as furniture, as suggested in another comment. Add a shelf running all around the place, just under the ceiling. Put your bed on risers and use the space underneath. Sacrifice some width in your living space and fill every wall you can with stacked books. If stability is an issue, use boards and bricks to make as minimalist a shelf as you can so you don't use up valuable book space. You'll be more of a fire hazard, but you'll also be well-insulated.

You might consider asking like-minded friends with extra space if you can put a bookshelf there, especially if you can fill it with books they would enjoy. Spread your library out.

For awhile in college my son, who also refused to let a book go if he didn't have to, kept the backseat of his car filled with the books that wouldn't fit in his apartment. Not a long-term solution, but it was the best he could do at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably Don Quixote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I've read that book five times. Still a favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually he manages to make it useful. To capitalize on Day's inability to not talk about him, one year Scalzi offered to donate $5 to charity every time Beale mentioned his name. Thanks to other people matching, ultimately $50,000 was donated to charities designed to uplift women, minorities, and gays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in the perfect age window for this book -- teenager in the 80s, found that damn hidden room in Adventure for Atari, the whole thing -- so every page had something for me. I liked it a great deal.

But I am willing to accept that nostalgia may blind me to other faults since his second book, "Armada," left me so completely bored I can't remember if I ever finished it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really hoping he makes his own at the end, with his own tech.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And there's your answer, from one of the haters in person, I guess.

If you use terms like SJW or virtue signaler or white knight or cuck or beta male unironically, if you are incensed at the idea that science fiction should ever be anything besides white men fighting aliens in space ships, or if you support someone who regularly spouts white supremacist, misogynist creeds, you'll probably hate Scalzi too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a pretty cheap enemy, it'll cost you hardly anything to oppose me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/KeepOurNetFree/comments/61q3mb/why_h_j_res_86_is_important_and_what_you_can_do/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current thought is yes, if it's a paid VPN service. I don't know that I would bet on it, but it's certainly better than nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you offering? What's the going rate for a nemesis these days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. Still an awful lot of bile coming from that direction, though. 

I don't understand people who seem to need enemies for them to really flourish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started it Sunday morning, Came back to it, finished it Sunday night. Enjoyed it, little annoyed at the blatant cliffhanger ending, but had a lot of fun reading it. It goes fast, since Scalzi focuses more on dialogue than description, but there's some fun stuff in there.

I read his blog, followed him on Twitter for years, and I've read a lot of his standalone stuff, but never tried "Old man's War" till yesterday. Not a military fiction guy, for the most part, but I decided to give it a shot anyway and really liked it. Starting on "Ghost Brigades" now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said in an interview (linked from the link above, in fact) that there are two, *maybe* three books in this series and that's it. The rest are sequels to other series and some standalone books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how you think this is insulting. This is the guy who proudly accepted the title of beta male and started selling T-shirts.

Every time someone insults him for caring about people, he finds a way to turn it around and make money for the kinds of charities that annoy the people who insult him. It's fun to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an issue with me. I love Wil Wheaton's writing, his acting, and based on seeing him talk at cons I'm pretty sure he could do stand-up if he wanted to. Very funny, personable guy. I follow him on social media and I think the world is generally better with him around.

That said, I don't like his reading voice. Maybe because it has some of the same nasal quality my own voice does, but when he reads I hear every "he said" and "she said" and I can never get into the flow of the story. The one audiobook I've ever returned was "Redshirts," for that reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scalzi represents everything Day hates, and he is relentlessly cheerful about it while also being more successful, happily married with a great kid, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While some may be sincerely dissatisfied readers, Scalzi also has a loyal contingent of haters -- mostly Sad Puppies/Gamergaters/MRAs -- who delight in dumping on him every chance they get. He fights back by mocking them and by being, generally, happier and more successful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope not. Maybe some help with some techy bits, but I'd like to see him on his own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a Heinlein fan and that is possibly the single worst book of his to start with. Not only does it build on previous books, without which it's even more difficult to follow, but you get all of his writing weaknesses without as many of his strengths.

One glaring problem with reading his work now is that progressive about women as he surely was, he was ignorant or dismissive of the idea of any genders besides the two. His women were brilliant, beautiful and world-class talented versions of the women in House Beautiful ads. If there were women in his stories that didn't eagerly want babies they were few and far between. Where were the "feminine men," the "masculine" women, the asexuals, or any of the many other types of people in the world? He briefly mentions a homosexual experience in "Beast" that was bland and unappealing, and in "Stranger in a Strange Land" one of his characters refers to homosexuals as "poor inbetweeners" who embodied a "wrongness." 

He had no problem accepting a woman as an equal -- or, more often, superior -- which was unusual and daring in his time, but he expected her to be a "very female woman."

ETA: Ah, now I have to refute myself. Thinking back, the judge and attorney in "I Will Fear No Evil" were unapologetically, happily bi or possibly ambisexual, there were suggestions of same-sex bundling between several main characters, and there were other ambiguities in there as well, including an ongoing question as to whether the protagonist would swing one way, the other, or both, which was never clarified. So he did acknowledge gay people, but they were still manly men gays and womanly woman lesbians or all-out hedonists, so that point still stands :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still one of my all-time favorite authors. His works got crankier (and, I think, better) as he aged. Read it all :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. If the book is compelling and entertaining, a longer book is fantastic because now I know I have hours and hours of enjoyment ahead of me.

A duller short work is obviously easier to power through than a dull longer one, but good big books don't bother me a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have intentionally loaded up on novellas at times, to keep my numbers up. I have no excuse. (hangs head) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have so many unread books waiting for me. Some on shelves, some in books, lots of them on my iPhone. Some of them are in series I started, drifted away from, and plan to get back to eventually (Pratchett's and Baxter's "Long Earth" series, most recently), some are books that caught my eye but haven't bubbled to the top of my list yet, some were gifts.

I've purged them on occasion, getting rid of the ones I'm pretty sure I'll never open to make room for new books, but on the whole I like having a stash of new literature at hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. 

We got the same complaints about the Civil War trailers, for example, but I don't think any of them even hinted at the final battle, if I recall correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, this cheers me up. I really didn't like the idea of Spidey being a Tony Stark product almost from the beginning and if this is how he's going to move out from under Stark's shadow I'm all for it. Homemade suits for the win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I hear this every time a new trailer comes out. But the last couple of times, all the big scenes in the trailer happened in the first half of the movie with none of the ending in there. Are they giving away too much of the plot? Maybe, we'll have to see. But I'll bet we haven't seen the really important stuff yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] So how SHOULD they write Superman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every post that mentions Superman, either in the comics, movies or TV, invariably brings out the "I don't read Superman stories, he's too boring" comments.

So, you've been given the comic. What would you do with him to write a compelling story and story arc? Anything goes (that's publishable by DC Comics). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it was "Battlestar Galactica." All my friends raved about it to me so much I got sick of it without seeing a single episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What popular movie/show/play you might like has been so hyped that you have flatly refused to watch it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you know offhand the Latin for my wife's choice for family motto: "It Seemed Like a Good Idea at the Time"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
