<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6292</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 23:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phrasing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 23:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Step 1: Find bucket.

Step 2: Eat at P.F. Chang's.

Step 3: (some time later) fill bucket in bathroom.

Step 4: Wrap and deliver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 22:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it... Not entirely sure what's going on, but I like it. Is this referencing something specific? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] When you lose interest in a video game before finishing the story, life goes on after your last save file. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 20:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens in the world when the hero just...stops? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you lose interest in a videogame before finishing the story, life goes on after your last save file... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 20:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 01:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brain threw the title words together as "rape costume." Image still fits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 15:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 03:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, I think. No prayers required for stationary objects. You just walk over there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 01:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the answer, great job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every season knows my reign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 01:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every season knows my reign,

though, some more so than others.

Yet, when you're faced with Summer's pain,

you'll pray to me for cover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 23:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure about the real-world prices for these things, but as the father of a five-year-old, I've seen more episodes of Spongebob than the Simpsons, and there are several occasions where they state the menu prices on the show, both referenced by the characters and written on the menu. As the seasons have worn on, the prices have varied from $1 to $5 per patty. 

Going off of those prices,  and given that there have also been dozens of episodes where the one and only cook at the restaurant is sent home early until he resolves some problem or other, thereby shutting down the restaurant's production entirely, it would seem that the Krusty Krab turns a significant profit. I would guess that Krabby Patties are made of faux meat, probably produced from coral or seaweed (abundant in the ocean), and therefore cost somewhere in the vein of pennies on the dollar to produce.

Also, it just occurred to me that I don't recall any episode specifically referring to the krabby patty as "meat." It's always just been called a patty. So, there's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 23:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually bought this app a year or two back, but some update earlier this year brought the ads back. I would pay again, since Readit performs wonderfully... That said, it would be nice to have to pay for a thing more than once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Panting, Steve sprinted up the parapets of the castle he'd spent the last several months building. A low growl sounded from somewhere above him as he neared the top of the cobblestone staircase.

He leapt out of the tiny guardhouse at the top of the stairs, spinning wildly as he flailed about with his diamond sword. There was a wet thunk and a groan, and Steve smiled as the Zombie poofed, leaving chunks of rotten meat on his newly masoned roof.

He made a note to clean that up later.

With a determined look, he braced himself and turned toward the spire in the middle of his castle. On the very top of the turret stood the one responsible for his night's grief - a dark figure, holding the glowing stone he'd so painstakingly rebuilt from fragments salvaged from the most hellish plane of existence.

The enderman had stolen it at sundown, just as Steve was returning from his day's foraging. This had plunged the entire library into darkness, leading to an unexpected infestation.

Steve had been woefully unprepared for the encounter, falling to nearly one heart as he fought to escape. He'd only just reached his weapons stash in time to defend himself from the skeleton that had chased him in, but it was all for nothing. His armor had broken, his health was failing, and a creeper had blown up his food store.

He'd been lucky to make it to the roof, gnawing on the flesh of his fallen foes in an attempt to regain a modicum of strength. His stomach rebelled, but he knew it would help in the long run.

Now that he'd fought his way clear of the castle, he knew his saving grace. Catch the enderman, destroy it, and restore the sacred light to its rightful place.

Thunder crashed as he stepped forward, and Steve's heart froze as the first raindrop touched his skin.

Then enderman shrieked, and with a dull *zzapp*, teleported away.

Steve could only watch in horror as his precious light source popped in and out of existence across the open field, finally disappearing seconds later to Notch only knew where.

With the light source gone, Steve was at a loss. The sun wasn't due up for hours, and even then, his castle was infested with the undead. Sure, he had a torch or two left, but he wasn't sure if he'd even be able to fight his way down to the library, let alone fix it.

Suddenly, a low *kssss* echoed up the stairwell begin him.

Steve gripped his sword tightly in one hand, and his torch in the other, feeling his resolve hardening.

"That is *it!*" he cried out to the night sky. "I have *had it* with these *motherfucking* creepers in my *motherfucking* home!"

Steeling himself, he charged, screaming, into the stairwell. He swung mightily as he saw the black of the creature's eyes, but his heart sank when he saw four more of the green menaces right behind its falling corpse.

*kssssss-ksssss-kssss*

"Aw, hell."

Sound vanished as everything was washed in a spray of red. Steve's final thoughts before losing conscious we were only this:

*You cannot respawn in hardcore mode!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Updated! Now has an actual ending.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Updated! Now has an actual ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UPDATED!

After your comment, the lack of a conclusion kept eating at me. Today, it finally popped into existence! I thought, given that you gave me the motivation, you should know about it. Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 05:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ***continued***

Aghast, i stumbled down the steps, sprinting back to my house as Mrs. Sawyer's remains swirled away on the breeze. Hands shaking, I locked the front door and grabbed my phone. No way was I going to work today, after that. I stammered off a vague excuse, dropped the handset, and went to lay in my bed.

The world was swimming. I thought about Sandra and her husband, and Mrs. Sawyer's prediction for them. As my mind wandered, I found myself plagued with terrible thoughts about everyone I could imagine knowing them - not their reactions to this event; instead, I saw a series of interactions that would inevitably lead to their deaths.

Before long, the headache came back, a shooting pain that blocked out my ability to function. I could barely move, barely even breathe for the pain.

*knock, knock.*

The terrible din of a gentle tapping on my front door tore through my consciousness, and I slowly made my way to answer it.

"Excuse me, sir," a harried-looking man said when I opened the door. "My car broke down, can I borrow your phone?"

My eyes screwed shut in pain as his words tore at my eardrums like knives. Instinctively, I reached out to hush him, missing completely and laying my hand upon his forehead instead.

Somewhere behind the darkness of my eyelids, I saw an old woman, smiling at me as I lay in a hospital bed. She gently whispered something, wiping a stray hair off my brow, and as the vision faded, I saw a tear slip down her cheek.

My eyes popped open to find the man staring at me in utter shock.

"W-what the hell was that?"

I felt a smile creep over my face as I realized that the headache had vanished. 

"That's how you are going to die." 

My voice was full of wonder at the realization, for it was so much more than I had said. After I released the man, I saw every step of his journey toward death. I saw the people he would influence, and the paths that would be taken by those who would never meet me, as influenced by his knowledge from this meeting. I saw all of their deaths, as well.

I even saw the people he would drive toward me, whose lives I would set on a new path.

As the man slowly backed away from me, I realized something that made me giddy with a new kind of fear. I had become the catalyst, the eye of the storm. Somehow, I had become the common factor in countless lives - no, *every* life.

I had become death.

And for thousands of years, there has been nothing I could do about it.

Until now.

Now, it's your turn.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 03:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the feedback! Sorry about the ending, but I left it that way on purpose for two reasons. First, I wanted to leave it open, since everything I tried putting there to "wrap it up" seemed to take away from the intensity of the moment, or just plain contrived. Second, I was running out of space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 00:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> updated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mrs. Sawyer had been my neighbor for two years before I finally knocked on her door.

I'd been warned about her by my realtor before buying the house. Apparently, she was regarded as some sort of witch by the locals - a fortune teller, or something. I couldn't get any solid information about her, but apparently her clientele, who she served all hours of the day, often left screaming, crying, or pleading with her.

I didn't think anything of it at the time, figuring that my realtor was just disclosing an urban legend, or perhaps blowing up the story so that i would pick a different place, sending her a bigger payoff from the sale.

I should have realized, though. No home gets sold for a quarter of its value without good reason.

The first few weeks, I didn't notice anything strange. Mrs. Sawyer had dozens of people come and go, all all hours of the day, and not one of them made any ruckus like I'd been warned of. I'd basically forgotten about the warning, in fact, until one night on my fifth week in that house.

I was jarred out of sleep by a piercing wail. I'd never heard such a mournful cry before, and I stumbled upright and over to the open window to see what in the hell was going on outside.

Was someone hurt? Dying?

To my surprise, I saw the front door of Mrs. Sawyer's house standing open, spilling light down the sidewalk and over the figure of a wisp of a woman leaning again the white picket fence. I saw her sobbing as Mrs. Sawyer calmly walked down her steps, approaching the distraught woman.

Curious, I leaned out the window. What the hell was going on?

"W-why?" the girl managed between sobs. "Why would he do that to me?"

Mrs. Sawyer shook her head. "I cannot say. You asked to see, and now you must live with the knowledge."

The girl moaned, somehow even more pitifully than before. After a moment, she peeled herself off of the fence, trudging slowly off into the dark.

Mrs. Sawyer looked up at my house, eyes twinkling. I was pretty sure it was too dark for her to see me, but I could feel her eyes digging into my soul.

Then, just like that, she turned around and went back into her house, closing the door just as a pair of headlights pulled around the corner of the block.

Completely confused at what I'd just witnessed, pulled my head back in as the bus drove by my house. I hadn't made it back to bed before I heard the squeal of brakes, followed by a wet thud.

Looking out again, I saw the taillights of the bus, still swaying from the swerve. As it vanished into the distance, I noticed the body lying in the road, not far from Mrs. Sawyer's house. 

With a gasp and a cry, I grabbed my cell phone and sprinted outside as I dialed 911, not even stopping to put on pajama pants or shoes. I sprinted across the damp grass in just my boxers, leaping over the curb as I reached the road.

I found a pulse just as the phone connected. I told the operator what had happened, and she told me to leave the girl still and direct traffic around her until the ambulance arrived.

While I waited for them to arrive, it occurred to me: The bus had been on the other side of the street from the girl. There was no reason for this girl to have been hit on accident.

I watched the girl's chest rise and fall with slow labored breaths as the sirens approached, wondering all the while: What had Mrs. Sawyer shown her?

-----------

**Edit 1:**

The next day, I started looking into the rumors about Mrs. Sawyer. 

There wasn't much to go on, to be honest. Some people claimed that she could see the future. Others claimed that she could only see death. Many of the latter even claimed that she cursed people with specific, gruesome deaths.

I didn't know what to believe.

It was apparent, though, that something odd was happening in Mrs. Sawyer's house. Within the next two weeks, I heard at least four more people screaming at her from inside her house, or out in her front yard.

"It can't be true!"

"Take it back! *Take it back!*"

"You lying witch!"

Each time, I watched through my window until it ended. Each time, she looked up at me with that piercing gaze, somehow finding me even behind my curtains at night.

Each time, I shuddered.

------------

There were lulls in Mrs. Sawyer's business, it seemed. Weeks of silence, followed by shouts and curses, day after day. Sometimes they were longer intervals, sometimes shorter, but I never saw a shortage of clients entering or exiting her house.

Finally, after about three months of this, there was a knock on my door. I opened it up to see a harried-looking man standing on my front step.

"Um," he said, standing there awkwardly. He was carelessly shaven, his eyes sunken and tired. 

After a moment I threw him a bone. "Hello."

"Um. Hi. Um. The, uh, the doctors say that you're the guy who called the ambulance for Sandra?"

I stared at him for a moment, confused, before remembering. "The lady who got hit by the bus?"

He nodded. "My wife, yes. Um." He rubbed his forearms anxiously. "She... she's in a coma now."

"Oh." I didn't know what else to say. How do you respond to something like that out of the blue?

"Yeah. Um. But, she'd be dead if you hadn't called. Um." He rubbed his arms some more. "My therapist said I need to focus on positive things. So, I wanted to see the man that saved Sandra. Um. And thank him. You. Um."

I smiled weakly. "Yeah. Sure. No problem."

He nodded, still fidgeting. "Well. Yeah. Um... okay. I'll let you get on with your day, then."

And with that, the man wandered away, eventually climbing into a poorly-parked SUV and driving off.

--------------

I didn't think of that man, or the lady I'd saved, until more than year later.

I was drinking my morning coffee and reading the newspaper before work, when my eyes fell on a small article on the corner of page 2. The words "Hit-and-run" and "Sandra" caught my eye, and I leaned in to read further.

*Hit-and-run victim Sandra Cummings was found dead in her hospital bed yesterday morning after spending nearly two years in a coma. Sandra was struck by an oncoming vehicle in a local suburb around 2 AM on the night of August 18th, 2013. Her injuries were severe, but she was saved by a nearby homeowner (who has chosen to remain anonymous) who witnessed the incident and called emergency services. Sandra was rushed to Carlisle County Medical Center, where she underwent emergency surgery. Her life was saved, but she fell into a coma during recovery, and had been in that state ever since.*

*Sandra's husband, Larry, stayed by her side throughout her ordeal. Loyal to the end, he was even there the morning she died, quietly crying next to her.*

The article went on, but I stopped reading. I suddenly remembered the man who'd appeared at my door all those months ago, how distraught he'd looked. That must've been Larry. And what was it Sandra had said the night she'd jumped in front of the bus? *"Why would he do that to me?"*

I jumped up from the table suddenly, a sick feeling in my stomach. I left my coffee sitting on the table as I strode outside, heading toward Mrs. Sawyer's house.

I stood in front of her door for a full minute before knocking, my heart pounding heavily. The door opened almost immediately, creaking slowly inward on rusted hinges.

"I've been waiting for you," Mrs. Sawyer said. "Ever since you bought that house. I knew you'd come knocking eventually."

I stood there, my voice lost, pulse drumming in my ears.

"You want to know what I do, yes?" Mrs. Sawyer smiled grimly at me. "It's not pleasant. I show people how they will die. Nothing more. Nothing less. Many... cannot take it. The manner of their death breaks them. Some even take steps to escape it."

"Sandra," I finally said. 

She nodded. "Yes. I remember her well. You saw her reaction. You saved her life. And in doing so, you ensured she would meet the end I saw for her."

I shuddered. "What did you see?"

She sighed, smirking wistfully. "I saw her in bed, asleep. I saw her husband smother her with a pillow."

Goosebumps rose on my arms. Seeing my reaction, she nodded.

"You've already heard of her death then."

"Yes."

"You doubt my prediction?"

"No."

She cocked her head to one side. "Would you like me to read you?"

I hesitated only briefly, but nodded. 

She reached out her hand, gently pressing her palm against my forehead.

I felt a sudden jolt, like a million volts of electricity jumping between us. Instantly, my head felt like it was about to explode. I had no vision, just the sudden, throbbing headache.

"What happened?!" I moaned. 

Mrs. Sawyer laughed, a sweet, musical sound. "Oh, thank god! I was beginning to think I'd never be free."

"Free? From what?" I grunted through the pain. I forced my eyes to focus on her. I blinked - her hair was greying before my eyes!

"I've been cursed with the Sight for thousands of years. Now I can be free!"

"I don't understand," I gaped. She was aging rapidly as I watched, wrinkles appearing and stretching across her features, skin sinking in around her bones.

"You will, in time," she said, grabbing my hand in her own. I felt her bones rapidly growing brittle as she pressed my palm against her own forehead.

Another flash of pain, and I saw the two of us standing there through her eyes. She released my hand, spoke, and then the vision faded, along with the pain.

My eyes opened to see her smiling. She was almost mummified as she released my hand.

"Well, that's not so bad," she said, before collapsing into dust.

**EDIT 2**
  Story continued in comments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, well. Still cool to know! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Know of any land-based vehicles that could do it, too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any currently-existing vehicle that could travel fast enough to pace the sun around the equator? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 14:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming an unlimited amount of clean, well-maintained, and straight road were available to do so.

Also, let's go ahead and exclude known geosynchronous objects, like satellites and the space station. Strictly in-atmosphere, here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You spot an unusual flower on the side of the road, and inexplicably feel compelled toward it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 03:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 20:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Always glad to get feedback. Critiques and criticism are welcome, too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 18:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five days.

Five days, they'd said, and they'd be back for me.

I open my last bottle of water and shake a few precious drips onto my tongue, and throw it aside in disgust. It bounces once in the dark box, landing between my legs with the rest.

So thirsty. Those jerks.

Five days... Or was it six? Hard to keep track.

I check my watch, but the glow had stopped working two days ago. I guess I'd worn out the button, checking it that often.

They'd said I'd be safe here, while they sorted things out. They'd held the money for me, so that there would be room for the water.

Wish they'd left some food, too.

So hungry...

So thirsty...

So tired...

Maybe I should sleep some more... I'm sure they'll be coming for me soon... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 02:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Part 2)
*		*		*

We were inseparable after that night. Our respective worlds merged, and we just about flew through life on wings of joy. Sooner than anyone ever expected, only two years later, we were engaged.

Leslie, my precious Rainbow, was pregnant less than two months after the wedding.

At the baby shower, when Leslie was about eight months along, Susan and Jim showed up. Susan had turned a greyish-yellow color, and seemed to be cradling her arm. She glanced up at me as she set a hastily-wrapped box on the table, and then moved to the living room without a word.

She didnt need to speak, though. Her color shifted to vibrant green at the sight of Leslies hand in mine. 

Then Jim walked in, and I reeled back in shock. I hadnt seen much of him over the last couple of years. Wed been in touch often enough, but one of us or the other had always found some way to avoid actual face to face contact since my initial trip to the hospital.  On the rare occasion it hadnt been avoidable, Id taken the cowards way out. 

I told him I was blind, just so I wouldnt have to look at him, to see how bad he looked now.

He caught me off-guard, stepping into the kitchen without his usual flair of a greeting, and what I saw now was worse than Id feared. Hed turned a sickly, mottled green, like rotting, boiled spinach, but even that was drowned out by the veiny, pulsating blackness Id seen in him before. It had spread through his being, overtaking almost all of the putrid green.

I pretended I didnt see him and told my wife that I felt claustrophobic, stepping outside before anyone could speak.

She joined me a bit later, and I noticed that her colors were marred with a grey haze. That had never happened before.

Whats wrong with him? she asked. What did you see?

I shook my head. I dont know. 

She shivered. Susan was hurt, she said. I know you couldnt see, but her arm was bruised. I think hes hurting her.

My head pounded from what Id just seen, my heart raced. I hugged my Rainbow for a minute, taking comfort in her presence. 

What do we do? she asked.

What could I say? I dont know.


*		*		*


Nothing happened at the shower.  I wish it had.

Jim sat quietly the whole time, across the room from his wife.

Susan spoke softly, avoiding eye contact with anyone.

He was a dark presence in the corner of the room.

She faded constantly from a sickly grey-yellow, to bright, verdant green when she looked at me.

I should have seen the signs. I should have done something.

We were washing up after the shower had ended. The sun had set, the last guest had gone home long ago. Leslie and I were having fun washing the dishes. Wed made a game of it some time ago  it was basically a race to see who was faster, the washer or the rinser. I was rinsing that night, and I kept sneaking clean plates back onto her side of the sink. Yeah, I cheated. We both did, usually, and that was part of the fun.

Then we heard the gunshot in Jims house.

A plate crashed to the floor. I dont know who dropped it.

Leslie grabbed the phone and called the police while I rushed outside. I started toward Jims house, but stopped short at the sight of a horrible figure moving toward me. It was a solid, deathly black, and it was pointing something at me. Even without the ability to see colors, the shape was clear enough.

Jim had a pistol aimed at my chest.

She wanted you for years, he growled. Years!

Jim Jim, calm down, I said Whats going on?

I waited, Greg. I waited, and then you found your girl, and I still waited for my own GODDAMN WIFE TO LOVE ME!

It hit me then like a freight train. The green from Susan, the color of lust, every time she looked at me. The blackness in Jim, growing darker and darker over time. 

The gunshot.

Oh, no, I said. No, Jim, what have you done?

He took a while to respond, but when he did, I was shaken to my very core.

She wants you so bad, he mumbled, she can have you.

My blood turned to ice as he raised the gun.

Jim, I plead. Jim, please-

He fired, and I was thrown to the ground.


*		*		*


I could barely breathe as the ambulance sped us toward the hospital.

My insides hurt. My chest felt like it had been ripped open. I couldnt talk, couldnt focus on of the faces around me. I was only vaguely aware of where I was.

Stay with us, the paramedic said. Keep breathing, come on.
I couldnt focus on his words. My world was clenched in my right hand, and I held on for dear life.

My Rainbow. 

She didnt let go of me when the ambulance stopped, wouldnt release while the ER staff ran us through the hospital toward surgery. She fought for every second she could get. Finally we hit a door, and the orderly had to pry her hand off of mine.

Her color had turned red, overlaid with grey. She was afraid.

As they wheeled her away, my heart shattered.

Shed saved my life by sacrificing herself, shoving me aside as Jim fired.  Id heard a second shot, and Jim collapsed to the ground, but I didnt care. Id rushed over to Leslie, my Rainbow, and tried to tell her it was okay.

She ended up comforting me the whole time. 

She was a stronger person than I ever could be. She was my light and my life in this world, and then

The doctor came out hours later. They couldnt save her. 

They wouldnt tell me about the baby.

They let me go in to say goodbye. I almost didnt have the strength, but I remembered her courage, the sheer force of her will, and I went in.

I cried. I tried to speak to her, to thank her for everything shed ever done, but my mouth wouldnt work.

My Rainbow was now the same featureless black as everything else in the room.


*		*		*


I dont know how long I cried over her body. The doctors gave me all the time I needed, though, and I walked out of the surgery room feeling completely drained. My world had been stolen from me so suddenly, and I wasnt sure how Id go on.

Friends and family came to talk me through the ordeal, but they werent much solace. It hurt too much for simple words to help.

But then the doctor stepped out, and said seven words that revived a piece of my soul.

Would you like to meet your daughter?

I followed him to the nursery, numb. I couldnt see through the glass, but the nurse wheeled out a small bassinet for me. 

Shes perfectly healthy, said the doctor. Go ahead, pick her up if you want to.

I peered into the basket, and my heart melted. For a brief instant, all of the pain of the last few hours faded to the background. I gingerly lifted my newborn, cradling her head against my chest as I watched the rainbows dance across her face.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Fiction/Drama]Blind [4004] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 02:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is Greg Martin, and I am blind.

I used to be able to see things the same way as you, in all its Technicolor glory. In fact, until a short while after I turned twenty six, everything was fine, visually speaking. I saw trees of green, red roses too, hehe 

Sorry. I like the classics, what can I say? 

Anyway, I should probably go on with the story. It was early summer when my vision went away. I remember that day clearly, because its the day I first saw her. Its funny, because if Id seen her before it happened

You know what? Im getting ahead of myself. Lets go back to the beginning.


When I woke up, everything was black.
And I dont mean that in, you know, the typical sense, like darkness and such. I mean, literally, everything was black. My ceiling, walls, bed, windows, hell, even the glass, everything was the same, stark, monochrome black. I could see shapes, textures, and edges, but all of the color had been leeched away from my world. 

At first I thought Id been pranked while I slept. In retrospect, that was absurd; theres no way even a team of people could have come in and painted my house and all of my belongings black. 
Anyway, I stumbled out of bed, grumbling, tossing my now-black sheets to the floor. I trudged over to the window and hauled it open, cursing every name I knew who could possibly have been connected to this.

My eyes widened in shock.

The ground outside was black. The houses, the mailboxes, the cars, all had been changed to the same matte black shade as my bedroom

But the most shocking thing of all was the sky.

As far as I could see, this blackness enveloped the world. The sky was black as anything, and the clouds above were puffs of black cotton over it.

To say that I freaked out would be a bit of an understatement. I started yelling and howling like a gibbon, debating the possibility of all this with myself. I tried to logic through it, but couldnt manage to reach any reasonable conclusion.

Only one thing was certain. Either something terrible had happened to the world, or I had somehow spontaneously lost my ability to see color of any sort.

Okay, Greg, I thought. Breathe. Work through this. What can you do?

It took a bit of thinking, but finally I realized the only sane thing to do in this situation.

Find a doctor.

So, I found my keys, made my way into the garage, and slipped into the car. It didn't take long for the glaring problem to become apparent.

The windows were solid, opaque black. Just like everything else.

I sighed, letting my head fall and bounce on the steering wheel. 
What else could I do?

The neighbors.

Yes, Jim and Susan. They could help. 

I left the keys in the car and went outside. The street was empty this time of the day. Every adult was at work, every kid was at school, and every dog was locked in the back yard. All that faced me was a charred representation of what should have been my green and verdant lawn.

My heart pounded in my chest as I stepped out. It was strange, stepping out across the darkened expanse. I cant properly describe to you just how wrong it felt.

Imagine you had a kid. Raised it for years. Saw all of its firsts, all of its falls, all of its growth and achievements.

Then imagine that, one day, you woke up, and the kid was gone. In its place was someone else. Someone you didnt know.

No, wait, thats typical parenthood around the teens. See, I told you I couldnt do it.

Anyway, I made my way over to Jim and Susans, but only made it about halfway before something caught my eye. Just as I walked around the tree at the edge of my lawn, I noticed a color.

Thats right, a color!

Not much of one, just an extremely light blue, almost grey, but it might as well have been a rainbow in the darkness of my world.

I turned and looked closer, and my jaw dropped. You see, this tree had been infested with fire ants for weeks. Id tried various home remedies to make them leave, but nothing had worked. Id been planning on going out that very day to get some actual pesticides and finish the job properly.

After what I saw that day, I could never bring myself to end another ant colony.

You see, the blue that Id seen was the path of the ants, a solid, pulsating line bisecting the tree from the ground to a tiny crack somewhere around shoulder height. I leaned in for a closer look, watching the tiny, frail-looking things as they marched up and down, like tiny ghosts coursing over the bark-textured darkness.

As I watched, another flash of blue caught my attention, darker this time, more pronounced, like an ocean wave. I tracked it to find a bird in flight  a mockingbird, by its shape  and my jaw dropped as I saw it join with another one of a slightly different shade. 

And as I watched, they danced around each other, flitting across the street, the houses, the lawns. Their colors shifted from blue, to teal, and finally to a deep green, before they flew out of my sight.

I dont know how long I was standing there, staring spellbound at the spot where the birds had vanished, before a voice broke into my awareness.

Greg? Jim called out from his porch. I glanced idly toward him  and then did a double take at what lay before my eyes.

It was still Jim, in every way. Same curve of the jaw, same typical button-up Hawaiian shirt he always wears on his day off. I mean, I assume it was Hawaiian. I couldnt really tell what color it was supposed to be.

What made my stomach churn, though, was how I now saw him. Jim appeared to me as a sickly green, like cooked spinach and baby vomit. Worse still, he seemed to have spindly black veins coursing over his entire person, pulsating like a beating heart.

Oh, god, I uttered.

Whats the matter, bud?

I dropped to my knees, shaking. Um, I said slowly. Um. I think I need a doctor.

He came toward me, and I averted my eyes, staring at the grass. I noticed a hint of brown between the charcoal blades  a beetle, crawling along.

Jim put his hand on me. You feeling alright?

No. I shied away. Somehow, I could still feel that disturbing color through his hand. Can can you ask Susan to drive me to the hospital?

Yeah yeah, sure. He backed off, and I felt a tension ease off of my shoulders as he raced into the house, calling for his wife. I slowly rose to my feet, and was leaning against their car when they came back out.

Susan was yellow. A bright, vibrant yellow, like a sunflower. She almost glowed. I frowned, because I recognized the cut of the dress she was wearing. It was supposed to be black, like her hair, but it was just as bright as everything else.

This was beginning to freak me out, but not as much as what happened next.

You okay, Greg? Susan unlocked the car for me, and I grunted uncomfortably as I slid into the passenger seat. I buckled in and waited while she gave her husband a goodbye kiss. Then she slid into the drivers seat, looked at me, and said, Dont worry. Well get you taken care of.

Looking directly at me, I saw her shift from yellow to green, ever so slightly. Then she focused on driving, and reverted back to her original color.

Just before she closed the door, however, I saw the blackness in Jim pulse, and grow ever so slightly.


*		*		*


I insisted that Susan leave me at the ER and go home. She argued with me, but I was stern about it. I wasnt about to die, and didnt need to be babysat. She reasoned that if I were too unwell to drive there, I shouldnt be on my own. I didnt tell her what was going on, but it was probably fairly obvious that I was in a fair amount of distress. I mean, Id just spent twenty minutes locked inside a black box I couldnt see out of.

It didnt really help that she kept fading from yellow toward green when she spoke to me. What did it mean?

I could tell that I wasnt going to get anywhere, so I signed in with her as my emergency contact and promised to call her as soon as I was out. She didnt like it, but agreed with me eventually, and left.

Four hours later, I was in the doctors office. He was an older man, late sixties by my guess, and to my new view of the world he was a dull red, like an overripe apple. 

He was also no help.

Inability to see colors is not an illness, young man, and people dont just change colors.

I know! I groaned. I wasnt getting anywhere. Its not normal. Something must be seriously wrong with me.

Look, son, I know when Im being played for a fool, the doctor said, setting down his clipboard. His redness brightened as his tone hardened. If you want drugs, you should at least try and come up with something borderline realistic.

But-

Get out.

Well, that was that. Four hours wasted, and Id gotten no closer to understanding what the hell was going on.

I didnt feel like calling Susan, and besides, I couldnt see the colors of my phone screen to dial anyone anymore. I decided to just take a walk, and hail a taxi or something later on.

That was a big mistake. I didnt think about the fact that, without being able to differentiate colors, Id lost most of the landmarks that I knew. All of the street signs appeared blank, every building faade was like a freshly cleaned chalkboard, with no indication of anything that had come before. I made it two or three turns down the road before I was completely turned around. Hailing a cab was out  I couldnt tell which of the cars passing by were yellow, or which of the ones with the vacant signs (I couldnt read them, but I recognized the shape) were lit. 

I didnt know what time it was  couldnt read my digital watch  but it must have been either closing time or lunch time. In any case, I was soon surrounded by people as I struggled to find my way through town. I was overwhelmed at first by the seething mass of chaotic colors around me  reds, blues, purples, every color of the rainbow and more. After a while, though, I started noticing things.

People talk, you know. You do it, I do it, and anyone who listens can learn about you if they took the time to pay attention to anyone but themselves. Well, on the street that day, I found myself focused on everyone who came near me, and I eventually realized something that rocked my world.

All of the colors I had been seeing  that I was still seeing, and still see to this day  were indicative of what lay at the core of a person. Red was passion, love or rage or dedication. Green was desire, lustfulness. Yellow was anxiety, uncertainty, or confusion. Blue was tranquility, peaceful serenity. 

There werent many of those around town at that time of day. Most of what I saw was yellow, shifting toward red at minor interactions with their surroundings.

I was baffled. How had this happened? What had I done to gain this ability?

I thought back to the day before, and nothing unusual came to mind. So I thought back to the day before that Still nothing. Further and further, nothing, nothing, nothing!

Eventually I sat. I couldnt think of anything else to do, so I sat, and watched the world go by.

It was the most beautiful day of my life, even before I saw her.

Id found my way to a fountain. It was interesting to see the water with my new eyes. I knew from experience that it was clear and clean, but I could see a faint blue tint across the dark surface, fainter than even the ghostly ants from that morning, swirling and spinning throughout the rippling black.

Think of liquid mercury, but take away the shininess. Thats about what the water looked like to me.

Anyway, I was sitting there watching the play of the blue on black for what must have been hours before she appeared to me. I wasnt even looking toward her, but she caught my attention as she wandered through my peripheral vision.

My heart skipped a beat, and my breath caught.

She glowed with every imaginable color, all at once. She was a literal beacon of light in the dark world Id found myself engulfed by. I would say she looked pearl white, because white is the presence of all colors in light, but that wouldnt be right. She was constantly shifting and flowing and ebbing with colors, each one an equal and great part of her core.

And she was walking away, cutting across the extreme corner of the square toward God knew where.

I dont think I thought about it. I jumped up and ran after her.

Excuse me! I called, and she looked up.

In the back of my mind, I saw her form. Plain face, plain clothes. Kind of frumpy, for lack of a better word. None of the typical trademarks of beauty, although she seemed to be at least trying to match current fashions.

What do you want? she asked suspiciously.

I swallowed. Im sorry to bother you, miss, I said before I could stop myself, but you are the most beautiful thing I have ever seen in this world, and I couldnt let you just walk away.

She stared at me, and for a brief moment I wished I could suck the words back into my mouth, unspoken. As I stood there dumbly, though, her colors shifted, swirled, and writhed like a billion tiny flakes of glitter in a snowglobe, and I knew I couldnt leave it there.

My name is Greg, I said, stepping back slightly. And I know it sounds strange, but I would like nothing more than to know who you are.

And I stood there, waiting patiently while she analyzed me, colors shifting all the while. It couldnt have been long, but it felt like a lifetime that I sat there under the razors edge of her discerning gaze.

Finally, she stepped forward and extended her hand.

Leslie, she said.

We both smiled.


*		*		*


We talked for hours that day, and I ended up going back to her apartment. We just talked, and I slept on the couch. I spent that entire weekend with her talking about life, the universe, and everything, and I learned that Leslie was quite possibly the most fascinating person Id ever met. 

She was a psychology major at the local community college, but also loved painting. She was insecure and underestimated herself constantly, but never backed down from a challenge. She knew what she liked and wasnt afraid to make it known, but was always willing to try new things, even if they were far, far outside of her typical comfort zone.

But most of all, she was passionate, and compassionate. She showed just as much interest in me as I did in her, mostly curious what it was I saw in her that everyone else in the world seemed to overlook.

I took a big leap, and told her about how my view of the world had changed, how I could now see the core of every living thing I encountered, and not much else. 

I told her that the sight of her had lit up my pathetic little life more than anything else ever had, or even could, and that I didnt know if Id be able to leave her side that weekend if I knew I could never go back.

She cried with joy.
*		*		*

(Part 2 in comments)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 03:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a four page short story. It's an after-the-fact confession of a man who pulled off a series of murders in a public place, got off clean, and accidentally triggered a rash of copycat killers.

If you're interested, I'd be happy to make it available. I always relish feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 16:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A complete and utter breakdown in the presence of cheese graters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 16:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, I existed around people. Let them get used to my presence. Study them, learn what they like, what they respond to.

Eventually, they talked to me. I responded honestly, but keeping to the mannerisms I learned they respond well to. In time, they came to accept me into their group. 

So, basically, I treated it like a research experiment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 16:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vagoo. It just sounds so warm and inviting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 16:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would conduct the ultimate research experiment, equipping each clone with implanted biometric sensors and sending them out into the world to experience every facet of life that they can manage. After a few decades, I'd have the results compiled for scientific analysis of the impact of various lifestyles on human development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 02:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably exhale slowly, and then say, "shit." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 02:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exhale.

It's so easy, you do it while saying it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 01:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has. Ultimately, I won full custody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grab a glass of water, hop into the shower, lay down in the tub and let it flow. The warm water soothes and relaxes you, the drain lets it all wash away instantly. It sound gross, but it's my preferred method when I know I'm in for the long haul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Palm or wrist implants linked to your bank account. No more wallets, everything tracked with a wave of your hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? I don't know that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preferred pastry.

Doughnut: Good.

Rice cake: Pure evil

Muffin: Awesome, kinda.

Bagel: Dr. Evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I went to pick up my daughter from daycare, only to learn that her mother had withdrawn her from the daycare without telling me, and was refusing to let me see her, without an explanation. Oh, and she called the cops on me when I tried to ask her why.

I know, it seems like a purely emotional thing, but I felt like I was being torn in half from the inside out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breaking bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like antiques road show and extreme makeover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't speak French either, but I'm pretty sure that sign is warning you that there's a risk of electrocution. Be careful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An unladen Swallow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a knife, toilet seat, and the mechanisms inside the tank. I'll be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inability to accept the possibility that they are capable of making mistakes.

And I don't mean like, "oops, I left the door unlocked, my bad." More like this:

"hey, could you do X for me?"

"Do X?"

"No, I said do Y. Weren't you listening?"

"I was. I heard X. You might have misspoken, though."

"No, I said Y, you need to listen better..."

Etc, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crazy train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because one is cheap and meant to be thrown away, and the other just gives you more dishes to wash at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about how far you've come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currency, as a concept, doesn't exist. Just, you know, poof that from everyone's brains.

Everything that exists is available to those who need it. Ask for it, come to a mutually beneficial agreement, and move on with your life.

Basically eliminating greed.

(I know, it'd probably backfire horribly, but a person can dream, right?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Married my ex wife in the middle of a custody battle, after which the woman tried to have my child taken from me by claiming an ridiculous number of alarming behaviors by me. 

He just watched. Now, he's forced himself into my child's life as her stepfather. 

I won full custody, though. Thank god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see... An asshole is generally rude or obnoxious to most people in his path, knows it full well, and wouldn't change it. A douche tends to act similar to that, but tends to be genuinely unaware that there might be something unsavory about his/her behavior.

Dicks and tools follow about the same definitions as above, but they're more targeted. 

Examples: An asshole wears the opposing team's colors on the home team's side to piss off the fans. A douche does the same, but only because they got better seats on that side. A dick, when confronted about this behavior, will use sarcasm or general bigotry to try and belittle the person who approached him, and a tool will render a self-serving bullshit apology, but do nothing further about the situation . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 23:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, it's called reddit. Since coming here, I've forgotten how to...

Um...

Ok, I can't even remember what I did before finding this place. Did time exist? How can time be real if my mind isn't real??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 23:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I knew a guy who tried to draw a stick figure of a nude girl in a lewd position, but was so good at drawing that he automatically gave it tone, depth, and some reasonably good shading before he caught himself. That's the only time I can think of that someone accidentally sketched porn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 18:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoot me in the face!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 01:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good people do the right thing, even when no one is watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 01:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boobs are pretty great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 01:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stapling your still-attached scrotum to your eyelids, cutting out the testicles, pulling out your eyeballs, and tying them together in a square knot while having wafer-thin segments of your penis sliced off by a white-hot blade and being fed the cooked meat from your own member.

There you go. Show me someone who's turned on by *that*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 22:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't tried it, restart your computer. If that doesn't work, try reinstalling the game. A file may have gotten corrupted, causing your problem, and a clean install would fix that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 05:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Answers on page 91." 

It's a Sudoku book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 17:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I took my drivers test, I actually lost points for doing that. They wanted me to turn and look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 12:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American driver here. In many states, all you need to get your license is to pass a written test, and then a skills test. While drivers education classes are everywhere, they aren't often a requirement of the state. Most people learn just enough from their parents to pass the tests. Many dump that information right away when they're done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 22:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just spent waaaaaaaayy too long trying to figure out how you made those blocks with the F's on them.

There are no F blocks. They are fences. I feel dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 18:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad I could help! A bit of warning, though, the first game is a bit dry, and clunky. Outside of the main story, it just feels tacked on. That said, very worth your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 17:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ****POTENTIAL SPOILERS BELOW****
Though I'll try to keep it clean.

Recently played through the entire trilogy for the first time, as Male Shepard, hedging toward Paragon, pursuing the Tali romance.

Based on that sentence alone, you should be able to infer that there are many different ways to experience the Mass Effect universe through the games. I tried not to put in anything plot related, but there are so many choices you can make that effect later points in the story that you could play through a half dozen times, changing your decisions every time, and still not experience everything the game has to offer.

You can save someone in the first game, who returns in the third with advice or assistance. Or, you can kill them, gain an immediate reward, and never experience that interaction.

You can choose save all sentient life in the galaxy from certain destruction, or doom them to that same fate.

You can help a wandering species return to their home planet, or change the very nature of a hostile robotic army so that they'll help your cause.

If you're REALLY good, you can do both. 

(I did)

You can choose to  cure a species-wide genetic disease that stops a warmongering species from breeding - losing a good friend in the process - or lie to said species about doing so, gaining their trust and assistance under false pretenses and ensuring their eventual doom.

These are just a few of the experiences that youtube videos can't adequately reflect. You watch someone else's playthrough of the game, and you can't ensure continuity. The decisions from one video won't necessarily reflect on another. On top of that, you don't get the satisfaction of knowing that your decisions made these things happen. You won't struggle with the morality of your choices, or the long-term effects of your decisions. Who lives, and who dies, would - to you - be no more important than the lives of the characters on a TV show, and you'd have just as much control.

In short, Mass Effect is an experience that you will only adequately understand if you play it through yourself. You wouldn't have someone else read your favorite book to you, you wouldn't want someone else to raise your child and only tell you about the highlights. You'd want to experience all of it first-hand - the hysterical highs, the dark, depressing lows, and everything in between. 

Play. The. Game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 17:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to say something like this earlier, but I may have phrased it poorly: Why don't you ask him?

By which I mean, if you really want to marry him, why don't *you* propose, instead of waiting for him to do so. 

In other words, don't say "when the hell are you going to propose," or anything like that. Just do it yourself. "Will you marry me" sounds so much nicer, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 01:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waiting is all fine and well and good... But have you considered asking him, instead?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 16:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During the time frame of you reading this sentence, I am controlling your thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 17:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trapped in a universe where people don't pay their rent on storage lockers, so the contents get sold to the highest bidder, who then tries to make up the cost and profit on said contents.

So, I'm in the real world. Meh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 19:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world never existed, then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 21:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend of a friend came to my house a few times. Generally a great guy, fun to be around and had a great sense of humor. So one day, my friend brought this guy over and we had a fun night, drinking a bit and playing apples to apples. The guy has a little too much, and starts hitting on my friend, much to her discomfort. So, I take him outside, and we talk for a while as I wait for him to sober up some. 

Fast forward half an hour, to when the guy announces that he trusts me enough to tell me about the worst things he'd ever done. I think, this'll be something commonplace, like theft, or carjacking, or hiding your sister's birth control and a few months later finding out you're gonna be an uncle.

Nope.

Guy proceeds to tell me that he's killed two of his friends. Then he goes into great detail about how he was bored and stoned for the second one, and just broke the guy's neck and proceeded to copulate with his eye socket, just because he wanted to know how it felt. Never got caught.

I'm thinking, what the fuck? I've got a family here, and I let him into my house?!

Couldn't react that way, though, the guy was obviously seeking redemption or something like that. I told him nice things to placate him, and gently sent him home later. Never invited him over again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 04:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The darkest joke I know? 

A clown detonated a nuke in the atmosphere, killing half the world's power.

The lightest joke: He then killed himself with helium.

Ha. Ha. Terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 06:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legally speaking, you don't have to explain why you left your old job, even if they ask you. If they ask, you can just tell them that it's not important to this position. Or, you can just leave the field blank, on an electronic or written application. What most people don't realize is that companies who ask that sort of question to you or your previous employers actually set themselves up for either a slander or discrimination lawsuit if they decide not to hire you. Honesty only goes so far, man, and sometimes you have to decide how much of the truth they need to hear.

NEVER admit to having a poor attitude. NEVER badmouth previous employers. Those are the only things I can identify that you did wrong. Always be as positive as you can - nobody wants to hire anyone who presents themselves poorly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 06:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you manage to attract all the zombies to a central location, anyway? I mean, what's the plan, here, to use me as live bait? Am I going to be encased in plate glass, so they can see me but not reach me, keeping their attention so that they don't wander out of the ship before it can be launched? 

Or, does the ship require a living person to pilot it to successfully leave the atmosphere? 

Am I, perhaps, piloting a barge, with a separate, detachable storage container which houses the Zeds? 

Does it matter if they reach the moon, or can they just be jettisoned into space?

Would it perhaps be better to release them into orbit, so that they can all be incinerated upon re-entry?

Am I going to be the only person on the ship? And if so, what will my role be? Security? Pilot? Engineer?

I see some promise, here, but it has to be properly executed to be 

1)believable

2)practical

3)entertaining </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 00:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too selfish to cooperate, too proud to admit it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 05:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slippery when wet.

Caution: contents under pressure.

E=mc^2

Chocolate Factory

Loading dock.

Exit only.

Entrance only.

Just Do It

Canned Ham

That's five minutes' worth for you. Enjoy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 05:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A stamp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 17:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whale oil beef hooked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 22:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was more the method than the event for me. More how it happened than that it did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 21:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Primrose Everdeen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 23:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Life is pain. Anyone who says differently is selling something." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 08:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fuck kind of ham costs $90? Is it preserved in gold foil or something?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 00:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's how it worked for me...

I started with a person. I thought, something needs to happen to this person. But what? What's interesting? What story would be fun to watch unfold under my pen?

Well, who is this person? Man, or woman? Man, easier, since I'm male. I can write that perspective. What's his background? What's his motivation? Was he rich, or poor? Poor is more interesting, but let's go even further. Very poor, and young, not quite an adult, but has to work to help his family. His dad's worthless, and his mom's sick, so it falls on him.

Catalyst? Something has to drive him forward, a loss of some sort... his mother. Damn, that's dark, but that's the only thing I can see to push it forward. But it can't stick, I don't like that... what if his quest is to get his mother back? Revive her, somehow, or perhaps she was never dead in the first place? How does that go? Who can help him? In what way can this new person guide my hero on his quest? What comes next?

And so on, and so forth...

My world evolved from one thought, which I carried on asking questions about until I worked out the basic skeleton of the story. Once I'd narrowed it down to the absolute basics of the path my story will take, I started working on the details - secondary characters, support characters, their motivations and roles in shaping the story. After that, I worked on locations - where they're going, when, the history of said places, and features unique to these locations which could influence how the story goes forward. How did each location relate to any other location to be used? What other characters or events might happen to push the story forward as a result?

So, I worked out the basic path, the basic character interactions, some more advanced, plot-related character relationships, important locations, and the most essential locations necessary for key story elements. I wrote all of these things out in their own document before I even attempted an actual scene write, and each specific item was about six pages of reference material for when I got going.  All in all, it looks like it's going to be at least three novels worth of material, of which I've written the first two to completion, and rewritten all of the first and a good portion of the second already.

I had tried just sitting and writing with a vague plan before, and failed miserably. I got about sixty pages down, and then lost track of the story, despite my best intentions. Giving myself this fully-considered track to follow has encouraged the realization of my greatest feat of writing yet.  And I'm still improving, still moving forward.

Don't quit. Don't panic. Try really hard not to get lost.

And don't worry too much about number of words or pages. It'll be whatever it becomes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 05:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Masturbate while flipping them off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 22:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sometimes get stuck in videogames </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 22:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 03:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have! I've remarried, to a woman I absolutely adore, and who does far more than anyone should rightly expect to make sure everything that she can help make good, is done. The journey was rough, but I don't think I'd change a thing, knowing where I'd end up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
