<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7051</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friend of mine, who's a Vet Tech, X-Rayed a pigeon today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 21:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I called them tar babies once and friend said they were your version. I was a little mortified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 05:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Along those lines, Metal Mulisha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 05:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metal Mulisha anything for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 04:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like this:

http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/University_of_Tennessee_Anthropological_Research_Facility </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 15:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 05:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, Fort Mac.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 05:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call your mother, they are gone sooner than you expect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 03:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wife here, LOVE IT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 03:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, share! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 01:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to go yell at my diabetic husband now. (He's actually super careful with his diabetes). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 18 year old got his license a year ago and it was 9 3. I was taught 10 2. I actually drive at 7. I'm lazy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 19:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only month I haven't seen snow in Alberta is August.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 03:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit, me neither! I thought they hired Darryl Hannah for this movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 15:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother went through the same thing here in Canada. And my husband's grandmother. It used to happen in schools. They'd rap your knuckles with a ruler.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 05:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm left handed and a girl and mine points left. I dunno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 22:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At our house fruit is considered dessert. And coffee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 21:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family history is littered with heart disease, stroke, substance abuse and mental health issues. I made it out relatively normal and decided the best thing I could do for my kids was set them up for success, which effectively meant avoiding everything my parents did. I loved them as a kid but now I realize they were the world's shittiest role models. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents cooked rich, fatty foods and we never had veggies (unless they were in a can, blech). No portion control was taught and my brother and I were never encouraged to exercise or anything. Their parent modeling was not positive. I hit three hundred pounds at 29. Got my shit together and started eating right and my kids eat great, too! My 12 year old makes himself salad all the time. Loves fish and healthy stirfrys. Vegetables never last in our house, but my kids still have candy leftover from last Easter. They see so much more than we think they do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy lazing around after I've exercised knowing that I deserve to now. Just makes me feel like I accomplished something before hitting the couch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chickens are easy to clean up after, ducks are pretty gross. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 05:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, boys will be boys. I have no illusions about what my husband does either. And no. No broken arms. He has a girlfriend too, so if it ever happened I'm off the hook.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 22:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't one person being straight and one person being gay the ultimate incompatibility? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 14:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not dumb enough to think it doesn't occur. It's perfectly normal. The only thing that grossed me out was the fact that I was holding a tissue in my hand. It very well could've been for a runny nose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 06:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went looking for something in my 18 year-old son's room. His waste basket was overflowing with tissues so I turned to his father just as picked one off the floor and said "Boy, he sure has a runny nose a lot". The sentence wasn't even out of my mouth and I realized. I died a little inside that day. I have no illusions about what men do, especially young men.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 06:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no idea what he was talking about. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 05:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ginger as in ginger tabby. Big old ginger tomcat named Willis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 05:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even see the picture. My big ginger tomcat, Willis. He's kind of a dick. And a big whiny baby.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 01:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because my asshole ginger rolls in the fucking mud. And then sits outside the door and cries for hours if we don't let him in. It's either wash the bastard or listen to his shit all night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 09:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or he took a nice picture and wanted to share it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 09:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alberta here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 08:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where I live it's K-6, 7-9, 10-12. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 03:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Dad's birthday was Sept. 14th. Mine is Sept. 13th. My son's is Sept. 10th. It's a hard, hard time of year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 02:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck am I looking forward to being an elderly lady! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 02:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Dad died in 2008. It's still pretty raw and I still think of him every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 02:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only lamb that ever died on me looked like this. The hip bones are prominent and there is so much baggy skin it looks like there is muscle wasting. They need to keep an eye on this guy because lambs can be good one day and dead the next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 02:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to be that guy, but this lamb is terribly underweight. I've had a few bottle fed lambs and never have I seen such prominent hip bones. Please keep a close eye on this lamb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 02:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This lamb is horrendously underweight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 01:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can't spell procrastination without the letters N-A-P. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 07:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DFL trumps DNF trumps DNS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 00:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only idiots that think Alberta is a fiscal powerhouse are the Oil Patch idiots. There is literally a panic going on here right now. There isn't just oil in Alberta, guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 15:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://youtu.be/wXlvy3sTTBk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 05:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I miss driving a beater. Ding my door, IDGAF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 09:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shelob, dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 20:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with my 40 year old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 15:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard of it before after reading all the comments I now know, so can confirm, can get it from the context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 04:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fish are friends, not food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 01:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost my Dad 7 years ago, I feel the pain of his loss every day, we don't need assholes being fucktards about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 16:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to tell you because it's hurtful, but he said something to the effect of "now you're too late, he never will". Stupid fucking trolls. Completely inappropriate for a thread where people are sharing grief and leaning on each other. Sorry, end rant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 05:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I lost out on that. I can't even encourage him to get into trouble (just a little, it's healthy!). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 05:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7 for me in November. I still miss him every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 05:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, FUCK OFF.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 23:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My two sons and I are hardcore Star Wars/Star Trek/Lord of the Rings nerds, I'm a chemist, eldest dude is going for Instrumentation and youngest dude is a Nintendo nerd. My husband, their father laments constantly about being stuck in a house of "fucking nerds".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 22:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My eighteen year old is sketchy as all hell. Hyper alert, jumpy, a bit paranoid. We used to scare the shit out of him every chance we got when he was little. We're trying to take it easy on his younger brother. (but not TOO easy). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oliver says "Hello!". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 21:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 03:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of all the minorities to be a part of it had to be this one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 17:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine eats it, then pukes it up on the rug. It's great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 06:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I recall correctly you can be excluded from Canada for DUI, which is exactly how it should be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 22:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a guy riding a motorcycle the other day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 22:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have my in-laws, you lose! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 22:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the pools we go to the children are allowed to wear life jackets for the swim test and are marked to ensure that they are wearing the jacket in the deep end. It makes safety just a little easier in a huge pool full of rowdy kids. I 100% agree with swim tests.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 22:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a rivalry. Calgary just sucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 21:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a bratty as fuck kid and he's had an ass whooping less than a handful of times in his twelve years and he deserved them. That being said, I hate doing it, but it works as a reset button for his smart-assed attitude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 15:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So clever! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 15:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you attack someone for being skinny/fat/liking a song/having a different opinion than you it makes you the same type of person. Live and let live. I can have a different body type, lifestyle or opinion than you, you can say it's wrong, doesn't make your opinion anymore valid than mine. I stated fact about lyrics and my opinion and apparently that's less valid than yours because you don't like it. Okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 05:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was hyperbole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 04:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So 9/10 songs dig on fat chicks but you dig on a skinny girl, which I don't think the song does, and it's offensive. Uh-huh. You come on dude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 04:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And right after she says "Nah, I'm just playing" and "So you think you're fat? I'm here to tell you that every inch of you is perfect from the bottom to the top". The song isn't about glorifying curvy, it's about being happy with what size you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 07:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Married twenty years, have sex nearly every day, longest we go between is two days. It's glorious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 02:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh, ghetto rich. Buy what you want, borrow for what you need.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 01:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wondered why there was so much Cream of Sum Yung Gui. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 22:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll admit that they were entertaining, although I did read Twilight high on percocet shortly after major surgery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 22:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong, I love smut, I just prefer well written smut.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 18:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called smut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 11:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caught in the Act. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 02:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 03:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband is diabetic. He packs all his needles home with him and disposes of them in his sharps container. Exposing someone else to your needles is totally unnecessary! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 15:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yoko deserved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 05:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We found two in the span of a month. One when were out of town at a wedding, she hid under our Jeep and wouldn't come out, we finally got her out and she was skinny and ragged and my son fell in love. The second sat on our doorstep and meowed until I found him. When I opened the front door he walked in like he owned the place. We still have both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 17:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost my Dad when I was 32. He had just turned 60. Lost my mother when I was 36, she was 57. Never felt older than at those moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 18:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't work worth shit in my hair that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 18:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dog drools for that shit. And crayons, loves crayons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 14:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So get the special stuff for her and the normal stuff for everyone else. Serve her ice cream to her just like you would every other kid. No one would ever know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 03:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand what is so threatening about it. Get your motor running with porn and then use 'it' on your wife. Sounds like a good deal to me! (I'm the wife). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 23:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look in the comments above she confirms it is. UNREAL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 23:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I strategically placed my tattoos so they can be covered easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 22:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 22:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 15:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hamlet was also born in the caul.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 18:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My house is filled with knick-nack's. Things I love, collections, not hoarding. For example, I love roosters, boats, old oil lanterns, seashells and a few other things. All the rooms in my house are painted different colors. BRIGHT colors. When I was still with my NMom and Nbrother I could never have anything of sentimental value because as soon as they got mad at me they would destroy it. I still don't make strong sentimental attachments to things (or people for that matter). My room was plain as well. My mother even kept the sheets that were taken into police custody for evidence when I was raped by a babysitter at age six. And put them on my bed. Had the evidence number and everything on them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 19:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband bitches when I load the dishwasher. Guess who doesn't load the dishwasher anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 17:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Alberta, Canada, I haven't used a scraper in years. It is my goal each winter to avoid them. I hate them. Luckily I have a garage and remote start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 02:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmmmm. Sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 02:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad that she'll only ever be famous for losing her shit on her sister's husband.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 16:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's disgusting and proliferates female on male abusive relationships. Men are just supposed to take it. He must have done something to deserve it. Reverse the genders and everyone would be appalled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 16:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost all respect for her after that incident. No one has the right to put their hands on anyone. Either sex.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 11:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a woman, I find that mindset gross.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 21:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll never be at complete peace. It's a lark. You never completely heal from some things. I am happy, healthy and able to keep my boat-load of issues in check. What more could I ask for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 02:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to ask a serious question. Is this the type of person you want around your child? If the answer is "no", then you need to take steps to prevent that sort of influence on their life. And don't underestimate how much stress she puts on you. You'll be a much better and saner person without her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 03:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion, sometimes flipping someone the bird IS cathartic. It doesn't detract from the photo set. It adds a humorous flair and I love it. I would frame that shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 09:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine licks the inside of my nose until I lift the blankets. It tickles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 12:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally think it's a stupid line. I didn't need to forgive my mother for being a toxic, abusive drunk to get peace, I just needed the bitch out of my life completely. She died three years ago of cancer, the fact that she spent her last days suffering as much as she made me suffer gave me more peace than forgiveness ever could. Some things are unforgivable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 22:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoomp! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 17:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband is diabetic as well, so he can only drink diet, and I'm not willing to have a entire day's worth of calories in beverage form, so diet it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 07:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 07:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine's eaten multiple 1 pound chocolate bunnies without ill effects. She's ten and still kickin'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 20:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're saying, for the sake of my health, thatI should be lying half naked, somewhere in the sun drinking "fortified" beverages. Sounds like a plan to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
