<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5471</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Communist Manifesto, by Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels**

**The Paradiso, by Dante Alighieri** 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say it matters on the time period. I am not too well read when it comes to pre 1890's literature. I would say in no particular order- This Side of Paradise, I know why the caged bird sings, fear and loathing in LV, Either 9 stories or Catcher in the Rye. I know there are more but these ones are the ones that come immediately to mind.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a copy on my shelf. Is it hard to read? I have heard mixed opinions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science Fiction Classics- Asimov, Heinlein, etc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for some science fiction recommendations. I'd prefer classics that maybe aren't too hard to read. I'm interested in Asimov, Heinlein, Clarke, Dick, but also open to others. disclaimer- I have barely read any sci fi. thanks ahead of time
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you should definitely get some framed pictures or busts of writers, philosophers, etc. Another good idea is to keep everything organized, alphabetized, and neat. Yes that is obvious but you'd be surprised how annoying a search through a cluttered bookstore becomes. I think deals with trade paperbacks are always wonderful. Like 3 books for $5. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 00:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like The Catcher in the Rye Signet Books cover because A) If I remember correctly Salinger got mad because they depicted Holden B) The quote on the front C) It's just a beautiful cover. http://www.printmag.com/wp-content/uploads/Catcher%20pk.jpg

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 15:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Norwegian Wood. I haven't read his other books but I loved NW. There were times were I just wanted to hug the guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 15:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard "Look Homeward Angel" and the following books in the "series" by Thomas Wolfe are similar. I could be wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 21:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Neuromancer good? I have heard conflicting opinions saying 1. it is genius + well written or 2. It is clunky and annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
