<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject582</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 03:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you let him out into a larger pen/yard/field often /:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Study Finds Marijuana To Be Effective Against Depression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 02:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 08:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a coincidence at all. Withdrawals from anti-depressants and anxiety relief drugs can be brutal. He probably was off of his medication then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 08:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, but the problem was that he was probably off of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 04:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.store.coffeemugpipe.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 06:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're sweet when they're young, totally great and manageable. Once they grow up though, it gets to be a lot. They have a ton of energy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 19:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true. I can definitely confirm I went through school before College without a fuss, but then I got a huge wake-up call. I have to learn to actually do a lot of work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 18:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm twenty and my biggest problems are getting the same grades in college that I got in high school (mostly A's, seems basically impossible now,) and trying to find a part-time job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 05:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pumpkin Spice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 04:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What strain is this? Looks like a delicious orange kush type but I'm probably wrong haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 04:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cute, but it definitely needs a bigger pot by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 22:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope someone helped it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 22:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You go girl. I'm only twenty and can never imagine something like that happening to me. You're too young for that stuff and I hope to whoever's up there that you never meet someone like that ever again. 

In all seriousness though, You go girl.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 20:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then there's you. Dumber than a rock. Hey stupid, WHITE PEOPLE CAN HAVE NATIVE BLOOD IN THEM TOO. He's completely right, unlike you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 20:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White girl with Cherokee blood in her speaking. 

Stephen Colbert is an ignorant dummy. 

That is all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 22:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Jeff. So what's the deal with the U.S. not investing in solar energy? I know it wouldn't benefit major oil companies/corporations invested in them, but it would help out everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 12:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) states:

Exposure to radio frequency (RF) radiation has climbed rapidly with the advent of cell phones and other wireless technologies. Studies of the link between exposure to RF and to electric and magnetic frequency (EMF) radiation have found RF and EMF to be potential carcinogens, but the data linking RF and EMF to cancer is not conclusive. **World wide, health physicists (scientists who study the biological effects of radiation) continue to study the issue.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 12:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These technologies are being placed very close to civilian populations by money hungry property owners, anywhere. EVEN ON TOP OF APARTMENT BUILDINGS. 

Not safe, buddy. People make money killing us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 12:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you should continue your research. These technologies are being placed very close to civilian populations by money hungry property owners, anywhere. EVEN ON TOP OF APARTMENT BUILDINGS. 

Not safe, buddy. People make money killing us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The widespread usage of cell phones has led to increases in cell phone towers. Worldwide health organizations are now expressing concerns about RF from the towers near human populations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 19:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 22:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not as smart as you think you are. Do some research on how easy it is to get into some shelters. AND DO SOME REAL RESEARCH ON HOW MANY HOMELESS THERE ARE IN AMERICA. EMERGENCY SHELTERS? ALWAYS FILLED UP. OVERALL? 600K LAST YEAR. 45K KIDS, TOO, BUDDY. THOUSANDS OF KIDS EACH YEAR STILL FAILED. 

http://www.endhomelessness.org/library/entry/the-state-of-homelessness-2014 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 22:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 22:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've clearly never been to a hospital on a reservation, have you brother? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 22:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have our reservations, though. That is a pretty big win for us, however at the same time a lot of rez land of course is lacking and not able to be given back. 

- A Native American </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dramatic Stamford Shooting Captured on Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 03:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 00:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 00:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/V5iBCE7

^^ Here is where Gaza's military is located, right in between civilian households. Think that's a mistake?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terrified Families Fleeing Northern Gaza Airstrikes Seek Refuge With UN, but military bases are purposely set up in these populated regions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 00:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 03:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain to me how such a prestigious school hired this guy had he never put up any red flags? My money's on he did, and the school did nothing about it but cover it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 03:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It got me.

 I laughed, squinted, then laughed harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 19:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP was just stating facts, if you don't think it's some evil plot that's great but let people think what they think of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 03:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sad truth. People decided to stop caring this week and it's disgusting to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 21:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a shock, the art of language deems significant once again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 08:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a native from cherokee, fuck this is right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 09:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not going to be able to want to do anything until you have a regular schedule and are doing more things that keep you calm and happy. What always helps me is just a huge breakfast with my 275 mg dose of Effexor, and I can handle doing a good normal balance of things at University (I couldn't off the meds) like laundry, maybe one hw assignment, and exercise. Whatever helps will drive you to do things, but take it slow and put those behind you (thinking of the past and future is very hard not to do but you can learn slowly), finish what assignments you can, and just start brainstorming for next semester, maybe a lighter workload, apply as part-time, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 09:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've cared before, right? You have felt happiness and it is attainable again. It is a mindset that is achievable, you just got to find the right ways to tune in and find out what puts you at peace and do more of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
