<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4131</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is nothing blasphemous about believing that you yourself are a god as long as you follow the word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you believe that he is a djinn and not a ghost? That makes sense, as he is tied to an object and not a location. How can I find what object he is tied to? There were some weird objects in the house when we moved in.

Another poster suggested having my house blessed but my wife won't let a rabbi in the house and my priest won't help after I spread a rumor about him. Will a blessing stop a djinn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bible is the word of the lord, and the lord gave me my great wealth as a reward for being a righteous person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry the public school you went to failed you so badly. It's never too late to try and get an education  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There can be other gods as long as they aren't being worshipped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If u can, I suggest you read the Bible, there is nothing wrong with great wealth or skill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't presume to be as great as Christ  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tithe 10% of my income before taxes, that is the requirement  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Believe me, he does. Im sick at COD, it's not uncommon for other players to start to worship me. That is pretty much the worst thing you can do from gods point of view </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to express urself here friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carlos asked about the fat girl at the bar, I am married and wealthy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is ok because it doesn't draw worship away from the lord. Read your bible friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is serious, I don't know why these other guys are getting butt hurt. How do you feel about religion in games? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's absolutely true, are you one of those people who harass wealthy people online? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I already stated, my friend Carlos posted that question about meeting a girl at a bar. I am married  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Convincing of what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the same, my skill plus being called godlike absolutely draws worship away from the lord </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in a crowded train station and I really had to use the bathroom (#2). I hated to do it but I had no choice. I went in the gross bathroom and began my business. Then some guy kicked open the door, took a picture of me, and said it was going on the internet! Then he said to give him my email and he will give me the link. I thought if I knew where it was I could tell the police the address so I gave him my email address. I didn't want to risk my wife or family or coworkers to see it! He sent me an email that said he changed his mind and wasn't going to post it as long as I gave him a bunch of people I knew's email addresses. He said so he could sell them Herbalife products. I figured it would be better that they got a spam email rather then see me on the toilet so I gave him a list. Then he sent EVERYONE on the list the pic of me on the toilet, including my wife and children, my friends and coworkers and my boss. There was also a fake audio clip of gross sound! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else wish they would remove religious sysmbols from video games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After reviewing things with the other posters, I think your theory of me being the ghost is not correct. There are just too many things that don't add up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he was in the backyard, he got to the end of the backyard where there were trees and bushes and slipped through them out of sight. When he was in the basement, he was just gone one day when I peeked down. When he was at the store, I left quickly because I was scared and he was still on line so I don't know how he left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue with my priest is that I had been telling parishioners that he had gotten in trouble for going to an Asian massage parlor, receiving an inappropriate sexual type of massage, and then running out without paying. In fairness, my priest has a very common name so when I looked up his name on Bing and found the police log of the above activities, you can understand how I got confused.
I'll try and find a Wiccan who can help and report back.

I think we have confirmed by this point that the man is supernatural, but we don't know if he is a ghost or something worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make it illegal not to believe in the Bible, the word of the lord  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You couldn't be more wrong. There is only 1 record that goes back far enough that will tell you if global warming is real or not, and that record is the Bible. The Bible clearly states that only Ezekiel can change the weather </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a cool name but it doesn't tell us anything about you, plz try harder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did you decide on ur LOL name? Help me pick a new one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking YoungChillionaire or ChillionaireTheGod, what do you think? I'd like my name to convey that I'm young, wealthy, and totally chill! I'm open to any other suggestions, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok I will try and report back once I see him again, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my trouble just doubled! I couldn't deal with 1 ghost and now I have 2 twin ghosts!!! How do I go about finding someone to bless my house? I don't know any Wiccans, I am not on the best terms with my priest due to an issue a few months back, and my wife would never let a rabbi into the house </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you may be on to something, he may have been draining energy. In my basement I have a car battery that he may have been using and in my bedroom there is an iPhone charger!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can I tell which is which? One of the posters suggested I wear a wool glove that has been dyed green and has a quartz crystal sewed into it, will that help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do I need to take any precautions before touching a spectral being? Do I need to wear a glove made of wool that has been dyed green? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm shocked but I think I understand. Thank god you were here to help. You are saying that the man may not be a ghost at all. This man may be a living, normal human who purchased my home after me and my wife died, and we are the ghosts. I'm not sure how it happened, I can't remember when we transitioned to the afterlife. Now that it's dawned on me my world has definitely changed into a darker, shadowy realm. Thank you for your guidance, I must make the rest of my journey alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god. Are you saying he might not be a ghost at all, but rather some other supernatural entity, similar to demons or djinn? Now I'm getting really worried. Walk me through my options </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone who is knowledgeable about ghosts help me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently moved into an old house with my family. When I first moved in I met a man who lived in the neighborhood. I came back from work early and saw this man running through my backyard. I asked my wife and she was all disheveled, she said she saw him too. She then told me that this man had died recently and must be haunting our new home! I have seen him several more times, once in my bedroom while my wife was sleeping and for a few days he was in the basement. My wife told me to stay upstairs so she could hold a seance to get rid of him, but came back in a few hours looking exhausted, saying it didn't work. I also once saw him in the grocery store at the checkout! Are there any ghost experts out there who can help me, I want to move but my wife refuses too. She says I should just ignore the ghost! Is there any way to get rid of a spectral being!?!? Please help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone complains about foreigners on US servers, but what do you do to help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so tired of people complaining about Peruvians ruining online games. First off, yes they have bad internet and computers. So what? If they lose the connection just pause it. If they feed or spam, take the opportunity to try and help him mature. These people live in poverty, they need our help, not our disdain. I had a Peruvian on my team, and he died 5 times in the first 10 minutes. Did I freak out? No, I talked to him. I trained with him. I wired him money to help with his bills and family. A friendship formed. Now he is he is great player. I was invited to his village for his birthday, which was a great time. I ended up being intimate with a beautiful Peruvian woman. Be helpful, it pays off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why foreigners playing online games on our servers is a good thing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Everyone. I'd like to create an open and honest discussion about why using foreign servers is a good thing. This is a safe space for people to express their thoughts and feelings on the topic. Please no insults or flaming, and keep an open mind and open ears. Thank you.

Some people get bent out of shape when players from other countries play on their home servers. This is foolish. I play on servers all over the world. It helps me experience another culture and meet new friends. Some guidelines to help you do the same are:

1.Pause early and pause often. Each pause is an opportunity for discussion and culture.

2.Use google translate. If you don't speak the language, pause every time someone chats and input it into google translate so you understand

3.Stand still. If your ping is too high to play effectively, stay out of the game and focus on convo

4.Get to know the other players. Insist on discussion, if they don't answer consider grabbing their attention with pings.

5.Punish unwelcoming cultures. If ur teammates don't participate, send an message that gamers is a welcoming community by Intentionally ruining the game.

Remember, playing games can be a wonderful and cultural experience if you invest the time and energy to do it right! Thanks and good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hind sight is 20-20. I was just looking for a little boost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA Don't use the services of HapJaks Gamer Professionals, the dont protect ur info </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol this guy is so jealous of that 5 year old, deal with it bra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U prob tried to play and get rekt and so now you talk trash to Dota players on the internet cyberville  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh they do bro, they do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks friend! I will upvote ur last 50 comments! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dota rules, u would prob get rekt if Ubtried to play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that it's any of your business by Carlos isn't here legally so he doesn't have his own email. He was staying with me a few days so I let him use my account. Many people do it everyday.

Also I don't push or force, I usually just reach in. U r making such a big deal about it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
