<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8940</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the challenge is to actually read the books, not find them?

Edit - Though having a book scavenger hunt could be very entertaining.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pope Joan by Donna Woodfolk Cross.  I appreciated that there was a section included at the end with the evidence (circumstantial or otherwise) there is supporting the existence of a female pope despite the formal denials from the Catholic Church. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorcery and Cecelia by Patricia Wrede is a book of written in letters (fictions/fantasy)

A Week in Winter by Maeve Binchy

Chew on This : Everything you don't want to know about Fast Food

Career advice I'd have think about...

A Walk in the Woods by Bill Bryson

Lolita.  Anne of Green Gables.  Sabriel.  The Unexpected Mrs. Polifax.

Murder on Monday.  Tuesdays with Morrie.  Drowned Wednesday.  Thursday Next (also the name of the main character).  Friday Night Lights. Saturday by Ian McEwan.   The Sunday Philosophy Club. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will have to look that one up.  I saw the IMAX film that they released but there's very little detail about the incident in that so I am interested to read a more unbiased accounting.  Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had actually seen "Left for Dead" not too long before this post on Amazon and started thinking about the perspective he gave.  He was extremely harsh about Sandy Pittman and not very gentle about a few of the other climbers as well.  Not yet having read any of the other accounts, I wasn't sure if that was because the other climbers were truly that inexperienced and that much of a liability that day or if Krakauer's own ego kept him from being truly objective.  Maybe the trauma and the grief played in.

It seems like the majority of the other survivors have put out their own books on the events of that excursion, so I will have to start working my way through them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
