<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3042</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I still find however that it had the weakest cast of characters mainly in Chakotay Kes and Kim

I enjoyed Chakotay so far, but Kes and Kim might as well not even be there. I think DS9 had the best characters. Or at least the best relationships between them. You could really feel the hatred, love, or friendship between people. The bromance of Chief and Bashir, obviously, is very memorable. But my favorite was the questing beast antagonism between Odo and Quark. Dax, my favorite character by far, had interesting friendships with various characters. She was Kira's bff girlfriend, but she was also one of the boys with Bashir and Chief and she had a completely separate friendship with Quark that the others weren't really in on. DS9 didn't even need a scifi plot. I could just watch banter between those characters for hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC they didn't have Thalaxian anatomy on file or whatever. They just couldn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I most likely will, but it'll take a while since it's something like 10 episodes longer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! And I don't know if I sounded too critical in the post but I do enjoy the show quite a bit, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been intrigued by that character's name for a long time so I can't wait for her to show up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh man, I'm glad they replaced her, I did not buy that other actress for a second </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, and it wasn't as interesting as Spock split into Vulcan and human could have been, imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a chance to see this thing at an expo in 2010. It was pretty impressive. [Here are some pics](http://imgur.com/a/Owvob)

EDIT: btw this thing is made by a company that also manufactures equipment used to take out mines in a mine field </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit.

Looks like I'll be researching behind the scenes stuff for the rest of the evening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't, and to be honest I have no idea how much a TV show episode costs, so that number doesn't really tell me anything. Is that a lot? Also, 24 mil in today's money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the end, though, does that answer make the explanation any better? Spirit animals don't exist and whatever they would say, it would still be made up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a pretty funny line, but ["Get the cheese to sickbay"](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=circ3_-JJy0) was pure gold. Actually, now that I think about it, Learning Curve was quite a comedic episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, yeah, you'r right. I forgot about that. But it kind of proves my point. I mean, the movie came out what, 14 years ago? And he still ends up as a clean hero by the end of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I started watching Voyager. Here are my thoughts on episodes of the first season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started watching Voyager, having previously watched TNG, TOS and DS9 (yes, in that order) and I decided to write down some short opinions on each episode. If this post gets any traction I'll do more for the next seasons I have yet to see. **(So please keep the comments spoiler-free for seasons 2-7)**

**101 - Caretaker**

**Summary:** Voyager is tasked with finding a missing Maquis ship but they are spirited away to the Delta Quadrant by a mysterious space station that is beaming energy to a desert planet. There the crew discover an underground civilization worshipping someone called the Caretaker. Stranded 70 000 light years away from home, the crew begin their adventures.

**Opinion:** This episode felt very much like TNG's Encounter at Farpoint, which is to say it was all set up and introductions wrapped into an uninteresting plot. Compared to DS9's darker and more oppressive visuals (Cardassian architecture is the worst) I welcomed the more clean an bright look of a Federation vessel. The underground civilization, filmed mostly on location, provided for some solid production values and overall I think the episode did a good job of setting up intrigue for later. I expect the merging of Voyager's crew with the Maquis rebels will provide some tension later on. The cast is a roster of PC-friendly characters (a black Vulcan, a female Captain, a Native American officer, an Asian ensign) an I look forward to finding out who will become my favorites.


**102 - Parallax**

**Summary:** Voyager tries to help a ship stuck in the event horizon of a picturesque singularity but they soon get into trouble of their own. Meanwhile, the open post of Chief of Engineering is a topic of hot debate between Janeway and Chakotay, who wants to promote the hot headed former Maquis Torres. And the doctor is shrinking.

**Opinion:** This episode represented what I think of as typical Star Trek in that it combined wondrous cosmic anomalies and temporal shenanigans with the intrigues of command and Starfleet loyalty. It also helped to flesh out some characters, especially Lt. Torres. A standout negative of this fairly enjoyable episode was a very obvious infodump by Neelix, who literally took Kes aside to explain to her in a pretty childish way what a singularity is. I don't remember Trek ever resorting to such obvious explanations instead of assuming that the audience is well versed in such cosmic matters (though I might just be forgetting other such instances from the previous shows).


**103 - Time and Again**

**Summary:** Voyager investigates a planet destroyed by a recent explosion of polaric energy. A subspace fracture takes Janeway and Paris back in time to a day before the explosion, where they find the planet's peaceful occupants battling their government's use of polaric energy. Meanwhile, Kes begins to flex her dormant psychic powers.

**Opinion:** Perhaps this episode was meant to be an allegory to nuclear energy and its dangers, but I don't think this angle was conveyed successfully. However, it was another fairly typical Trek scenario with time travel and trying to stop a disaster and I enjoyed that quite a bit. Exterior shots on locations were also much appreciated as it gave the production values of this episode a nice esthetic boost. It was also the first episode where Kes had anything to do, which was nice.


**104 - Phage**

**Summary:** Searching for deposits of dilithium crystals to fuel the ship, the crew instead encounter a species of organ harvesters who steal Neelix's lungs. As Voyager pursues their ship, the doctor attempts to keep Neelix alive.

**Opinion:** I was intrigued by the idea of getting one's lungs stolen in what has to be the ultimate sci-fi mugging. I also liked the fact that Voyager needs to find fuel - in fact I was reminded of early Battlestar Galactica episodes with this plot line. Kes helps the doctor with some character growth and Neelix is more than comic relief this time, which I appreciated. The organ harvesting aliens were nicely designed, with make up that was quite gross and conveyed the idea behind this race very effectively. 


**105 - The Cloud**

**Summary:** Looking for energy reserves to fuel Janeway's coffeemaker, Voyager flies into a colorful nebula. However, it turns out to actually be a huge life form that the ship accidentally wounded by its passage. Janeway decides to heal the creature, much to the chagrin of Neelix, while Paris invites Kim to his holodeck hideout and Chakotay introduces the Captain to spirit animals.

**Opinion:** I though it was kind of ridiculous that the driving force behind this episode's plot was filling up depleted energy reserves and yet the crew waste a lot of energy running a holodeck simulation of a French tavern. The idea of a giant creature that can be mistaken for a nebula is intriguing but I didn't find this episode very engaging. Neelix's lamentations that Janeway puts the crew in danger by exploring stuff instead of just going home was pleasantly meta and on point, though, and it was my favorite part of this episode.

**106 - Eye of the Needle**

**Summary:** Kim discovers a micro-wormhole that leads to the Alpha Quadrant. It's too small to fly through, but they establish communications with a Romulan science ship on the other side

**Opinion:** This is the first time the crew actually worked towards getting home and they came pretty damn close. It was an intriguing episode and it did some good work establishing that they are really far away and they miss home (something I think the previous episodes kind of failed to do). It was a real bummer that the plan didn't work out, though I didn't expected them o get home in the first season, anyway.


**107 - Ex Post Facto**

**Summary:** Paris is convicted for murdering a scientist and sentenced to relive the deed from the dead man's point of view through a memory implanting procedure that causes him brain damage. Janeway is determined to prove his innocence and Tuvok investigates.

**Opinion:** I really liked the idea of punishing a murderer by making him relive his victim's ordeal over and over again. It was a cool concept, but I wish they did something more interesting with it. The aliens had terrible make up (I honestly don't know what they were going for with [this](http://imgur.com/a/tvJAd) mess) and the murder plot wasn't very engaging. 


**108 - Emanations**

**Summary:** Having discovered a new element in the ring system of a planet, the crew investigate an asteroid's cave, where they find dead bodies cocooned in a white webbing. A subspace anomaly then transports Kim to a funeral parlor on a planet where they're big on the afterlife.

**Opinion:** This episode had a very interesting idea behind a largely boring plot. The crew inadvertently shatter a whole culture's idea of the afterlife and they all have to deal with that. It's a great idea ripe for philosophical exploration but I don't think this episode's script was up to the task.

**109 - Prime Factors**

**Summary:** A famously hospitable alien race invite the crew for some shore leave and Kim discovers they have technology that could transport them at least half-way home. But they won't share it with them.

**Opinion:** Not a bad episode. Again, there is a great idea here that I don't think was explored enough. The alien race never shares their technology with anyone as a rule, because they don't want it to be misused. While the crew are angry about it, Janeway points out that other alien races might feel just as angry about Starfleet's First Contact policy and they should respect the rules of someone superior just as they ask inferior races to respect Starfleet rules of non-interference. Also, I once again did not expect them to get home so soon so it was obvious that the technology wouldn't work even when Tuvok obtained it illegally, so no surprises there.


**110 - State of Flux**

**Summary:** After the crew discover a piece of exploded Starfleet technology on a Kazon ship, Tuvok suspects they may have a mole in their midst. Chakotay's former Maquis crewmember and lover Seska is the prime suspect.

**Opinion:** This was a pretty good episode and it actually gave Seska a pretty good reason for working with the Kazon. My only problem with it is that there was really only one suspect the entire time and all the clues pointed towards Seska from the beginning, so there was no surprising reveal at the end. It was just like yeah, we were right the entire time.

**111 - Heroes and Demons**

**Summary:** Kim goes missing inside his Beowulf holodeck program and Chakotay and Tuvok disappear too when they go looking for him. It's up to the doctor to save them inside the program.

**Opinion:** I was kind of disappointed that another Trek show is doing holodeck malfunction episodes. I had enough of those on TNG, thank you. But, having said that, this was actually a good story and pretty enjoyable to watch. The doctor leaving the sickbay for the first time was a good way for his character to grow and experience new things. However, the final "something tells me this wasn't the last time" wink at the audience was pretty cringey. Yeah, I get it, there will me more holodeck filler episodes with the doc.


**112 - Cathexis**

**Summary:** Janeway's Victorian holodeck adventure is cut short when a shuttlecraft with Chakotay and Tuvok aboard is attacked. Chakotay is left braindead and the crew begin to act strangely as some unseen force is stopping the ship from entering a nebula and pursuing the attackers.

**Opinion:** I always enjoy episodes that have a "The Thing" vibe to them where crew members aren't who they appear to be and you can never know whom to trust. DS9's The Adversary is a favorite of mine for this very reason. Cathexis gave several characters stuff to do and it even gave Chakotay some depth despite the fact that he was absent in most of it. I was definitely glad the episode took this route as the holodeck cold open had me expecting something very different and much more tiresome. However, I'm noticing a somewhat annoying trend where either an episode doesn't deal with getting the ship back home *at all* or they come super close only for it to fall apart at the last minute. Will there ever be some middle ground where Voyager just gets *closer* or they achieve *a step* in some greater plan to get to the Alpha Quadrant?

**113 - Faces**

**Summary:** The organ harvesting aliens from 104 kidnap three crew members including Torres, whom they split into her Klingon and human selves. 

**Opinion:** I wasn't expecting the Vidiians to make another appearance but it' a good thing they did. After intriguing me with stealing a whole set of lungs they did something even more interesting and split Torres into two people. Her strong and brave Klingon version inevitably clashes with the weak and scared human and it was a fun way of exploring the character. I only wish this duality was more central to the episode, as it took a long while before the two Torreses even met. It also got me wondering what it would have been like if they made an episode of TOS in this style and split Spock.


**114 - Jetrel**

**Summary:** A member of the Haakonians, a race warring with the Talaxians, arrives on Voyager. He is responsible for creating a WMD that wiped out a whole Talaxian moon with Neelix's family on it and now he is looking for the cure to a disease caused by the fallout.

**Opinion:** This was an interesting episode that might be best summarized as a meeting between Oppenheimer and a Japanese war veteran. It gave Neelix an unexpected depth that made him out to be a much more serious character than previously presented. While the pace of the episode was quite sluggish, it had some very interesting conversations and introspective moments, making it another example of classic Trek: slow and deep. But I thought the final reveal of the episode, that Jetrel was actually trying to resurrect vaporized people, was a bit too much and it certainly needed a long conversation on the ethics and nuances of bringing people back from the dead.


**115 - Learning Curve**

**Summary:** The ship's irreplaceable bio-mechanical circuits ale malfunctioning and Tuvok is tasked with training insubordinate Maquis crew members.

**Opinion:** This was a great episode (albeit not as a very good season finale) and I think this is what most of season 1 should have been about. The writers had so much potential stories about integrating the rebellious Maquis people into the Starfleet crew, but instead they wasted time with standalone stories like Emanations or Ex Post Facto. This episode was what I was hoping Voyager will be when I started watching. I can only imagine how amazingly the merger of two rival crews would have been handled on a more gritty show like BSG. But when I look back at the 15 episodes, I guess I can't really complain that much. I think Voyager had a better first season than TNG and if it only goes up from here, then I'm hopefully in for something good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/movies would explode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I can't stand Redmayne's acting and I think Garfield nailed it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually people post this info to show what the movie is up against so I though of it as showing competition instead of just mentioning what else comes out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 10:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It will collide with Ninjago, and be released a week before Kingsman 2, and two weeks before Blade Runner 2049.

I don't think any of those titles are really competition for this film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Name your favorite actor/actress and a type of role or movie they haven't done yet that you would like to see </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 09:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a couple of favorite actors and actresses but I'm gonna go with Tom Cruise. I really like his movies, I've been a fan for most of my life and I admire his dedication.

But Tom usually looks amazing in all his roles and that really takes away some of the believability for me. I often find myself watching Tom Cruise instead of watching a character played by Tom Cruise and this is mostly because of how great he always looks. When was the last time he was dirty, unshaven and had messy hair? (Obligatory mention of Tropic Thunder... aaand moving on.) He rarely changes his physicality and I don't see him ever losing a lot of weight or gaining a lot of weight for a role. And I don't really need him to do shit like Christian Bale. I would just like to see him in a totally down to earth role where he just plays a middle aged dad who's way past his prime, with gray messy hair and a five o'clock shadow, cracking dad jokes to his bored teenage kid. The closest he ever came to that sort of role was the working class divorced dad he played in War of the Worlds, but even that was just immaculately looking Tom Cruise in a baseball cap and jeans saving his kids from explosions. 

What are your picks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 09:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that was really dumb. And the station was so ridiculously huge and advanced that it made Deep Space 9 (Terak Nor) look like a stone age pig sty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why Denzel specifically? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> girlfriend loves dogs, I love women in bikinis

this is a gif for everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how many times are people going to post this scene? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that scene is the only really great thing about that movie (great as in memorable, stand out, holy shit moment) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There have been numerous mentions of "industrial replicators" on DS9 so I would assume they have to tow some huge replicators somewhere and then they use those to create the stations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> finding one of these would cheer me up immensely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The second season was dragged out. It could easily have been just 8-10 episodes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot unsee the compressed air tank in one of the chariots

edit: [pic](http://i.imgur.com/GWjOU.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 10:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't every movie a genre movie? I mean, even a drama is a genre.  A biopic is a genre. A musical is a genre. Why do people cluster scifi, action and fantasy as genre movies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no idea how happy I am to read this since I have the exact same opinion! Other people don't seem bothered too much by that narrated montage scene but I fucking hated it. It's my biggest problem with the movie. I mentioned this in a [post](https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/5uash7/i_rewatched_arrival_and_i_think_its_a_nearperfect/) I did recently about Arrival but the whole thing didn't go over very well since apparently it's sacrilege to criticize Dennis Villenueve's work on reddit, but that scene was really out of place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't let it last more than four hours, though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I really missed the slowpoke meme](http://imgur.com/a/FLm8M) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you could argue that having a very weak and forgettable villain and still being a great movie is a testament to the strength of the characters and the story. To me, Logan wasn't about Wolverine's fight with a bad guy so much as an existential, violent road trip exploring fatherhood and old age. The badguy was there just to jumpstart that story and I don't think either the doctor or the robot arm guy were all that important, or really needed to be. The standout villain of the movie was X-24 - essentially Logan's old, berserk self that he's spent so much time running away from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> many car scenes look obviously fake even today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I view the Mad Max movies as folk tales with Max as an almost mythical hero (Paul Bunyan, maybe) so in that context it makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no problem with the idea of a ghost army. It's actually really cool. It's the execution that killed it for me. The way those ghosts look like a weird green wave that just sweeps across the battlefield is terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I still really like the movie but that sci-fi aspect always strikes me as out of place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, the rubber alien outside the escape pod at the very end of the film is way worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean "Instead of a dark lord you would have a Queeeen!" ?
I always enjoyed making fun of that scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your least favorite part of your most favorite movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming you don't deal in absolutes and don't consider your favorite movie to be absolutely perfect and flawless, what is your least favorite part of you most favorite movie?

My most favorite movie is Blade Runner and my least favorite part is when Deckard pretends to be an inspector at the night club and he does a funny (effeminate?) accent. It really doesn't fit in with the rest of the movie's serious tone and overall subtlety.

What are your picks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  this is series of movies about a teenager who gains the powers of a spider

Except he looks more like a teenager's father - which is why I hated the casting of this movie. Maguire was 27 when the first movie came out and 32 by the time the third one came out. Contrast that with Tom Holland, who is currently 21 and still looks pretty young.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never heard of it and google didn't come up with anything useful beyond a game for android, but I guess I'll take your word for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy in front of me on the escalator carried fruit in an orange metal basket hung on a string </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but on top of that it was also a prequel to Spiderman Homecoming and Black Panther and probably the second best Iron Man movie, too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always though that Civil War was more of an Avengers movie than a Cap movie, though. There are just too many other characters for it to be straight up Cap. This is why I think WS is a better Cap movie than CW but CW is a better Marvel movie than WS. If that makes sense.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of like your comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first attempt at tilt shift - this is the old town center of Bratislava from a bridge lookout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What does it actually mean when a deodorant or antiperspirant claims to have been developed with athletes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they ask an athlete to test their products and see if he sweats/stinks after a run?

EDIT: I don't mean when an actual athlete is shown in an advertisement (his face/name visible, someone famous). I get that this is just an endorsement. Sometimes they literally say they developed it with athletes as if the athletes were there during R D or something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a cast and crew are so amazingly talented that they manage to make a really good remake of one of the best and most influential sci-fi action movies of all time then imagine what that accumulated talent would have been capable of doing with an original idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I can tell, only one person chose to draw something from Alien 3, and it looks great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the blue headless fish is supposed to be a headband. [Parker wore a blue one.](http://imgur.com/a/tWPJ3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the best one. Should be framed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was only ten when the first movie came out and the best quality I've ever seen of it was on dvd. I would love to see it in the cinema. But not a remake or reboot. Never. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to keep spoiler free so I don't want to watch this video but from the thumbnail I gather the person has only seen 12 minutes of the movie. Can you really condemn a whole movie based on a 12 minute excerpt?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> someone at Honda should consider *seppuku* at this point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No love for Jane Levy here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Jessica Chastain - Dark Shadows (not Tim Burton's)/Mama

She was already Oscar nominated for The Help and for Zero Dark Thirty before Mama came out. I'll give you Dark Shadows though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, being ignorant of something is pretty much the definition of not giving a fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that was a pretty poignant episode. I hope the show will be back with a second season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They enjoy losing money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's said that 50% of the director's work is casting. If I'd just take Fincher's (amazing) casting, I wouldn't be doing half of my job.

Wow, that is some amazingly flawed logic. According to that, every sequel that's not directed by the original's director should be recast. So, no Weaver in Aliens, no RDJ in Iron Man 3, no Radcliffe, Watson and Grint in Prisoner of Azkaban. I guess according to Alvarez's logic, James Cameron, Shane Black and Alfonso Cuaron are lazy directors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the shows that usually grip a large audience are the ones on netflix, anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Columbo: The case of the grandson who hates fairytales </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's too bad she won't live, but apparently the franchise does" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to see Silence. Theater was about a third full. The movie was supposed to start at 6.30pm. Which means at 6.30 the lights go out and trailers and ads start. There were about 15 minutes of these before the movie actually started at around 6.45pm. About ten minutes into the movie, a middle aged guy and his wife (I assume) walked in. So they were 25 minutes late! I don't understand why the attendants even let people in after the lights go out, not to mention after the movie starts. But this isn't even the worst part.

In my country we have assigned seating, rows and seat numbers. This dude walks to some people sitting in front of me and, standing above them and blocking the view, he starts harassing them that they are sitting in his seats. I don't know if that's true or not (sometimes people confuse which row they're supposed to be in because they are labeled in a bad way) but anyway, it was his problem that he came in 25 minutes late. He should have just sat somewhere in an empty spot and leave everyone alone, which is what some people told him. This back and forth went on for a while and the dude was still blocking my view and people sitting behind me as well. I asked him how much longer this was going to take and several people shouted at him to sit somewhere and leave everyone alone because he was ruining the movie. His reply to everyone was to fuck off. Finally the people just moved over and they sat down. Then about 30 minutes later he turns around and asks me in a pretty loud and disruptive voice what my seat number is. I would've loved to tell him to just shut the fuck up, but I figured he would just be more disruptive, so I just told him the number. He started looking around my row and informed me I'm not sitting in the correct seat (I 100% was). I still don't understand what his problem was. Then literally about two minutes before the movie ended his wife got up to go to the bathroom, taking her sweet long time blocking the view and walking through her row, disrupting other people that were sitting next to them.

edit: some words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I edited the comment for clarification, hopefully to your satisfaction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captain Obvious to the rescue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fried Butter

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> War on drugs in all its pointless glory. As if taking down that one small plane will stop a whole drug cartel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you mean Hailee Steinfeld's character, the actress was also 20 when the movie came out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I've seen some rumors Inarritu might be coming out

Oh?

 with something this year

Oooh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn this guy kills me every time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> links? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree with what you're saying, but I have to point out that those mid-season cliffhangers always felt cheap and forced to me. It always felt like the writers just forcefully came up with some huge moment to end the last episode before hiatus just to make sure people would tune in again in a couple of months. If you have to make a huge cliffhanger to keep people's attention then your show probably isn't all that great. If they had a really good show with compelling characters, people would want to come back to it regardless of cliffhangers. What I always hated the most about these things was how they always got resolved so quickly. Example: In the last episode before hiatus, suddenly out of nowhere one character shoots another character in the last ten seconds of the episode to create a cliffhanger. Four months later, the new episode starts. The gun jammed, nothing happened, nope, thanks for tuning in, here's the rest of our show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 09:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I also have a video to share](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FTQbiNvZqaY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think what he was trying to say was "stop making movies about racism and racism will go away" which kind of makes sense and doesn't at the same time. Racism is the sort of thing where even good publicity is bad publicity, because no matter what anti-racist statement you make, you're still talking about racism and fuelling that word, keeping it alive. It reminded me of an interview with Morgan Freeman where he condemned Black History Month because it reduces an entire race's history to some sort of weird 30 day event. IIRC he argued that it shouldn't be called Black History Month, it should just be history. Calling it Black and making a thing out of it is just another way of separating it from white history.

edit: [the interview](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FRnTovm26I4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, this was a weird one but otherwise the channel is pretty good with a focus on action movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His take on the Netflix "release it all at once" model is surprisingly old-fashioned. On the one hand, I get what he means when he says: 

 I would want people to come back every week and have the experience of watching something at the same time.

That kind of "holy shit, did you watch last night?" conversation the next day at work is great. But that's not a lasting thing and it's not a universal thing. The shows get syndicated to other countries that might air them differently (one station in my country usually airs at least two episodes back to back) and you have the home video releases. The experience is fleeting and cannot be repeated. So why limit yourself by adhering to it?

I would also argue that "holy shit, did you watch last night?" is still applicable even with binge watching. When Stranger Things came out, it was still a major water cooler conversation topic. It's just that people talked about multiple episodes instead of one. Experiencing a show together and binge watching are not mutually exclusive things and airing something weekly does not guarantee the communal experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to be *that* guy, but I think Buffy became one of those not very good shows sometime after its third season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't the "Toho" part of the copyright that was spoilery, though. It was the "Godzilla, Mothra, King Gidorah, etc" that gave it away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So those pointless shoehorned token Chinese characters like the scientist in Kong Skull Island or the pilot in Independence Day Resurgence are annoying to them, too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the very end where [the characters end up together, their lives improved after their experiences, and everyone lives happily ever after?](#spoiler) Yeah, that was a total fucking trope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP, was [this video](https://youtu.be/2Lj2LmJowwQ) an inspiration for this post by any chance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if by clever you mean stupid and obvious, then yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else notice how during the end credits the Toho copyright claim spoiled the reveals of the after credits scene? On Guardians of the Galaxy they showed the copyright for Howard the Duck *after* the scene. But not here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is Heat + Drive + Scott Pilgrim? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, thanks WB, now I don't have to watch the movie anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How is frozen food still perishable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do frozen foods still have a best before date? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just seeing the one, but on a big screen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it. Where are all the bad hombres? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a viral marketing campaign extending the universe of the movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is not a trailer, though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mein Kopft tut mir weh trying to decipher that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is really cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a neat video. I liked the mesh masks. 

I really hope the marketing campaign for this movie won't turn out to be far better than the film itself. (Which, I feel, was the case with Prometheus.) For example, that previous video they released with the going-away crew party was great, but I sure hope the film itself will manage to show us the bonds between the crew and not just rely on us having seen the youtube clip. The movie should speak for itself without prior external knowledge filling in blanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, Ferrari will screw the drivers with bad strategy and pit lane fuck ups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The imdb page of this movie doesn't have a rating or even a year for the movie. That is kind of weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It did feel quite pointless to me, too. I definitely got the sense that they left out all the most interesting and dramatic parts in-between the periods depicted in the movie. It definitely felt weird to me that [Mahershala Ali's character died offscreen, so we never even got to watch how Chiron dealt with losing a father figure.](#spoiler) I also thought that seeing the transition between Chiron's confused and bullied high-school self to his tough adult version would have been interesting to watch instead of a short recap in a diner room conversation. The film was very episodic and only lightly touched on themes without actually exploring them. Even the LGBT angle that is so talked about felt underdeveloped to me. There were only three short instances of Chiron's homosexuality even coming up. As a kid he asked what faggot means, as a teenager he had a brief sexual encounter and as an adult he had a quasi date. That's it. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC this was just the marketing campaign  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also: 

Generation Kill 

Saving Private Ryan (obviously)

The Big Red One

Letters from Iwo Jima </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 13:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  looks CT

see through? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 11:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going to Tokyo in April. This does not give me much confidence that I'll be able to navigate the city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No cell phone signal / characters that don't just solve a situation easily with a phone 

Horror movies still haven't adapted to the modern age where phone calls are readily available to everyone and phones can solve a lot of situations. Most horror movies do one of these things to work around phones:

* there's no signal

* battery runs out

* the character inexplicably just doesn't use the phone

* the setting is in the pre-cell phone era or the existence of phones is ignored

[The Monster](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt3976144/) is a movie that totally subverted this cliche. A woman has a car crash in the middle of nowhere on a forest road but the phone works and she actually immediately takes it out, calls for help and the help actually arrives. I was dumbfounded that this happened. A working phone that was used with a positive result. In a horror movie. Wow.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The comment was meant to be tongue-in-cheak but I guess it didn't come across </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the difference is that us redditors are simple everyday people who shell out their hard-earned money to enjoy two hours of escape from reality and we are annoyed by a stupid ad ruining that experience. Whereas these actors bitching aboyt casting get paid millions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's interesting that they included John Boyega as someone "landing prominent Hollywood roles," which I guess is a reference to Star Wars - the franchise filmed in England and filled with a shit ton of British actors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/tipofmytongue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the Brits are better actors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my favorite part:

 "They come here because there are more opportunities and they actually get paid when they work here."

 But, he added:  "We've got a lot of brothers here that need to work too."


That sounds A LOT like Trump talking about Mexicans. Should Hollywood build a wall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then maybe he shouldn't play a super villain with a speech impediment in a British spy movie, because how could he possibly understand that role? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think the characters and performances are really bland all around and the themes of the movie are very surface level and not very subtle.

The characters deal with incredible emotional struggles and the movie is filled with introspective scenes. Roy Batty feels more alive and has had more experiences than most real people, yet he is doomed to die, making all those moments he lived through lost like tears in rain. He wants nothing more than to prolong his life. It's a great struggle for a character and an interesting theme. Tyrell basically makes these replicants completely human, giving them memories and the ability to have emotions, yet he gives them just four years to live, essentially sentencing sentient beings to death. Does he have the right to do so as their creator (manufacturer) or do they have a right to live?

Rachael's story is also extremely intriguing and imo very well acted. She is a person who finds out that she's not actually a person but a machine with someone else's memories, which completely destroys her identity and self image. But it also raises an interesting question about what it actually means to be a person and how do you define that. Were her emotions fake just because her memories were fake? Or does she has legitimate sentience and the same rights as humans?

And of course we have Deckard, whose identity is completely ambiguous and up for debate. Is he a real person or just another replicant designed to hunt other dangerous replicants, essentially a tool to do people's dirty work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 11:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never interpreted that scene as rape. More like Deckard forcing her to acknowledge the emotions she is dismissing because she has a huge identity crisis. He more or less orders her to say that she loves him. As in: if you love me, just say it, it doesn't make a difference that you're not human, you feel love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 09:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something similar was done two years ago in the Czech Republic, but with a Jim Carrey impostor. A team from a TV show did it, it was very covert and no one had a clue that wasn't the real Carrey for several days, IIRC. here is an [article](http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/movies/jim-carrey-impersonator-crashed-czech-oscars-revealed-article-1.2127493) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not the fault of the movie. It's the fault of a shitty education system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep he was a blade runner, too. I am fairly certain that the police chief mentions this to Deckard when he has him in his office. If not directly, it's at least implied. There's also an interesting deleted scene where Deckard visits the guy in the hospital (he survived the shooting)

Edit: It's also clear that the opening scene happens in Tyrell Corp. So not a mining company. I guess the replicant was trying to infiltrate Tyrell Corp (probably by getting employed there) to gain access to Eldon Tyrell and he was discovered through this screening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't make it impossible by any means. Not that I'd want them to do it. Just sayin' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won best picture not best documentary. 

I'm not saying it's ok for historical movies to be inaccurate but I strongly believe the inaccuracies don't detract from the strong filmmaking craft, performances, visuals, score, and overal emotional impact of the film. And those are the things that made this film best picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article was ok but I hate sites full of ads and since the title of your post suggests only photos, I decided to provide only photos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I didn't know this movie was her baby, that's cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know they didn't just hire a pretty face but a dedicated actress. But damn she's rocking that Blondie look </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [here are just the images](http://imgur.com/a/qGOG7) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, the plot is just there to service all those philosophical questions and I love all of them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
