<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9746</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll never forget reading that last word of the chapter and just thinking "George, you bastard." Great choice here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You da bomb.com  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Six of Crows duology had a pretty satisfying ending I thought. I couldn't put those books down. 

Edit: A word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently reading Columbine and it is probably the most unnerving book I've ever read, especially because it's non-fiction. I was pretty young when the tragedy took place so I wanted to know why these kids did what they did. I've only gotten through about 100 pages or so of it but wow is it an intense read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This^^^^^^

I'm not a fan of constantly texting someone that I'm currently seeing and I will always be upfront about that. I'd much rather spend time with them in person but I can see why some people do enjoy constant communication, however it's just not something I personally enjoy. Now, OP, I would say the "it depends" situation is about the context of the text message. If I see my SO message me something that may require an immediate response, then I'll reply within a reasonable amount of time. If I see it's just a random conversational text message I'll probably do what you did and put it off for a while (especially if I'm at work). I would try to talk to him and let him know that you're just not the type of person to respond instantaneously to messages unless it's something urgent. I always figure that if it's truly urgent they'll call but that's just me. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, same here. I'll never forget reading that scene during a college Bio class and I read the Red Wedding scene (including the Arya scene following it) and looked up all bug-eyed thinking to myself "Is anyone else seeing this crazy shit that's going down?!" Sadly it was just me haha. I would definitely say the "For the Watch" part in ADWD got me the worst though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perks of Being a Wallflower really hit me hard and continues to do so each time I read it. A Song of Ice and Fire (A Storm of Swords and A Dance with Dragons) left me in straight despair after some of those chapters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
