<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3445</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's not the only thing that ripped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Beat a Claw Machine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minneapolis police officer charged with kicking suspect in face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miami police officer arrested after allegedly robbing people he pulled over </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miami police officer arrested after allegedly robbing people he pulled over </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kill nightmares, baby, and make your dreams come alive! I've got a 12K sq. ft. yard full of cars we could sand together. Perfect day for it too; it's a radiant 23F today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed; that [unsupervised sanding](https://youtu.be/WAgJ5Tm4T6g?t=46s) changed his life.

Edit: Legend has it that he is still sanding cars that haven't been paid off to this day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww! I'll be your fan! [Go, go, go!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3nONOuNEhhE)

BTW: I'm still waiting too, brother or sister; I"m 41.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> assume to your doom
 
-me 2017 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too late; she traded it in or trashed the last one she would let you do that on before the end of the 20th century. Chevy Cavalier bought it brand new, and it died in five years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do! I pinky swear. Cross my heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He actually is 45 now; two kids, three houses, City job closing in on retirement. I think he shrugged it off by now. 

Edit: The [sanding exercise](https://youtu.be/WAgJ5Tm4T6g?t=46s) was a key part to his development.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cousin did that for my mom with sandpaper though. He was about 24, so don't feel bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wrote the script based off what he read on the F5. He improvised the words for the ad lib scenes, like the tornado chase, he also directed what the characters should be doing in each scene. I positioned the camera for him and worked iMovie for him to render it into a video. Thanks for the compliment; I'll let him know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you become her biggest fan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On road trips, I actually guiltlessly eat both. Washed down with a lot of free coffee. He's with you on the Occupy Time Out movement. We'll put your vote through committee.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 10-year-old son spent a couple of weeks filming this stop-motion video about the fastest car in the world for his writing homework. Please be gentle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not too sure, for he showed past defenders were unable to deflect a shot when the shooter pump faked, after being challenged by the left hand, and went up the middle. But he could probably be illustrating how even on offense "old school" players performed more effectively. I think his intended outcome was to highlight the mistake that the defender could easily correct by mirroring the ball with his left hand. Hence not a negative critique of today's total defensive approach, but just a recommendation on how that one deficiency can be easily corrected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His time in the NBA, together with MJ, marked the evolution of how they play today imho. He is definitely the ideal commentator on what worked during his time, before then, and now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isiah Thomas gives a great explanation of how a basketball player made a shot exploiting the defense then demonstrates how it was done in the past in comparison to how it is done today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, that's will power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merriam police rescue puppy from hot SUV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merriam police rescue puppy from hot SUV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reporter gets contact high off burning weed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Pepe Le Pew](https://youtu.be/OP7k4LXM1rE?t=38s) needs you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shoulda had a V8 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Will](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=azM6xSTT2I0) is alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was going to be a lot worse (e.g. a car running a red light causing a front-to-side collision); it looked like he would walk away from this accident alive though. Hope he was alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly; dozens as in multiples of 12. We had our 100 call days; but there was no robodialer or pre-recorded intro; we dialed the numbers ourselves; and we weren't allowed to hang up. I think we had to get approval for a follow-up call. Moreover, the calls that we felt had potential would last long; sometimes more than 20 minutes. 

I have been more effective allowing for follow-up calls and without hammering a lead until he hangs up; so the strategy did suck; but we were basically just burger flippers lifting the spatula the pre-determined amount of times.

Edit: these days were non-stop 7 to 7 shifts. You will be convinced that I worked hard and the job sucked :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote dozens because it wasn't hundreds of calls. You did spend some time with some people on the line on a few calls if you felt you could sell him; so you could only physically call the amount of people for which you had time. We weren't supposed to hang up on anybody, unless they hung up on us first. And we worked 7 to 7 nonstop. I would say the range was from 60 to 100 calls. 

Edit: No robo dialer or pre-recorded intro; this was like 95. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will probably keep us from destroying aliens after we treat and rescue them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crushing vice and other tough stuff with hydraulic press </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually worked in one of these chop shops about 20 years ago, selling stock for the Stratosphere in Vegas. The owner of the place didn't have to put on a big speech to get us to sign on, for making $200 a week didn't sound that bad living between a room and taking ladies to my aunt's unfinished basement at 19. Only two of us worked under some dude who said he was the Vice President of the firm. 

We would say we were him over the phone. 

We had to memorize a few pages full of rebuttals that we kept pinned on the fabric wall. I made dozens of calls daily. Everybody said no, hung the phone up on me, or gave me the run around. I learned how to talk really fast, and there were a few times that I was almost close enough to sell somebody, but they either stopped picking up the phone or said no on a follow up call.

After 4 weeks I made my first sale of 150 shares; however, I closed him myself; they never told me to refer the call to my boss. He simply called the client back and got him to buy more shares. My boss cut off my tie, and pinned it against the wall next to my rebuttals. After a couple of days, I was given $20 because I was supposed to have split it with my co-worker because he was behind me while I was on the phone. My commission was supposed to be a couple of hundred bucks. 

I was also supposed to get back pay for the weeks that I worked; I never got paid. I went to complain to the owner, and he left me waiting at his door. 

After that I was told I was going to be laid off. I asked my boss for my money; he said that the firm didn't have any funds. 

I spilled coffee over all the phones in our cubicle and walked out. 

Anyway, based on all the sales encounters I have experienced, Boiler Room is not too realistic. Not a lot of people will bite when you give them easy ways to exit the sales transaction like what they do in Boiler Room. 

Wolf of Wall Street, although may exaggerate somewhat, is more realistic. I would like to see what these guys do for Belfort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the most part human beings are a helpful and overall good species. These videos celebrate the best part of human behavior.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Natural selection; our attention spans are weaker functions that have been extinct. Our superior species is now attracted to everything.
On to the next random stimuli! Where was I? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abscess big as balloon on street dog treated and healed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] Casey Neistat's speech during this Samsung promo is oddly inspiring. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Kong virtual reality promo actually got my heart pumping a little bit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's crazy how once you think the part of the trail they're on is tough, then it gets worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYPD: Hate crimes increase 55 percent in NYC since 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-Semitic Hate Crimes in NYC Spike 94 Percent in 1 Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NBA Rookies on facing the GOAT Michael Jordan (1997) ft. AI, Kobe, KG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally with you. There have been so many improvements in medical treatments and collaborative technologies that I see senior citizens living longer and happier lives. I have met a number of them, including some family members, well into their 80's and 90's that keep getting fixed for a lot of diseases that would have probably killed them 20 years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Han is the smoothest player in the universe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Han is the smoothest player in the universe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven Baltimore police officers were arrested Wednesday on racketeering charges, accused of stealing from hapless victims who often committed no crimes and of filing bloated overtime claims that almost doubled their salaries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious; what makes it non-vegan?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahh; bodega [ramen](https://i5.walmartimages.com/asr/70513cc8-6133-4595-a75c-ce8e160a484e_1.f0c4cbcb844c73559bb1bd6963a3a860.jpeg?odnHeight=450 odnWidth=450 odnBg=FFFFFF); I always opted for a [St. Ides special brew](https://untappd.akamaized.net/photo/2016_04_24/8160b889440c713eb0ef5c23313b5350_320x320.jpg) and [beef patty with coco bread](http://farm7.static.flickr.com/6124/5937673768_32aa19ce7f.jpg). During my depression era. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that thing can chase you and stomp on you with the Mario hop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 95-year-old cooks Italian Ice as it was prepared during the Great Depression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steph Curry (in disguise) Helps Fan Win $5,000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lifeguard rescues a lifeguard during Elephant Man video shoot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's FCC wants to let your cable company sell your data, because who cares about privacy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It looks like the FCC wants to roll back rules that'd force internet providers to get your consent before selling your data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Person gives dog food, and the mother dog brings it back to its puppies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawking's Aliens --"I Am More Convinced Than Ever That We are Not Alone" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teen arrested for impersonating police officer, conducting traffic stop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> York County police officer charged with 50 counts of child pornography </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog with respiratory illness is taken off the street and nursed to full recovery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newborn puppies left to die in a bag by a countryside road are rescued. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cold... to be exact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Special effects pro takes his family snow tubing through Hoth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hopeless wounded dog dying on side of street rescued </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moon is on COLLISION COURSE with Earth, Will Take About 65 Billion Years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The police academy mantra is more like, "When in doubt, arrest."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll live... unfortunately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chattanooga police officer fired for false arrest, harassment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Threepio was REALLY telling the Ewoks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk says Universal Basic Income is going to be necessary. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probationary SPD officer arrested in connection with homicide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horse kicks girl in the head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he got got! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get that fake horse outta here!

["They better break north before we get the four pounders"](https://streamable.com/nexmh) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Driver barely escapes rows of collapsing trees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll lose so much weight on AYD's that people won't even see you anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or splurge and buy the $4 hand citrus juicer. 

But seriously; this is for that commando moment when you're stranded on a deserted citrus farm after you drank all of the coke. The tractor's out of gas, so you go MacGyver, baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like stabbing the alien to death and dying after its blood splashes on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wim Hof teaches Dutch actress how to effortlessly hold her breath for over 3 minutes and take an ice bath for almost 2 minutes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dominican newspaper mistakes Baldwin for Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's AG: "Fundamentally, almost no one coming from the Dominican Republic to the United States is coming because they have a skill that would benefit us and that would indicate their likely success in our society." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wichita police officer arrested for rape </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nine-year old girl wrestles alligators </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> lofi hip hop radio - beats to relax/study to [hip-hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man makes laser and lights matches painted and set up to look like Homer Simpson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man show face on camera stealing cash from laundromat safe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's like a broke Rosie O'Donnell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Jiz Angel can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's no mind jack; he gave him some head jack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not; each strictly drives a [Yeti](http://www.skoda.co.uk/SiteCollectionImages/Models/New%20Yeti%20Outdoor/Extended%20Model%20Pages/large_tile1.png). Anything else would be uncivilized.

Edit: I second your claim! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could just be the intro before the first verse; or an instrumental chorus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I know who I am!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was about to say he would have done great getting punished in the Army like in [those old cartoons](https://youtu.be/aDDvpTMABOQ?t=8m18s). But I didn't peel one potato during my entire Navy contract. Did chip paint, nonetheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 08:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bon appetit!
https://streamable.com/6ixid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I saw this thing like 16 years or so after it came out, and it was hot! New York City almost like I remembered it. There were shootouts and more murder when I was coming up though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 38 years ago yesterday "The Warriors" was released... "Come out to play-ee-ay!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Truck drives over baby who lays down just in time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Had to rub some Blistex on his lip to seal up the cracks. They're better moisturized now. 

Edit: Please don't call the chapped-lip police on me :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She reportedly [died falling on iron railing.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mdi5xRA8sGQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joven colombiana con visa de turista deportada al llegar a EEUU </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 14-year-old girl thrown off ride at amusement park in Chongqing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caught this on the news last night. That's an expensive outfit if the leaves are real.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sasquatch covered in cannabis leaves interrupts live weather report during snow storm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN reporter gets contact high and has amazing time with people buying and smoking cannabis in Colorado. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deputy accused of showing up to work drunk suspended without pay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Student beaten up for wearing Make America Great Again hat, gets suspended instead of attacker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so terrible; my heart goes out to the family of this man. But it's important for people to know, so they can be alert and very careful when dealing with snow. 

This accident is unlike it, but I got into a car accident years ago in the snow that could have killed me and my cousin. And the only thing that caused the accident is that he was driving at around the speed limit. The car skid on an uneven patch of snow and spun, knocked down highway light pole, and stopped after crashing into a tree. I had my foot on the windshield, so I wouldn't fly out of it when the car crashed.

Be very careful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice; it is a little Buddhist monk exercise. I get it from Wim Hof (he's my hero). I have read that tolerating cold temperatures holds a number of health benefits. You develop something called [Brown Adipose Tissue](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brown_adipose_tissue) that helps you stay fit and strengthens your immune system. First hand, cold showers always take any aches I may have when I work out too strenuously. I started by taking cold showers about 13 years ago. Now I could tolerate single-digit weather for a couple of hours before I start shaking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes; I do. Three times a week. The other three times, I work out at home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wife; trust me, I would have worked out in the house otherwise. Thanks for your concern.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Major shot out to Bushwick. That's my home away from home back in the day. Troutman and Knickerbocker; used to be all up Flushing, Broadway, etc. It was a lot more dangerous and violent back then, but a lot of partying and fun too. 

Thanks for the compliment. Greatly appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best way to stay warm right now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I worked out in a Queens playground in the snow storm this morning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video shows ex-officer punch man while arresting him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video shows ex-officer punch man while arresting him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My sons find out there's no school today because of snow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That cat just wants to hang.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The road runner grew some balls and learned how to talk. You go, bird! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York City public schools closed Thursday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great footage of takeoffs and landings captured from behind an airport fence. (x-post r/videos) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm excited, I don't have to get up so early tomorrow; thanks for the kind compliments. Greatly appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow; that dog's a champ! If only humans could only give birth so effortlessly. First time I have ever seen a dog give birth. My childhood dog used to always give birth past my bed time. We would wake up and the puppies would already be sucking milk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does he get a special permit to film that close to them? Great shots; my compliments to your mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without the suicide, of course, that actually happened to a Navy shipmate of mine when he hit the strip club one night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing but respect for these dudes. Even with all your ammunition, you're practically naked in that jungle. You don't know from where the next piece of shrapnel, bullet, or anything that can rip off a body part is coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nice how you synced the positioning of the frames to match. Did you do that maneuvering the drone or with your video editor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The news stations have been reporting the snow storm since this morning. My wife's school announced tomorrow's closure, but it's a private school. I didn't think public schools would close, for they have a reputation for barely ever closing. The first time they had closed in decades was a big blizzard that hit us in 2014. Even the airports closed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boys find out they have no school tomorrow because of snow storm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Many celebrities aren't sure what causes to support. Kevin Bacon's organization 'SixDegrees.org' links big stars with small, grassroots charities that can use the boost. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-MATA CEO among 42 arrested in Memphis prostitution sting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Brady commercial that aired after the Super Bowl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puppy trapped under rubble is rescued and returned to its mother </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Immigration Policy Turn Vancouver Into Silicon Valley? The Canadian city already hosts a range of companies, from Amazon to Hootsuite. After President Trumps executive order, it could really capitalize on a tech sector built by foreign workers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Trump Tightens Immigration, Canada Courts Talented U.S. Tech Workers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tumor with fishing line gets removed to save dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-cop convicted of stealing from drivers during traffic stops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-cop convicted of stealing from drivers during traffic stops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The state has approved funding to reimburse 11 Connecticut municipalities for the purchase of police body cameras. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strong 5.6 magnitude earthquake rattles parts of Colombia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This actually happened a few blocks away from me. I hope this family finds closure having arrested this poor lady's killer. New Yorkers be very careful and alert when running in trails and desolate areas. Maybe carry a bottle of pepper spray. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right; but Sessions won't prosecute unless Trump tells him to do so. I don't think Session wants to end up like Sally Yates. And if Trump tells him to prosecute he's going to cut billions of dollars out of the economy. With the way things are going, I don't think he wants to further jeopardize his chance for reelection by slaughtering such a fat cash cow into which the cannabis industry has grown.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These gentlemen made that camel hustle to catch up. That last runner's stride was so fast it was blurry. He would have caught the Road Runner and sold some rotisserie to Wile E. Coyote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 14:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's already repeated that he supports medical cannabis. And he has said that the states should be left to enact cannabis regulations. The only potential snag is his AG pick. Sessions, nonetheless, appears he will do what he has to do to keep his job. Hence if Trump says to legalize or don't interfere, I don't think Sessions will move against his boss's orders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Administration Deletes Cannabis Opposition From WhiteHouse.gov </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 14:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
