<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4827</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude,  did you now that midrange archetype generally struggles against aggro? So what you are saying doesn't make sense.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pirate warrior is really strong and people are underestimating the power of the deck, I don't think it is gonna disappear anytime soon but hopefully it drops to a T2 maybe T3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Karasu" By Wizyakuza, Digital art. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The artist account is on instagram if you want to watch more, but sadly this is the only YYH tattoo I saw :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stunning Hiei Tattoo, done by @gezhangart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the fight scene between yusuke and ch when they where doing the knife edge death match, it was so fucking badass and 

other scene I liked was when genkai and toguro meets in the deep hell for last time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, you made me feel better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lul xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raizen was badass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be awesome but this is almost impossible friend :( Togashi hasn't even finished hunter x hunter, I doubt he is gonna get in with yuyu any time soon.. but if it's ever done that would be so fucking badass exploring the demonic world and fighting again with the most powerfull class S yokai :D oh boy I miss so much yuyu :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree with you, the character development in the last arc was absolutely  georgeous  but it's also true that they could make at least 10 chapters, maybe it's a caprice most of us wanted to see mukuro showings she's technics and some of the other fights too but I'm really happy how all ended :) btw now that I finished yuyu I dont now what to do with my life :'( do you now if theres an anime like this out there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 10:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took me a while.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in the same dilemma as you 2 weeks ago and decided to craft N'zoth, have no regrets of it, he is an excellent card and un'goro is bringin a loot of new deathratle minions so he is going to be even better in both formats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> N'zoth curator mill rogue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The End" By Tianhua Xu, Digital Painting, 2016. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
