<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1780</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you are but what am I?

^^^^^Thanks ^^^^^bby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'll definitely keep you updated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eva Green! Dope interview. /r/30press 4 lyfe, dawg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I vicariously agree with you through Grind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dope, I'd love to get something together! I'll message you shortly about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I love it! Nothing wrong with getting excited over lists! And I love the goose! Something something Willy Wonka! Exclamation point!

No but really thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woohoo! You're old now. Probably better to wax them off than dye them, *if you know what I mean.*

- How do you crank out episodes so fast?

- If you weren't doing horror, what genre would you be involved with?

- Did you know if you give a dog enough popcorn, it makes the same mouth motions as peanut butter mouth?

- Who's your favorite James Bond?

- What's it feel like to be the chosen podcast to end **[REDACTED]**? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I..I just wanna live in your mind for a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the psychological dependence gets put on the backburner too often. Like you said, learning how to live and function after spending so long in an altered state can be even worse than the physical problems. Thanks for the support and best of luck! If you ever need some help, feel free to shoot me a message. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's going live on February 10th, and I'll absolutely update when it's officially ready for purchase! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well thank you very, very much. I hope everything works out well for you! If you ever need someone to talk to, feel free to message me anytime! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know it! Also, got your message. I'm down! I'll text you in a bit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the support! I didn't even think about the published list - kinda stoked for that, I won't lie. I feel like it's an exclusive club. Will I get a golden goose egg? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet it won't have *anything* to do with James Bond. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Release and Drug Addiction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

After many, many delays and procrastination (mostly procrastination), I'm ready to release my first book, a collection of poems and songs that I'm calling *Typos Included.*

This collection consists of my writings from about the age of fourteen (Tiny Mike!) up until I turned twenty-two. It's really special to me, and I've been unable to actually commit to this for years because of the things it reminds me of.

You might be asking yourself, "Mikey, that's cool and all, and I understand that you're nervous about releasing deep cuts, but what does this have to do with drugs?"

Well, after berating you for asking such a wordy question, I would share with you that during this entire time I was heavily experimenting with drugs. There were *a lot* of nights I would come home high and write. Hell, almost to the point that I couldn't write unless I was on drugs. But this isn't about me at all. 

For those who know me, I've always been very outspoken about drug addiction. I've experienced the effect of drugs and watched addiction consume people I love. I want to help people get away from that life. I've spoken with some local rehabilitation centers in Cleveland, Ohio and I've chosen to donate **100% of all money earned** from sales of this book to Helen's Fund at Recovery Resources. That specific fund is to assist people who don't have the financial resources to receive help - something I find very important. No one should be turned away when they want to get away from drugs.

Now, I don't expect this book to be some best-selling work that generates a ton of money for donations. Due to that, I'm going to match the sales/donations up to $500 every year, forever, to make sure the donations are worthwhile (unless I get super rich and famous one day, in which case I'll contribute more).

I'm hoping that my book will be a nice incentive to generate donations, but if you don't like me or don't want the book then consider donating directly to Recovery Resources [here](http://www.recres.org/Donating). 

Finally, to prove I'm not being shady or anything, I will be keeping a completely open spreadsheet on Google Drive that I will update on the first day of every month proving that the money from sales is going where I said it will. 

All of this goes live on Friday, February 10th. I'll have another post that Thursday with links and all that jazz.

That's all I've got.

If you know someone that needs help, reach out. Sometimes that's all it takes to change a life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Release and Drug Addiction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

After many, many delays and procrastination (mostly procrastination), I'm ready to release my first book, a collection of poems and songs that I'm calling *Typos Included.*

This collection consists of my writings from about the age of fourteen (Tiny Mike!) up until I turned twenty-two. It's really special to me, and I've been unable to actually commit to this for years because of the things it reminds me of.

You might be asking yourself, "Mikey, that's cool and all, and I understand that you're nervous about releasing deep cuts, but what does this have to do with drugs?"

Well, after berating you for asking such a wordy question, I would share with you that during this entire time I was heavily experimenting with drugs. There were *a lot* of nights I would come home high and write. Hell, almost to the point that I couldn't write unless I was on drugs. But this isn't about me at all. 

For those who know me, I've always been very outspoken about drug addiction. I've experienced the effect of drugs and watched addiction consume people I love. I want to help people get away from that life. I've spoken with some local rehabilitation centers in Cleveland, Ohio and I've chosen to donate **100% of all money earned** from sales of this book to Helen's Fund at Recovery Resources. That specific fund is to assist people who don't have the financial resources to receive help - something I find very important. No one should be turned away when they want to get away from drugs.

Now, I don't expect this book to be some best-selling work that generates a ton of money for donations. Due to that, I'm going to match the sales/donations up to $500 every year, forever, to make sure the donations are worthwhile (unless I get super rich and famous one day, in which case I'll contribute more).

I'm hoping that my book will be a nice incentive to generate donations, but if you don't like me or don't want the book then consider donating directly to Recovery Resources [here](http://www.recres.org/Donating). 

Finally, to prove I'm not being shady or anything, I will be keeping a completely open spreadsheet on Google Drive that I will update on the first day of every month proving that the money from sales is going where I said it will. 

All of this goes live on Friday, February 10th. Assuming it's cool with the mods, I'll post here on the OOC again that Thursday with links and all that jazz.

That's all I've got.

If you know someone that needs help, reach out. Sometimes that's all it takes to change a life.

**Update:**

[The book is live!](https://www.reddit.com/r/NoSleepOOC/comments/5t83il/i_published_a_book/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luck, mostly. A touch of regularity in posting. A sprinkle of /u/decomprosed's skin flakes. ^^^Bribe ^^^the ^^^mods. 

Don't get discouraged! It happens to everyone. I wrote a bangin' story with /u/vainercupidOOC that got like 3k upvotes and I haven't gotten close since. It's just life, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quality drug programs in the CLE? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to make a donation to a local organization that works towards helping people with substance problems get their lives back. I want to make sure that my money is going to be put to good use. 

Any good suggestions on where to donate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you fucking let me down. I have a very particular set of skills. Skills I have acquired over a very long career. Skills that make me a nightmare for people like you. If you hold up this bargain, that'll be the end of it. I will not look for you, I will not pursue you, but if you don't, I will look for you, I will find you and I will kill you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I really like to listen to Les Claypool for creativity boosting. Try anything he's involved with, but specifically his project with Sean Lennon (John Lennon's son) - [The Claypool Lennon Delirium.](https://youtu.be/nxH8Bc0cHok)

I've also been secretly composing music for this using only a bass guitar amd various effects. So that might be out soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You *know* what I'm going to ask you, and you know I know your answer. But enough about our sex life. Who's your favorite incarnation of Jimmy Bond? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 05:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brewnuts is my absolute number one. Peace, Love, and Little Donuts after that. A lot of people have said Jack Frost, but they just don't do it for me. Always too greasy, and get stale *way* too fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jurassic Park 3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not in the business of writing series too often, but what helped me was not looking at it as a series. Yeah, plan it out is the best method, but like you I tend to get overly excited. But it's all smaller pieces of one bigger story, isn't it? It's kind of like starting a story, then coming back to it later on. Except this time, you let the public see what you've written thus far. I guess. I've run out of steam on this one. It's not you, it's me. Uhh. 

Mind over matter is my point here, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woohoo! All aboard the gravy train! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will concede that I should have spent ten seconds researching the chosen drug before writing this. My bad, everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Blame the Snooze Button  /r/shortscarystories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 03:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Blame the Snooze Button </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 03:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I need twenty bucks, that's it. C'mon, man."

"..for?"

"Drugs. Duh. I'm obviously an addict spiraling down a self-destructive path due to my obsession with being high literally *all* of the time."

I just stared at her blankly. Her accent was a thick, sarcastic one. So thick, in fact, that I'm not sure if she knew that I was aware of her addiction. Li...she was convinced she was fooling everyone because we were all too scared to speak up. Close friends and family pondering their loved one's existence while fearing phone calls from unknown numbers on a regular basis - all too busy standing in line at Starbucks to make a difference in someone's life. 

I wasn't the exception. I gave her the twenty dollars.

Li was driving on the highway when the heroin she injected earlier that morning kicked in. She typically would shoot up while she was doing her makeup so the high would kick in before she started heading to work. That morning, she had to do it while she was letting her dog out to pee before she left because she hit snooze too many times. Knowing Li, she was probably singing Michael Jackson and doing her eyeliner when she slammed into that dividing wall. The coroner told us that the cause of death was a severing of her spinal cord by a piece of her dashboard. He assured us that between the drugs and how she died, Li probably died almost instantly and didn't suffer. 

She didn't suffer. But she did, didn't she? 

She was suffering all along while we were all busy in line waiting on our lattes. I know she was. She sits at the side of my bed and tells me about it every night as she cries and pricks my arms with needles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait. Are you telling me that I can add additional space between paragraphs?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 03:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out /r/writing. They cover almost every single thing ever. Just search "scripts" or whatever applicable term works for ya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 17:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got a pretty good, concise answer already but I've gotta recommend really diving in yourself when you have time. I don't think I've ever read about someone so disturbed before. Dahmer and those guys were messed up...this dude is on a whole new level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 15:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just here so I don't get fined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read everything you can about David Parker Ray. Especially the transcripts of his audio recordings. If that doesn't unsettle you then you're dead inside and I would recommend church or an applicable spiritual equivalent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been in your shoes. I've had threats come my way a couple times. Especially from the story /u/vainercupidOOC and I wrote about the election. I've found that once it gets to the point of a PM, immersion doesn't matter anymore. Play along if you'd like, but if it gets creepy, let them know it's just a story. If it persists, I'm pretty sure you can report them or at the very least block them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh you done goofed, son. I can see *everything.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 14:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although I almost exclusively use RiF, I've witnessed the atrocity that is linking on the website. I would like to cast my vote amongst my peers that are in favor of change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, I don't. We're in the final days until Inauguration and you think we're worried about a dog? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw, thanks! That means a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? Poor kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woohoo! Congrats, /u/RusticEyesore! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same thought. This is like number three or four in a day or two. I love to help but this is slightly baffling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fixed it for you ;)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 14:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - 5.You can't handle the truth. The mods know this and deleted it to preserve your innocence.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could I entice you to read my story by also adding in [ice cream?](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5d9k0j/aliens_n_ice_cream/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, he doesn't need any reminding there. 

^^^^^^^^^winkywink </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you do it. Don't you *dare* fucking do it. I'll tell mom. I really will! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can post it over on /r/nosleepworkshops. It's deadish, but maybe I'll make a surprise visit when your story is up ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as the story has never been posted to NoSleep, you can make an alternate account and post it. Reposts will get you a lashin'.

I'd avoid things with big smiles, too many teeth, mold, anything involving the word "spire," and take it easy on the gore unless it's relevant to the plot.

Damn. I should be a mod.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immersion. That's it. You can always message an author privately to give them constructive criticism if you'd like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *load* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm excited to be part of this love triangle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It varies. Everyone has a different workload and production process. I've had stories take two weeks or more to get done. I've had some get done in a day or less, too (sup, /u/IrrationalFearsHost and /u/atticusjackson). 

Just keep in mind that everyone has something going on and until it becomes their career, this is done between jobs and personal affairs. So, don't worry :) 

Ooh. Thought of something else. It might vary depending on whether they reached out to you, or if you reached out to them. This is just my opinion, but I feel that a narrator would be inclined to voice something they sought out more so than a request they receive. So, that could be a factor. Idk. I don't narrate. **Yet.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's perfect! I love /u/decomprosed's squishiness! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh Jesus. He's gonna be so insulted! I love these, though. Like, they cut deep. Not just a simple "you're ugly!" and walk away. This. This is lasting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welp, your country is cooler than mine. I feel like I can safely say that based solely on this grammar lesson. Wanna trade? 

And can you provide me with an insult? For literary purposes. Not to degrade /u/decomprosed or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 13:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is sweet! It makes me want to dig up my old stuff. 

P.S.

I believe I saw most of /u/manen_lyset's name in there. 

^^^^^Hashtag ^^^^^conspiracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to NOLA in '14. Fan. Fucking. Tastic. I've fallen in love with the city. Everyone there is so pleasant and happy. I took public transportation the entire four days I was there and had zero issues around the city and it's surroundings. I went to the pre-party. Stood in line for *hours* waiting to get my hands on merch in the hot Louisiana sun and still couldn't complain. I met amazing people who loved 311 just as much, if not more than I do. The show was on point. Such a crazy amount of energy and positive vibes. Seeing 311 in a huge venue like the Smoothie King Center was a whole new level for me. 100/10 would recommend.

Might be worth mentioning I went completely alone, too. And I still had that much fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been the most exciting thing I've been a part of since the last exciting thing I was a part of! 

Also, check the chat. I found gold, Jerry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you using one of the apps or a mobile browser? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your coping skills? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As creative types, I'm curious if we cope with negative emotions in unique ways. I know myself and some others inject things into our stories, but what else do you guys and gals do? 

What makes everything okay again?

P.S.

Happy birthday to /u/fourberry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you love James Bond, and I would like to formally inquire about your favorite incarnation of the character. 

It's for the greater good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> `It's almost impossible to read your story in this format.` </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I have a series of stories about a character who calls himself "the Record Keeper." The titles are always the endings of his letters (e.g. *Sincerely, the Record Keeper*). The moral of those stories is to not be a dick because you don't know what someone is capable of. Or something.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 04:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about what makes you choose to watch something on Netflix.

Is it the aesthetically pleasing slideshow?

Is it the title of the movie/show?

Is it the description of the movie/show?

Is it the rating?

See, as writers, we have no access to making a cool slideshow. We do, however, have the ability to title our stories in creative, appealing ways. We can't describe our stories, but we can have such a strong opening that readers instantly get sucked in. Orrrrr...a lot of people (and I mean *a lot* of people) will read the highest upvoted stories and we can't do anything about that. 

So, maybe consider what makes you pick something new on Netflix and apply that to your story.

Or just be really fucking lucky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 04:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *I found an old ring in a river* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 04:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. I just lost a fingertip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 22:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude's so edgy I cut myself just *replying* to this comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 08:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm dead inside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...sssslllllleeeennnnnddddeeeerrrrrmmmmaaaannnnn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By far, horror is my favorite genre. I don't have much of a preference between types of stories. I do, however, prefer writers who don't overdo it on the descriptions. Like, I get the whole "show don't tell" mentality. I agree. It's smart. But if a man is sitting in a chair smoking a cigar and holding a glass of whiskey, just say it. I don't need some flowery description to let me know he's doing that. So yea. That tends to turn me off of stories. Everything else is cool though. I like pretty much anything, I just prefer horror.  

I'm also a big Bukowski fan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 13:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wolrd's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hollow Bones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 22:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I bet I could fly." She said

while she stood on the ledge.

My camera bounced twice

as it hit the ground. "I don't

think that's a good idea, Jess.

Come down."

"No, really! My bones are

hollow like your ideas. I'm

weightless."

"Jess! Stop!" 

She started convulsing and

plummeted sixteen stories. 

I ran to the ledge where 

an eagle rose from below.

I looked down after and to

my surprise

Jess bounced twice

after she hit the

ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 21:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You excited?!](http://i.imgur.com/N82Pe.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 03:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what if it is genuinely progressing the plot and that many parts is legitimately needed to convey the point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 00:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm. I like that it would take almost two months to do this. I'm gonna go ahead and give you a firm maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 00:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. **Yeah!** It isn't finished! Sup, /u/vainercupid?! Go get Liz and make her eat poop or something. Yeah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 00:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um. It's *unlikely* to happen. But when you put something on the internet there's...7 billion people who can potentially see it in the world. So, nothing is *impossible.* Super unlikely though. I mean, I openly mention how I live in Cleveland, Ohio in a lot of things and so far no one except for /u/vainercupidOOC has tried to track me and kill me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gross. [This](https://soundcloud.com/irrational_fears/my-friend-hasnt-been-in-contact-since-this-series-of-weird-text-messages) is way better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *have* to be that guy and say that I don't consider anything I've written to be bad, and I feel that each one was amazing in its own way. 

Buuuuuuuutttttttttt....at the moment, I consider [Robots Need Less Than Three](https://www.reddit.com/r/libraryofshadows/comments/5ckuyq/robots_need_less_than_three_noir_contest/) to be the best story I've written/personal favorite. Why do I love it so? It's a darn tootin' good story! Oh. And I feel that I acheived a very good level of world building and character development with it. I read it and feel immersed into the world my character, Micah, is living in. I've gotten a lot of praise for it as well from peers here as well as people from my personal life. It also reminds me that I can step out of the box and do something great. I thought I would always be writing scary stories, and this is a Sci-fi/Noir. I didn't know I could even do that! I love it. It's also a tribute to a friend of mine and my younger days. I'm not going all mushy, though. 

Biggest screw-up? Man. [This one](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4o9owl/she_has_to_know/) haunts me. I wrote it when I first made this account and started contributing regularly. I had these great ideas, subtle hints, and a mindfuck ending...and I'll missed the mark on every single thing. The story became a jumbled mess of what I thought was going to be a juggernaut of a story. I still have a soft spot for it, though, because it reminds me of exactly what to do wrong. I learned a lot from writing it - how to be clear, details, etc. It was also a concept my girlfriend and I came up with together. Blargh. No more mushy. 

Also, this woman on the train keeps staring at me with *those* eyes. I'm uncomfortable. I think she's a hooker. Like seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Sigh*

This always happens to me, too. My last story was a bet from a series of tweets with /u/IrrationalFearsHost. Got like ~500. My last passionate one got 50 or something. 

C'est la vie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries - we've got you! We might even have *better* advice than those other subs. OOC!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, *this.* Lifestyle inflation is a killer. Get accommodated to the 52k. Depending on your location that could be more than enough to have a good life. Then, if you land the higher paying position, invest in your future like Ash points out above this.

**DO NOT** buy fancy new things because you got a 10k raise in six months. **Don't do it.** 

Adding on:

If you can avoid it, don't do it for the first raise, either! If you can keep your costs low and income high, you will be in a beautiful spot my friend. By this I mean don't force yourself to eat ramen and watch t.v. on a 16 inch tube, but don't eat at Applebee's every night and buy a curved flat screen. Moderation. Balance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say accept the CSO position solely because nothing is guaranteed until you sign papers. Yea, there might be a 99% chance you get the second position in a few months, but until it's on paper it isn't there. Take the position. 

Remember, you're number one. Not a company. 

**Also:**

That's a 30k increase, man!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 14:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Team* - **Rice Wine and Cheese Doodles**

*Working Title* - **South Dakota Doesn't Exist**

---

Matt's New Year's Eve party was *the* gathering of the year in our group of friends. He was one of those guys that was made to be successful, and he spared no expense making sure everyone knew he was doing well for himself. Every year, he would pay off his neighbors and have the entire top floor of his downtown apartment vacant aside from those of us lucky enough to make the guest list. This past year, on top of the fully-staffed open bar he had in his apartment, he hired an entire staff of cooks from one of Michael Symon's restaurants who were making virtually anything your heart could desire. 

I won't lie, I wasn't a huge fan of Matt - he was kind of a dick - but we grew up together, and deep down I knew if I missed his social gatherings it would kill him. What I did instead of bailing was take full advantage of that open bar. Drunk Mary is a more tolerant Mary - one that can deal with the Dick King. 

The party, from what I remember, was booming. The dance floor was so packed that I swear the floors started bouncing when the DJ played "Shots." It was fun. I'll admit it. Even from my post at the bar, it was fun. Well...until about 11:30pm when the DJ had the bright idea to go around the room and have everyone announce their resolutions for the new year. 

"To lose weight!" Some guy yelled.

"Pay off my student loans!" From another.

"Not have a baby!" Matt yelled - everyone laughed. 

"What about you, Miss Thang?" The DJ pointed his mic to me from across the room. 

"I...I don't, uh. I don't have one, sorry." Everyone laughed at me, too. 

"Come on, Mar. You've gotta have *something* you wanna do!" Matt slithered over to me and put his arm around my shoulders as everyone watched us. I'm sure it made at least four girls jealous. "What do you want to get done? Anything in the world!"

"Um. I guess I'd like to travel more. That'd be cool." 

"Travel! Our girl Mar wants to travel!" Matt announcrd, causing the room to erupt in applause. 

The DJ moved onto the next person as Matt stayed with me and helped himself to the stool next to mine. He had that *fucking* grin on his face. He was about to say something stupid. 

"Mar. What if-"

"Mary. You know I hate it when you call me that." I interrupted. 

"So sorry, *Mary.*" He chuckled. "What if I told you something crazy that would blow your fucking mind? Two patron, man."

"Go for it." 

"South Dakota. You know it isn't a real place, right? Like, it's just a paper state. It holds a place on maps and that's it!"

I chuckled. "Really? That's what you're trying to 'blow my mind' with?" Matt winced - he always hated when I imitated him. We took our shots. 

"No, really! Have you ever met someone from South Dakota? Been there? When was the last time something from South Dakota made the news? Listen. You want to travel, right? I'll *pay* for you to go check this out. Whole trip. Plane ticket. Hotel. Food. Fuck, I'll buy you a whole new wardrobe for the trip." 

"I don't know. It sounds cool, I guess. And I can make you look like an ass just by going on vacation. I'll have to see if I can take time off of work."

"Mar. *Mary.* I've got it. You know better than anyone that I can fix that up for you."

"Ha, go for it, dude."

"I will! You're like a sister to me. A sister I've banged a few times, but a sist-"

"Stop."

"Okay, okay. I just want to help you live life. I'll make the arrangements. You just show up. Let's fuckin' dance!" He yanked me off of the stool by my wrists and the rest of the night now sits as a drunken blur of bad decisions in my memory.

True to his word, Matt arranged for me to have two weeks - paid - off of work by the end of the following day. He was an dick, but a powerful one nonetheless. My plane ticket was hand-delivered to my desk by the man himself.

"6:17am. Friday. Allegiant out of Akron/Canton. Towncar will pick you up at 5. Let's go shopping and shit."

"Jesus Christ. You're really serious about this?" I replied in disbelief.

"Duh. Let's go."

Matt didn't spare any expense in his bribery. Saks Fifth Avenue. Nordstrom. Victoria's Secret. Oakley. I felt like a call-girl that he was trying to keep quiet so his main squeeze wouldn't find out anything...but it was nice. Over the years I ran through a nice streak of terrible men. Getting spoiled a bit was refreshing, to say the least. Even if it was for Matt's personal gain, as stupid as it was. I just didn't get it - why South Dakota? Matt couldn't really answer anything aside from making wild claims that it just didn't exist.

I spent my free time before the trip Googling everything I could about South Dakota. Airports. Companies. Politics. News stories. I couldn't figure out where he got the notion the *entire state* was a sham. I mean, they have a freaking [*university*](http://www.usd.edu/) for Christ's sake! I couldn't find anything online except for some poorly designed conspiracy theory websites that even hinted at South Dakota not being real. The only thing I could give Matt credit for was that I had never in my life met someone from the state. At my job, my entire role is dealing with hundreds of clients from all across the United States. South Dakota was the only state I had never had a client from...and I highly doubted that no one in the entire state had medical debt. For what it was worth, that slightly arose my suspicion.

Friday morning, just like Matt said, the driver was in front of my house at 5:00am sharp. Friendly guy, and damn good driver. He got me to the airport in less than thirty minutes and didn't run a single red light. I didn't think that was possible for a human being to do. My flight was another story. With Matt being so willing to splurge on clothes and frivolous items to make me agree to the trip, I didn't expect to have to deal with economy seating. 

About three hours into the flight, the pilot came on over the loudspeaker with an announcement:

"Ladies and gentlemen, it looks like we're going to have to make an unscheduled stop before reaching our destination. It uhh...appears our plane was improperly fueled for this flight. We'll be landing at Hettinger Municipal Airport in Hettinger, North Dakota to refuel. On behalf of Allegiant Airlines, I would like to apologize for the inconvenience and I reassure you that the airline will compensate you for the trouble. Thank you. Could all attendants please prepare for landing procedures."

When we landed down, I turned my phone back on and the first thing that popped onto my screen was a text from Matt.

"Got you a rental. Don't worry about it. You're just outside the border. Head down to Hertz and they'll have ot ready for you."












 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 14:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't make it to the newspaper. There's vomit and urine in the hallway. My B, dawg. 

But, uh, sup sexy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 14:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Team Rice Wine and Cheese Doodles - wassup?!

/u/Dove_of_Doom
/u/offiziersmesser
/u/ceramichornets
/u/distantoranges
/u/iwantabear
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Furlough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 14:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dentistry was my entire life. Teeth, I mean, everyone sees them. Nice smiles go farther than most things. You need them to eat. Bite. *Nibble.* I can't remember a time when I wasn't obsessed with teeth. I was the top student in my class and I was the youngest dentist to receive a position with the prestigious office I worked at.

Then they "downsized."

I was told that they were giving me an extended vacation until the numbers balanced out again. Then, they would bring me right back on board. I was young. I believed them...for the first few months.

My wife was mostly supportive until about six months in, that's when she told me to "get a job...or at least a hobby or something." She was right, even if she was being a bitch about it. I didn't do much for that time I was out of work and once I realized it, my mind went into a panic. What if I lost my skills that I spent a fortune honing and perfecting?! 

Luckily, I was able to purchase a *really* nice kit of dental tools off of Amazon for less than a small fortune, as well as dummy teeth for practice. It was lovely...for a while. The problem with fake teeth, however, is they don't get the true wear-and-tear that human teeth do. I needed to go back, but my office stopped answering my calls. 

I'll admit, I was leery of performing any work without novocaine. One of my philosophies was to always make sure the patient was entirely comfortable and free of pain. But, my wife was a master of dishing out pain, so I didn't worry when she squirmed underneath the restraints. However, I *did* feel kind of bad as I drilled right into the roof of her mouth. The crunch was loud enough that I didn't really need her screaming in my face to tell she was hurting. She fucking moved though. Who moves when there's a drill in their mouth? Idiot. While I was plugging up her wound with gauze, I noticed her molars were atrocious. They needed to be fixed...but I opted for extraction instead. Honestly, there is only so much a dentist can do for a tooth. 

An unintended side-effect of too much dental work at one time was the passing of my wife. I didn't want that. I just wanted practice. There was too much blood - I couldn't stop it. 

An interesting side-effect of my wife passing, however, is the lack of blood when I practice on her every day. It seems as time goes on she's just drying up. It's nice, honestly.

I wonder if any funeral homes need a dentist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Called "Sleep" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Isn't there something more?" 

She shook her head.

"So, we just lay there without anything going on and it's fine? 'Bodies' can't handle that. Hell, if I sit too long I get messed up. But you're telling me I can lay in one position for hours and my body is cool, and that's that. No. We *have* to be updating or something. The system doesn't stop. We'd become self-aware."

"Sorry. I don't have an answer for you." She replied as she hooked wires to my temples. "When you see the number '100,' answer the phone. Tomorrow is a new day." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 05:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 103.87% of the time, I write my stories in a new text thread. I'll usually have an idea in mind, but I write it there. Then I'll copy/paste to Google Docs and check the word count, errors, etc. It all starts with a new submission though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe. The more I watch it, the more I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook Live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It started with her singing. A song with lyrics about lost love and depressions. Then she started speaking his name in vain - her lover. He was half her age and three times as manipulative. No one fully understood the emotional rollercoaster he put her through...until now.

The video continued on with her airing out *all* of her dirty laundry. She couldn't take anymore and she wanted the viewers to know the truth. The likes and comments came flooding in as the minutes dragged on. Messages of "don't do anything" and "it will be okay" were a blanket in the comment section. 

Yet no one called the cops. No one reached out to her family.

With tears in her eyes she pulled out a gun and held it to the side of her head. 

*Bang.*

The phone fell with her. Gurgling. Clinging to life. Finally people acted. Luckily it wasn't too late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pompous Revelation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 04:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It was late," she said,

"He wouldn't listen to me..

..so I fucked his friend." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 16:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, I have a friend that lives in North Dakota. South Dakota on the other hand...

I work in an airport. I've never seen a flight go there. Never met a passenger heading there. Nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clever Horror-Themed New Year's Eve Pun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 01:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sup peeps? 

What're you sickos up to tonight? Ritual sacrifices to the giant head in the sky? Gettin' crunk? Repeating "this is the last time I'll ever do this in 2016" to your justifiably annoyed friends and family? 

I'm getting turnt up on sparkling fruit juice with this [lightweight](http://i.imgur.com/HT3c3RW.jpg) and my fam. Then killing a virgin. For posterity.

**Hashtag MOOCGA**

^^^^^Remember ^^^^^that? ^^^^^I ^^^^^do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 22:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I systematically place minor errors in my stories so I can catch thieves. It's a highly complex process and I can't spare details for fear of them finding out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 14:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dd o4msbzlepw0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 13:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **December 2016**

**12/1** - [I Wrote This With One Hand](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5fx506/i_wrote_this_with_one_hand/) - /r/nosleep

**12/2** - [Growth and Development](https://www.reddit.com/r/HaikuSleep/comments/5g58q4/growth_and_development/) - /r/HaikuSleep

**12/3** - [Memory Foam Bath Mat](https://www.reddit.com/r/DrabbleRousers/comments/5gfk6k/memory_foam_bath_mat/) - /r/DrabbleRousers

**12/4** - [Whittling](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/5gfmn6/whittling/) - /r/shortscarystories

**12/5 [Appeal]** *(Bathtub Day)* - [Clawfoot](https://www.reddit.com/r/ShortSadStories/comments/5gsmry/clawfoot/) - /r/shortsadstories

**12/6** - [You're next. - the Record Keeper](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5gt4ge/youre_next_the_record_keeper/) - /r/nosleep

**12/7 [Appeal]**- [The Numbers Game](https://www.reddit.com/r/DrabbleRousers/comments/5h6yxd/the_numbers_game/) - /r/DrabbleRousers

**12/8** - [Insomnia](https://www.reddit.com/r/youpoetried/comments/5h73dr/insomnia/) - /r/youpoetried
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 04:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I just looked...and that's a completely incorrect claim. I saw *maybe* two or three that could be clickbait. One of those I would say is 100%, but 10+? Nah. 

It's totally subjective. So it might look different to you than it does to me, but I get your point. Try presenting it in a more...not dickish manner though. 

Are you sure you sorted by **month** and not **year**? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 00:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little bit of [this](https://youtu.be/doUNMfLEI70) usually puts me in the "banjos and piggies" mindset needed to write messed up things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm. I'm closing a store. Changing jobs. Going to Arizona for a week. Attempting to actually publish something. 

Yea. Yea. I can do this too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll never forgive you for this recent transgression. You should be ashamed. You will now forever be known as "Fiddlesticks," the greatest insult amongst my peoples. 

**Edit:** What in the actual fuck happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, she's my dad's mother-in-law. That probably would have been a better explanation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 13:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was my mom's mom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 06:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [100%](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/58cdy9/my_name_is_mikey_knutson/?ref=search_posts) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 03:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm not mistaken, one of the rules covers this and can result in comments being removed. But yea, dick move. I feel that the common courtesy if something *really* bothers a reader that much is to message the writer privately. As opposed to calling them out in front of x number of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 02:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's still in Harbour Court. Apparently doing well and still baking every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 23:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate your sympathies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 23:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we role-playing *again*? Jesus. Get a new kink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 23:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I SAY NAY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 23:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a lot of inner demons, which translates into *literally* every story I've written to-date having some sort of truth about me in it. Whether it's an expetience, fear, etc. Writing about it really helps me cope. For example, my mom was recently in the hospital with kidney failure - I wrote [this](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ebeyg/give_it_to_her_shell_die_without_it/https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ebeyg/give_it_to_her_shell_die_without_it/). Sometimes it isn't central to the plot like that. It's always there, though.

Also, to be perfectly honest, I've always wanted to be a great writer. It's just taken me 25 years to become comfortable with trying. So that constantly keeps me motivated to keep publishing stories and writing about new topics. 

Finally, I *love* horror. I grew up on it. Think what you will, but my mom introduced me to horror movies when I was still a single-digit age. It didn't scar me. Well, I do have some *irrational fears* from some things (ha, get it /u/IrrationalFearsHost?! I said your podcast name), but nothing that's negatively impacted my life. Instead, I fell in love. I love being scared or disturbed. I love not being able to sleep at night. I want to do for other people what all of those great horror directors amd writers did for me.  

Full disclosure: I didn't read the full post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 23:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much more. To this day I can still see her face as she smiled and carved into her gums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To this day my stomach churns at even the sight of peppermint bark.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true. All it takes is a visit sometimes...although saying that kind of makes me a hypocrite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That...that's quite an accurate portrayal of those places.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grandma's World-Famous Peppermint Bark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moment we turned the corner and the orange-bricked high-rise came into view, my stomach churned and I winced. 

"It's okay, bud." Dad said as he put his hand on my knee. He must have noticed my unease. "Grandma is doing fine. She just needed to live in a place where people can help her when she needs it."

As we pulled into the sloping, cracked parking lot I could finally make out the tiny letters above the forest green awning: *Harbour Court.* An assisted living facility...my grandma's new home. 

Grandma was passing out candy on Halloween when she had the stroke. A little boy dressed up as the Grim Reaper rang her doorbell and as she was leaning out of her screen door to place a candy bar into his pillowcase, she collapsed. Fortunately for her, the little boy ran and got his parents. If he didn't...my grandma might not be here today. Dad liked to joke that she thought "death finally came for her," but I knew the truth - I went with my dad to everything. I was sitting on grandma's old flower-print couch while Dad sat in the kitchen with the doctors. The truth was that she wasn't healthy. Too many high calorie foods and too many sweets. They said it clogged her arteries and it finally caught up with her....and it could happen again. Dad didn't want to take the risk of her being alone next time. 

The lobby smelled like lavender body spray and milk, either from the residents or the haggard looking receptionist who checked us in. 

"Room 216, elevators are on the left." She croaked. Dad had a hard time trying to hide his laugh. 

We rode the elevator up, and as soon as the doors opened we were greeted by a woman wearing scrubs that barely covered her and her tattoos. 

"Hi, I'm Megan. Are you the family of Mrs. Lemons?" She asked in an overly bubbly tone.

"Ye-yeah. Yes. I'm her son, Abe, and this is her grandson, Sade." 

"Awesome! Nice to meet you guys! Really quick, I just want to go over some things with you before you visit with Mrs. Lemons. Follow me, please!" She walked over to a small, dingy desk with a slight skip in her step. 

"So, you guys are like, the first people to come visit her since she moved in aaaaand we don't know how well she's going to do with family members."

"We're her only family. Her daughter - my wife -  passed away a couple of years ago. She doesn't have any living relatives." He informed her, almost under his breath.

"Oh. *Oh*. Okay. Well, you should know that there have been a couple of incidents with our staff in-"

"What do you mean, 'incidents?'" Dad interjected.

"Um. Welllllll...she just gets really weird sometimes. Like, we let her cook to help with her motor skills. But she'll like, make so much food to share with people. But the people don't exist. And she like won't let anyone touch it. She just kind of hoards it." Megan, for the first time, lost her spunkiness. Whatever my grandma was doing genuinely seemed to bother her.

"Guess we'll just have to carry some crosses then, right buddy?" Dad joked as he tuffled my hair with his hand. 

"Right!" I exclaimed. If my dad wasn't bothered by something, neither was I - no matter how scary it seemed.

Megan walked us down the short hall and left us in front of a light brown door with the faded blue numbers "216" adorning the top of the frame. 

"If you need *anything* I'll be right down at the desk." She said as she walked away. 

"Jeesh, maybe the phone number for the store where you buy your clothes." Dad chuckled as he nudged me towards the door. "Let's go on in."

I pushed the door in and it let out a loud creak that startled the old, gray-haired woman sitting at a desk.

"Hi Grandma!" I ran over to her and gave her a hug.

"Jesus, Sade! You almost gave me a heart attack! Aw, but you're so big!" She returned my hug, smothering me in her floral print bosom. "Come here, Abe!" 

My Dad walked over with a smile on his face, but it slowly diminished as he came closer. 

"What's with all this food?" He asked my grandma as he pointed to the wall behind her. 

In my haste and excitement, I hadn't even noticed the mountains of sweets piled halfway up the barren, cream wall. Trays, plates, and pans overflowing with everything imaginable. Cookies, cupcakes, buckeyes, peanut brittle...even her famous peppermint bark! 

"Just some baking I've been doing. These people are nice to me and don't want me to stop like those stupid doctors do." She snarled at the end. " Go ahead and have some! *There's peppermint bark.*"

"Maybe later, Ma." Dad said quickly.

"Oh honey, don't be stubborn. *Everyone* loves my peppermint bark. Eat some!" 

Dad ignored her and walked over to the large window that was illuminating her room. I followed him over, but not before Grandma handed me a little piece of the bark while holding her index finger up to her lips. It was really hard, so I didn't take a bite. 

"They treating you okay?" Dad asked her as he looked out the window. 

"What's wrong with my candy?" 

"Sorry?"

"What's wrong with my candy?" My grandma was standing up now, holding a plate of her bark and tears in her eyes. "Eat it, Sade."

"I'm okay. I'm full Grandma, I'll eat it when I get home - promise!" I said with a smile. Dad taught me before that a little white lie never hurt anyone. My dad turned around a stared at my grandma with a concerned look on his face. My heartbeat started tripping over itself as I moved a little closer to him. 

"Sade!" She yelled as she dropped the plate. My dad put himself between my grandma and I. She bent down and picked up a larger piece of the candy. "Eat it, Sade. It's delicious - look!"

"Mom!" My dad shouted in a commanding way, but she didn't respond. My grandma took a bite of the bark in her hand. I could hear the crunching across the room. It made my stomach hurt. 

"Look, it's fine!" She smiled, letting thick blood ooze out from between her lips. It ran down her chin and fell onto her blouse. Dad didn't move - he just held me behind him. 

"I have some stuck in my teeth - can't have that, can we?" Her tongue wiped her teeth clean as she spoke. Then, my grandma took the peppermint bark and dug a pointed edge into her gums, wedging it in all sorts of different directions as more blood rained from her mouth. "There we go!" She gurgled. She took her fingers and pulled a tooth from her mouth. "No more of that."

My dad was a statue, slowly turning white with a hint of green. I stayed behind him hoping he would do something...but he didn't. My grandma kept walking towards us, digging peppermint bark into her gums and ripping her teeth out while blood fell everywhere. She never stopped smiling as she removed all of her front teeth. Grandma stopped in front of my dad and bent down to my level. 

"Make sure you brush when you're done eating." She chimed as she turned the bark vertically and began rubbing it between her gums like a toothbrush. She was so close that I could see the cuts being made into her mouth, like a saw cutting into wood. I couldn't take anymore. I ran out from behind my dad and out to the desk where I found Megan. 

"Code Three!" She screamed as she ran into the room, closely followed by a bunch of men and women also in scrubs. I ran after them too. 

In the room, Grandma was on top of my dad's chest still carving into her gums with the peppermint bark. She was leaning over his face, letting blood squirt into his mouth, eyes, and everywhere it could go. The aides stuck a large needle into her neck and she collapsed to the side. They split parties, some tending to my dad and others to my grandma. 

The combination of the sedative they used, her loss of blood, and mania caused her to die almost instantly. She was cremated - a decision made by Harbour Court as no one was claiming responsibility for her. There was no funeral. 

After my dad got out of the hospital, he wasn't the same. Apparently having a stroke as bad as his can severely disrupt how the brain functions. We lived very quietly for a few months until some men from the state came and took me. My dad was forced into the local assisted living facility - Harbour Court. While I was in foster care I used to write him letters every week...even though he never responded. Once I turned eighteen I went to Harbour Court to visit him for the first time. When I got off of the elevator and older woman covered in tattoos greeted me in an overly bubbly tone.

"Hi, I'm Megan! Are you here to see Abe?" 

"Uh. Yeah. I'm his son, Sade."

"Okay, awesome! Before we go over, you should know he's had some...incidents." She paused. "See, we like, let him bake to help with his motor fun-"

"Sorry, I have to be going." I interrupted her, then walked away.

I've never gone back.

---


[Mikey](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject1780) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grandma's World-Famous Peppermint Bark  /r/nosleep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um. I just wrote one titled ["Grandma's World-Famous Peppermint Bark."](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5kxqyx/grandmas_worldfamous_peppermint_bark/)

Mourning Wood is another good one. 

The one /u/jaksim wrote last month had a really strange title. Something something colors. ~~I'll come back to this.~~

This is a good question. I'm stoked to see more answers! 

Edit: [Came back.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5d2um3/there_are_secrets_hidden_in_the_colors_you_cant/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grandma's World-Famous Peppermint Bark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moment we turned the corner and the orange-bricked high-rise came into view, my stomach churned and I winced. 

"It's okay, bud." Dad said as he put his hand on my knee. He must have noticed my unease. "Grandma is doing fine. She just needed to live in a place where people can help her when she needs it."

As we pulled into the sloping, cracked parking lot I could finally make out the tiny letters above the forest green awning: *Harbour Court.* An assisted living facility...my grandma's new home. 

Grandma was passing out candy on Halloween when she had the stroke. A little boy dressed up as the Grim Reaper rang her doorbell and as she was leaning out of her screen door to place a candy bar into his pillowcase, she collapsed. Fortunately for her, the little boy ran and got his parents. If he didn't...my grandma might not be here today. Dad liked to joke that she thought "death finally came for her," but I knew the truth - I went with my dad to everything. I was sitting on grandma's old flower-print couch while Dad sat in the kitchen with the doctors. The truth was that she wasn't healthy. Too many high calorie foods and too many sweets. They said it clogged her arteries and it finally caught up with her....and it could happen again. Dad didn't want to take the risk of her being alone next time. 

The lobby smelled like lavender body spray and milk, either from the residents or the haggard looking receptionist who checked us in. 

"Room 216, elevators are on the left." She croaked. Dad had a hard time trying to hide his laugh. 

We rode the elevator up, and as soon as the doors opened we were greeted by a woman wearing scrubs that barely covered her and her tattoos. 

"Hi, I'm Megan. Are you the family of Mrs. Lemons?" She asked in an overly bubbly tone.

"Ye-yeah. Yes. I'm her son, Abe, and this is her grandson, Sade." 

"Awesome! Nice to meet you guys! Really quick, I just want to go over some things with you before you visit with Mrs. Lemons. Follow me, please!" She walked over to a small, dingy desk with a slight skip in her step. 

"So, you guys are like, the first people to come visit her since she moved in aaaaand we don't know how well she's going to do with family members."

"We're her only family. Her daughter - my wife -  passed away a couple of years ago. She doesn't have any living relatives." He informed her, almost under his breath.

"Oh. *Oh*. Okay. Well, you should know that there have been a couple of incidents with our staff in-"

"What do you mean, 'incidents?'" Dad interjected.

"Um. Welllllll...she just gets really weird sometimes. Like, we let her cook to help with her motor skills. But she'll like, make so much food to share with people. But the people don't exist. And she like won't let anyone touch it. She just kind of hoards it." Megan, for the first time, lost her spunkiness. Whatever my grandma was doing genuinely seemed to bother her.

"Guess we'll just have to carry some crosses then, right buddy?" Dad joked as he tuffled my hair with his hand. 

"Right!" I exclaimed. If my dad wasn't bothered by something, neither was I - no matter how scary it seemed.

Megan walked us down the short hall and left us in front of a light brown door with the faded blue numbers "216" adorning the top of the frame. 

"If you need *anything* I'll be right down at the desk." She said as she walked away. 

"Jeesh, maybe the phone number for the store where you buy your clothes." Dad chuckled as he nudged me towards the door. "Let's go on in."

I pushed the door in and it let out a loud creak that startled the old, gray-haired woman sitting at a desk.

"Hi Grandma!" I ran over to her and gave her a hug.

"Jesus, Sade! You almost gave me a heart attack! Aw, but you're so big!" She returned my hug, smothering me in her floral print bosom. "Come here, Abe!" 

My Dad walked over with a smile on his face, but it slowly diminished as he came closer. 

"What's with all this food?" He asked my grandma as he pointed to the wall behind her. 

In my haste and excitement, I hadn't even noticed the mountains of sweets piled halfway up the barren, cream wall. Trays, plates, and pans overflowing with everything imaginable. Cookies, cupcakes, buckeyes, peanut brittle...even her famous peppermint bark! 

"Just some baking I've been doing. These people are nice to me and don't want me to stop like those stupid doctors do." She snarled at the end. " Go ahead and have some! *There's peppermint bark.*"

"Maybe later, Ma." Dad said quickly.

"Oh honey, don't be stubborn. *Everyone* loves my peppermint bark. Eat some!" 

Dad ignored her and walked over to the large window that was illuminating her room. I followed him over, but not before Grandma handed me a little piece of the bark while holding her index finger up to her lips. It was really hard, so I didn't take a bite. 

"They treating you okay?" Dad asked her as he looked out the window. 

"What's wrong with my candy?" 

"Sorry?"

"What's wrong with my candy?" My grandma was standing up now, holding a plate of her bark and tears in her eyes. "Eat it, Sade."

"I'm okay. I'm full Grandma, I'll eat it when I get home - promise!" I said with a smile. Dad taught me before that a little white lie never hurt anyone. My dad turned around a stared at my grandma with a concerned look on his face. My heartbeat started tripping over itself as I moved a little closer to him. 

"Sade!" She yelled as she dropped the plate. My dad put himself between my grandma and I. She bent down and picked up a larger piece of the candy. "Eat it, Sade. It's delicious - look!"

"Mom!" My dad shouted in a commanding way, but she didn't respond. My grandma took a bite of the bark in her hand. I could hear the crunching across the room. It made my stomach hurt. 

"Look, it's fine!" She smiled, letting thick blood ooze out from between her lips. It ran down her chin and fell onto her blouse. Dad didn't move - he just held me behind him. 

"I have some stuck in my teeth - can't have that, can we?" Her tongue wiped her teeth clean as she spoke. Then, my grandma took the peppermint bark and dug a pointed edge into her gums, wedging it in all sorts of different directions as more blood rained from her mouth. "There we go!" She gurgled. She took her fingers and pulled a tooth from her mouth. "No more of that."

My dad was a statue, slowly turning white with a hint of green. I stayed behind him hoping he would do something...but he didn't. My grandma kept walking towards us, digging peppermint bark into her gums and ripping her teeth out while blood fell everywhere. She never stopped smiling as she removed all of her front teeth. Grandma stopped in front of my dad and bent down to my level. 

"Make sure you brush when you're done eating." She chimed as she turned the bark vertically and began rubbing it between her gums like a toothbrush. She was so close that I could see the cuts being made into her mouth, like a saw cutting into wood. I couldn't take anymore. I ran out from behind my dad and out to the desk where I found Megan. 

"Code Three!" She screamed as she ran into the room, closely followed by a bunch of men and women also in scrubs. I ran after them too. 

In the room, Grandma was on top of my dad's chest still carving into her gums with the peppermint bark. She was leaning over his face, letting blood squirt into his mouth, eyes, and everywhere it could go. The aides stuck a large needle into her neck and she collapsed to the side. They split parties, some tending to my dad and others to my grandma. 

The combination of the sedative they used, her loss of blood, and mania caused her to die almost instantly. She was cremated - a decision made by Harbour Court as no one was claiming responsibility for her. There was no funeral. 

After my dad got out of the hospital, he wasn't the same. Apparently having a stroke as bad as his can severely disrupt how the brain functions. We lived very quietly for a few months until some men from the state came and took me. My dad was forced into the local assisted living facility - Harbour Court. While I was in foster care I used to write him letters every week...even though he never responded. Once I turned eighteen I went to Harbour Court to visit him for the first time. When I got off of the elevator an older woman covered in tattoos greeted me in an overly bubbly tone.

"Hi, I'm Megan! Are you here to see Abe?" 

"Uh. Yeah. I'm his son, Sade."

"Okay, awesome! Before we go over, you should know he's had some...incidents." She paused. "See, we like, let him bake to help with his motor fun-"

"Sorry, I have to be going." I interrupted her, then walked away.

[I've](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject1780) never gone back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try [this one](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4zqq8s/mourning_wood/) by /u/decomprosed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
