<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your feedback, I appreciate. I will be checking out more about CBT, because I do think that something more structured might help me. I'm giving myself my month off to see if I can climb back up the hill without meds, but if I'm still run down in a month, I will consider taking them... can I pm you if I have any other questions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12 DPO, nothing going on except a nice triphasic chart (which just gets my hopes up for nothing) so I'm just waiting for AF to show up in 2 days. Today I plan on going outside for a run and doing a few things around the house. Numero uno, I should get my ass outta bed!! Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay that's a line, congrats!! I hope it sticks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought of you guys as well when I read this...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahaha I love the bear of luck, it's perfect! 
And I've read that meds can make you sleepy and tired and stuff, and I can't imagine having less energy than I currently have. I wonder if I'd just sleep all day lol. 

I'm not sure how I feel about my therapist. She mostly listens and asks questions to get me to process my thoughts and come to solutions by myself, but I'm not sure if what we're doing is CBT or not, I'll try to see. 

Thank you for the support:)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. It always helps to see I'm not alone. I've also started telling close friends and family and it feels better not having the weight of secrecy anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tips. I know I need to go out and about and I'll remember your suggestions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not dumb at all! I will try and go out regularly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! The prospect of taking meds while TTC and then possibly while pregnant also scares me honestly... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Just having the official diagnosis feels like now I can start working on it instead of asking myself if it's really that. I feel like a big weight has been lifted off my shoulders  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) I will definitely try to remember all that. And daily walks with my Great Dane are part of my plan. Thanks you for being there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just scares me so much. Medication that acts on the brain is scary shit to me. I'm afraid it'll just make me numb and zombie-like and I can't deal with that. The side effects also seem worse than what I'm feeling right now. I know it's stupid and vain, but the weight gain I know I won't be able to deal with, it'll just make me feel worse. I decided I would take this month to see if rest can help me feel better on my own, and if it doesn't work then next month I will consider the meds (grudgingly)... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just wrote a book about my depression diagnosis on here this morning... And this is the first day of my 4-week sick leave off work. I'm not sure what I should be doing haha, I don't know how to just relax... I'm strange that way. 

Also, I POAS this morning and got a BFN on 11DPO, just like I knew I would. So I'll be waiting for AF to show up this week so that we can move on to cycle 4... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your kind words. The idea of putting TTC on hold really stresses me out... I just feel like I've already waited for so long and I can't see how I could willingly put it off again... Anyway I feel like it'll take us a while yet as my body is not cooperating thus far.

I can't wait to be in a better place, and hope I can get there without meds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :)

Actually, staying home alone sounds bad, but I really plan on taking this time to rest, sleep, eat well, and to really just take time for me: yoga, running, drawing, and home projects, as things present themselves. I've been a "to-do list" addict for too long and so I have to learn to just be in the present moment.

As for TTC, I cannot resolve myself to completely stop trying, but in the last month it has not been the major cause of my stress, so I think we will just keep on trying without stressing about it, even though I know the timing isn't the greatest. We'll see how it works itself out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second Miroet. When I naively started TTC, I figured I would try to avoid holiday babies for the same reasons you mentioned OP. Fast-forward to now, although I haven't been at it nearly as long as Miroet, I have only ovulated twice in almost 7 months, so you can bet I will not be wasting any tries just to avoid potential due dates. I just want a baby, whenever that may happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just reminded me I wanted to read that! Next time I order TTC crap on Amazon I shall treat myself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay congrats!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww :( thanks for all your wisdom on this sub. I wish you the best of luck and hope you still hand around and let us know when you get your BFP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats Babytimes so happy for you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have any useful info (sorry!), just wanted to wish you good luck and say that I'm seeing my doctor tomorrow (will be 7DPO then) and so will ask for bloodwork to check the very same things as you! My TSH in November was 3.7, and I feel exhausted and depressed all the time so worried it went up! I'll be looking out for your updates in case they are relevant to me. I hope it's an easy fix for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. "Just relax, go on vacation and have sex!"

*cue eye roll*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( I hope you get some answers soon.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the info!

By the way didn't mean to offend anyone with weight issues/prejudice, it's just that PCOS is so often represented with the typical picture...

I am definitely asking for more in-depth bloodwork, as I have doubts on my thyroid as well, which could be causing some of the similar issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I did mention that I felt I had some symptoms in November. My doctor said I was really not a "typical" PCOS candidate but of course if things keep being iffy I might push a bit more. I'd have been more worried if my 2nd ultrasound had shown kysts as well but there was nothing. Also I know it's not always the case and that PCOS does not always correlate with obesity, but my BMI is like 21 which is probably partly why my doctor didn't immediately lean towards this.

But I will definitely keep an eye out for all symptoms. You didn't sound obvious, just helpful thanks :)

ETA: When you mention you changed your diet what did you do, was it keto or simply eating a bit more balanced/less sugar etc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great, I hope you get crosshairs soon! :) Enjoy your niece! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay, hii!! I'm excited, I've never been synced before haha what with my crazy cycles :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww Kitty cat :) So cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woohoo! I was waiting for the Waiting Wednesday thread haha! So much waiting...

6DPO, waiting for symptoms, but mostly waiting for AF.. I know I'm being pessimistic but I just don't feel it at all. I don't even know if I'll bother testing, unless I feel very off, but that's hard for me to identify because I have zero symptoms before AF except bad cramps a few hours before it starts and I'm exhausted a day or 2 before. However, I feel like I've been exhausted for weeks now, so it's not like it'll change anything haha!

Man I hate waiting. Patience is definitely not one of my virtues...

ETA: I'm trying to ease the stress of the TWW with very low (read no) expectations, and also by stressing over my appointment with my doctor tomorrow! Man, brains are such assholes sometimes :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, that is so annoying... I've been waking up before my alarm this week which really sucks, I temped twice this morning and got 97.7 and 97.9, I took the first temp because I didn't really fall back asleep between the 2... I would second the recommendation to go with the temp closer to your usual temp time and/pr close to your usual temp for this CD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not the Emily from Indiana, but if I was, I think I'd have tears in my eyes reading this... Thank you for taking the time to try and convey your empathy. Even to others TTC like me (only for 6 months so I cannot imagine the pain of 5 years TTC), it feels good knowing that some people do try to understand how it feels.

I really hope she reads this and knows that we're all supporting her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't know that, thanks! Last time was in the morning, I had eaten about 30 minutes prior so not sure if my blood levels of glucose and nutrients were elevated yet or not! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the tip, I would definitely like to get some answers on that and make sure I'm as good as can be :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha good luck with the BD'ing! Nice to know that you're going to ovulate on your own :)

I had a CD41 ovulation last cycle and yes it is a neverending wait, but at least we're ovulating! My first cycle off HBC lasted 106 days with no ovulation, *that* was long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I'm actually seeing my GP tomorrow and will ask her about checking my TSH again, and the possibility of a low dose of Synthroid to get it below 2.5, especially as my mom has Hashimoto's so I am predisposed to thyroid problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, yep, gotta appreciate the small victories when you live up north!! Same here :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohh congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put in the first day where I actually have to put in a tampon or use a pad. Light spotting in the evening wouldn't be my CD1, but other people might have different guidelines.

Good on you for temping, you'll see that all this beautiful data is great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol! I haven't dared shorts yet, but I did switch up my big Pajar boots with a more fashionable model :) 

And getting to run on the pavement instead of snow and slush is heavenly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Miroet. You were actually one of the first ones to welcome me to TFAB, glad to find you again here (even though like you said, it still sucks we're all *still* trying). :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in Canada (Quebec more precisely), so getting temps above zero Celsius in February is like "whoa"! And we're in a weeklong above-zero stretch, so I'm taking it allll in :") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been lurking and commenting on here for a few weeks but never introduced myself... I was a little bit shy and intimidated TBH.

I'm only in cycle 3, but have been trying since August, so if you do the math my cycles are not regular at all so far... 

Cycle 1: 106 days anovulatory (that was such a loooong time to just wait for something to happen, anything at all), had an ultrasound around day 90ish which showed a 3-cm kyst on my left ovary. Bloodwork in November didn't show anything blatantly wrong, except my TSH was at 3.7, which I find a bit too high. I'm always tired with cold hands and feet, so I'll ask for a repeat TSH check soon.

Cycle 2: Had a repeat ultrasound in January (2 months after the first one), kyst was gone and there were no other kysts. This cycle lasted 56 days, and I ovulated on CD41 (yay!)

Cycle 3: Currently on CD28, 6DPO. My cycles seem to be shortening, which is good. I still feel like there definitely could be something off in my body hormone-wise. Since getting off HBC I've had really bad acne, oily hair, grown some new hairs on my chin and upper lip (FML). The 2 periods I've had were super short and light (2.5 and 1.5 days), my CM is almost always dry (I've had something resembling EWCM for barely 1 day both times I ovulated), never got a truly positive OPK despite peeing on about 50 sticks. So, despite me being only on cycle 3, I've got a feeling that this could take a while.

So, here I am, in that awkward stage between TFAB and stilltrying... I'm participating in both subs, but the fact that so many of the ladies who first welcomed me onto TFAB 3 months ago are on here made me want to follow.

Thanks for reading my book haha, and I wish all of you deserving ladies on here a BFP really soon :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish you the best of luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may have created a secret Pinterest board for baby nurseries... :O

This may or may not be in correlation with the fact that our friends had their baby on Sunday night...

Oh well, at least I didn't spend any money on baby items </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so awesome of you to share! All the ladies in the US who'll get a box will be very happy for sure :)

I love the Girl Scout cookies   Black tea breakfast, hoping your cramps are not too bad.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, that sucks. In this case I hope you can start your next cycle soon and that it'll be the lucky one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm, your LP is so different from last cycle (in a good way though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sucks not to have answers, especially when you're been trying for so long.

The upside? You have a *phenomenal* uterus!! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6DPO, still nothing to report. It's Wednesday, I'm at work, tired, cranky and stressed. Woohoo! Upside is the really mild weather we've been having this week, some of that 16-foot snowbank in front on my house might melt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations on your quick BFP! Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhh congrats!! I'm happy things worked out so quickly for you! :)
Good luck for everything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be very variable coming off HBC. I personally had 106 days, 56 days, and now I'm 6DPO on CD28, so expecting a 36 day cycle. You never know how your body is going to function, but if you had EWCM then just to be safe I'd BD. Your CM can swing back and forth between EWCM and Watery/Creamy/Whatever. I can't rely solely on that because it's really not clear-cut. Also checking your cervical position really helped me, because even though I used a helluva lot of OPKs I never managed to get one truly positive in the both time I ovulated since August.

As so many have said on here before, "When in doubt, bang it out!"

The wisest words of TFAB. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww, I'm sorry you have to deal with that every day...
It sucks, but you're not a failure because you're not pregnant. Just try to remember that. You're a whole lot of other wonderful things, and you will be a mother someday (hopefully soon).

Sending hugs your way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My temp went up a little bit more this morning, somehow it kind of reassures me. It's hard not to compare cycles haha, although I've been temping 5 months this is only my 2nd temp shift :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahahaha well at least you guys actually managed it! We just gave up on that one time. Not our most glorious moment haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the well wishes, we will see how it turns out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! There are time like that, but the fact that we can laugh about it together then go on to have great sex on another night is what I love about our relationship.

Our worst time was last cycle when O was coming up, DH was leaving for a business trip for 3 days, so I wanted us to BD before he left. So I had an alarm set up for 5 a.m.... Needless to say I was half-asleep and not super into it, but we still tried for a while, when he went limp. I panicked, he felt bad, then he left.

Thankfully it was the only time that happened, but lesson learned: do not try to have sex when you're still sleeping!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 01:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [5 DPO, worried about my temps.](https://www.fertilityfriend.com/home/subject1257)

I did have a temp spike but I'm worried that my temps are not high enough... They were higher last cycle after I ovulated. Is this normal or could it be a sign of a "bad" or weak ovulation?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 01:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whew that's a lot of BD! Way to go :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *fist bump* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy, 1 week? That *is* quite fast though haha, I don't know if I'd have the guts to do that! Because afterwards you actually have to go back you know?

It just sucks that some bosses will really hold it against you, when it's so unfair for women to have to choose.

Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! Well good luck on waiting to test! :) You can do it :)

And if this cycle doesn't pan out like you want, temping next cycle will be an additional source of data to look at :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless, you were good to do that! I like just drinking something hot and tasty, which is part of why I haven't quit completely yet.

I think it's good not to limit yourself too much, go get your life back this cycle! There's nothing worse than putting everything on hold for TTC then realizing what you've been missing out on for nothing.

Have a good cycle, wishing you a happy ending :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, of course I'll be your cycle buddy u/iheartallthethings ! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww man, I am not willing/able to cut it out completely, I've cut back but even then, when I started this cycle I indulged in a few extra coffees for sure!

I *loooove* coffee. Enjoy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I think you should wait a few days so that you're at least 7-8DPO. Seeing as you don't know when you did ovulate it's a bit harder. Do you temp? It really helps when you can see a thermal shift, even if it's not a big spike in one day (I get a rise but it takes a few days to go up). Whatever you do, remember you're not out until AF shows and I wish you the best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( AF sucks, but I hope both of you can practice some self-care this week, and maybe even indulge in some wine or drinks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently 5DPO and so far was never able to have actual cycle buddies with my 106 and 56 day cycles! Looking like next cycle I might, seeing as my current cycle should last about 37 days. I'm getting closer to "normal" lengths woohoo!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also curious, I am convinced my CM is spermicidic, so... I'll be waiting for your lab report! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, I know what you mean!

I really hope that you can make a decision that'll work for you.

The job I absolutely would like to have is going to become open sometime in May/June. It's at my old workplace, with whom I maintain a good relationship. Since I started TTC last August and haven't gotten pregnant yet, I'm just hoping that when they hold the interviews I'm not visibly pregnant as that would kill my chances. Seeing as it's taking a while, might as well get lucky with this job! On the other hand the one thing I want most in life is to be a Mom, but if I can get both the job and a baby in the near future it would be perfect.

I'd still feel bad taking the job then leaving on maternity leave not long after, but hey, that's life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the active members who first guided me when I started out on here and who thankfully graduated will continue to contribute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5DPO, as per usual no symptoms, nothing. Trucking on at work.

Will try to drag my ass out for a lunchtime run, because after work I'm so exhausted I am literally no good. Especially Tuesday when I have my appointment with my therapist, it just drains me, like all the pressure I accumulate all week just falls.

Our friends just had their baby girl on Sunday night. Little squishy ball of cute baby Flora, can't wait to meet her, but I know it'll be hard on me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Hurricane :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets you know about your thyroid gland's functioning.

[Thyroid-stimulating hormone.](http://www.webmd.com/women/thyroid-stimulating-hormone-tsh#1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'll be my battle point when I see my doctor on Thursday.. My TSH was 3.7 in November, and my cycles have been super long and not that regular (they're getting better though), and I'm always tired, so I will definitely bring in research about TTC, early pregnancy and the right levels of TSH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm just not convinced my CM would allow sperm to survive very long, which is why if I had gotten advance notice of impeding ovulation I would have tried to go for -2, -1 and O :)

But yes, I know it's not too too bad. This is my type-A perfectionist side chiming in, would've liked to do *more*. Whatevs, I guess we'll see! Thanks Coog, you always have some encouragement for my pessimistic self </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing as I ovulated for the first time in January (stopped HBC in August), it still feels like a feat for sure!

Assuming that I ovulated on CD22 (most likely but not 100% sure), we hit O-2, O and O+1. FF had at first predicted I O'ed on CD21 (pretty sure that was wrong), then that would have given us just O-1 and O+1.. In either case, I'm not optimistic, but at least my cycles seem to be normalizing a bit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second u/MC-jigglebutt ! It's not an obligation to temp and track if you're fine without it. If you'd like to get pregnant and you're having unprotected sex, then you're trying. I wish you luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay, happy for you! I cut back by 19 days this cycle haha, ovulated on CD22 instead of 41 yasssss. I know how you feel!

Except I wasn't expecting it so soon (never managed a truly positive OPK), so our timing wasn't great. Hey, at least I ovulated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats on your home! And I'd vote a fat-day off as well :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome to see such good improvement! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
