<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5769</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone's bio (xpost r/iamverybadass) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I am a dynamic figure, often seen scaling walls and crushing ice. I have been known to remodel train stations on my lunch breaks, making them more efficient in the area of heat retention. I translate ethnic slurs for refugees, I write award-winning operas, I manage time efficiently. Occasionally, I tread water for three days in a row.

I woo women with my sensuous and godlike trombone playing, I can pilot bicycles up severe inclines with unflagging speed, and I cook Thirty-Minute cookies in twenty minutes. I am an expert in stucco, a veteran in love, and an outlaw in Peru.

Using only a hoe and a large glass of water, I once single-handedly defended a small village in the Amazon Basin from a horde of ferocious army ants. I play bluegrass cello, I am the subject of numerous documentaries. When I'm bored, I build large suspension bridges in my yard. I enjoy urban hang gliding. On Wednesdays, after work, I repair electrical appliances free of charge.

I am an abstract artist, a concrete analyst, and a ruthless bookie. Critics worldwide swoon over my original line of corduroy eveningwear. I do not perspire. I am a private citizen, yet I receive fan mail. I have been caller number nine and have won the weekend passes. Last summer I toured Albania with a travelling centrifugal-force demonstration. My deft floral arrangements have earned me fame in international botany circles. Children trust me.

I can hurl tennis rackets at small moving objects with deadly accuracy. I once read Paradise Lost, Moby Dick, and David Copperfield in one day and still had time to refurbish an entire dining room that evening. I know the exact location of every food item in the supermarket. I have performed several covert operations for the BBC. I sleep once a week; when I do sleep, I sleep in a chair. While on holiday in Australia, I successfully negotiated with a group of terrorists who had seized a small bakery. The laws of physics do not apply to me.

I balance, I weave, I dodge, I frolic, and my bills are all paid. On weekends, to let off steam, I participate in full-contact origami. Years ago I discovered the meaning of life but forgot to write it down. I have made extraordinary four course meals using only a mouli and a toaster oven. I have won bullfights in San Juan, cliff-diving competitions in Sri Lanka, and spelling bees at the Kremlin. I have played Hamlet, I have performed open-heart surgery, and I have spoken with Elvis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> S O A P Z </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Halp lonly pi11ar f1nd fri3nd5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 09:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> REEAALLYY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gamer dudes, dudettes. When it comes to keep your gamer gear at peak performance, oh the games people play. REALLY. A lot of you game assassins seem to think that skill alone is gonna get you to the victory lane, as you go leaping from level to level, room to room, and world to world! With little or no effort. Ooooooh planet rangers, you wanna know one little dirty secret? Yeah-huh do ya? You're not gonna get there if your gear's all crapped up with gamer gunk. Dust. Chip dip. Greasy sticker slimy game residue! It's a fact! Dirty gear doesn't perform as well as clean gear, and may even crash, and burn! OH NOO! UGHHH! You can't do it dirty, you gotta do it clean, and here's how. This stuff, right here, this stuff!? This is the good stuff, the right stuff, the Dust Off stuff. The only stuff you should use to clean your gear. First, because it works, duh. Second because when used properly its completely safe. And third, cause its the best stuff out there. According to experts, like me! Lets get cleaning. Now, the keyboard. Grab it sideways kinda like youre gonna play an accordion. Grab your Dust Off Gamer Gear duster from your gamer kit, and holding the can upright spraying short bursts as you work your way around all those nooks and crannies. Oh man! Just look at all that crap flying outta there. There mustve been an entire bowl of cereal down there, and uh enough skin fragments to clone yourself. When youre done spraying, take a swab for the tiny places, and then take this Dust Off Gaming Gear wipe and wipe off the top, the front, the back and the sides so you kill all those nasty germs. KILL THEM ALL! PSHEW PSHEW PSHEW PSHEW PBBBBB. FINISH HIM. Keyboard is done baby! Now the mouse. Same drill as the keyboard. Hold the Dust Off LCD spray, give it a spray, then a good wipe-down with the Dust Off Game Gear swab and wipe. And youre all set. You may be saying you can skip this step because you have one of those cool laser meeces. Lasers need to be cleaned too, so youre not off the hook on that one. Next, we move onto the screen. For this step, we have a specially formulated Dust Off screen spray and Dust Off shammy. And let me tell you folks, it is not a paper towel and window cleaner. It is not that. Its totally safe for the screen and for you! Spray it one like this, wipe it off like this! And youre all set. Oh and uh you can spray on the acrylic parts too so theyre nice and shiny. Mom would be so proud. Now, for the scary part! THE COMPUTER! Its definitely worth another reminder from Mr. Safety. Now make sure, the entire computer is off. Not hibernatin or sleepin. But completely O. F. F. Off. Thanks Mr. Safety. CPUs have just a couple of screws. You can unscrew when you unscrew the housing, your manual, assuming you didnt throw it away like I did, uh will show you how to do it. Carefully remove the housing and, ITS ALIVE! Welcome to the inner sectom. This isnt so scary. Were not even gonna touch anything. Grab your Dust Off Gaming duster, and blowing from the inside out, very important, inside out, spray the fan. Then, spray the motherboard, and other components. Do not use a leaf blower! VOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO. Do not use a vacuum! VOOOOOOOOOOOOO. Vacuums can cause static discharge and could severely damage your computer. When we are done, replace the housing and were just about finished. The last part of the cleaning does require that the computer be turned on, so turn that baby on man! soft rock Listen to that baby hum. Now, were gonna clean the optics of your CD, DVD, and Blue-ray player. Using this special formulated Dust Off cleaning disk, open the tray, slide it in ;). And follow the audio instructions. If you hear closely, you can hear giggling coming from the player, its so happy to be cleaned. Thats it ladies and terminators. So remember, before you get your game on, get your clean on Gamer Gear Dust Off. Keep it clean, keep it new, keep it Dust Off, for gaming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gamer dudes, dudettes. When it comes to keep your gamer gear at peak performance, oh the games people play. REALLY. A lot of you game assassins seem to think that skill alone is gonna get you to the victory lane, as you go leaping from level to level, room to room, and world to world! With little or no effort. Ooooooh planet rangers, you wanna know one little dirty secret? Yeah-huh do ya? You're not gonna get there if your gear's all crapped up with gamer gunk. Dust. Chip dip. Greasy sticker slimy game residue! It's a fact! Dirty gear doesn't perform as well as clean gear, and may even crash, and burn! OH NOO! UGHHH! You can't do it dirty, you gotta do it clean, and here's how. This stuff, right here, this stuff!? This is the good stuff, the right stuff, the Dust Off stuff. The only stuff you should use to clean your gear. First, because it works, duh. Second because when used properly its completely safe. And third, cause its the best stuff out there. According to experts, like me! Lets get cleaning. Now, the keyboard. Grab it sideways kinda like youre gonna play an accordion. Grab your Dust Off Gamer Gear duster from your gamer kit, and holding the can upright spraying short bursts as you work your way around all those nooks and crannies. Oh man! Just look at all that crap flying outta there. There mustve been an entire bowl of cereal down there, and uh enough skin fragments to clone yourself. When youre done spraying, take a swab for the tiny places, and then take this Dust Off Gaming Gear wipe and wipe off the top, the front, the back and the sides so you kill all those nasty germs. KILL THEM ALL! PSHEW PSHEW PSHEW PSHEW PBBBBB. FINISH HIM. Keyboard is done baby! Now the mouse. Same drill as the keyboard. Hold the Dust Off LCD spray, give it a spray, then a good wipe-down with the Dust Off Game Gear swab and wipe. And youre all set. You may be saying you can skip this step because you have one of those cool laser meeces. Lasers need to be cleaned too, so youre not off the hook on that one. Next, we move onto the screen. For this step, we have a specially formulated Dust Off screen spray and Dust Off shammy. And let me tell you folks, it is not a paper towel and window cleaner. It is not that. Its totally safe for the screen and for you! Spray it one like this, wipe it off like this! And youre all set. Oh and uh you can spray on the acrylic parts too so theyre nice and shiny. Mom would be so proud. Now, for the scary part! THE COMPUTER! Its definitely worth another reminder from Mr. Safety. Now make sure, the entire computer is off. Not hibernatin or sleepin. But completely O. F. F. Off. Thanks Mr. Safety. CPUs have just a couple of screws. You can unscrew when you unscrew the housing, your manual, assuming you didnt throw it away like I did, uh will show you how to do it. Carefully remove the housing and, ITS ALIVE! Welcome to the inner sectom. This isnt so scary. Were not even gonna touch anything. Grab your Dust Off Gaming duster, and blowing from the inside out, very important, inside out, spray the fan. Then, spray the motherboard, and other components. Do not use a leaf blower! VOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO. Do not use a vacuum! VOOOOOOOOOOOOO. Vacuums can cause static discharge and could severely damage your computer. When we are done, replace the housing and were just about finished. The last part of the cleaning does require that the computer be turned on, so turn that baby on man! soft rock Listen to that baby hum. Now, were gonna clean the optics of your CD, DVD, and Blue-ray player. Using this special formulated Dust Off cleaning disk, open the tray, slide it in ;). And follow the audio instructions. If you hear closely, you can hear giggling coming from the player, its so happy to be cleaned. Thats it ladies and terminators. So remember, before you get your game on, get your clean on Gamer Gear Dust Off. Keep it clean, keep it new, keep it Dust Off, for gaming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chinese master race? Considering the current geopolitical situation, H E L L Y E A  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T H U R S D A Y  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T H U R S D A Y  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
