<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2315</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHO FUCKING CARES! Holy shit, how petty can you be?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cabbie was coming over to help him right before the little shit revealed he was trolling! This doggo did me a bummer bamboozle!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sort of. But it's not a conscious racism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, because of some Hadith.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do agree that Saudi courts aren't just and are completely corrupt. But let's not fucking fool ourselves here; the US justice system is also totally corrupted and unfair in its own right. Particularly if you're poor and/or a person of color. Would I rather have a trail in America than in Saudi? Obviouslyyy. But I'm not going to pretend like due process is actually given to the majority of folks who go through the American courts. It absolutely isn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barbaric was the wrong word choice. Yes, decapitation is barbaric and crude, I agree. However, it is far more effective than lethal injection, as I stated. If you support the death penalty at all, then it is hypocritical to lambaste countries that perform the death penalty in a way that makes YOU uncomfortable. 

It's the same argument as dog vs. cow meat. There's no difference between eating a dog and eating a cow except marketing and cultural norms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every doctor I've seen here is male and always alone, so idk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, Saudi is an awful place to live for many reasons. But you have to remember that much of the exceptionally wild shit you hear about (such as beheading for apostatizing) is propaganda like everything else. Yes, they behead people here. Mostly for murder, rape, child molestation, etc. America still has the death penalty, and the American method is far more barbaric than a swift decapitation and much less effective. Often death row inmates do not die painlessly or quickly in American prisons as they are giving drug concoctions that do not really work since European pharmaceutical companies have refused to continue supplying America with the proper drugs to execute people. 

I can assure you that I am not going to be arrested or beheaded for speaking ill of The KSA in the privacy of my home just a few blocks from the American Embassy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Everything's together and ready to go. 

As far as my "therapist," I have rather severe panic disorder and he was really helpful until he told me this dumb shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. But I'm so thankful to be getting out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the yawning thing has always been confusing as fuck to me. My husband reprimands me when I make a yawn noise or a yawn face.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, how depressing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's Jordanian and has actually been extremely helpful up until this point. The Saudis mostly work at military hospitals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
