<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They better send in the feds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crosby is actually right handed.

It's one of the reasons why he has such great puck handling skills.

He has his stronger hand on the butt of the stick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fix your garbage matchmaking for dominion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Players load into the game:

Our Team:

108 (me)
108
108
101

Their team

5
32
20
47


Is your matchmaker coded to fuck one team? Is that how it works?

I'm pretty sure I don't need to tell you which team won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there ever an instance when a Glock can discharge without your finger on the trigger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been reading up on the Glock, and I've noticed that there seems to be a plethora of articles on Glocks accidentally discharging.

Can the Glock discharge if you keep your finger off the trigger?

I figure any reasonable gun owner knows to keep his finger off the trigger, and that in itself is a huge deterrent of any accidental discharges.

But then you read about police chiefs and sergeants accidentally discharging their glocks during maintenance etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "You wanna see something really cool...." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 07:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 07:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So who wants to make a bet,

Gravedigger or Big foot drove by?

Big foot was always the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 07:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like a good teacher.

So why aren't you getting a raise? And by you, I mean specifically you.

Could your union be blamed? It seems like they push the lowest common denominator, by protecting their base and their own interests, while resting on the shoulders of the "few" good teachers who do exemplary work to use as an example of why the Union deserves more.

You sound like you've invested in a career, and an important career, as educating our youth will come to benefit or haunt us in spades as they take over our worldly responsibilities.

You put in the time, the effort, and the expertise. So where is your monetary gain? 

My question to you is seriously, who do YOU blame, the union or the state/local government? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 07:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't necessarily agree with this.

A lot of social workers do the work because they love it, and the pay is apparently garbage. You need to love your job, especially one like teaching and taking care of others, before you can be intimately involved enough to change lives and the direction those lives are heading.

Yes pay can draw in "talent", but what you're stipulating is that throwing money at teachers should "fix" the education system.

Now if we paid High school teachers 100k a year, do you think the results would be better? I'm sure they would be (marginally or more so), but would that be the best use of the money.

The fact, is that we have students dropping out of school, and we need to figure out why students are dropping out of school. We also need to find ways to encourage students to be successful, not necessarily in math or physics, or biology, but successful in life.

Learning about math, and biology, and physics should help shape them, and give them tools to succeed, but it shouldn't be a baseline for their success. 

Get rid of the baselines, and start teaching students to be happy, and strive for their own goals. Give them tools, but make sure learning about those tools doesn't end up causing them to drop out and fall on their faces before they even get a chance to spread their wings as young adults. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you're making the assumption that all abusive relationships end up in murder.

If you were a law student, then you would know this notion that "almost always" or "absolutes" is counter intuitive, especially when you don't have any facts or statistics to back up your crazy claims.

Can you explain to me how 1700 women (out of 150 million women in the US) dying to spousal abuse every year is somehow alluding to whatever the fuck you're talking about?

Can you also explain to me how the law and police barely protect anyone? If that was the case, how do police forces keep being funded, if they don't produce results? After all, even police have quotas, and they have a requirement to meet those quotas.

You do realize (that is, being a law student, lol), that people in a relationship, is also synonymous as a partnership, therefore there are two people involved, and two perspectives. The police need to take these two perspectives into account because arresting someone is a serious matter. The due diligence of the law far outweighs crazy claims that all abusive relationships end in murder.

Furthermore, in 2013 they reauthorized the VAWA (the original VAWA dropped domestic issues by 64%), so yes congress is trying to tune the law to protect people the best they can.

This idea that the law can protect everyone is nonsense, there are cases where no degree of policing can protect someone. Especially when they need to respect privacy and property laws. Furthermore, there is human error, after all police are humans. While it's awful when a spouse is killed, that doesn't mean our system is failing, it just means that we need to figure why it happened and fix it the best we can.

Now if you have suggestions for a better overall system, then by all means, run for congress and throw around nonsense claims. I'm sure you'll attract a few people who want to delude themselves into the idea that the police are useless and (almost) all abusive relationships end in murder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand how paying teachers more money is going to make "education" better.

I'm not saying they don't deserve more money, as everyone deserves a raise within a 5 year period.

But I just don't understand how you equate teacher pay to valuing pubic school children.

We need to separate the two issues. Teaching is a job, and the pay that goes with it should have no bearing on the quality of education.

Instead, we need a flexible and modern curriculum, find out what our generation is interested in, and design a learning curriculum in what students WANT to learn. 

It seems like education has turned into this treadmill, where the object isn't about quality, but instead about placating this notion that students need to finish school to be successful in life.

School should be a place that doesn't define you, but helps shape you. We need to encourage students to be successful, and follow their passions. Sure we need to teach them the basics, like reading, math, whatever, but mix it up.

If the system is leaving some students behind, why not experiment with these students. Test new curriculum on them, see if it works, instead of just funding these so called "drop out" factories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this was a fact, then the battered woman's defence would be a sound argument in every instance of abuse.

As it stands, just because a spouse is abused, it doesn't mean that they can turn around and kill their spouse out of fear for their lives and claim self defence to protect themselves from an impending threat. So the battered woman's defence isn't applicable in every notion of abuse, because statistically what you're claiming doesn't hold any water.

Some spouses live in an abusive relationship for years, others leave, others invoke the law to change the situation, and in a small fraction, a spouse kills another spouse. According to google, 3 women are killed everyday by a spouse. 1,700 women were killed in 2015 from spousal abuse. How many abusive relationships are there? I would assume in a population of over 300 million, probably a lot more than that.

This idea that every case of abuse turns into murder is absolutely insane. If that was the case, it would be lamented as an epidemic, and the police would be highly vigilant in any notion of domestic abuse.

They would also get rid of the 2 strike rule and someone goes to jail on a domestic abuse emergency call, and instead arrest the "supposed" offending party immediately to investigate thoroughly, as statistically the abused party will be murdered eventually.

Don't go around making outlandish claims that all domestic abuse leads to murder. You sound like a fucking twat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, what?

Almost always abusive spouses (or boyfriends as you put it, because women can't be abusers apparently) escalate to murder?

What the fuck are you smoking.

So why don't we put all abusive husbands or wives in jail for 25 years pre-emptively. Since it's going to escalate to murder anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 05:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1ZXHsNqkDI4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 05:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While this is a really sad situation, if you really think about it, in a rational way, it's almost impossible to prevent these kinds of situations entirely.

How do you decipher the difference between an angry abusive boyfriend, from one who is going to snap and kill his girlfriend?

Sometimes the cops prevent catastrophe, sometimes they don't.

We could fund more police personnel, but in the end, sooner or later, one sad horrible incident will slip through the cracks.

It seems like a good chunk of murderers who kill their loved ones, don't go out and kill anyone else. So both reactive and preventative measures are going to be limited to basic law and enforcement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 09:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah its easily the worst online experience I've encountered.

I tried dominion a few times back when the game came out, wasn't nearly this bad.

They have a lot of work ahead of them, because as far as I'm concerned, dominion is in pre-alpha condition.

I'm doing moves I don't even input on the controller the delay on movement is so fucked. I'm doing storm rushes and riptide strike's at random, because the game has no idea what the fuck is going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy Shit, the Dominion net code is awful. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 08:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally play 1v1 or 2v2, but decided to grind dominion for Orders and the last bit of levels I need for Orochi Rep 3.

The net code really doesn't work on dominion at all.

My back steps and counter guard breaks are delayed. Deflections are luck. Parry is 50/50.

Yet in 1v1 and 2v2's I can actually time the attacks.

What the fuck is this?

My ping is 10 to most speed test sites, and my down is 80mb/s and up is 30mb/s.

So my connection isn't the issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you guys recommend, a Glock or a 1911? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both seem like great guns.

Does anyone have both, and would you recommend one over the other? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Duke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL That John Wayne starred as Genghis Khan in the movie "The Conquerer" (1956) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did he hit the skateboarder in the first place?

He was just going by him.

The way he staggers backwards while making the phone call, just screams "fuckhead". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guys history has a lot of this.

Funny guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking exactly the same thing.

I wonder if they gave him a shot of some kind of pain killer before the picture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do this with an iPhone 7 right?

Is it water proof, or water resistant? The later meaning your phone is fucked if you do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you guys pick up your brass at public shooting ranges? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always cleaned up after myself.

If you see people leaving their brass after shooting at a public range, does it bug you?

Normally I don't care what others do, but when I see people leave brass on the ground, it just seems lazy.

What's your guys thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that an atmosphere on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pepsi points were very real.

I earned a velvet CD case with them.

I was really young, and coerced my parents to buy Pepsi in bulk. They didn't know why, just that it put a smile on my face every time I took the plastic thing from under the cap out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does he do this all the time? Or was it a bug?

The way he falls over makes me think it's an intended joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't see the sub before clicking the gif, I thought he was going to pull it off, but then he fucked it up. I checked the sub, and everything makes sense now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't agree with this notion that we have extremities of right and left on a Federal level. 

Canada is different in politics for a plethora of reasons. Our responsible government model really perpetuates this toe the line mentality, so when Canadians give a majority government the reigns to do as they like, you tend to see a lot of bills past that our either center left or center right. 

We also don't attach political beliefs to our parties like Americans do. Rarely if at all do I see pro or anti abortion rhetoric in campaigns for either side. The question on homosexuals being able to become married was entertained by both sides of the aisle here. 

Our politics are really center, so when you hand the reigns to the liberals or the conservatives you see very little change in any direction. It seems to be what's best for the country as a whole.  The conservatives will be a bit more conservative with their budget bills, and the liberals will be a bit more liberal. But never a sense of extremism or urgency for change with either or. 

In comparison to the US you see this waring of factions, democrats vs republicans. A lot of baggage is attached to both sides. It doesn't seem like what's best for the country, but instead what will spite the other side. 

It's really sad because in the 50s and 60s it seemed like politics in America was about the people. At least from what I read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So show me the parallels between Marxist Communism, and the USSR under Stalin. Show me how the plan from Stalin and his power base was to, and I quote:

"In fact, the realm of freedom does not commence until the point is passed where labor under the compulsion of necessity and of external utility is required."

It seems like Stalin did quite the opposite, and instead just used Communism as a means to manipulate everyone. His power base got richer, and the poor and impoverished got poorer. He did this by enslaving everyone to the state, either through force or dependency. There was no plan for freedom. 

In return I'll show you the parallels of Friedmans theory of capitalism and how it conspired in the deregulation of Wall Street and the 2008 mortgage bubble. 

Greenspan even apologized and admitted it wasn't what he expected. 

I'm a moderate, both ideologically and politically. This idea that capitalism unhinged is some shining light is bullshit. 

We have a balance in practice, and that's why western societies function.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is it not working?

They just started implementing the ID attachment to ticket sales. 

The only complaints that have arisen are ticket buyers worried about not being able to offload tickets they can't use. 

Secondly, as one news article has stipulated, the ID attachment is the equivalent of a performer adding DRM to their concerts. 

If an artist doesn't want their tickets to their concert being resold for a higher price why are they not allowed to stem it with systems in place that prevent the resale of their product?

Informal markets have been stemmed here in Canada. A two tier healthcare system has been shot down many times. There is a small demand for it, but as a whole Canadians want to keep our single tier universal healthcare system. 

If artists and venues don't want their tickets resold, and they put in the proper systems to prevent it, then you'll see any informal markets done away with in regards to ticket reselling. 

How do you get around bulk ticket buying limitations, ID attached to each ticket? You don't.

Secondly ticketmaster has a 3rd party site to pay a premium for tickets. The difference is that it's a pre arrangement between the venue and ticketmaster. There is also a small amount of tickets reserved for this said service. Which leaves the rest of the tickets for the actual event goers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friedman wasn't right wing?

Friedman wasn't against the welfare state?

Both Stalin and Sung never utilized a pure socialist state. It was a perverse oligarchy that victimized the poor and anyone against their position or views. 

The point is that all western states employ ideologies from capitalistic and socialistic regimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what it is. 

You're citing right wing pro capitalist economists. Minus Keynes. 

All of which view the government as a business entity. 

Friedman influenced Alan Greenspan. Look how that turned out for America in 2008.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be true if businesses and corporations ran the state. They do not, therefore its socialism and socialist ideologies that shape our social welfare systems. 

List a couple of your "proper" economists. 

Curious to who you're referencing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think in general people forget that all western societies are comprised of both socialism and capitalism.

We have regulatory bodies and social welfare, and at the same time we try to allow unrestricted competition in the economic markets.

The general good is something we should be aiming at. The only way to really attain this is a healthy balance between socialism and capitalism, while giving legitimacy and issues through democracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What it feels like being Canadian and reading Reddit about US Politics for the past 5 months. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is wrong.

We don't live in a society that is pure capitalistic in nature. In fact no society exists with pure capitalism. All western societies are both capitalistic and socialist. They have regulation and "free" markets dictated by laws.

Therefore this idea that economics makes sense with ticket scalping is absurd, as the laws and regulations are clearly heading to restrictions on ticket reselling. The reason for this is clearly because the people involved, performers and consumers don't want middlemen marking up the price of tickets. Both the performer (seller), and the consumer (buyer), don't benefit from scalpers in anyway shape or form.

Nobody here is complaining about "ticket price", we're here complaining about ticket price being ballooned by scalpers, who offer nothing in return. 

Those ticket prices set by the artist should be the price of admission, hence why the complicated relationship between artist, agent, financial accountants etc, and Ticketmaster dictate a certain price.

Now if the performer/venue side of things charge $500 dollars for a ticket, that's fine. Their fans may be upset, but at least the performer and artist can put that gross profit into the performance or venue.

The scalper, doesn't add fuck all to the performance or venue. They get all of the benefit of a profit, without adding a single fucking point of value to the performance. The only risk they take, is if they can't offload the tickets, in which they take a hit. Then they end up selling the tickets in front of the arena or venue for a loss, in which those tickets would have been better available on the website where they were originally being sold, where the people who could have gone to the show, would have bought them in a convenient and planned manner.

Now if the scalper made the tickets more accessible to the public through some infrastructure, then sure, they could charge a surplus. But instead, they make getting the tickets more difficult. They take away the chance for the show goers to get the ticket originally intended, AND, they then charge a surplus to resell the ticket on craigslist or in front of the venue.

Now if you want to allow "economics" to have free reign, then you would need to allow the scalpers to use these "Bots" to purchase tickets en masse. Since everyone would have "access" to these bots (since you can buy them online or from someone who codes them), that would be fair competition.

Secondly, if you want economics to have free reign, the performer shouldn't have a say in how much each ticket costs. Sure they can set a reserve, but every ticket should be auctioned from Ticketmaster. You remove the secondary middleman, and Ticketmaster and the performer make the profits.

Free reign economics is a mess and it's garbage. Hence why we have regulatory bodies, consumers and performers wanting it to be a simple "Buy this ticket", then go to the show process.

Not a frantically competing with not only people who want to go to the show, but also scalpers and resellers, when you're trying to buy tickets online from Ticketmaster.

Now you guys can throw around the "Economically this...." all you want. But keep in mind, deregulation is what fucked up the housing market between the late 90s and 2008. Profits and economics took priority over the general good.

We have no problem with "sellers" making a profit. We do have a problem with people "reselling" without adding any value to a service or product. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not true.

Labour laws, minimum wage, etc.

What about preventing monopolies? Monopolies take advantage of demand to raise the cost, by eliminating competition. 

You guys are all fucking retards. Anyone who advocates for scalping tickets always, and I mean always, grasps at straws to defend it.

Just stop, consumers (through legislation), the performers (through the fact that they do the performance and dictate through themselves or their agent what they want), and even Ticketmaster (the actual ticket selling middleman, who also adds a cost to the ticket for their services) are eagerly putting in measures to prevent it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 10:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What logic?

Let's take your luxury car example. Lamborghini sets a price for their speciality cars, and they go based on a waiting list. It's not based on who wants to pay more or not. 

There is a set price by the retailer/manufacturer, and they usually stand by that price. 

When a hot item comes out, a lot of retailers will put a 1 hot item per household. Why do they do this? Because resellers who buy an item and then resell for a higher price create an unnecessary added cost for the item. This doesn't benefit anyone except for the reseller. 

The two most important parties involved in a product or service being purchased is the seller and buyer. If the seller and buyer agree to not have a middleman in the transaction, then they should have that right. Furthermore, there is an added benefit of buying from the supplier, knowing that your product is authentic and guaranteed. 

With scalpers you don't even know if the tickets are real. Another reason that our city and ticket master are cracking down on scalpers. Fraud runs rampant among resellers. 

The process of buying and selling is both cheaper and more efficient when you cut out the middleman and just buy from the supplier. 

Now logically, the consumer would rather buy Katy Perry tickets for:

$125 dollars from ticket master 

Instead of 

$300 dollars from a piece of shit scalper. 

The added cost isn't because they provide a service,   Or benefit to the consumer. 

Lastly, if you cut out the reseller through measures and systems, you'll only have one type of consumer and purchaser: 

People who want to go to the concert, or buy tickets for their friends and family who want to go to the concert. 

We don't need scalpers or resellers in the ticket sales business. They don't provide anything the consumer demands. They are dirty little bitches who manipulate the system to gain a profit. The regular consumer pays the price for the resellers greed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 10:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go read another Milton Friedman book. 

You seem to think that the consumer and performer have no say in how the tickets are distributed. 

This isn't the free market per se. 

It's a contract between the performer, venue, and ticket master. It's also the cities issue as a lot of people dislike scalpers hawking tickets in front of the arena. As our news coined our scalpers as an "eye sore". 

If all three of these entities want to regulate the distribution of the tickets then the free market takes a back seat. 

I'm sure most performers rather their fans and people who intend to see the concert get the tickets. Why would they want a middle man cost added to their tickets? How do they benefit from this?

You have a dog in this fight. Are you a slimy reseller?

Only two kinds of people advocate for scalping. Scalpers themselves and clowns. 

Which one are you?

It's like you get a hard on at the thought of some person making a profit off reselling tickets. The fact that a family of four cant afford to go to a concert or hockey game because scalpers inflated the price of the tickets to hundreds of dollars probably makes your heart palpitate. 

Your mother must be proud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the most absurd thing I've ever heard. 

The base ticket cost is too low therefore we should rely on resellers to inflate the cost to a more appropriate level. 

What the fuck are you smoking? 

Also, if the tickets are undervalued, I rather the artist increase the cost, instead of some scumbag middle man profiting off reselling the ticket. 

Just stop you clown.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're wrong on every single point except for the complications of buying tickets for your family or friends. 

You can blame the scalpers for this complication. There is a cost to preventing people from abusing the system. Unfortunately this is one of the costs. 

Fortunately many areas are adopting new regulations on ticket sales, which inherently prove your points as moot.

You could also have bought those tickets from the vendor window as last minute as well. 

Also as far as our housing prices here, the government is actually trying to cool the market with a 15% tax on foreign buyers and other means. 

Our property tax went from $6k a year to over $12k, so yeah property owners are crying their eyes out. 

Listen I get what you're trying to do. But you need to stop. Scalpers and reselling tickets is an issue. Performers and venues don't want people adding a middle man cost to tickets unnecessarily. Consumers looking to go to the show also don't want this added cost. 

Go take a nap. Wake up and try to realize how ridiculous you sound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And my point is that they need to put systems in place that prevent scalpers from abusing the system. In fact they should put systems in that prevent scalpers from doing what they do. 

That would benefit everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're missing the point. 

You're taking tickets away from people who want to go to the concert but weren't fast enough to beat you to the punch. 

My point isn't that you alone are a drop in the bucket of the resell issue. 

My point is that if 200 people do what you're doing, then they take thousands of tickets away from actual concert goers. These concert goers then need to pay a mark up because of people scalping the tickets. 

A better system is if no one bought surplus tickets to resell for a higher value, and instead people who wanted to go to the concert were able to buy the tickets at a base ticket value. 

Nobody likes resellers/scalpers because they piggy back off the performers and venue presenters, to make a easy buck, but that buck comes from ripping off the poor people who just want to go see a show. 

Nobody likes scalpers, get that through your head. You're not some smooth operators profiting from ingenuity. You guys are losers. 

I would put scalpers, rapists and pedophiles all in the same category of societies degenerates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better yet how about if scalpers didn't buy the tickets in the first place. Then people who actually want to go to the concert or venue to actually enjoy it could buy those tickets at face value. 

That too much logic for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go take your medication and go to sleep. 

You're so full of shit. 

You're buying a commodity that is very limited and marking up the price. 

These concerts only come around once every couple of years for people's favourite artists. 

People want to go see the concert. They don't want to deal with resellers. Most rational people would love a system in place that enforces the base ticket cost. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually those are two different things. 

A soda can isn't a one time show.

Buying and reselling a ticket from a performer isn't ok. The performer sets the price and that should be the price of admission. Period. It shouldn't balloon to twice the amount just because someone wants to profit off of a performers tickets. These events should be affordable so young people and families can afford to go and have fun. 

Buying a hockey ticket for the sole reason to resell it for a higher profit is what prices out a lot of families from going to see the games here. After all it's a family event, not an event for fuck heads to make a profit by reselling the tickets for exuberant prices. 

You're assuming I can't afford to go see these venues or games, I can easily afford either base price or resell. So I don't need to get into your line. 

The point is, as a city, things are slowly changing for the better. Not only have the consumers here advocated for scalpers to fuck off, but so have big name performers and venues. Ticketmaster is putting in measures to prevent resell, and its wonderful. 

Your point is moot. Anyone who advocates for scalping is an idiot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did. I guess Reddit didn't want to actually put the reply to him. No idea why.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. 

No thanks. 

Like I said, the scalping in my city is so bad that most of the performers and venues are transitioning to the ID being attached to the tickets. 

Your mentality is fucked if you think scalping is fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's easy for you to say. Come to Vancouver, Canada and let's see you say the same BS. Scalpers are doubling ticket prices for very popular events/concerts here. 

In fact they started making the tickets ID required. You can buy tickets for your friends, but you need to go in with them if the tickets are attached to your ID. 

People like you have no idea how bad scalpers can be when you live in places with high costs of living. 

Our average housing prices here are $900k. You can thank flippers and investment hedge funds for that as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better yet. 

Tie the tickets to the buyers ID. 

Fucking scalpers have ruined the ticket prices here in Vancouver.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should be hunting down the idiot who did this. 

Then torture them before they put a bullet in their head. 

Fucking piece of shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of those instances where no one wins and everyone loses. 

Really sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Trespassers will be shot, survivors will be shot again." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah ok, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You recommend grease over oil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your experiences with cleaning kits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which ones are the best in your opinion?

Looking for personal experiences. Want my dollar to go as far as possible with this investment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best moment is, initially when Mr Meseeks is trying to help Jerry with his golf game. 

Square your shoulders, and follow through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's good. It's like got milk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "His marriage is hanging from a thread. " </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you hear me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A pile of severed penises.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Oreo ice cream good?

Never tried it before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure the management has plans drawn out. He wasn't part of those plans. 

Have some faith in our organization.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will miss the guy. 

Hope he does well and enjoys his stay there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Samsung should be last. They shouldn't even be on that list. 

One of the worst customer and tech support I have ever had the displeasure of dealing with. 

The top in my opinion for customer support in general have always been the "big 3". 

Apple
Amazon
Microsoft

They clearly hire people who want to do the job. They are articulate and English is their first language. 

I don't want to come off as an asshole, but if the people phoning in are from North America, it's a very likely chance they are speaking:

English
Spanish
French

I don't know where Samsung hires their people, but it must be an outsourced call centre where the people working there are underpaid, under trained, and they don't give a shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this picture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stewart is in great shape for a guy his age.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think this is what they mean by "draining the swamp".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is he comfortable with someone clearly not mentally or physically capable of operating that vehicle is bouncing on his lap.

Like what the fuck are they trying to achieve? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Richard Simmons turns out to be fine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean on the Home screen. Not necessarily on the physical packaging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm alluring more to it only showing on PS4 Pro's.

For the standard PS4 it could show that it is HDR enabled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they could add that too, the point I'm making is that it would be nice if they added some kind of indication that the game is optimized for the PS4 Pro, and how it's optimized.

HDR support etc, Frame rate, Resolution, whatever.

For the regular PS4 they could put an indication for HDR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it would offer an incentive for game companies to come in and optimize their game for Pro support though.

When they patch it in after the fact, they can add the "Pro" symbol to the top right corner of the game on the Home screen.

I'm sure game companies want to offer support for their game consumers, and that should include Pro or Boost support.

I'm not talking about the physical packaging, I'm talking about the home screen icons:

https://i.ytimg.com/vi/A3KDyQQcPxQ/hqdefault.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you rip open someones driver side door, yank them out of the drivers seat, curb stomp them a little for good measure, and then commandeer their vehicle.

I'm sure adrenaline kicks in to where you don't even give a shit who's behind or beside you to check your rear view or side view mirrors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think it would be useful if PS4 Pro optimized games had the "Pro" logo in the top right corner. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://assets.vg247.com/current//2016/09/ps4_pro_enhanced_logo_1.png

The framed "Pro" in this logo, if they put it in the top right corner of your games on the Home screen.

The games that are "boost" enabled, should also have a framed "Boost" on the top right hand corner of the game icon on the home screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So to clarify, if a game is optimized for the PS4 Pro, boost mode has no effect? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It only affects games that have not been optimized for the pro, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does a top of the line, professional paint job look like? How much would such a paint job cost you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the paint jobs I've seen on this subreddit are done by the gun owners. The paint jobs don't look bad.

I'm wondering, what would a professional top of the line (crme de la crme) paint job look like?

How much would one cost, if you were to have, let's say, an AR15 painted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the point of it. 

Vikings is quality entertainment. Easily one of the better shows on TV right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah man. Seeing that picture again brought back feels. 

Great actor. Great person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While I think the Reiteras Gladiator idea is cool. I think a Russel Crowe/ Spartacus Gladiator would be more preferred. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A dual wielding Gladiator. 

Balanced somewhere between a Peacekeeper and a Berserker. 

Capable of devastating counters. 

Very effective against shield users. 

https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/b1/24/8f/b1248f6a2acb4824f78475ce9d38fdde.jpg

http://img.gawkerassets.com/img/17qjkule6iw4njpg/original.jpg

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I think this is cool, I wouldn't want this to be the sole Gladiator. 

I want a Russel Crowe gladiator. Two swords, yelling "are you entertained".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rick: 

"Sorry, please proceed with your story about banging my daughter in high school. I'm not sure you want to take romantic advice from this guy, Morty. His marriage is hanging from a thread. " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Later this year. I think they started recording and animating last month for season 3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need to flog this guy. 

Also the mother of the girl is a bitch if she's forcing her to keep the pregnancy against the girls wishes. 

Fuck this world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew a rick and Morty reference would pop up. 

Need season 3 to keep my sanity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should be more accurate:

"The greatest paddle board in the world"

Trump would be proud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who hates needles, I hope edible vaccines can be engineered for human diseases as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real problem with bad policing is when cops over step their breadth of the law. 

We need serious measures to prevent miscarriage of the law. 

For starters, being answerable to the people they harass illegally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much do those balls weigh?

That shit looks heavy. This guy is a monster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emmitt was around during one of the Cowboys best era. 

Romo not the greatest eras. 

He also sat out for the best interest of the team to let a rookie player carry us to a Play off showing. 

Not once did he show any disappointment. He was purely professional and team centric. 

He's a class act and it's a huge blow to our team to lose him. 

There's a reason Jerry loved the guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No man. Romo bled for our team. You can't just say bye to that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now the real question. Who do you cheer for next year? Romo or the Cowboys? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you get the crown gems without the crates?

Did you open the crates?

Did you buy those crates from the feature tab?

Like I said before, the only place to spend those crown gems is on the crown crates/gem tab. 

You need to navigate there. 

Push R1 on the PS4 to get there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens when an object leaves our solar system? Does our solar system travel away from that object at 800,000km an hour? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stop thinking about this after hearing about how fast the sun travels, as well as the helical model.

Is traveling out of our solar system a one way trip? Could a space ship ever catch up to our solar system, if our solar system is rotating around the centre of our galaxy at 800,000km an hour? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol.

One of those jokes you won't admit you laughed at.

I didn't laugh at this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only person who thought it wasn't very good?

It wasn't bad by the stretch of the imagination. Just really lacklustre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I know where this gif is from.

Fucking thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a dude?

Trying to figure out the "Mannister" part. 

If that's a dude, it's ok.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is more scientifically advanced, weaponizing anti-matter or GRB's? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I think it's the executioner accusing me, I fight like hell to stay alive

If it's not the executioner, I fight, but not too hard. Sometimes dying can make your town smarten up and go after the accuser who usually turns out to be an overzealous mafia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I see this guy I keep thinking of the House MD episodes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crown gems are for crown crate items. 

Go to the crown crate tab.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you're the retard here. 

Only a retard would defend the telecoms in Canada. They are referenced as a cartel for a reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Than your job.

But I wonder if the surgeons in your hospital would state that their job isn't as taxing as a homemaker?

Like I said, it's all relative, there are many jobs down the list that are easier than being a home maker. There are also a lot of jobs that are harder. 

It's just weird how we praise home makers here unequivocally, when we have guys and women in dangerous mines every day risking their lives. 

Every body has a role to play in society. A job doesn't have to be difficult to be praised. It's just ridiculous when we put certain jobs on pedestals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At a subsidized cost?

You mean quid pro quo?

They aren't subsidizing it for free. They are getting 2 years worth of patronage from each customer. The fact that you think they are just subsidizing the phone for no reason is ridiculous. 

You subscribe to them as a customer for two years. They subsidize the phone, which in reality is a drop in the bucket compared to the profit they make off you as a customer. 

At the end of the contract, they unlock the phone for you as your relationship as customer and company ends on the terms set out. 

You really are a company man. Good job being a schill. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: never mind. You're the original commenter I responded to. I don't read Reddit names often.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that Daggerfall blue?

Are you Daggerfall?

Just asking so I know whether to praise you, or loathe you. 

Good day, sir.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're either a troll or retarded. 

If I pay out my contract over the two years, then the phone company should be obligated by law to unlock my device. The device belongs to me by that point. 

The unlocking fee is just another iteration of the Service Maintenance Fee back in the 90s. Where the telecoms are putting the bottom line above the consideration of their customers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is relative to whatever job you're doing though. 

I'm sure being a homemaker is significantly less taxing than being a:

Blue chip lawyer
Surgeon
Regional Manager with hundreds of subordinates relying on you.
Rocket Scientist
Air traffic control 


Bill Burr kind of nails it here:

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=QoJrMaFlxOk

My Aunt was a homemaker. Her job was important, and it was dependant on being responsible, but to equate my Uncles breadwinner responsibility, as less than is incorrect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is seriously intense shit. 

Professional musicians are like surgeons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luck involved too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is sad, but true. 

They should be obligated to represent the best interests of the citizenry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Really good beginner guns? Ones to avoid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in beginner being easy to handle and maintain. 

A gun you can recommend to someone knowing they won't be disappointed or turned off from being a gun owner. 

Which ones would you recommend staying away from. As in people recommend for beginners but in your experiences there are significantly better options. 

Thanks in advance for any input.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you nail that parry and can start punishing like a relentless animal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 08:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God man. Gino was a titan back in the day. I can't believe he was/is in a wheelchair. 

Time really fucks up good things and people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never really cared about players being traded. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until Burrows.

I have an authentic $400+ Burrows Jersey, I bought the same year they made that Stanley Cup run. (Sometime in January). Have never bought another Canucks jersey prior to this. You see a lot of Henrik and Luongo Jersey's, not a lot of Burrows.

Have always loved guys who played with heart, which he was the epitome of.

At least the Sens are benefiting from him.

It's weird rooting for a team when they trade your favourite player. I was born and raised in Burnaby, always loved the Canucks.

Feels weird man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the Shaw version of the DCX3200M support HDMI CEC / Anynet+? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't connect it to my Samsung's anynet+.

Wondering if anyone knows if they are compatible.

My TV Model is UN55J6300AF

My Cable box is: DXC3200M </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 00:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So did they get "actionable intelligence", or no significant intelligence?

I can't tell with the mixed messages.

What the fuck is going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was the Messier Era for the Canucks really as bad as fans and journalists let on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read a couple of articles lately that are comparing our current Canucks to the 90's "dark era" Canucks.

I don't remember the Messier era being as bad as fans and journalists let on.

What do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is this game? When everyone was playing CS 1.6, I was playing Rogue Spear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 12:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering if this has any of the charm that the original Rainbow Six's had.

I read in other forums that this game has a lack of a community, and the numbers are dwindling. Is this true? 

I would probably buy the game on PC or PS4. Which one has a better population? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 12:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much this.

I used to peruse their subreddit, then you realize they are all nuts.

It's one thing to win the election, it's another to be a train wreck right out of the gate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this mean we're fucked?

Why won't the republicans acknowledge this crazy shit?

I don't know a lot about climate change, but watching all that ice wither away is really making me wonder if we're fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a sad case all around.

Her other kids lose their parents for the rest of their lives, no matter how crazy they are.

And this kid needlessly lost his life.

While I agree with religious freedom, I think we really need to start taking an interest in whatever these pastors are advocating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are fighter jets really this fast? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
