<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6945</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not gonna lie, I think glove skins are silly, but I don't see the problem with cosmetic micro transactions. You don't have to buy them, and you can get some for free just by playing. So. What exactly is everyones problem with it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who are the 14 that you have ahead of Nuk then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'd take me quite a bit, but alright. 

Where can I find those? On the Steam page right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting back into CSGO after not having played since April 2015, did I miss anything important? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the title says. I stopped playing after college but I'm getting back into it with some of my old buddies. 
Is there anything I should know about regarding the meta/gun recoil updates etc? 
Or will I be okay just jumping back in? 

Also, my old rank was Gold Nova Master, I just one my first MM gam again, I went 18-5 and we won but it made me a Silver 1, is that normal? Did they tweak the ranks or something?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 18:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *ROWS THE BOAT AGGRESIVELY*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm honestly more worried about you guys than any other team in the NFC. 

Stafford looks unstoppable and he could probably have his way with our Defense. 

I'm wicked happy the lions are doing great this year. 

See you in a few weeks 

FTP  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 22:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh. I feel like adjustments should've been made to deal with Barrett's scrambles and they should've totally tackled Samuels during that run on 3rd down instead of letting him backtrack, run right, run left, re-tie his shoelaces and then make it within a yard of the marker. 

I'm not gonna blame the refs. OSU outplayed us when it mattered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Offense: 

Body like Cam. 

Brain like Peyton Manning. 

Moves like Sweetness. 

Arm like Dan Marino. 

Hands like Cris Carter. 

Runs routes like Jerry Rice. 

Blocks like Larry Allen. 

As athletic as Bo Jackson. 

As noninjury prone as Eli. 

Defense:

Brain of Ray Lewis

Ballhawking like Ed Reed. 

Hits like John Lynch. 

Coverage like Champ Bailey. 

Run defense like Mean Joe Greene. 

Pass rush like Lawrence Taylor. 

Other: 

As likeable as Larry Fitz. 

Game. Set. Match. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 06:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna have to go with The Hills Have Eyes. 

I've seen that movie dozens of times and it still gives me the creeps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 06:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark Side was the first one I ever listened to, but Meddle was the first one I ever listened to on vinyl and was the only vinyl I had for a while. 

Meddle is probably my favorite album, Echoes is in my opinion the most beautiful song they've ever written, and listenenig to Meddle (and echoes) just brings back so many amazing memories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 19:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never thought of it that way. That's a good point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 19:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't have to be rude about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 19:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe everyone has a right to an opinion...but in what ways is Gates better than Gonzo?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 17:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's okay! If you don't mind me asking, who is your number 2 behind Gonzalez?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 17:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sports games like Madden or 2K. 

Games like Skyrim and Fallout are good for this as well. 

Somebody else already said it but RPGs like Diablo or Path of Exile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 02:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh it depends on what you look for in a TE. 

If you want a great all around TE that can block AND catch you'll want Witten. 

If you want a great receiving TE whose only flaw is his blocking you'll want Tony G. 

To each their own, I think Tony G is one of the greatest TEs ever, but I don't think he's head and shoulders above Witten. It's a lot closer than people think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 02:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking hate Jacob Tamme.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 01:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgive my ignorance, but what is the "Henry Effect?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 08:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No desire to move. I love the cold, if anything I'd move more north. 

For reference I live in Syracuse. We got around a foot of snow in just the past couple days. It's marvelous. :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 07:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not an asshole at all. We're 9-1 baby!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 06:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just stop debating it with Non Dallas fans. 

If the Dallas Oline was the only reason Zeke is averaging 5 YPC then why isn't Morris productive? Obviously the Oline helps a ton but Zeke is the god damn man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 06:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a Tyron Smith color rush jersey the week before the Browns game. 

Honestly they're fuckin sexy. I'm surprised. Hopefully next year our color rush is Blue considering the fact they're called, ya know, color rush.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 06:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm eating crow still. But it's worth it. 

It was the way someone on Reddit described it, Ramsey (Ramsay?) wouldn't have made our defense elite, but Zeke makes our offense elite. 

Plus Anthony Brown is playing great so I guess we got our CB anyway. 

Also, fuck the 9ers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 22:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. So let's keep out Larry Fitz, LdT, Moss, TO, Tony G, Urlacher, and take out Marino and Seau cause none of them won one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which audio log? I beat the game yesterday and can't remember what one you're talking about. I must've missed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 04:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's dangerous about this? I'm worried because I've done this before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. 

I'm also thankful that there's no audio as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite was 2011, the one with Tebow on the cover. 

I also had 2006, probably my second favorite one. 

I remember making a two way Safety/Quarterback for Boise State. 

Oh the memories. 

The soundtrack for '06 was great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What am I looking at here? Is this a video summary of Michigan States season?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 03:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SEC bias. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 00:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DEFINITEY GO

Probably one of the better spots in the city IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately Davis played in the era of Tony G, Gates, Witten and Gronk, four TEs that are indisputably top ten arguably top five at their position all time. Maybe if Davis kept up his doninance a little longer or played in a different era he'd be in. 

Gore probably could eventually, but he also played in an era that included LdT, AP and Faulk (iirc, not sure when Faulk retired). 

I'd say Gore has a better chance than Davis. To a lot of people Davis seemed like a Flash in the Pan so to speak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 07:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to try it out anyway. 

I'm one of the only people in my friend circle that bothered playing any of the Deadrising games past 2 and to be honest I like them all in their own way. 

1 is a classic imho. 

Chop Till You Drop was interesting to say the least. Probably the weakest one in the series, but still fun nonetheless. 

2 and Off the Record had the weapon crafting and coop. 

I really liked 3 due to the map and I have it on PC so the amount of bloodshed I could have at once was a treat. I would agree with other commentors that the weapon combos got a bit crazy in this one. 

I never really played coop, I mostly use video games as a way to escape everything and everybody, so this isn't a big issue for me. 

However. 

I'm hearing all of these things about Frank West being different and I hope it's not true. A comment or on this post said,"So it's just another guy named Frank?" And if that's the case I'm going to be disappointed. 

The whole point of Capcom adding Frank back to the mix was to appeal to fans of the first that missed his awkward black humor and little catchphrases. 

Too much of a good thing is a bad thing, and if this game flops it'll just prove that Capcom should've left it alone. 

I'm still going to wait for some reviews and Let's Plays before I decide to spend money on this iteration. I'm hoping it turns out well, but every article I read paints it in a darker light.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping that it's not too late to ask this. 

I'm loving the game so far. I just arrived to Addermire, about 2 hours in. 

My only annoyance however is starting to really frustrate me:

Is there s way to turn off the notification that says "A bone charm is nearby, equip the heart." ? 

I have the heart equipped almost a third of the time and whenever I put it away it pops up with that annoying little message EVERY DAMN TIME  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The refs didn't give us that game. You aren't going to win a playoff game giving the ball away twice and only scoring 3 points in the second half.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. We beat the lions because they only scored three points in the second half and Lawrence sacked Stafford on back to back plays to force a fumble to end it. 

You aren't going to win a football game by only scoring three points in the second half. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally think it's because your Dline stepped up yesterday. They looked really good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. That's why I root for you guys a lot. There's a lot of players that I wanted Dallas to grab that they passed on. 

Granted Hali was mostly in hindsight because Spencer was pretty good for a while but injuries did him in. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see:

BIGGEST ONE: Randy Moss over Greg Ellis 

Hali or MJD over Bobby "Fucking" Carpenter

Weddle over Anthony Spencer

Chris Johnson or Jamaal Charles over Felix Jones

Brandon Flowers or Jordy Nelson over Mike Jenkins

Mike Wallace over Jason Williams

Kam Chancellor over Akwemi Owosu Ansah

Justin Houston over Victor Butler

Travis Kelce or Leveon Bell over Gavin Escobar

That's it so far. I might add more after work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. The 90's dynasty would be a completely different team. Safe to say no Triplets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 00:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad he's balling out for you guys. I always liked Newman. 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 06:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how I worded it at first, but like you said he'd be extremely OP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 06:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you actually! I was about to ask that next. 

I could be wrong, but I think his play would be more accepted if he played the 3. The rebounding would seem to low for a guy playing the 4 or 5, and the points and assists would be low for a guy playing the 1 or 2. 

I'd like to see other people's opinions on this too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 06:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm thinking as well. 

I'd chime in but I really don't know too much about the NBA. I mostly play 2K and watch whatever game is on. 

This might actually be the first time I've ever posted here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How valuable would a player that averaged a 5x5 be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 06:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title explains, if I have to add more due to rules I will, but I'm genuinely curious. 

Mind you, he would still only average 5 points, but he's even more valuable when you factor in the fact that he would also be getting 5 assists, rebounds, blocks and steals a game. 

Would he be the ultimate role player?

Would he make any team he was on objectively better? 

What sort of contract would he be offered? 

I'd like to see what you guys think!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No sir, fuck the Eagles! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. We could easily rotate our QBs each quarter. 

"Defenses hate him!"

In all seriousness though Kirk is definitely slept on. He's making me eat crow this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 00:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What NFL teams have the least amount of following in their local areas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 21:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if the title is /r/titlegore material but Ill explain further here. 

Basically, what NFL teams are out on the backburner for other franchises or teams in their area. 

My uncle lives in Atlanta and says that nobody really pays attention to the Falcons and it's more of a UGA or GT fandom with the NFL fans supporting whatever team they rooted for before moving to Atlanta (considering a lot of people there are transplants). 

Are there any other teams like that?

Are the Titans overshadowed by the Volunteers?

Do the Wild and Vikings have to compete for ratings? 

What about the Lions and the Wolverines/Red Wings? 

Maybe even the Saints and LSU? 

I would also assume that there are fans in Texas that favor the Longhorns or even high school football over the Cowboys. 

This isn't meant to sound pretentious or anything, I'm genuinely curious. As someone that is a Cowboys fan first and an NFL fan second it's weird to me to think about other sports overtaking my Cowboys fandom. 

Thanks in advance and I hope for a good discussion!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to try that out then. Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on PC. I'll have to download that when I get out of work. Would you happen to have a link?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberation of Skyrim quest broken. Any known fixes? I've tried everything. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 19:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all! I've been playing Skyrim: SE for PC and have had absolutely zero problems until the past few days.

You see, I started the Civil War quest by joining the Stormcloaks. Survived the Ice Wraith, Completed the Jagged Crown, and liberated Whiterun. Jarl Baalgruff (sp?) is not longer the Jarl so on and so forth. 

The next objective I had was to report to Ulfric, and there is NOTHING THAT INITIATES THE NEXT QUEST! I've tried every single dialogue option, I've tried waiting, I've tried only talking to him when he's sitting in the throne, I've tried using console commands to advance the quest, I've tried using console commands to reset the quest, I've even tried traveling to the next area with hope that Galmar would be there ready to initiate the quest, but to no avail there is nothing that seems to fix it.

Am I completely boned? Because if so I'm pretty pissed off. 

Even with its repetitiveness and faults, the Civil War questline is one of my favorites in the entire game. I love raiding the forts, I love saving the prisoners, I love the espionage, everything about the civil war quest line is worth me trying endlessly to get it to work.

The only thing left for me to do is to reload a previous save, and I am NOT about to do that. I did the first few quests for the Thieves Guild, Dark Brotherhood and did the quests for Clavicus Vile, Molag Bol, Hircine, found Meridias Beacon and finished the Forsworn Conspiracy before starting the Civil War quest, I'm not about to do all of those quests again just to do the civil war (no matter how much I love it).

If you ask me, this is a bit ridiculous. You'd think that since they remastered the game they'd at least try and fix a few of the bugs that were prevalent in the original release. 

Anyway I digress, is there anything else I can do? Or do I HAVE to restart from a previous save? Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 06:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. I run 1080 60 on my PC, but not all of my games run on high but they run great and that's enough. 

I have my console for sports games and exclusives like Last of Us and Ratchet and Clank. Use my PC for everything else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 19:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I'm in Dallas right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 19:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else at the game? 

I'm Section 108. This stadium is amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 14:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd pay more than $50 but they need some money for the players. /s  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 05:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 05:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the uneducated. What's a perfect day exactly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 22:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A picture of Mark Sanchez in a Dallas jersey simply because it still surprises me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 22:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liked - Witten, Zeke. 

Disliked - McClain, TWill. 

Honestly not too positive on dislikes. I know if it was 2015 the answer would be Hardy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should have mentioned that! We are looking for an American type restaurant. Burgers, ribs, stuff like that. 

Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 05:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys fan coming to Cleveland for the weekend! Have a few questions about your city. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 04:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if this is the right place to post this. But tomorrow my father and I are driving to Cleveland to catch the game this Sunday. 

I was wondering what sort of things are fun to do around the city? Our plan is to go to the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and then go out to dinner someplace. Do you guys have any advice or personal preferences? 

Thanks in advance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 06:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the Cubs now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 05:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have work in 5 hours.

I'm not even even Cubs fan. 

I'm bawling my eyes out. 

This is amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm giggling right now because I'm imagining that Gronk parties post game with his helmet still on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 07:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's asinine that even though the police or legal system or whatever already said there's not enough evidence to make a case the NFL is still pushing the matter further. 

Fucking ridiculous. 

An employer is not above the law, no matter how big they are. 

Fuck the Shield. 

*sigh* 

Can't wait for next weeks game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 04:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either Childrend or the Mace of Molag Bal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 19:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say that as if every promising player gets better no matter what. 

By the way Ron Dayne says hi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 01:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wear cowboys stuff out in public without being called a faggot or a band wagoner or belittled etc etc. 

I'm not allowed to have a positive opinion about my team without being called stupid. 

Literally everything positive that ever comes out of a cowboys fans mouth (whether on r/NFL or in real life) gets shut down. 

I've gone out to bars and talked football with people and once they find out I'm a Dallas fan they start shit talking and the conversation starts going nowhere. 

Plus Skip Bayless is a Dallas "fan." Thats honestly the worst part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 06:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a $200 buy in for the league. 

I may or may not take it too seriously. 

I may or may not have a drinking problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 06:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I shouldn't have started Charles in my flex. literally any other flex player and I would have won. ](https://imgur.com/gallery/Wg9Uv) 

But that's the way the game goes I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 05:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tied my game. 

Tied. 

If DT didn't have that drop on third down it would've been in the bag. 

The worst part? 

It counts as a loss for me. I'm not sure why. But I'm livid right now. 

I tied and Jamaal Charles gave me 0 points. 

I could have played Stefon Diggs instead and I would've won.

I could've played Coby Fleener instead and I would've won.

The bright side is im still in second place in the league, but the guy I tied with is the Ruxin of my league, dead wife and all, minus the success in fantasy football. I cannot stand him. 

Fuck you Mark. Fuck you Elizabeth. I'm going to fuck your husband in the playoffs so hard you're going to roll over in your grave because even though you had juicy tits and a fat ass he's never going to be as satisfied as he will be with me. 

Now if you'll excuse me I'm going to drink my own weight in gin and tonics and ask my girlfriend to see if she can put on a Packers jersey for me and let me pound her ass while I shave her bald and call her Marky.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 10:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have clinical depression. Survived my suicide attempt on October 17 2015. 

I talk about my feelings all the time. It makes it easier to deal with them. It makes me feel normal if I am able talk to people about it. 

I used to bottle them up, and drink a lot, and do pills a lot. But now I'll hang out with my friends and they'll always make sure I'm doing okay. 

I don't like the double standard with men's emotions. The amount of times I was ignored is disgusting. The amount of times I was told to "man up" is disgusting. I cut out a lot of people because they had attitudes like that and my life has steadily improved since. 

The idea that men need to be stoic because they're men is ignorant. 

Nobody should be afraid to ask for help. 
I shouldn't have been afraid to ask for help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 20:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 20:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have a video of that no call PI that I see everyone talking about?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. I love Romo. But watching Dak play the past few weeks has been something special. I haven't been this excited to watch the team in years. This team has me happier than 2014. 

Keep Dak in. I love you Tony. But I'm a Cowboys fan, not a Romo fan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 04:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Why is your wife's alcoholism a running joke?!"

I just spit milk out my nose and I wasn't even drinking milk. Fuck Fuccilo. Fuck FSU. GO GATORS!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 04:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think our offense is set. I'd personally want Keuchly, Watt or Von Miller. 

As someone that loves watching our offense flourish I'd love to have a guy like AB or Julio or OBJ across from Dez.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 02:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Escobar is a blocking TE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2007 Cowboys vs Bills is the first one that comes to mind. Not sure of any others. 

EDIT: Duh. Seattle vs Green Bay in 2014. Idk how I forgot that one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 18:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a nightmare that my girlfriend was at a party with me and started blowing my best friend right in front of everybody. 

So that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 21:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to sound heretic but I'll bust out my old McNabb jersey to come down to that bar. Sounds perfect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 00:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao I can't wait to see how I react then. Thank you :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 00:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 00:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going to be trying LSD for the first time tonight, just had a few questions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone! I'm going to be trying LSD tonight. I have a few questions. 

1) Will I have a problem going to work tomorrow night if I trip tonight? 

1b) is there a hangover or afterglow that I should be worried about? 

2) anything I should have out ahead of time? Such as water or snacks? 

3) will video games be out of the question? Will I be too far gone to play something like Rocket League or Madden? 

4) I'm experienced in dissociatives and psilocybin, in what ways is LSD similar to those? 

5) what are the "unwritten rules" of LSD? Things to look out for that a new comer wouldn't exactly be familiar with. 

6) how do I take it? Do I eat it or put it on my tongue and let it dissolve? I have no idea. 

Thanks in advance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 22:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh so since he isn't an Emmy award winning writer he can't criticize South Park? 

Ignorant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 07:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That feeling when you started David Johnson and Larry Fitzgerald. 

Up 50.6 to 0. 

:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 11:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's probably drunk in a pond somewhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 Man. Standard Scoring. Keeper league. 

QB - Brees

HB - David Johnson, Jeremy Hill

WR - OBJ, Demaryious Thomas, Stefon Diggs

TE - Martellus Bennett

K - Justin Tucker

D/ST - Bengals

Bench - Bortles, Dak, Tannehill, Jamaal Charles, Larry Fitz, Maclin, Kevin White, Coby Fleener. 

Bonus points if you can guess who I kept.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 15:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just woke up. Basking in afterblow right now. Feeling great. 

I ended up walking down the street to my buddy's house and smoked a bong and took a shot of whiskey and went back home. Lmao.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 08:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> definitely worth it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 07:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hulu is worth it just for South Park and adult swim shows honestly. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 07:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same here.

south park just has better characters. and there really isn't a single bad episode that i can think of off the tpp of my head. ,aybe. idk  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 07:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. It's 1:11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 07:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What time is it where you're at?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 07:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 07:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's still funny but family guy isn't a show that I've seen as a satire. I liked it more when it was just mindless fun, but it seems like the creators are trying to attach a message to every episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 07:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually not that bad. 

I mostly watch it because it brings me back to my childhood. I remember watching family guy as a kid and seeing it now is astounding. I try to cling to things from my childhood. I like the comedic style personally. And some of the jokes in the newest season are actually pretty dark. 

I still much prefer South Park. 

How like have a been typing? 

Idk. 

I feeel like family guy is trying to go more against the grain. But they aren't doing it right. 

They don't have the characters for it in my opinion. 

It's kind of disappointing. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
