<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5027</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait for reply, "a normal Saturday"
Circle jerk comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's a bad Saturday for reposts here on r/gaming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoever this Kellie fella is he's gonna have to try harder to get out of the 1920s cause that reads like a joke with no punchline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, you wrong.
She's blatantly taking on the ownership of wrong doing in that language used.  
While you reading into his "problems" that aren't mentioned at all might help your argument... You just made that up to have a way this could be blaming the partner. Toaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it turned out the zebra did it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The leaf?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very in!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awcktualllyyy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 best performance by a hand with paper this year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bitch I'm fucking broke!!
Bitch I live a fucking trash can!!
I'm the poorest mother fucker on Sesame Street!
Ain't nobody trying to help me!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *is* awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Business will dictate. I was just chatting with my EB Games here in Canada, that's our GameStop, and they're making whatever room they can but this particular store was going to remove 75% of the shelf space dedicated to Wii games to make room for incoming full switch displays. They'll still have stock and you'll be able to get games there for some time it would seem. But. It has begun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The videogames section of the Flyers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good get man! Happy for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to agree with the the Redditors here. I love this chef, one of my favorite, one of the few that continues to inspire me. 

There are many chefs who have a healthy trajectory in our industry, starting out low paid unskilled workers and ending with decent wages and impressive resumes. They maintain high standards and are willing to move to keep moving up the ladder and maintaining an increasing wage lifestyle. They save and invest properly and continue to work for great chefs who understand how to manage successful kitchens. 

Unfortunately these are the smallest percentage of chefs and the vast majority get stuck in disfunctional kitchens with ill equipped owners and often under skilled chefs.  There is a shortage of line cooks because it's physically and mentally demanding labor that pays the same as low effort employment like retail or any entry level service job.  More often than not passion is crushed under an imbalance of expectations against reward.  

The industry is creating it's own problems and those towards the top often forget why.  I support programs like these or even the cunt Jamie Oliver when he helps out recently free paroled criminals.  There is a heart to some chefs bigger than the normal people could imagine...

But ultimately as consumers demand competitive prices while multinationals stuff gym mats into grinders to create a cheaper burger, there just isn't going to be enough money in this business to lure in the top budding minds when confronted with the weight of working expectation.  Many of us recognise it and choose to put our no nonsense direct, aggressive personalities into other ventures instead.

My first chef, very successful, top of my country at the time, numerous restaurants, retired at a decent age, told me simply..

"Do you wish to make money in your life?"

"Yes chef of course," I responded.

"Then get out of the kitchen and do something else"

*Edit - spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vatican  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your existence is superfluous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, I did the same just recently and so so worth it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Still the best "Continue / Quit" screen [Max Payne 2] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're ten pounds of shit in a five pound bag kid.  And everybody seems to recognise it, which is enjoyable to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little alloy! Xpost from r/horizon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking yikes indeed :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not so closely no! I'm a fallout guy through and through, although I do support anyone who works and puts efforts in to help fans realise new gameplay glory!! So they definitely deserve a cheers too I'm sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show support or move on. Nobody in this thread is interested in you're "never be finished" attitude. And please stop PM'ing me pictures of your anal fissures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha good man!! Cheers to you again. Any idea what you'll be tackling next? I'm so excited it's not even healthy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'd have to agree. The Redditor is trying to claim a conspiracy about hiding Netflix originals when he presents an elegant argument for why the system needed to be changed.  Beautiful work with the quotes, I really think they're fairly intelligent for acknowledging that people act as critics instead of just acknowledging enjoyment.

I'd like to point out that I don't love the new system, and that since its inception Netflix has been making strides to accommodate the lowest common denominator toaster, but let's take a moment to realize that yes; most people are idiots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cliff rash look who's taking a bath  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smash one. Fuck these people, office space this shit. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just tip another one over and smash a component have a serious chat about how they're throwing money away and inviting a lawsuit because Lord knows it might just come down on someone next time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is OP a fag? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory "I put my cocaine in these" comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man thanks for the heads up, as soon as I'm off work I'll look into making a new thread for bug reporting! If any mods see this and can just unlock the previous one that would be fly as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. Lot of infighting here in the comments but I'd like to bring us back to the point.  This is yet another hike in our already expensive cellular plans, and nobody is coming to help us.

I've emailed the CCTS, TheCommissioner for Complaints for Telecommunications Services, and my email will be copied into this comment, feel free to bombard them with a copied version of the email. 

But I'd also like to help, suggest anything that can help and let's try to organise for this. Black out date. Mass migration to another company. What do you think would be the best most practical way to proceed and grab the largest number of people.

My email to the CCTS, feel free to use or alter however you want. Please help however you can........

*
I'm emailing today in regards to the increase in rates I've been told about by Bell Mobility.


To my understanding every major provider will be adding approximately ten dollars to their services, excluding koodo.


I am not one to email my outrage to consumer protective organizations as I tend to believe that others, more easily prone to outrage, will be first in line. However I must express my disgust with Canadian mobile service providers and as well those charged with protecting consumer rights, such as yourself.


It's recently been publicised, and numerous times before, that we have some of the highest cell phone rates in the world. Here is a recent article for your validation:


http://www.cbc.ca/beta/news/business/crtc-phone-study-1.3717093


With this in mind it is absolutely egregious that these companies have unilaterally moved forward with yet another rate hike, blatantly disregarding the consumer and laughing at the impotence of organizations such as the one you work for. While some of us may not struggle with rate increases, others have come to very much struggle with paying for what is now considered essential technology for the job market.


I will be encouraging others to write you as well as putting forward options to find a solution to show our disgust in a proper way, as you have failed us yet again.


Sincerely

*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In light of top comment I'd like to give a shout out to everyone helping this along too. You are all hard on worthy Titans!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll buy it off you for ten bucks if you actually hate it fucktard toaster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out, but also go fuck yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude I haven't been to the dentist in like ten years. Is this what they're like now? Sign me up doc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a little heart breaking. Like. A tiny heart breaks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Negative. Our friend OP and his crew has been working tirelessly on this FO3 re-engine and his posts and updates are always so damned welcome!!!
Edit - OP is not alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude as always I'm so impressed with the work you are doing. You are right now, no word of a lie, the project I'm most excited about and most looking forward to. Thank you again so much for this passion protect. Please keep up the good battle!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's such a shame. It looks like they had a major change in staff and no one got the memo on not fucking the dog.
Shame I say. Shame! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dip your head under and.. Nope... Nope nope nope </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could of've or could veof but never call me Shirley </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha yes. Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah just down vote and move on. These posts are just fucking brutal at this point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You both seem like assholes to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. It's pretty alright.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just the uninitiated, it's kind of a shit post without simple context. Just left to guess what he's grinding or circling for.... You suck OP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xpost from dank memes. Thought y'all would get it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valid point bro. Hit up the steam forum, the devs are fucking great for this game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They listen and surprise you. Come home and suddenly there's your favorite chocolate bar, or a PlayStation game you wanted or something. Ring it. Toaster out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey no one said you didn't suck, settle down OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never been more proud to be a Newfoundlander </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at the gams on that dame. Wowee that'll make the minister shave the nickel with a hoolahoop and ya can read about *that* in the gazette tomorrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to sound foolish at first glance but it's tried tested and true for thousands of years.

Water.

Drink plenty of it and you'll need to piss in the early hours. Famous from the Simpsons reference it's actually been used for ages to wake at early/irregular hours by many societies and remains ultra effective to this day. Truly I have not used an alarm in... Jesus I can't even tell you when.  Whether it's early rise, or overnight flight, just clear your system and down some real water levels before your system goes into stasis.

For most of us it's very difficult to deny this urge and it will force you to get up and out of bed. And most importantly, at that point just *stay up*. 
 
If you're having this much difficulty with alarms it's possible there's more at work on your head, including an abject rejection of the day or situation to come. But skipping all the potential issues at play I would suggest you go for the oldest alarm clock in the book and chug several tall glasses of water just as you're about to sleep.  

You'll know your body and your bladder so make sure to drink enough... But good luck with it all and try not to smash any phones! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's implying for planned outages or inclement weather, more so than being an illiterate dickhead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only everyone just posted trash and basically told us they didn't give a fuck about content we'd know who to hate a lot easier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you sleep at night.

This is the evil of marketing incarnate. You sound like you should blow your house with kitten souls you monster.

I'm sure you're alright but keep that evil deep inside yo, they don't need any extra help screwing us over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a major foodie are ya. 
God you sound like you're fun at parties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck I thought for sure this was going to securely lodge behind him and crack his drunken neck like a twig. *Shudder* 
Cross post this shit to r/nononoyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why we lock our door in white neighborhoods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her name. Is Roberta Paulson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's the comment I was looking for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahah.
Nice. Nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I support atheism I find this argument less than compelling. It's like saying that because doctors commit a fuck ton of murders we shouldn't have healthcare or medicine.

http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/j.1556-4029.2006.00273.x/abstract

I understand the relationship between a religious indoctrination and the psychological issues that arise, which I assume is the point of this "numbers post", but by leaning on statistics, particularly a one month sample, we weaken legitimacy to our arguments. 

For instance we could look at this and say, more people died falling out of bed than clergymen were arrested this month for *all charges*... This doesn't even include bed related injuries.  Making the real demon bed manufactures. We must therefore remove beds from our society.

Clearly beds are ok. At least for me. But by reducing our religious arguments to statistics and number games, rather than the the elements which drive them, we do our cause no favors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though it's pretty much how this subreddit works haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roger that, consider it removed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ambulance of freedom! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This sign near a rural airport </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Sunday gang! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bless the rains down in Africaaaaaa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to talk about three-ply, was not disappointed. Toaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point, let's talk about the fallout that don't exist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes agreed, best actual use of Photoshop, have an updoot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on that was funny! Dang.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is blatant sarcasm meant to help end a super repetitive theme on this subreddit. I believe everyone else seems to understand this from the comments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for that. It's no hate intended, I get being proud of a new purchase, but come on now... let's make some room for repeating and abusing the next big thing on r/gaming... Presumably nier automata ass memes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you kind dude, and to you as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Really getting a tad repetitive at this point </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow fuck you buddy, why would someone try to help an attitude like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new controller, would it charge when plugged into the Ps4 directly, on original purchase </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait until the industry eats her aliiiive. I'll buy her half lifeless body for half a schilling and use it to clean my toilet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he did get one thing right. Fuck cazadors, them shits are assholes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got a great project going man. Maybe take a break and upload an album of screenshots for us!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have to agree with this. The expectation is that with the current market climate there will be further increases in unemployment and decreases in the housing market. It's not getting better anytime soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah don't live downtown if this is the kind of question on your mind. And you will *not* be getting parking for two cars downtown </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. It's really out of hand lately. It's like OP doesn't know what accidental means. Considering what their mother says about em, you'd think they'd understand what a fucking accident was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 07:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why we want to be saving people again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause your moms would beat your ass awake son </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha best "screech in" in town is upstairs at Christians. Drinking age only though!
The guy running it is fucking phenomenal at it. Twenty bucks a head, get to eat some authentic Newfie steak, get a shot of screech, learn some facts, stomp out a song, and get official Newfoundlander certificates at the end. Plus Christians is just a great bar to hit, free cover, long term friendly staff. Again call ahead but they do several screech ins a day, the evening one is at 11pm ish. Gotta arrive ahead of time to sign up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem! The guy who opened it is super cool really happy for him. Just be sure to call ahead they can get booked up especially on a weekend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an axe throwing place downtown. Jack axes. Fun and safe but they serve alcohol so call ahead to see if it's classified as a bar, I really don't think it is and it's a great time so am absolute must.

The rooms is our museum of sorts, and while not for everyone it's architecture makes it fun to explore and red oak have a restaurant up top floor, can't remember it's name but they're all great and the view is fucking amazing.

And always happening you can grab some small plates and enjoy some Jazz at the fifth ticket downtown.

Signal Hill is a classic and amazing spot, the wind is high and it gets cold as you can imagine. But looking back at the city in night or out into the ocean can be captivating.

Other than that take a stroll downtown and enjoy. Best restaurant in Canada is here, Raymond's, but the owners have opened a second place called merchants tavern which is a bit more accessible to the general population and has all kinds of nautical theme and a gorgeous open kitchen too watch the boys work.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three Ply toilet paper.
I don't give a fuck what the plebs say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 11:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it just amazing! The atmosphere alone. I was hooked at first sight and so pumped every step of the way. Just fucking stellar. I think I'm gonna fire it up again right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Veronica Vaughn is one piece of ace, I know from experience dude. If you know what I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this struggle. My Little jerk likes to watch with disdain before she sits on my lap and tries to claim my arms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. It's the missles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That unicorn is an English pro and you know it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I had to put it up. I was just shocked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Circling vesperpool area you'll run into three or four cockatrice. 
Warp strike their heads specifically and frantically to get cockatrice crests.
You'll get up to four around vesperpool. 
The respawn is pretty quick, they don't seem to be out during the night though. 
The crest will get you expericast lvl. 2. 
Also a number of quests lead here so it's nice to have them open to have something to kill the nights with, but whatever works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I discovered, with savage fucking fish, Holy shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starches behavior for potato's can be brutal. I'm not the best prepper I'm here trying to get my life in better order but I am available professional chef. You have to be sure to boil potato's from a cold water... If you drop them into a boiling pot you will shock the starches and it will be an awful reheat. Other than that it may be the microwave reheat as another redditor suggested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fallout fans are all losers... Ha ha
Now that should be unpopular.
Also to note. They are not losers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You talked to them, you didn't suck their dick and pledge allegiance. Surely you must see what he's saying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now they will dip their hands in Maple syrup.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now is "our" chance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The side quest comes up when I complete the dungeon and then camp there.. two times now it's happened. But the chocobo seems completely unrelated. I really think square Enix has just shit the bed on this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah totally didn't. Not much for racing side games ever. Clearly missed the boat ... Chocoboat..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just assumed!! Talk about blinding awesomeness, when the little guy just kept going into the water I'm pretty sure I cried tears of joy a little. Best mistake I've made yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 90hrs in... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 05:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I just discovered chocobo can swim... I'm a fucking idiot. I've been circling vesperpool to collect cockatrice crests... And I just learned they can swim... I'm... I'm an idiot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like freedom fries. And murca murca murca. Poor things, can't handle a little culture of yogurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Games amazing. Super fun single player. Still in its early stages so there's some glitches and issues, but the devs are working pretty rapid.
Strongly support for the cost, haven't regretted it for a minute since I got in last year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just a little treason! It's still good it's still good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Label as such and I'm sure it'll fly off the shelves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alive and well in Canada anywhere you can find Coca Cola! Had it with McDonald's just last week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
