<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be interested to hear what other strategies are available in these situations. Waiting it out doesn't seem smart... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they were PAID to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever planning a return to the Oryx and Crake universe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... Was he drunk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an endless vein to be mined there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, a little bit. But anyone still supporting Trump is racist, ignorant, insane or all three. And that is worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone still supporting that sack of human garbage is the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More on Maerlyn's Rainbow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rental gear on Bali, had a fluctuating pressure gauge that I should have mentioned on my first dive. On second dive, we stayed down deep for a bit looking for a pygmy seahorse -- which we eventually found, but by the time we were coming back up slowly, and I was at 50 bar I found it incredibly hard to breath. I would get a little bit at first, then the gauge would drop to zero and it was like trying to drink out of a closed straw. One of the guys we dove with the day before reported a similar issue. Couple that with a longer than normal safety stop (+8 minutes ASC warning since we stayed down too long on our second dive after a deep first dive) and I started freaking out a bit and shared air with our guide. Luckily, I didn't just pop up but remained somewhat calm and shared air. Scary experience. 

Lesson learned: Always speak up about any issues with your gear -- especially rental gear, immediately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speak for yourself. I saw it on a huge IMAX screen and thought it was overwhelming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing turtles! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also on the Google Play Store.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Badass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should be counted as casualties of war for surely most of, if not all of them would not have taken their lives had they not been sent to war.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the first letter of each song title ETLITMFISRFKOTWSYML could be read as Trimmest Swiftly Folk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah true. Good luck. But don't not go out to dinners etc. because you honestly never know who you might meet or get along with in this life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FIS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If leaving is your plan do it now. Otherwise you're just wasting your time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on who your coworkers/bosses are! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not required, but if you don't participate this time and if you don't go to events like it in the future, better believe it will 100% impact your career. Often it is these outside the office meetings where the real business happens and if you can't or won't include yourself then you are going to lose out on opportunities and on developing relationships.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweetness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Debt management. It's a huge business. Learning to do it at scale is what matters and we have experience doing that in all kinds of industries, especially after WWII. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any advice for someone thinking about going up a mast for the first time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gave up? My dogs have done 10 mile hikes! And they're city dawgs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lifeless CGI movie has a lifeless CGI looking poster. There is no feeling or story to this poster, just a bunch of set pieces vamping for a camera that they know exists. What a bore. I hope Disney doesn't become the new Paramount.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. Any advice for someone thinking of doing quite a shorter sail for the first time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disagree. It's completely necessary. It's just long and slow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Def read Insomnia first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever get worried up there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always always always double-check your equipment especially if renting. Not to say the gear was faulty here just saying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but not really. The Mr. Mercedes trilogy is pretty amazing stuff. Not like his earlier work but still solid, well-paced and delivers the goods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THX! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I flipped the videos orientation to give a somewhat better view. And think it was very shallow so the red filter didn't reproduce the colors all that well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is this called? Tulamben Bali edition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dove in Tulamben with Matahari Tulamben and on Lembongan with Andy @ Bali Diving Academy. Both were great operations, but Bali Diving Academy was better in my opinion -- Andy has a wealth of knowledge that isn't easily reproduced. 

Using a GoPro 4 -- mostly without lights although I employed my torch in a couple of these videos, which appear to need a more consistent form of light than my erratic flashlight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scuba Cancun is pretty great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet! It's like a sea dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bali Diving 2017 Compilation featuring turtles, white-tipped reef sharks and biodiversity! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing Manta shots! And great nudi stills as well! What kind of camera you using? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet little baby tortuga there! How big was it and were you not breathing at all or did you mute your audio? Amazing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just doesn't know what a trumpet is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A month is great! But you never know what your next dive might have in store for you! We had two weeks and it wasn't enough time! Strong currents and not the best weather being rainy season but it was a blast underwater.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gorgeous coral at Mangrove Point, Nusa Lembongan, Indonesia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We just thought it was a really different, cool looking fish. Then we showed it to a marine biologist DM on Nusa Lembongan who clued us into the identity of this fun little guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got back a few days ago. Thought the Liberty Wreck was a lot of fun as were the Tulamben dives, but we had much better visibility over on Lembongan / Nusa Penida.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Juvenile Emperor Angelfish swimming near Tulamben, Bali </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet video. Nice bull shark encounter. I've only seen reef sharks there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great pic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive coral at Crystal Point, Nusa Penida, Indonesia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valentine's Day is for Hallmark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IDK but my mind is blown pretty much every time I drop down. There's always something new or unique to see -- although I'm not sure that always translates to great videos. Then again, I'm not into underwater filming or photography yet -- I just experience it. My GF does the recording/photography.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like much better visibility on your dive but I was there just a few days ago -- rainy season so we were lucky to have this kind of visibility to be honest. 

And crystal bay was amazing. That massive coral there is just jaw-dropping ... didn't get any video that shows the whole thing but it's amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some things might need to be experienced rather than captured or reproduced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree that the reef is like a life bomb, so many species of fish, coral etc. that it's pretty intense. I saw lots of stuff I've never seen before and can attest that in real life, it's pretty impressive. This video obviously doesn't showcase the entire dive site -- just one cool encounter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great footage of a turtle on drift dive off Nusa Penida in Indonesia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No stupid questions just lots of stupid people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you sound like a prick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No people are making their stand on the I don't want the environment FUCKED for the next generation line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RESIST this shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He might be President, but he is not the choice of the people. The popular vote is completely clear as far as that goes. Clinton destroyed him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least in NYC this was a transformative protest, one without an oppressive police presence. Sure they were there but it was not an adversarial thing, instead it was an expression of inclusion and love for all, including the police.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NYC was huge. Lots of dudes there too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What crimes has he committed in the USA?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's not going to have the same experience most of his pee-ons endure to get ahead in the industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roatan is pretty great and you can fly direct from Houston </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. He has an encounter with Bev, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a fucking terrible idea. Make traveling easier and more convenient. Such BS just to hit a arbitrary bottom line.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
