<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9931</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> with limited exceptions for travel for diplomatic or military purposes in the service of a VWP country

If he visited Iran for diplomatic purposes it was OK

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would some of the biggest companies in the world invest in competition? It's easier for them to wait until someone else figures it out, continue burning that cheap cheap fossil fuel, and buy out the tech later. 

Maybe not in the US, but many fuel companies are invested in biofuels. Most current diesel fuel sold around the world contains 5-10% biodiesel. This is mainly because the production of modern low sulfur fuel damages the lubricity of the fuel, and biodiesel is often the cheapest additive to bring it back up to spec. 

EDIT: However that biofuel is usually from crops or crop waste (canola for diesel and corn/sugar cane/beets for ethanol) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks u/Somnif, this and below is an excellent summary of the general field and the specific issues with algal biofuels.

I have dabbled in algal biofuel research and have a large project looking at biofuel emissions (when used in diesel engines).

Even with the advances in this paper the economics are a long way off. The lowest cost approach I have seen with algae is to use local saline species in open pond systems in areas of the coast which are too arid to support agriculture. 

Even then - fuel is usually the lowest value product you can get algae to grow. There are already large algae farms for pharmaceutical and cosmetic applications.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which side of the wall will trump put the bomb on though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I was elected to lead, not to read" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 15:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12% of Americans have a masters or doctoral degree. 

However 25% of Iranian-Americans do. 

Now obviously Iranians are only one group affected by the executive order, and some of those in the stats above would be citizens. 

Other stats I found - there are over 100k muslim college students in the country, vs ~20k muslim refugees admitted each year on average. 

EDIT, Sources:
http://iipdigital.usembassy.gov/st/english/article/2004/01/20040113191603atarukp0.6147425.html#axzz4XXMyrs6y
http://www.people-press.org/2011/08/30/section-1-a-demographic-portrait-of-muslim-americans/
http://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2016/10/05/u-s-admits-record-number-of-muslim-refugees-in-2016/


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dapper Ducks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what way is America more "anti-science" or "anti-intellectual" than European countries?

There are many examples:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Indiana_Pi_Bill

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scopes_Trial
(how many other lawsuits have been held in the US over teaching (or not teaching) evolution)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But did it look as cute as these little black ducks? http://www.abc.net.au/reslib/200708/r167145_622126.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK I lol'd at that one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this stage I get the impression trump is just trying to make sure he doesn't piss off his voter base (if he goes through with the deal).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is just Trump trying to show his base that he doesn't like the deal to avoid losing support over it. But I suppose that will only be true if the deal goes ahead. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AI Wins First Poker Game: Libratus, an AI built by Carnegie Mellon University (CMU), racked up over $US1.7 million ($2.2 million) worth of chips against four of the top professional poker players in the world in a 20-day marathon poker tournament that ended in Philadelphia on Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australian here. Have driven through Texas.

The thing I remember most is a comment (from a Texan) about Australia. "The size of the US but the population of Texas" 

Nice place though, Friendly people. Just don't discuss politics, religion or gun control. 

The border guards were also friendly and didn't check visas of non-hispanics...

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would guess that the majority of people affected by the executive order would be better educated than the average American?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm, no. A medical resident has already graduated and can call themselves Dr. The residency is "on the job training" to give them a licence to practice on their own. Many professions have similar (e.g. engineers)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 08:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try. The scientific consensus on this one lies with IARC. EDIT: properly qualified scientists (toxicologists, cancer epidemiologists).

Oh and I forgot to add that Chlorinated drinking water is group 3 (not classifiable). 
There is one chemical that IARC have ruled is definitely not carcinogenic (group 4). 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 07:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pointless, however one last try...

If YOU'D have bothered to read the article posted, rather than dismiss it as an industry shill because you didnt LIKE what it said, you'd see that the IARC drew conclusions from studies that the study author's themselves disagreed with.

No need to shout. If **you** however had read my post properly above where I mentioned meta analysis you would understand how that is possible.

 Again with the activist bullshit. Anyone who disagrees with your narrative and conclusions is automatically an industry shill. 

I am a scientist (and farmer), not an activist. Please don't insult me. 

I was not referring to Iida. I have made no comment about her. My comments have been referring to the other blog she linked to (David / The Risk Monger) - who from his bio has worked/works as an industry lobbyist and consultant. That of course does not preclude him from having a valid opinion, but opinion is not science and science is not opinion.

This is really like the climate change issue. Who should we believe, the huge body of impartial scientists, or the other group - oil companies, politicians, bloggers with undisclosed conflicts of interest.  I guess you are on the side of the oil companies there too??? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You're no different.

Sorry but I am. As a (part time) farmer who uses glyphosate, I would be happy if someone can prove it is not carcinogenic in humans. It would be convenient to bury my head in the sand but that would be pointless. Instead I minimize my use of glyphosate and wear proper PPE. 

The best cancer experts around the world have reviewed the data (including your reams of research). How about you read the actual report and tell me what is wrong - instead of blogs written by industry shills.   

http://monographs.iarc.fr/ENG/Monographs/vol112/mono112-10.pdf

The IARC themselves say:
6.1 Cancer in humans
There is limited evidence in humans for the
carcinogenicity of glyphosate. A positive association
has been observed for non-Hodgkin
lymphoma.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yet you included the mention about knowing personally someone on the board.

I stated that in an attempt to make it clear that I have knowledge of the process from one of the scientists involved in making the decision. You seem to be reading all sorts of stuff in that isn't there. The person I know is a scientist who is not a member of the IARC board, however has sat on some panels within their field of scientific expertise.  

 It just very convenient that a lot of industry led research happens to get thrown out by their standards then. Research that stands up to peer review.

Which research are you referring to?

 That's gotta be the shittiest argument to not take someone seriously i've ever seen.

If you read my post I wasn't using that to critique his work. I was using that as evidence of bias. If you read the blog post it is full of glib/BS statements like:

 For the record, IARC considers sunlight as a known carcinogen (Category 1) but I dont see regulators banning people from going outside.

Which is clearly a strawman argument. 

I don't have the time to go through everything that is wrong with the blog line by line. 

By the sound of it your mind is made up and there in nothing that could persuade you. At the end of the day, it comes down to who should you believe. A bunch of impartial scientists who conduct their study in open session using well defined methods that are decided at the outset. Of the industry making money from glyphosate sales.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 04:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> um, you do realize most terrorists haven't come from places that have been bombed (not saying they don't care about it though). 
Also many people have short memories, so stuff happening now is more likely to be an issue... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Large scar on my foot - exercise bike

Large scar on a couple of fingers (almost lost them) - boat hull </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You misunderstand the process. The IARC do not form an opinion, then see which studies agree with it. That would be cherrypicking. Rather what the IARC do is what is known in science as a meta-analysis. The look at **all** studies which meet their **inclusion/exclusion criteria**. These criteria do not change between panels, and are **based on quality of the study, not the findings**. Their deliberations are open and their methods are clearly published beforehand. AFAIK most of the studies they excluded were funded by the industry and wouldn't have made it through the peer review process of a decent journal - either due to flawed methods, incomplete data/methods or undue conflict of interest.   

Its biased because.....it reinforces its claims with a link to a blog that seems biased to you? Care to expound on that?

Sure - the bio on the blog states:

David believes that hunger, AIDS and diseases like malaria are the real threats to humanity - not plastics, GMOs or pesticides.  

This suggests he holds biases. He may be right in his views, but belief has no place in science, so he is clearly not a scientist. 

A colleague (friend) of yours was on the panel. I'm to understand you have a favorable view of the panel because you know someone on it? That's meaningless on my end.

Colleague, not friend. I am basing my comments on the rigour of the IARC process. As a scientist/engineer by day job I trust the process is sound and not driven by agenda beliefs on either side. 

EDIT: 

I agree completely with the comments and critiques that the list does not give relative risk. i.e. bacon, salted fish and uranium are all on the list, but the dose required to give an average person cancer would vary widely between them. AFAIK they are thinking of moving to a relative risk approach which would make more sense. 

There are also statements in the blogs that some of the findings have not been supported by authors of individual papers included. This is the whole point of a meta analysis. By combining studies you add statistical power beyond any one study (the whole is greater than the sum of the parts).

The IARC look at 

*evidence of cancer in animal studies
*mechanism of action (how the agent causes cancer) - and confirmation that the same mechanism exists in humans
*evidence of cancer in human studies


Class 1 needs to demonstrate all of the above conclusively. It is possible that in the future a larger body of rigorous studies may downgrade glyphosate on the IARC list. However I recall the animal data was pretty conclusive. 


Note that the biggest concern is farmers (and their families). So even if you don't agree with the findings, make sure your PPE and cabin air filters are up to scratch. Just in case the IARC turn out to be right after all.  


TL;DR: 

The process the IARC use is fixed and does not change between studies. We don't see any serious disagreement with their findings on tobacco smoke or excess sun exposure (causing skin cancer). 




 

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SMS Seeadler. 

The pirate ship of WW1. 

It was a sailing boat that was able to capture 16 enemy ships in 1917.  Because it was a sailing ship it was able to sneak up on enemies and pass through blocades unsuspected. They used many pirate tricks like false flags or hiding in estuaries to catch their prey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is well written but somewhat biased. 

e.g. they mention the research that was excluded by the IARC - with a link to another (seemingly) very biased blog. The IARC have a policy of not including research where the methods and/or conflict(s) of interest are not properly disclosed - i.e. they only include good quality, unbiased research. 

One of my colleagues (in my day job) was on the panel. I don't doubt the IARC assessment. 

She is however right that the classification doesn't assess risk. 

However I will continue to use it on the farm, but with very good PPE/controls. Don't forget that diesel exhaust is class 1!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
