<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3268</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-07 14:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could I have the shadow nimmo? : </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-07 14:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to be a complete n00b but can someone link me to the anchor page as I can't find it :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-05 22:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-05 18:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I unsubbed from all my exes, frienemies, wingy bitches etc. Now I only have posts left from my mom, my brother and my fiance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-03 20:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this game, it's so simple yet so beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-28 11:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had an Implanon implant in my arm that I have just had taken out - I've read online that the constant elevation in your hormones can cause thyroid problems, and I have displayed all the other symptoms of thyroid dysfunction - dry hair, etc. I will make sure to get checked out when I see the doctor on Friday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-27 21:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't told what to expect at all by my doctor - he just put me on them and basically told me to get on with it. I had to read online about it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-26 12:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are people upvoting an automated response? D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-23 19:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Derp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does the human brain process the black and white to colour optical illusion pictures?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-22 20:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it to do with how the brain perceives the image, i.e a person, we know what their skin colour would be, so our brain sees that colour?

I probably don't make sense :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-22 10:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I often have dreams about being one of the last people in the world - me and a grou of ''survivors'' living in a massive superstore in the UK called Tesco Extra. You could survive for years in there!

The first thing I would do is go to the Soft Furnishings range and set up beds for everyone by dragging the sofas from the changing rooms. I would make it cosy, with lamps from Home furnishings, a little TV and some makeup areas / changing areas. I'd have a female and male section to respect privacy.

Next thing I would do is make a cooking area, setting up the little electric stoves, a fridge, microwave etc. We would have cutlery, plates, etc etc.

Next on the agenda is toileting - There is toilets in Tesco so that is fine, but I would make them pretty and put in lots of lovely towels and nice soaps. Again, we would have a female and male toilet.

Then I would organise all the food into perishable/non perishable, obviously eating perishable first, but I would organise a vegetable patch out the back of the superstore and plant potatoes and carrots and things, so we could survive long term. We would all live in Tesco and have fun, watching the giant TVs, DVDs, Game Consoles, Books, Toys! It would be amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-17 22:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ''hey honey, does this rag smell like chloroform to you?'' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thrown away over a thousand muffins and random junk like sandals etc. Still no avi. What have I done wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-17 18:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting disheartened now as I have thrown away about 1200 muffins and spent around 20-30k buying all the rotten things. Can someone tell me what I am doing wrong? D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 22:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do dwarves have knees? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 21:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never, in my life, seen a dwarf climb a ladder or run up some stairs. I believe this is a fault in their DNA. Do they have knees? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 19:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ''Don't give him a dolla, then he knows you got more'' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 13:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ''Madagascar has closed its ports.'' Worst five words ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 13:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good Guy Bloodstains doesn't forget about you on Valentines day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
