<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7913</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool thx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it overall. Maybe the modeling/lighting could be stronger on dolphins? Their shapes are hard to make out, especially with the pattern. I think a simple background is good to offset the 'sculpture', I don't know about the rainbow alternate dimension thing though.

Is this entirely from imagination? Or do you have a cool swirling dolphin sculpture? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does tag mean 'give me some constructive criticism'? New to arty subs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do people get extra cd keys? Just buy another copy from Bliz or somewhere else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the book it mentioned the room dimensions gradually got smaller as you approached the throne, to create an optical illusion that Paul was a towering giant. That's impossible to render in an illustration though (I think)? I don't remember the, ah, 'towers.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way we could get them all fast enough while they are forming from the ground. Once they are up and running with their Estocs we're done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quality Of Life :) I'm stuck on a Mac for now so even the simple stuff I can't use. Going to get a Windows gaming laptop soon though. Is maphack safe on Bnet? I can't use it anyway on Windows but assumed there weren't any nondetectable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, sorry! Just curious if you did any qol mods, sounds like you've been playing a long time. I guess muling is less of a hassle with multiple clients running tho huh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 09:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'm playing single player only for now, but I'm moving to the East Coast in a couple months, if I can get a computer/connection upgrade I'll try Bnet again. Do you play non-Ladder so you can mod? After using GoMule it's hard to imagine going back to dealing with muling... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip - cleared WSK and Baal and got my first Ist. Do you do them players+, what build do you use? I also ironically scored a Bulthakos wedding band from Countess before I ditched that bs lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multiple chars. It's also not too difficult to make a fresh Sorc and rush to A5 if you're out. If you're on Bnet even easier, just get a rush. (I'm single player tho). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 10:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, I sort of knew that ;) no MF just means less magic/rare/uni rolls on stuff that drops ya? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm starting pretty fresh so only need some mid levels runes, like Lem for Treachery etc. Hell Cows with zero MF is good for general rune hunting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't the whole pack always cold immune? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 15ias jewel, plenty shaels and socket quests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ideal Sorc Build for Hell Countess? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title. Also looking for a good alt Sorc build to compliment my Blizz MFer in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reapers Toll Tips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got my first Reapers Toll on SP. it's unfortunately not Eth but still a great upgrade. Is it correct that Guliarmes Face and Treachery are the ideal compliments? I have a Vamp Gaze on him currently. Any tips on what to socket in the Reapers? I have some +35% dmg jewels and assorted mid-range runes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Berserker is a good budget build? Never played barb before, thinking of trying it. Why best MF? Seems like Sorcs/Hdins are the ones most used. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing self-found with no mods, what are some milestones I can look at for when my budget hdin will be able to outperform a fairly well geared MF Bliz Sorc? I won't have any Ladder RW because I'm on a Mac. 

I tried hdin for first time recently on Ladder, but I quickly realized it's difficult to position/survive without enigma... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorc Bliz vs. Lightning in Hell (SP No Mods) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Important to preface this with the fact that I'm doing single player with no mods except GoMule...so with no recourse to Infinity, would Lightning be superior for dealing with Hell immunity considering that a combination of Lightning Mastery and a Lower Resist wand at least has some immune breaking ability while Cold has zero possibility of that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once in college my childhood next door neighbor and I crossed paths on the street. I lived 3 states away and hadn't seen him since we were little. The street was kind of deserted which added to the surreality of the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you do just 20 in Nova and Bliz + 2 sysnergies? Why is Nova better than Lightning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, scratching my head because Hell Ancients are all cold immune (or do they spawn with different immunities each game?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Light/Fire Skill to compliment Blizzard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the best cold immune killing skill to use the extra skill points for in Bliz build? Lighting? Meteor? Meteor has the highest dmg at 20 but wondering if a high cast speed might make Lighting or Fireball better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 06:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The easiest approach for me has always been tower shield + spear or Estoc if a Str build. They are weak to lightning so some resins help. Go in stocked on healing items and shield poke away at them.

Also, the next Garg will be summoned whenever 1 of them hits 50% health, so it's best to focus on 1 at a time to slow down the summons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did notice a lower resist wand made dramatic difference on my Trapsin, so that makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, had no idea they worked differently. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 10:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure I understand, looking for good high exp targets that don't have cold immunity. Sorc already has a lower resist skill, so a wand wouldn't be helpful and lower resist can't break immunity (or can it??). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hell Exp farming for Bliz Sorc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 10:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ideas pls on best strategy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard to beat Sorc's unique abilities, especially 'free' teleporting - but Hell is quite difficult without dual elements, and that requires pretty developed gear. Trapsin is slower but you don't need to worry about immunes, plus some excellent survivability skills. And it's less gear dependent. You'll be slow without good gear, but you can definitely clear Hell.

For straight MF, you can't beat Blizzard if you're starting fresh. Bliz can MF certain Hell area practically naked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some thoughts on Trapsin for HC: fade's res all / hidden dmg reduction %, ability to put practically all points in health, 2 elements on 1 skill tree + corpse explosion, spamable stun and meatshield. All of NM can be cleared practically naked, and with minimal gear Hell. With a lower resist wand on switch you can sort of get the Infinity effect for cheap (minus immunity breaking of course). Only real downside imo is the lack of teliport, but again, staff works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 07:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Falconers at game entrance in NG+ drop them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 07:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On same general topic, any thoughts on best light strike weapon in game? Or is it Mace? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 06:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well done! I'm curious about your setup since I just started Hell with my SP Sorc. How many +skills do you have? Merc gear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started playing SP with GoMule, I'm planning to eventually just make 1 of each class and beat hell Baal with each, nothing wasted ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been told that bad people in Hawaii dispose of bodies in the lava tubes, so lava-ghosts maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI the falconers at game entrance drop them in NG+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When using a LS in right hand and an Estoc in left, you get a synergy where the Estoc can attack near-instantly after a LS attack. Same with any rapier I assume but Estoc is Str scaling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll need to be close to SL 150 to 1H CBS while also having min amounts of life/sta/agi. When I made a build for it I did Gulch last and used other great souls etc. to get my stats up, my GAxe  and sidearm was maxed by then. But do you by all means, gl! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are making a new char for a CBS build, you can start using the same moveset before you are able to get the actual sword. If two weapons have an identical moveset practice with one = practice with the other. If you already have the sword and the stats for it, then ya, no need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due to the state of online play I recommend using stash mods on single player. You can also activate Ladder only content like runewords and Uber's on single player. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he would have relished more worthy opponents, but where can anyone find them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya I may have to just respec to Blizz now, I assumed dual tree would be better for clearing the game and was going to swap to Blizz for farming after...but ya it's already a grind in A1-2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant a specific one, it's called "Greataxe". It has the same moveset and range (or close) as CBS. Just some extra time with the moveset while leveling if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 08:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iirc it's something like 1 min = 1 min it will stay open empty, and 5 for 5, I don't think more than 5 is a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 07:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya I got through Duriel but my merc died like 20 times during A2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 07:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I just beat Duriel and don't have the will to deal with A3 atm, going to MF Andy and AT a bit. I suspect I may get stuck on Diablo though, my merc dies whenever anything looks at him too hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also farm medals from the Hawk dudes where the game starts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's strong enough that either pure Str uninfused or all-in Dark are both good. If you go for Dark, definitely do 30/30 and infuse it. It's one of the highest damage weapons possible with that setup iirc. GL hitting anyone with it in PvP. One good way to 'git gud' with the swords move-set while leveling up is to use the Greataxe from Lost Bastille blacksmith, identical moveset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SP Meteorb Hell Playthough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any tips for Hell for my SP Meteorb Sorc? I'm starting Hell at lvl 71, skills +4, pretty bad resists unfortunately on Sorc but decent CB and Duriels Shell on Holy Freeze Merc.

My first time playing Meteorb and definitely noticed the power plateau at the end of NM.

Using GoMule but nothing else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is poise useful against NG+ bosses? Seems like dodging would become more and more superior the more amped the mobs get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your adaptability at? If your dodge games decent you should be ok, but you'll have to be patient chipping away with that +2 LS. It is possible to summon the white phantom outside Dragonrider's entrance and take him over there with you (if you didn't already summon him). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dam son! Lol, I dub thee the patron saint of SP gaming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for honesty, unlike everyone on this thread trashing OP for "humble bragging". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, don't worry dude ppl be salty when they see some raw talent. I wonder what it would look like with a light wash of watercolor on the figure.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 04:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya thanks I heard about that in another thread, but unfortunately I can only run Mac right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 04:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What class/build do you mainly play? I'm just getting started with a Meteorb Sorc for MF. I got some good luck though on a 50 Wartravs and a 40 Gheeds so I'm ramping up pretty quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Main reasons for me are mediocre connection, temp banning, ability to pause game (I can never play without interruptions), and infinite shared stash ala GoMule. I was playing Ladder until recently. I've also noticed it's more satisfying for me to self-find (so far anyway) and find leveling strategies. The static maps someone mentioned above are also a big plus to take some of the grind off of MF runs.

I thought I would miss the Ladder runewords but actually I don't. I realized a lot of those mid-range RW are pretty overpowered. I enjoy sorting through all the uniques I never bothered with before. For example, my merc has 85% crushing blow because of some random uni yari Id never seen before. I have no high runes, but I can up that to an elite which will be nearly as good as some of the runewords. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 01:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess there's no way to tell if something is duped huh, didn't think about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SP Trading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do SP players ever trade items on Open Bnet? Just started playing SP with GoMule so just curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never had any problems doing the above. Just remember waiting 5 minutes only gets you 5 minutes so don't take too long xfering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I think of Max resists as a must for end game, I would prioritize getting your res up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have exact same experience as you. FYI in case you're playing single player, GoMule works fine on Mac. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One decent budget option is upgrading norm/exceptional unique weapons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wut?! Would this work on Mac? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been able to draw exceptionally well since early childhood. I recently started drawing again after doing practically nothing for about 7 years and there's no difference between my best work from before and my work now. Talent is a fascinating thing. Grateful I landed one somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summon adds more damage per point than Mastery,  plus you get more skels faster = more meat shields. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 07:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Potion Dodgeball free-for-all. Last player standing wins top prize, with runner up prizes. Could also do team matches where all players get same prize with a special prize for MVP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
