<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject419</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any tips for warlord? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get a longbow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can report offensive emblems. Theres always guna be folk who fuck about with shit like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer it to 2v2 and dominion by far but it is annoying getting ganked. Though i find people are quite happy to 1v1 at first  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help refining my play </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv been playing on a raider for about 5 hours today. I think one of my weeknesses is spamming, has anyone any tips for me to stop spam clicking when trying to parry or attack? Also, i tend to use heavy attacks almost exclusively, is this a bad idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv only played raider but i play on pc so i dont know what r1 and r2 does. Whats the signature movr? Any tips for playig raider? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily im on pc haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv just done the advanced one, it tells you there. Doesnt say how to revive people though. How fo i do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hardly again when iv played 3 games so far lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should probably do the tutorial lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samurai spear thingys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These guys are seriously op! Im playing a raider cos i am viking and i cannot deal with these at all. Any tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know what a creative sound card is, and given my ignorance im guna guess i dont lol. Im fairly sure its just the onboard sound card </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too watch vikings and taboo! And pretty much no oher tv show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of lean that way too. Except for the fact it only ever happens with lotro, i run league and wow and skyrim and other stuff all with no problems at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was more hoping to see if its a common problem or something someone has experienced and solved. Iv googled a few things, guna try some when im home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game crashes pc randomly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, iv been playin lotro for a few weeks now and its becoming sifficult for me to play due to the game crashing my pc at random intervals. Sometimes it will happen at character select, other times ican go for a few hours. But its got to the point where im restarti g my pc 2 or 3 times each time i wana play. The audio loops like the last second and the screen has red and grey lines down it. It only happens when playing lotro and i use the pc for a lot of games with nothing like this elsewhere. Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different circumstances then. Carry on love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I struggle with this. Do you enjoy your work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quiver and cloak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a lot of movies where people be wearing a quiver and a cloak, lord of the rings being a prime example. However, i cant see how this can be achieved without trapping the cloak to your body and restricting movement. Has anyone got any tips for achieving this sort of thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 10:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slightly off topic, but how long can i expect to be in moria? And it doesnt seem particularly linear, is this just me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 09:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That first chain i dont use, i use the other 2 though, and the 21-212-2121/21212 chain for healages. Il try getting 31 in there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warden question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi iv been trying to play a warden and i think getting a little better, actually know a few gambits now lol. Iv been using fist shield fist for groups, shield spear shield for heals and spear dhield fist for single target. My question is, 1v1 what us he most effective dps? Iv only been playing a short amount of time and im still learnig, so any help is appreciated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is perfect, where do i go to get them on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats all im wanting, a bar down the left side for my travel skills. How do i get plug ins? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Action bars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was watching a video on youtube the other day and noticed one guy had extra action bars floating around. How do i get extra bars? Would be nice to have my muster spells in one place... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But how does it actually work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does this game play on pc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wandering what the controls are like for pc? It looks strance to play with a mouse and iv been trying to figure it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ears yo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 10:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Collars are the bane of my existence! We need more people like you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 09:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the idea of these guys but im terrified of tryig to paint them, they look haaaard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No spoilers] halfdan the black </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anywhere to find a decent image of halfdans haircut? Iv looked but always seems his right side is hidden or turned away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a reference to something? I feel its a feference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for this! This is perfect! Clear and concise instructions. I like it. I am in the uk though so wont be able to get that primer you mentioned, at least iv bever heard of it. Il look into the wet pallet too. I already have the modelling stuff and i made some knight guys. Its very fiddly i find. Especially heads  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The website said they was about 4 or 5 quid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im having an issue of joining a kin that isnt just get as many people as possible and no on talks. Iv only been playing a week or two but havent met anyone yet and would really like something more friendly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres a shop in the town i live in. Iv been in but really struggle with everyone knowing everyone and what they are doing. Im not very confident in stuff like this lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rather sadly i feel il have to give up. I know no people that play so id be doing this to just have them sit on a shelf or something and never get played. Pfft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats 13 paints, roughly 65 quid. More than the bloody box lol. How do people not get immediately put off?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do i not need to use the games workshop paints? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be a good human. Also accept the fact people are cunts by nature but doesnt mean you have to be all the time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice on painting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im going to go buy the skeletal horde get started box, which is my first real attempt at the hobby. I have no paints though, so my question is as a real novice and beig as cheap and few as posible, what paints would you recomend me getting for that box? Im thinking of getting the white spray paint as a base as they are obviously boney dudes... and i was thinking of tryna get a purple and cream motif across the guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv got to the end of the lone lands, i assumed the expansion got me the next bits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Once that and helms deep is purchased what else do i need? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Once that and helms deep is purchased what else do i need? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Expansion quad pack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv heard of he quad pack and have googled it but i only find things in the us, is it a thing i can buy in the uk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! Finaly someone who sees the truth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frodo! Hes whiney as fuck and it rustles my jimmies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I speak english though not a bastardised version if an already bastardised language. Love it. You please me tremendously  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have patience. Love unconditionaly. Be there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And i got arrested for fighting, i presume they just thought i was pissed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never got charged. I was just held in cells over night cos me dad wouldnt come get me lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You failed your attempted ironic use of yo by capitalising it. And i was asking a more specific question, not the same question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem was promises not met. They raised expectations so high and never lived up to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once got arrested whilst off me tits on coke. That was terrifying. Nothing came of it for some reason  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 09:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The posh wank, wanking with a condom on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 08:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like collecting things, and they are on offer! I have listened and i just ask more. Tryna learn yo. Shouldnt belittle someone seeking knowledge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im thinking more of ease of play at a decent level when max. Also easy leveling may be nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the 3 buyable guys like? Im guna get them whilst on offer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im thinking captain is supporty type? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Class difficulties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wandering what would be the easiest and hardest class to play? Iv been playing a captain, currently level 26 and im feeling it may be too difficult for me at higher levels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im really nervous. Im brand new and havent painted anything yet! I got 2 starter boxes, skeletons and ghosts. Hopefully they wont be terribly bad as im anticipating  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you do the purple and stuff? It looks amazing and definitely the way i want to go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Set an alarm. When it goes off, get up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have an ileostomy and had a few instances where this happened. Because it does,you have 0 feeling so accident happen. However i cannot imagine possibly not cleaning up after ones self. I remember when i first got it i had a situation at a friends. I had to change the bag and made quite a mess in his bathroom. I did everything i could, and went downstairs to inform him of the situation. I was in tears. He was however fine about  the whole situation. That was how i learnt honeaty was best and pretty much everyone knew i had the bag and was always super understanding  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh sweet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the map on the door? It looks similar to my middle earth one but the geography doesnt seem quite right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently was looking at a house and one of the gratest things was the dining room, which, as a single young man, i had every intention of making into my games room. It was perfect. Didnt get the house though. Yours looks ace! I love the millenium falcon poster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Death army summoning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there, im completely new to the hobby, except from when i made a isengard war of the ring army years ago. Basically im thinking of starting a death army and love the idea of summoning. Can someone explain what can summon and how it works? I havent found any rules about it this far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found pictures of my (now ex) fiance with another mans dick in various places and other things. This was how i found out she was cheating on me with her manager. We promptly split up. I now have a massive cuckold fetish. Strange how the world works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Offline][England][Leeds][D D] pretty much noob looking to start </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hi im pretty much a noob at this, i have listened to a number of podcasts and read the rule book and played a fantasy age game though. im located pretty much right between leeds and bradford and im looking for some people to start playing with, preferably on weekends as i work rotating shifts so weekdays are difficult to peg down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still beating her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your mums writig was very curly tiffany. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 17:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should be back on within the hour </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My captain im on atm is eorlford. Im on now if you are! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for kin on evernight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 15:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi im a new player, currently a level 12 captain and just started a minstrel. Im looking for some friendly people i can play with who can help me get more to grips with the game and generally have a laugh! Also i live in the uk and speak only english </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 23:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats an arvo? Iv only got that far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blood for the blood god! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is dragonlance still being written? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 07:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to google the publication date is 1984 to 2011. Does that mean there will be no more dragonlance books? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it actually bad to masterbate alot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 08:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course i defined myself by that, it was the only thing that had happened in my life. I should have died and it gave me something to prove. I struggle to convey my thoughts a lot of the time. But now i see myself as nothing but a scarred wreck of a person who will never be remembered. It all seems rather pointless, and frankly im ok with that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 07:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its completely vain, il be honest. It made me special. I was 21 when i got it. And i travelled and did a lot of things and never let it stop me doing anything and it felt good. Now im nothing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. I had my stoma reversed last march. I miss it. Keep up the good work! I couldnt have done it without people like you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You a stoma doctor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That list is awesome! Thanks! Aparently after ordering a couple of books earlier, once they arrive i will have all the classic core novels, which should keep me occupied for a while. Many thanks for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cos then you get a young kid stood inbetween 2 blokes with there nobs out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just thinking, could you recomend a chronological reading order for me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 12:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Straight after a shower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 12:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a yorkshireman i salute you. WHITE ROSE WHITE ROSE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 12:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pissing after holding it. Taking a dump at home after being away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grimdark question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv just started hearing of this thing called grimdark. Can someone properly define this for me please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone recognise this edition? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 13:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://m.imgur.com/ju1HVwo

I have this copy of the call of the wild on my shelf, iv no idea where it came from. Its a hard cover and has old english price, 7s 6d which is 7 shillings 6 pennies as far as i can find. Iv looked through all the editions on good reads and cant find it there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone recognise this edition? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 13:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 01:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saxon. They was terrible. The support band was amazing though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 01:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole sonic temple album by the cult </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 00:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was one of my christmas presents to myself haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 00:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://m.imgur.com/a/KZLUn

There they are, apologies for my abysmal photography lol. Its not something i do as a rule </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Il take a picture when i get home. Warning, some are in real bad condition. But im proud of my collection  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baguette. Javelin it or light saber it. Its ingredibly versatile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 16:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a lot if dragonlance books i inherrited from my uncle. Including the hourglass mage. Theres 2 shelves roughly of them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv just got the twins trilogy, thats next after the chronicles trilogy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love bupu! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 12:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im rereading dragons and just said goodbye to bupu and i just love how much more she brings to raistlin! As someones whos introduction was the chronicles trilogy i had an idea of raistlin and bupu showed he was still capable of compassion. I love it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do it alphabetically by author and new books go in top in roughly the right place until i run out of space then redo the alphabetical order </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It freaks me out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate being with bald women, point blank refuse if there are 0 pubage. Id prefer arm pit and leg hair but understand the social stigma that is associated with that so ya know. Hairy is best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do people download porn? Like just go watch a video or sumat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there actually any working designs now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 13:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was also a bi witch. Also a bloke. Middle school was a weird time. Im still bi and also have pentagrams all over me. I havent chanved much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Runescape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because im lazy and refuse to do anything about it basically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 22:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im confused. Can you not please thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think im in love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 13:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3rd movie hermione was fiiiiine! No idea who nikki webster is though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
