<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3600</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Up Candy Hill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 07:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Candy Hill](https://www.reddit.com/user/subject3600)

Have you ever heard of Candy Hill? Its a local legend around my part of Alabama. Not many want to talk about it, nor what happened up there that makes people hush when you mention it. Some tourists come through, stopping to see the Ave Maria Grotto, and there on the map, physical or digital, itll say Candy Hill at the top of Cobbler Lane. Sounds like a joke, but its not, I promise. The horror up on that hill...well, maybe Ill do it justice. Maybe shell let me tell you. Maybe she wont.


I was young, but old enough to know better, and still dumb enough to do it anyway.


Wed bike around the neighborhood. No cell phones, no parents, just two tires and the road under us, a gaggle of goofy kids, who didnt know better than to climb storm drains, and locked gates.


Candy Hill had such a gate at the bottom of it, and a long fence, extending out from the road that led up to it. The fence conceivably encircled the area, going all the around the mountain. Google Maps shows me now that this isnt so. The gate had about 100 yards of fence stretching out on either side of it, but stopped once the ground got too rocky to continue. I guess they figured if a car couldnt get across, there was no need for more fence.


But to be fair, the fence never wouldve kept us out anyway. It only encouraged my little neighborhood gang even more.


The story goes that Sally Jacobs climbed that hill with her boyfriend one night. He drove his old Chevy truck straight up Candy Hill and parked in the little lot at the top. You can see some of the city from there, the little lights and a few billboards shining in the dark. It was a good parking spot in the 90s. Until Sally


Well, Sally died up there. Her boyfriend cut her into pieces, piercing so hard into her stomach, he sliced the upholstery of his truck seat, too. The blood got everywhere, coating the inside of his windshield, his dash, and even his face and clothes. It ran in rivers over the bench seat, and out the doors on both sides. Sallys blood stained the blacktop.


He left her up there when he was done, a destroyed body slashed to pieces and tossed into the bushes only fifteen feet into the woods that surround that blacktop.


People dont go to Candy Hill anymore. The fence is there for a reason.


But no one wants to tell kids what a vicious and unhinged teenager did to his girlfriend, so we were given the PG version: Construction, danger, lots of glass and rock.


Of course word gets around. We all knew why we werent allowed up there. Sally Jacobs trusted the wrong boy.


One cold November day, I joined my ragtag bunch of kids to stare through the gate that lead to Candy Hill. It wasnt a tall gate. Nothing we couldnt scale easy.


John had dared David that he wouldnt climb the fence, and David dared John that he wouldnt either. They were bickering over it. Who was more scared of dead Sally and Candy Hill.


There were only two girls in the group, myself and Jesse. We were always out to prove something, that we were stronger, faster, and braver than the boys, because we were, but hell if the boys believed it. Jesse and I had to prove it more often than not.


Ill do it! I volunteered, when John and Davids argument had stretched into long annoying moments of inaction.


Pfft, yeah right, John taunted me. John was a dick.

Prove it, David dared.


I swallowed, regretting my bravado. Fine, I will, but you gotta do my math homework for a week.


David laughed, Sure, but you aint gonna do it.


Id take that bet. I jumped the fence, the chainlink bouncing against the poles with that metal jangling sound that fences give when protesting the weight of a small child. Lodging the toes of my sneakers into the small diamond openings, I began hauling my minor body weight up the gate.


Jo! I wasnt serious. Maybe you shouldnt! David looked at Jesse, Tell her she shouldnt.


I aint telling her nothing. You started this, shes gonna finish it.


I reached the top, and swung a leg over.


You proved your point, stupid. Now come back. David was scared Id get him in trouble for this dare, like the time he told me I couldnt make a six foot jump from the roof of his moms truck to the roof of his house. I didnt make it. His mom was pissed.


Two weeks of math homework, and Ill come back, I told him. He considered before nodding.


Fine, I acquiesced and went to swing my leg back over again. Something was snagged on the metal fence. I turned to look and found myself staring straight into the milky white eyes of a rotting face.


She had grabbed my jeans, latching fleshless fingers into my belt loop. I screamed bloody murder and tried to struggle free. All I managed to do was fall six feet straight on top of the zombie.


We landed hard, and her rib cage gave a bit as I sunk into her decaying corpse. I pulled away, the stench eating up into my nose, and my arms came back coated in slime and gore. I screamed again.


What I could only assume was Sally sat up and grinned at me, eyes still milky, but now hanging out of her sockets. Her hair had pulled away from her head in a sheet and was barely hanging on, her skull a perfect white under the slipping flesh.


Wheres Kyle? Sallys mouth couldnt really speak the words. Her tongue had shriveled, and was barely there. Her mouth flapped a bit, and in the rough whispering, I could barely understand her meaning. Where did Kyle go?


Kyle Peters, her boyfriend. The one who cut her up and let her bleed out in his truck. He spent a few years in a mental ward before being released to guardians whod promised to keep him in line. Insanity saved that seventeen year old. He lived cozy with his parents, with a Playstation, a new Chevy truck, and enough medication to keep him floating calm in Candy Land.


But did Sally need to know that?


Where. Is. Kyle? she rasped out.


Uh...uh...w-w-with his parents over on Orchid I told her.


Pay she shook me, her bony fingers squeezing me tight. He...pay Her jaw fell off then, bouncing down into the gore of her stomach. I winced and tried to back up, but she held on with one hand, and reached into her torso with the other. After digging around in the muck, which the sight of made me nearly puke, she pressed a grime coated pocket knife into my hand. Pay
 she wheezed, more of a breath than an actual word.


She wanted Kyle to pay.


I came to on the far side of the fence, clutching a red handled pocket knife Id not had when Id climbed the fence. Jesse had jumped the chain link to wake me up, when the others had raced off. I wasnt hurt, just a bit winded, and very confused.


Sally? I asked.


Jeez, did you hit your head. Maybe we should go to the ER. Im Jesse. She pointed at herself. Jesse.


I waved my friend off and stood, dizzy. Long minutes passed, before we climbed the fence and biked home slowly, the heavy knife in my pocket.


No one else had seen anything, no ghouls, zombies, or ghosts. I was alone in my delusion.


And it stayed that way in the weeks after when Sally insisted on waking me up every night to wheeze the word PAY into my ear. Her milky white eyes hanging on her cheeks were ingrained into all my nightmares, and even some waking hours.


After a month, I couldnt take it anymore.


I guess thats why I went to Orchid in the middle of the night, and left my bike in the gutter, as I made him pay in the dark of his parents house.


Just like Sally wanted.


Five years in a mental institution for disturbed youth, and an affidavit that my parents will keep me stable afterwards seem like sweet justice for Sally.


[Lets hope she thinks so, too.](http://fb.com/subject3600writing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Set Them Free </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 02:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Read the others first.](https://www.reddit.com/user/subject3600/submitted)

My grandmother died when I was twenty five, almost exactly a year ago. She spent a few weeks in a hospice, before drifting off into a coma, and then passing quietly when her heart failed.


It doesnt matter how magical we are, Death will come for us all. My grandmother waved as she left with the winged creature, fading out in the hallway as she passed me. Death smirked, knowing one day shed be back for me as well.


The house where wed spent so many years was deeded to the all of the children, and majority winning, it would be put up for auction after we cleaned it out.


I volunteered for the cleaning crew, and had plenty of help the first two days. On the third day, everyone else refused to show up, after Cal, the haint in the fireplace, wrecked the dining room with soot and ash from a blowback draft down the chimney. After that, the family wanted to hire professionals to clean the place out, or just set it ablaze and be done with it.


It honestly wasnt Cals fault he was pissed that a new family would be residing with him soon. All the others in the house were angry as well, but most took my offer to set them free, instead of waiting to see if the next owners would be as cool as my grandmother.


Cals temper tantrum took an extra week to clean the place out. It was a sad thing, throwing out items that at one time my grandmother had held, but memories are stronger than things, and truth be told, the couch, hand towels, and kitchen knives were all a little ragged from forty plus years of use. The only thing I fought to keep was the family bible. While not my religion, the extra large tome had sat by the front door for several decades and seen more than anything else in the house. It was special.


I kept my grandmothers cane as well, something shed whittled a few years prior after age had set in, and she couldnt move around the farm so well. It was dressed in runes and sigils, stories and psalms, and held some power for repelling both negative thoughts and naughty grandchildren.


Halloween came, the last day before the hired cleaners were due in. I finished up in the house the best I could alone, doubled checked that both Fireplace Cal and Jameson (from the basement) were staying after making them promise not to wreak too much havoc on the next family, and hid the key under the back door mat. I wouldnt need it again.


My grandmother waited by the driveway, looking out over the cornfield. It didnt surprise me.


I stowed the few things I was keeping in my car, but kept the carved cane in my hand, before walking over to her. She smiled, and nodded towards the field.


It was fallow currently, only a few stalks left to compost. We wouldnt have a harvest this year. The scarecrows stood tall among the otherwise empty field.


Whatcha want? I asked her. She stepped out into the dirt, and drifted away. Confused, I moved forward. As I crossed from grass to tilled soil, my surroundings changed. I cursed myself for forgetting the date. The veil was thin today. Halloween was a good time to reach across, and a great time to get stuck on the other side.


The farm on this side was darker, reality just a bit more wavy, and less sure. Before me the corn stood tall and thick, but a closer look at the ear revealed smut, a corn fungus. Confused, I stepped farther into the field, looking over the crop. Why was the field sick here, when there was no corn planted on the real side?


My grandmother appeared beside me, and took my arm. We walked quietly through the stalks, her leading me gently along.


The farther we traveled, the sicker the corn got, the stalks browning, the ears drooping, the soil turning grey under my feet.


I started to understand. We reached the sixth scarecrow. The festering rot spread out from his base, eating into the entire field.


In my cleaning, I had not offered to set the scarecrows free. Honestly, Id been too worried about what might escape if I did.


My grandmother pointed at the sickly ground around the sixth scarecrows pole. I looked at my dead grandmother. She smiled, tapped the cane tucked under my arm, and stepped back. She meant for me to deal with this alone.


I considered telling her no dice. This did not seem like my idea of a good time. But before the house left the family, something would have to be done about the disease spreading over the field, and other than Anna, I was the only capable one.


Youre gonna owe me, I told my grandmother, before I stepped up to the scarecrow. His appearance hadnt changed much on this side, if my memory served. Bloated face, perfect embroidered features, and a terrifying grin looked down at me. I shuddered and drew the circle wide, digging the canes rubber stopper deep into the dirt.


Focusing on the carvings my grandmother had made in the wood, I summoned up the energy needed to bring the scarecrow to life.


He screamed.


Seething from the top of his pole, his gaze seared me. He continued to scream. It was probably agony. A pole up your backside as support is hardly comfortable.

He slithered from his height then, dropping into the sickly dirt and coming for me. He walked as all scary things do, with a twitch and a flash.

I guess I needed to cleanse and release him. If I didnt, hed likely continuing poisoning the ground, and the next person to own the farm probably didnt deserve it. I wondered if his poison had hurt any of us.

His face loomed near mine as I focused on his souls tether to the scarecrow body and found the thin thread that stitched him down. I was about to cut it, when a hand touched my shoulder and I jumped. Behind me, the other five scarecrows moved in, detached from their poles now. The leader, the one I found solace at the base of so many years ago, tapped my arm gently, before he and the rest surrounded the sixth.


The man I refused to call my grandfather would have an escort to the afterlife. May he burn.


I severed the tie, and all six scarecrows fell to the ground lifeless. My grandmother smiled and faded away.


The other side let me return to the mortal plane with only a pop and no real struggle. On this side, the scarecrows stood upon their poles in a circle around the sixth. I thanked them silently, before gassing them down with old kerosene, and lighting up the field. I would leave no ties for any wicked souls to return.


It felt like a real goodbye when I left this time, the farmhouse in my rearview mirror for too long before I turned off the country road and headed back to town.


Its been a year. The farm sold, and I think the new farmer managed a healthy crop, according to my uncle, who still talks to the guy.


But the astral is calling again, some new problem, and my grandmother stands by my bed. I dont think itll be so easy to get back out again, but I know Ill try anyway. I cant deny her. If you don't hear from me, I may still be on the other side fighting. Something must really be wrong. [Why else would she be back?](http://facebook.com/subject3600writing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
