<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8219</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt mention  - i cant run due to a broken knee i had last year. I cant join  a gym as i have no money.  I do however walk between 10 and 25 thousand steps per day.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the quickest and easiest way to lose a big belly. With no equipment. No money and pretty much no time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went up 6 ranks and got 2 million! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mushrooms in Amsterdam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a more cheerful note to my psychosis thread....

One of my craziest trips happened in 2005. Here's the story ! 

Speaking directly to those that use and abuse drugs...have you ever been fixated on a chemical or a drug or a plant? Like you want to do a drug. So research it like mad, reading everything you can? Looking up pictures excitedly...you are practically high off it before you do it. You are mentally wanking over the experience you want to have.

Well in 2005 i got that feeling. It had been a while. I had had a break from all substances and was basically a raging alcoholic. I was so unhappy, on citalopram for depression, miserable...i turned to the internet for some sort of excitement and found a site dedicated to magic mushrooms. 

My experience with mushrooms was a few trips off liberty caps which were brilliant,  back in the 90s. But I'd never seen anything like these psylocybe Cubensis.  I spent full evenings reading trip reports and looking at images of people's grow logs. I decided I simply had to do them. I needed to reawaken my mind.

I had a trip to Amsterdam booked for that summer, I used to go regularly, and this all just felt like fate as i had read that shrooms were legal in Holland  (they have since been made illegal). This would be it. I researched shops that sold them. I researched it all. Right down to the strain i wanted to try. Hawaiian. They just sounded and looked so exotic. They were rated as one of the stronger types, and I was looking for a mind blowing experience!

Fast forward a few months.  And i am disembarking from  the plane at schipol airport. Literally within half an hour i was at the magic mushroom gallery. And within one hour of landing i was in my creepy as fuck hotel room eating these raw mushrooms. I swear they tasted fucking grim. But nothing would or could stop me...the woman in the shop had recommended I take half the box. But I decided id take a bit more just to be safe. I was experienced and she didn't realise that (lol!)

Literally within half an hour i was on my ass. I was supposed to be meeting some friends in the city centre. They rang on my mobile....when I explained what I'd done they were equally amused and scared for me. I promised I would meet them but I needed some time to compose myself. 

With every ten minutes the visuals became more and more intense. It was a lot stronger than i expected,  patterns hung in the air, not like the familiar geometrics of acid, but 3D kaleidoscopic visions. I tried to get off the bed and i swear the floor was like mud swirling around my feet.

When there was a knock on the door i freaked the fuck out. Who was it?  What could they want. Could I even communicate in this state?....i literally crept to the door and looked through the spyhole. It was my friend I was supposed to be meeting. He has come. He had come to help me....i opened the door as though it might reveal monsters behind it. I couldn't tell whether it was day or night the patterns were so forceful. I just saw swirling shapes and 5he entire corridor seemed to be breathing. 

"Oh my God! " my friend exclaimed looking at me. "How much have you done?" When I told him he laughed and said "let's get you out of here". Its a good job Amsterdam is a liberal city as he literally held me by the hand and led me out of the hotel. 

On the streets, the people all looked like busy ants scurrying around so rapidly my vision blurred. I focused on the floor. Each step forward. One foot in front of the other. The paving slabs were like hexagons and each one i stood on lit up with bright white light. 

"Yes this is the right way!" I thought and grinned. My friend took me to a place called The Greenhouse. There all of my friends were stoned. Smoking skunk they laughed when they saw me and you know what, I felt this deep love like on E. 

I sat in this crazy place, surrounded by people smoking grass...the visions began to peak. I remember looking at my friend and thinking "why the fuck does he have a parrot on his shoulder?" Then looking back and it was gone. Nothing but a momentary pirate i thought. Nothing to be scared of. It was like i was slipping into a comfortable trip now after an intense come up. There was no questioning of what I was experiencing now. Only acceptance.  I knew this was as strong as it would get. I stopped fighting it mentally and just let myself go. I smoked some weed which made me feel so high. I had a pint of beer and i just looked around. I remember seeing a barmaid and thinking her hair was like me medusas snakes. A rowdy group of Americans looked like bloated toads, aggressively demanding things at the bar.

After a while we left the bar and i walked outside into the night. The buildings looked like lego. The canals looked like oil. Everything just seemed so fluid and connected. It was just so beautiful.

The trip eased off gradually in the coming hours, i felt tired and fuzzy headed. As intense as it was in the first hour, i knew it was something I wanted to experience again. And i did, many more times. 

Peace !



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP of the thread. Trust me I knew my shit. I had always used a lot of different substances and knew how to deal with everything from acid to coke. I did coke loads of times and never got hooked, I could take it or leave it. But meth. I couldn't stop. It was like living in a different world. For a start i had a few months where I felt like a God.  Then after that time. I was too screwed up and hooked to stop.

I genuinely thought I'd never be that guy. Even when my friends told me I was developing a habit, I still didn't think I was. I am now only addicted to smoking and its a similar pattern of addiction. Where it creeps up on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rockstar servers unavailable right now please try again later. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sooooooo fucking annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote a long trip report on my psychosis from crystal methamphetamine. But here is another about LSD.

It was about 1997 and at Glastonbury back then it was full of new age type people. We were sat just chilling, smoking weed and drinking fruit cider when a hippy looking couple walked by saying "acid! Anyone want to buy acid?"....to say I chased them down like a wold on a sheep is an understatement. There was no doubt of this being real stuff cos these guys were so off their tits they just oozed the tripping vibe with massive eyes and big smiles.

I bought a few micro dots and a strip of alien logo blotter. I took one of the blotter and just went back to sit down with my mates. A few others dropped and we just relaxed as the acid came on strong. And it was very strong. I remember the sky looking like a nest of snakes. And we went on a walk through the crowds, tripping balls.

Now for the psychotic bit. It was one of those intense...not quite funny trips, where you feel like jumping up and running away. The paranoid anxiety at the back of your mind to compensate for the insane visuals. I was seeing people with painted faces like animals. The grass alive like worms....it was strong.

But not strong enough to stop me taking a micro dot and an E at the same time.

Cut to an hour later.

I was watching Pulp. Amazing band I loved so much. I was now in a different world. Disconnected. Hallucinating vividly. My bro pushed my arm and said "what are you watching?".... i was literally stood for an hour not watching the band play. Or the screens. I was staring into the darkness watching some really quite sick stuff. I saw psychedelic scenes but mixed with violence. I remember several images clearly. In one, police men beat a man in a gutter and in another a girl freaking out like in a horror film as someone chopped down her door with an axe. I was watching it like it was on a screen. But it was like a kaleidoscopic television. 

I dont think it was a bad trip. It was just an insane trip. Everywhere I looked was these insane scenes. At one point, the crowd looked like zombies with hollow eyes and glowing face paint.

It was intense and mind blowing. I was 17 and it has always stuck with me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think my point is in the depths of addiction there is no using drugs mindfully. I didnt sleep because I was always on crystal. I took large amounts of it because after a year I was building up a tolerance which led to reckless dosing... there are some drugs that are just harmful period and thinking you can control it or do it in a less harmful way is exactly what I started out doing. Its that "it will never be me, I'll never be that guy" way of thinking that so many people think will keep them safe... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im better than back then, I read about amphetamines damaging the areas of your brain that give you natural pleasure and I guess it's true because I feel so depressed most of the time....but im ok ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play as a woman character and love choosing a really good outfit. Coordinating shoes and accessories, hair and make up.

I just wish there were more... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its like this, if i dropped acid back in the day, even when I had insanely strong micro dots where I was led there watching the world disappear and all i could do for 8 hours was say the phrase "its not working yet".... i knew in my mind I was on acid.

This was different. I believed the delusions 100%. One of the most disturbing things to me is this...i was in the woods believing all this. If an innocent person had approached me, well, I have no doubt it would have ended badly. To me at the time it was very very real. I wrote bad trip, but it wasn't really a trip. It was a true psychotic episode. I have since worked in mental health and it is the same experience as paranoid schizophrenics have  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is up with its ears ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screamadelica is an outstanding and upbeat album for the psychedelic experience! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 1998 it was popular round where I live. It was around for no more than a year and i was unfortunate enough to get caught up in it. 

It was before the second wave of ecstasy came into its own (my experience of a true E was a catalyst to me giving up speed all together. In the loved up euphoria i faced some hard truths). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can i just add something (i dont know how to edit my post....).


I had a best friend from back then. He too went through a lot of what I did. We were best friends but the meth eroded that as we each began shutting down. 

I saw him a few months ago. The first time in about 15 years.  It was all good. When I commented on how crazy it was back then, he was walking off in his own direction and turned and said exactly the truth :

"It always stays with you" and it does . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shadow people and whispers about yourself are the worst ! To this day i cant cope with low level noises.  I sleep with earplugs to block everything out. I hope you are ok! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mentally im a screwed up person! But I'm glad I'm alive!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id be really sad if it inspires someone to do that ! I could add bits about how i stole off everyone I loved. How i slept rough in abandoned houses with heroin addicts. How i didnt wash for days. How my teeth are fucked. How i would carve things into my arms just to feel something....i could go on and on and on. Its SHIT ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sad thing is, the anxiety and paranoia i got from that period has never left me. I tried to kill myself a few more times. And it was 3 years before I finally was clean of amphetamines. I got into a rehab unit and was prescribed dexamphetamine to wean me off the crystal. It was a truly horrible time man.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meth psychosis. Baaad trip. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I talked briefly about this in another thread the other day and it had been a long time since I had thought about it. So I thought it may help someone if i tell this story. 

This happened to me almost 20 years ago now. 20 years later its still vivid in my mind it was so traumatic. 

The back story. 

In 1998 i moved from smoking pot to doing crystal methamphetamine. I remember the first few times,  I felt like a God.  I felt like I had discovered some secret. That the rest of humanity were weaker beings needing to sleep. I was full of life. Full of confidence and social. When I ended the nights out and went home, id lie there so wired i couldnt even blink. In my head running over fantasy scenarios and dreaming whilst awake. Dawn would come and id drop off to sleep. I had dropped out of work and was living off benefits which I used completely to buy crystal. It felt so good. 

This carried on for a while, I got confident, got a girlfriend. I hadn't had one for a few years  (im an ugly bastard!). Anyway. My confidence spiralled into egotistical wankerdom. I believed the grains of white crystal i held in my pocket were magic. Then one night this illusion swung violently into a nightmare...

That night.

I hadn't slept or eaten anything proper in days. I was wired to fuck already. I met my girlfriend, who in reality was a drugged up skank from a rough family and we went to this shitty local pub she liked. I went into the toilets and thinking "this place is shit, I'll liven it up about", I took out my baggy and proceeded to bomb double what I usually took. It seemed to hit almost instantly. I was in the cubicle and the rush was pure terror and anxiety. I sat there and heard a few guys come into the toilet. They were talking about me. They were plotting to beat me up.  I sat there with my heart pounding and eyes bulging thinking what will I do? What will I do...

I go out cautiously and there is nobody there. I go into the pub area and my mates are playing pool and drinking.  I try to pretend im ok but it must have been so obvious i wasnt. As one of my friends commented "you need to calm down on that stuff". My girlfriend said "let's get out of here you look crazy". So we went to her house which was just over the road. She said "ill make you a brew to help you calm down".

I sat there and my mind was racing. She was in on it. I never drink brews. She was trying to poison me. Or slip me some downers so the people in the pub could beat me up. I sat in the lounge on my own. And looking around i saw some tools her dad had out, he was installing laminate floor. There was a hammer and a few other bits. Then I saw it. A retractable Stanley knife. I picked it up quietly and slipped it into my pocket. Not even thinking what the fuck I was going to do. I just knew if these fuckers came.  I was going to defend myself. 

My girlfriend came in and gave me the brew. I put it down and obviously didn't drink that poisoned shit. The curtains were drawn, but I saw the shadows outside of a group of people. They were coming. I needed to get the fuck out of there. 

My girlfriend starts coming on to me. I pretended i was into it. THEN! seizing the element of surprise i push her off, jump up and shoot out of her house. I sprinted the fastest i have ever ran. Her house overlooked some fields at the back that led onto woods. I just ran and ran and ran. Once I was a good distance away i looked back and they were coming.  I saw them coming. Fast. So I turned and carried on sprinting. On that night I think I'd have given Ussain Bolt a run for his money.

I reached the woods and literally felt sick at the thought of going in. It must have been agouti midnight now and it was pitch black. There was no place else to go. I hurdled the fence and ran in. I found a densely overgrown spot and hid behind a tree. My heart pounding in my chest. My hand in my pocket slid out the blade of the knife...

I stayed quiet for what seemed like hours. I saw them. Theirs dark silhouettes and hooded heads. They looked big. Like body builder types. And there were loads of them. I heard them whistle to each other in some sort of code.

Then the worst thing ever happened.  The clouds cleared and the full moon shone bright light down, illuminating the woods and revealing where I was. I saw them moving between trees. They were playing a game. They were hunting me."just get it over with!!... what have I done to you??.....why are you doing this !" I screamed into the dark.  But still they didn't come. They just sort of circled around me in the woods. My mind raced to every person i might have pissed off. To think who could be behind this. I knew whoever it was, to have this many people out here in the woods. They were serious. 

"COME ON! COME AND DO IT THEN! I'VE GOT A FUCKING KNIFE" I literally screamed into the dark woods. It was probably now about 2am. The shadows just kept darting between trees only now... they looked small. Not even my height (I'm not very tall). The moon had gone back behind the clouds. But then all of a sudden  a bright white beam came down from  the moon to the middle of the woods. My mind then, and I remember with clarity, thought "i cannot believe this is an alien conspiracy, oh my God im going to be abducted, ill disappear and no one will ever know what happened "..... it sounds ludicrous in hindsight. But the terror i felt in that moment. I pulled out the knife. I thought. No. Id rather fucking kill myself than be taken by aliens.

The time now must have been about 4am because it literally started to grow lighter....i looked around in horror. The blade of the Stanley knife to my wrist. It was like my whole soul screamed "NO!"  

The light came fast. I looked around. There was no one. No beings. No people. Just me. I was freezing. My eyes were literally bulging out of my skull. A moment of clarity came smashing through all the horror. I collapsed to my knees and looked at myself.   I was covered in mud. Id actually cut into my arm and blood ran down my hand.. I was filthy. I sat there with my head in my hands crying for ages. What had my life become.

I pulled myself up and walked home. All the way, paranoid thoughts rushed through my head. People in cars stared at me. Men in white vans were going to pull up and bundle me into their vans. The reality was it was about 5am. There were hardly any cars about. The bad tripped lingered. I had to force myself not to look at the shadow people. I remember one vividly leaning on the bonnet of a car cradling a baseball bat. I forced myself to look down and just get home. Now the reality that it was a bad trip, was a thought I could understand. I felt distraught.

I got home. I got into bed. And i slept for two full days. 

I got up after that 48 hours, and I made a serious attempt to kill myself. 

My mum found me unconscious.

I was in hospital for 3 days. I woke up, discharged myself. And you know what? Went and scored some more meth.

Please. If you are young, or any age. Don't do that shit. It is evil. It is the worst most horrible thing. It will make you do terrible things to people you love. It will make you do terrible things to yourself.

It just is not worth it.

Peace guys ! 




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have terrible mental health problems and am just winging it every day. I work 3 jobs have 2 kids and spend the vast majority of my life doing everything for everyone else. When in reality im acutely depressed then acutely manic. I used to be a drug addict and alcoholic.  Now all I do is smoke. So I suppose there is that. 

There is so much i want to do. But my crippling anxiety holds me back. I live my whole life like im wearing a mask. And honestly some days i dont know how I make it through. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, just having a moan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
