<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6703</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hooded Justice is thought to be gay because one of the opening panels of Watchmen has two gay men that really seem like they could be Capt. Metropolis and Hooded Justice based on the characters' backgrounds and appearance.

There might be more to it that I don't know about but if there is, I don't know about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THEN I GUESS I'M SIGNING UP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the only way to get this through them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow you're fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to make "playlists"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean kind of like [this](https://marvel.com/comics/discover/47/infinity-the-complete-event).

It would be really nice so I could use the reading order sites to make the playlist, and then not have my reading interrupted by having to look at the list and then find it again. It would also be nice to see other people's who are more knowledgeable about Marvel than I.

And while I'm asking questions, is there a way to view multiple series' issues at once? Like having the concurrent runs by Hickman open at the same time so I could go in publishing order? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roles could be reversed, like Hercules become the narcissistic serious one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's relatively short, I think it took me like 6-7 hours but I'm terrible at video games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a Frank Miller book tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That comment took me like four times longer than it should have because most words kept autocorrecting to other words and it was really pissing me off. Looks like one got through.

Fuck you smartphone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Logan was so good it honestly kind of ruined my enjoyment of Kong a little bit.

I was excited for Kong since the first trailer, but seeing Logan the day before made me enjoy it a little less because I was still thinking about Logan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fourth honestly seems like a rip off made by the sci-fi channel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of solely the amount of good stuff, I'd agree.

Episode I had the posters, Darth Maul, and Dance of the Fates.

Episode II had Coruscant, the arena (fuck you I liked it), Natalie Portman in a cut off shirt, Republic Commando: the movie, and Christopher Lee as Dooku.

Episode III had a shitload of large scale battles, Previous, **WOOKIES**, Obi Wan's best story, "dewit", and the Palatine speech.

However, I'd say the amount of shitiness peaked in Episode II so it kind of depends on the metric you use to gauge the movie's worth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I watched those as a kid, I always thought it was really shitty that they had this unbeatable, untillable army but then they still sacrifice the lives of a bunch of their own soldiers, rather than just letting the ghost army finish off the orks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The part where they started going off about Thanos and his stupid name had me giggling so fucking hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean? I've never read his GL but I've only heard good things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, that apartment seems like it's twice the size of my house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoever made this bot can fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is overpowered tho 

Source: I fucking suck at CS but I can easily get around a 2:1 KD ratio if i use the AWP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of both.

There really isn't much else like Lovecraft's work. It's a special kind of feeling you get when you read it, and I think the elements that make that so would lend themselves to board game mechanics well.

Then again, the aesthetic of the mythos is something I've always loved. The almost noir-ish atmosphere set against the backdrop of a vaguely Victorian Massachusetts is fascinating to me.

I guess I'd just expect solid storytelling (in as much as a board game can offer) with smooth, investigative and survival elements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This helps, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but like co-op, and that game's like $400. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WSIG] Looking for the best Lovecraftian board game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now, I'm trying to decide between Mansions of Madness, Eldritch Horror, Arkham Horror, and Elder Sign. I'm really interested in trying one of these out, but they all seem kind of similar. They're also not very cheap so they makes it a bit more important to find the right one so I don't waste a lot of money.

Mansions of Madness - This one seems the most unique of the four. I like games with miniatures and it seems the most like a horror story, seeing as you're only exploring a house. Also seems the most true to Lovecraft's writing. The only things that make me hesitant about it are the amount of replayability (four base scenarios seems like four playthroughs? I know there are expansions but still. Option for player made scenarios) and the cost. I have a gut feeling I'll like this the most.

Elder Sign - This one is half the cost of the next cheapest.

Arkham Horror - Seems the most complicated, and its the second most expensive. Not sure about even putting this one on the list.

Eldritch Horror - Seems like a condensed version of AH.

This is a real predicament for me. I've done research but the information I've gotten isn't helping. I'm really looking for theme, immersion, and solid gameplay. It seems that all fit this at least a bit.

The recommended template on the wiki isn't really helpful in this case, but I can tell you that my favorite board game is Betrayal at House on the Hill.

Sorry for the long ass post. I want to give the most information I can but I really don't know what exactly I'm looking for in these games, if you know what I mean? Like because they're all similar and I'm pretty open to whatever. So, pros and cons of the one(s) you've played? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The part near the end when he skitters off into the sewer was my favorite part of the movie.

Its this super "serious" scene and he just does this weird little fucking fishtail maneuver. My friend and I start cracking up and we were the only ones in the theater who seemed to think it was funny, which was embarrassing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to punch you right in your healthy face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK knowing this isn't going to exist hurts me emotionally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A collectible miniature type game (like HeroClix) but it would play like a board game. Essentially you can buy whatever "characters" you like, and then bring those to the game. It would be less like card gaming because it wouldn't just be a battle. Maybe something like Betrayal at House on the Hill, but with more character interaction.

Highly thematic, with preferably small "game world" (again like Betrayal, it's just a house, not a huge map) and a lot of replay value.

I've been thinking about this a lot lately and there's a lot more to it, and what I described actually sounds vague and lame, but in my head it's awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "boingboing"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellow Portlander? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know where I can get this in the states? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> # **triggered** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any movies going OOP soon? I'm fine waiting a few more months for the actual 50% sale if not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NWR considers Drive his superhero film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait to explore haunted houses as the Virgin Mary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for somewhat realistic or generic "civilian" miniatures, any idea where to look? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm making new characters in Betrayal at House on the Hill and, while the miniatures aren't necessary for this, I think it would be more fun if they matched with the new character cards.

I'm new to tabletop/board gaming so I don't know the places to look. Google and the websites I looked at didn't help much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be keeping an eye out for you.

**THERE CAN BE ONLY ONE** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  old store

Sounds like you made the right choice. The three guys who work at mine are all really cool and trustworthy, so I don't have any problems like that. Shout out to Cloud 9 Comics! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 06:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So has every generation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My local shop has a system where if you give them your card info, they charge you when the books come in. The upside is there's a 5% discount. Win win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 01:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking for ideas on how to make my Robotman mask and I think you just gave it to me, thanks! Looks great by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you've probably already said it somewhere, but I can't find it. What's it made out of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain this to me? I'm just getting into DC and I've seen this several times. It seems like Superman would be considered the heart and soul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one of the reasons its arguable. There's some stupid stuff, but that movie also has some really good scenes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying its a bad movie (the bug scene stands out, its fucking awesome and terrifying) but compared to the original, Mighty Joe Young (it counts!), and the 1976 version, it just...doesn't compare.

The 1976 version is arguable though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 07:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol whatever you say hombre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Key can have the role of Black in the first movie, the nerdy comic relief, which is kind of what I expect. Though he is actually a decent actor.

As for Munn...I don't know. I haven't seen her in much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I volunteer for a 6th grade camp every October, and this is like all you need to know to be a counselor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would feel you, if Shane Black weren't the director. That guy knows his stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend told me she loves King Kong.

"Which one?"

"The one with Jack Black. I've never seen the other one."

That one hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cthulhu doesn't fit in with the others at all though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know its cool to shit on cinematic universes now, but belay that right now, if you don't want to see classic huge monsters fight each other, I don't know what to tell you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why remake a perfect movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just checked out the rest of his artwork. I would really love to see him do a Kitty Pryde mini. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weren't the original RvBs made on an original Xbox? I'd imagine that's why, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ?

That goes either way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  lol okay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know where to get these with the discount? I know the 90% off is for retailers, but it seems like most of these have stayed at the same price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To the person who broke into my car for fifty cents and a Great Clips gift card. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I know, none of mine are worth more than $20. But the one most valuable to me is Deadpool: The Circle Chase #1. It's in horrible condition, maybe like a 1 or 2 if it was graded, but it was my first comic ever. It's also the first solo series for Deadpool, it's embossed, and I actually really like the arc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The owner told me it's because his construction business has been doing really well lately, and it was just not enough return on the comic shop to make it worth the stress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sucked when they closed because that's the shop I went to for years, especially when I was first getting into comics. Unfortunately, no other shop around here is like them.

Tony's is alright but for most Salem people, it's out of the way. Tony is also kind of a dick sometimes.

Borderlands is okay, but they only carry big titles and not a lot of back issues.

Wild Things is like Borderlands but with an even smaller selection (I'd guess, it has been a while since I've been there). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 09:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 06:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you could buy tapes without renting them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 06:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was probably the best Tinder name pun I've seen. Excellent work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 06:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is my favorite Reddit post of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I just said double tap because she already slit her wrists and seemed to be dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 10:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking about this in the theater. I don't think it'll work as well as the movies, considering one of the reasons the movie works so well is because the plot is simple and the action is so fast paced.

Comics, for the most part, don't capture movement as well as movies. Also, a comic that's action with a slim story isn't usually great.

I hope the Dynamite series is good because I love the movies, but I just don't see it working too well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Miss March was pretty close... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The double tap for the lady in the tub was so loud it made me jump a little. Fuckin awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put this on the DVD cover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm fairly certain that was just them trying to be clever, even though it made no sense. The bounty didn't really have anything to do with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn that sounds kinda fun actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That movie is fucking incredible. The build up to the Mortal Kombat fatality in love action made it all the more insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, the erotica movies. Are those porn, or..? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where can I get more of this?

One issue will not satiate my hunger for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I forgot to include that part. That makes it all the worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compliance

A guy convinces a young woman that he's a cop over the phone, and then fucks with her for a while.

I've never felt the urge to turn off a movie until I saw that, and I watch fucked up movies all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You hit the nail on the head repeatedly. Thanks for putting this into words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  100 Bullets

That would be fucking huge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the whole first omnibus and it was alright, but I guess just a little underwhelming, considering all the stuff I've heard about it for years. I'll definitely have to try the Claremont one, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome news, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read a couple minis, like the one with the ancient sith planet that was sort of medieval.

I love Star Wars, but a lot of the Dark Horse stuff just seemed kind of weird not and Star Wars-y to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, and hell if I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! 24 hours

Edit: lol fuck me right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew about the heat ("It's like 90 degrees-""**BLUUUUHRUUR**") but I didn't know that the band isn't there. That's so crazy to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Best Dark Horse licensed series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking into DH's line of movie licensed comics, and I'm not sure which to get, seeing as I like all of the movies.

The options are Aliens, Predator, Terminator, and Indiana Jones. I tried AvP and Star Wars, but neither of them are what I'm looking for.

So, which do you recommend? I might have missed some but those are the ones I know of.

Edit: I mean as a whole. I'm going to be getting them in the omnibus editions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like the Eric Andre Show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I agree, as much as I love the series, I don't want them to drag it out after the end of Clerks 2. I'm just saying that it happened before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is adorable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, it would follow the trend. Clerks ended with them deciding to go do something with their lives, and Clerks 2 opens with Dante working the same job 10 years later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think James Cameron said something similar about Terminator: Genysis.

Not saying I that's how it'll turn out. I'm actually optimistic, but I just thought I'd throw that out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what will Brubaker even be doing as a producer? I guess I don't really know how the business works, but I thought producers were pretty much just investors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 06:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> now kiss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 05:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read this series, who is this guy and how did he "slip through"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have to use material from other movies, just to mock the actors, then it's not an honest trailer of the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 09:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that honest then, is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 04:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been into LOtR or Narnia but if what your saying is true, holy shit that makes it way better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay but Secret Empire isn't happening for at least several months, so I'm sure those stories aren't gonna be too affected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not being an elitist and not trying to be condescending, but if you think the movie did all this so well, then you don't know much about comics, superheroes, etc. The movies aren't really even that shallow if you look at some of the smaller details.

This kind of stuff comes up all the time, its not original to Watchmen (let alone the movie version). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's really not necessary or funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had to know the first three weren't gonna last anyway. Don
't act like you thought those books were gonna stay on the shelves for years.

And as for Champions, I doubt it will end because of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know if the BNFEB17 code works with pre orders? It won't work for me, and I suspect its the Saga Deluxe Volume 2 that's doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
