<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1841</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weed varies a LOT depending on what strain you take. Can do a lot of different things. Smoked every day for 5 years with varying results.

NEVER gonna try heroin.

Never tried LSD but not entirely opposed to the idea.

Coke honestly didn't do that much for me, only ever had it drunk and it just made me jitter.

Molly can be seriously good, like so good you wish the night would never end. You love your friends and loved ones like 100x more if it's good. You look like a tit gurning away though. It can increase libido but can actually hinder this area too.

Honestly the worst one I ever had was Speed. Shit is pure trash, you get a crazy headache in exchange for a few hours of fast conversation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That ending completely floored me. Same with all the subject 16 puzzles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The starting cutscene of that game terrified me for some reason. I was little and my brother played, I had to get my mam to take me outside somewhere just so i didn't have to watch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never loved and hated a game so simulatenously. Grinding, wondering why, then grinding, ad nauseum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still shake my fist to the sky over Sean Murray, 6 or so years on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way you're taking kairi's heOOHHHH CRUD NOT AGAIN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hooolyyy crap it hurts to remember. Pure terror the second you hear it. And when she gets you it's almost like she's laughing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
