<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4332</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly I think this was inevitable since he wasn't going to be a company man. Wonder where he will end up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seven Cities of Gold:

https://www.gog.com/game/seven_cities_of_gold_ce

I can remember trying to walk through a village and not kill anyone (as soon as your avatar touched them, natives would 'pop' and they would all jump you).

I never could just spread love and happiness, it always came down to death and mayhem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologize. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you are walking into a funeral. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 15:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Movie - Goodfellas

Book - The Name of the Wind

Album - Rated R </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 12:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm seeing the beginnings of it at 46 and it isn't pretty.  The irrational behavior is certainly to be expected.  You can PM me if you want additional details that I'd rather not express in an open forum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't. We use mine. I really don't mind them using it and I will be in the pack for another 4 years....

That's a good idea thought and then I won't be put out when someone breaks mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 11:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I was thinking like - right now we have a Rubbermaid tub that holds a bunch of pots/pans/etc that have been donated over the years.  All of our dutch ovens are owned by the leaders, we have no lanterns at all.  We normally ask our troop to put that sort of stuff on loan to us if we see a need for it.  It would be nice to have our own...

Thanks for the input! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is on your wish list? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 22:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our pack has a benefactor that is planning on donating around $500.00 for the pack to use for any purpose.  What are some things you would spend the money on?

We just purchased a new pinewood derby track so we can't spend anything on that.  We'd prefer to spend it on a hard asset that will be used for years vs. a give-away item like a t-shirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 13:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this has any chance then what they need to do is roll this into the horrible State Liquor Control Board.  Think about it, the state already regulates alcohol for profit, this would only mean more profit to the state.

The state already has the infrastructure of a delivery system in place.  Just add a section for the sale of marijuana and go. Profit!  I'm not a big fan of the PLCB but this may be one instance where it actually works in the favor of the residents of the state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 19:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First Month Free Link:

https://pocketderm.com/invite/QQ0ILTU

So far so good - working for my son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 12:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Carville said 'Pennsylvania is Philly in the East, the Burgh in the West with Alabama in the middle'.  I live about an hour west of Philly and that is a fair assessment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 16:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was so happy when they ditched him.  I couldn't stand all the cuz talk the yelling into the mic.  I like Jody Mac   Ray, that to me is the sort of sports talk I could listen to all day.  Unfortunately 94.1 seems to be going in the shock jock direction.  Oh well, I guess they know what is going to get them advertisers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
