<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7911</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diary of Donna Redd [Part 1] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last week I was returning home from the bar, it was close to my apartment so I usually walked there. I had some chat with my friends while we gulped down some glasses of fizzing alcohol; it was normal, thats what we normally did. But that day we had a couple extra glasses so after I left the bar I was having a hard time keeping myself balanced and my vision was getting blurred out with every step I took. I was tired and I wanted to reach home as soon as possible. I was conscious enough to walk that small distance from the bar to my apartment.

I had to pass a graveyard. It was dark and silent; the cold winds blew with the dust as the moon shone brightly above me. It was awkwardly silent, only my footsteps echoed through the dark street and the hollow sound of winds.  As soon as I came close to the entrance of the graveyard thick grey clouds obscured the moon and it only added to the darkness that hovered all around me. Then, I heard something, something that sent chills down my spine, I heard a girl call out my name.

Daniel 
It was soft, like a whisper on a wind, like a spirit. 

Just my thoughts, its my mind, nothing else I told myself and I kept walking. 

After I took a few more steps, I heard her again, Its me, Daniel, the same spine chilling tone, like a whisper with shades of malice in it, and this time I recognised the voice, it was someone whom I wish I had no memory of. My blood froze with terror and I started walking faster and louder. 

You cant escape, you cant forget about me, this time it was not a whisper, it was louder and scarier, my heart started hammering, her cry had wrath in it and it shook me, that wrath wanted me dead, just like her. 

I started running. 

You cant run away

You cant hide

Your death is at bay

Its going to be a fun ride

She sang. I was panting, I heard footsteps behind me. Oh my god! Is she here? Is she following me?
I looked back and I saw nothing but an empty dark street and as soon as I turned my head back again I saw a still and stiff dark figure in a cloak, I dashed into it and fell down on the cold ground. My head was already spinning because of the drinks and now it was aching, I took a few seconds to come back to my senses and then I stood up and I saw nothing, that dark figure vanished, there were no more whispers. But then when I saw what lay next to my foot on the ground I was taken aback and almost fell down again.

There in front of me on the ground lay the diary of Donna Redd. The very first thought that came to my mind was to abandon the diary and leave the place, but I knew that it was of no use as I had to take the diary with me cause she has come back with her game, the very same game I started five years back, if I lose then I die and the only way to win the game was through the diary, so I had to take it with me.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then, we learned one thing today, not to click on links that can't be trusted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another link...hmmm...something's fishy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
