<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5081</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said there's money to be made, and I know that the market is small, and I never said that funding VR games is bad. What I am questioning is the statement that "Oculus is pushing VR further". 

I don't want to drag this further. Oculus is pushing *their* agenda and *their* hardware. That much is clear and it's perfectly fine being a private company. But they're not pushing the VR market, their pushing their HMD.

Regarding the fact that we have devs that got into VR "Only because Oculus gave them money", again, I have no stats for this, and your logical conclusion does not provide any tangible data - it's your own conclusion,but it's not backed up by any official statistic. 

So I'm saying that the statement "Developers got into VR only because Oculus gave them money" is false until proven otherwise with tangible data.

EDIT: a line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It works with HOTAS (at least mine, Logitech thrustmaster X) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm seriously asking, hope not to come across as snarky: do you know for sure? Are you or do you know or can you point me to a developer who said, "If I didn't have Oculus money I would not have gotten into VR"?

Also, is there a statistic about this? Like, of 100 developers for VR games, 20 entered the game thanks to Oculus money or they would have never considered the gig?

I don't have such statistics, and that's why I think the statement is up for debate! So if you do have sources and numbers, I'll be happy to retract from my position :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we talk strictly money, Valve has more money than Oculus because Valve has actual cash flow from Steam. Oculus "only" has money because they have Facebook behind.

Honestly, it's kind of a sterile discussion that's been around for a while. Maybe I'm a pessimist and I choose to see the glass half empty when it comes down to funding for your own platform, while you see it as half full because of devs getting into VR (which I don't know, because I don't have any data to back up that claim). 

Still, I won't support Oculus because their business practices are shady and their communication style is misleading. That is a fact that's not up for discussion I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Developers don't have to disclose if they took money from Valve. So we don't know.

I know exclusivity is six months, which is the only reason why I'm ok with it and understand it - I give you money, you release on my platform first. Again, I'm not judging the giving money per se, more the statement "is pushing VR forward" because not really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying funding is bad per se. Valve is giving developers loans to finish their games and push them out for **all the platforms**, not only one.

That's the bad part. Oculus is pushing their hardware, not the VR industry. They have the least market share, so if they really wanted to push VR, they'd fund games that run on PSVR or at least SteamVR. 

I think we have to thank Luckey for the vision that brought the kickstarter up and the spotlight back to this incredible tech - but it's a very sad story after the Facebook acquisition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 11:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 10:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I understand your feelings, but I urge you to be patient (pun intended!). AAA games take time, and VR has been in the wild only for less than a year. The user-base was ridicoulously small (and to some extent, still is) but now we have ~1Mil PSVR, half this number of Vives, and half this number of Oculus. 

By the end of 2017 we're gonna have the first AAA games where you'll be able to sink 50+ hours in. Hang in there buddy, that's first gen, we knew it would have been a walk in the desert (content-wise) with some great oasis around.

Also, Oculus might be funding a lot of games, but not really pushing VR further, because their business practices are shady. A company that wants to push a tech forward adopts open standards. Oculus wants to sell their HMD because in the end they're Facebook, and they want to have as many info on people as possible. To end this, Oculus games are not AAA - they're "indie" with a bit more of polish, which might be appealing in those first months, but trust me, in the long run, you'll forget all about it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 10:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, 1969 was a good year, it's a shame it was downhill from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 10:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thoughts exactly, well said! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 08:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone confirm it still needs a restart? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 08:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty cool. Graphics are unreal and so far I'm having fun and no motion sickness! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The number 3 shall not be pronounced
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know because I haven't tried it, did they try it? 

All the reviewers that got hands-on were pretty blown away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I did wait a good amount of time to play it but it became Vive compatible after the Oculus launch. Still, superb game. 

I don't know how many first-gen tech you ever had tried in your life - the pain is real waiting for content/upgrades, but VR has already a great head start compared to other first gen techs I've seen in my life, so we can't really complain :) we knew what we were getting into when we bought a Vive, right?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always something missing my friend! Having said so, I for one discovered yesterday a VR Gem which is EVE:Valkyrie. AAA graphics, gameplay, really super game. Pricey? sure, but to me it's worth it as I can see the playtime go up to ~100 hours pretty quickly! 

Future is bright!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I'm just ok at Onward :) plus I'm playing EVE:Valkyrie right now (which, albeit expensive, is frakking awesome!).

I am just a bit tired of the fact that one game has to be better than the other. While this was of course a concern in the very beginning of Vive ownership, now I think we've enough players to cover different gamestyles, so there's no need to attack one or the other! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah I'd like to know as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leggere i commenti di questo sub mi ha intristito. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok pero' il fatto che altri siano nella stessa situazione / situazione peggiore non aggiunge niente al fatto che sia un problema. A meno che non vogliamo fare mal comune mezzo gaudio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ottimo articolo de "Il Post" sulle traduzioni:

http://www.ilpost.it/2016/03/16/traduzioni-doppiaggio-film/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heaven </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As per my edit (I can't edit the title) I meant stop saying one is better than the other. They're different.

So discussing differences is perfectly ok and I do it myself as well, but saying "LOLPAvlov winzz" or "Onward beats it" is useless! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 12:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So let's actually make a post with objective differences and final thoughts on which game is suited to what style of gaming, without saying if one or the other is "better" but just highlighting their wonderful differences! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 12:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, one thing is comparing the features and gameplay - this is useful comparison - the other one is saying "This is better".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clever! Maybe I could have worded the title better, but what I mean is, compare them all they want, they're apple and oranges. Some might like one better but there isn't a winner! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 10:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't fall for these scammers. I'm OP's dad, trust *me*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 10:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on the moment. If I know I have time, then Onward. If I want to jump in a quick and dirty, Pavlov. As I've said, they're different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 10:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've watched your videos and I like the idea of yours, where everything will be breachable. Again, yours is gonna be different from both Onward and Pavlov, and while comparisons will be made of course, it won't be a direct "competitor" of one or the other. 

I understand excitement, VR has been unreal so far, but imho the attitude of "X is better than Y, full stop" is detrimental to the enjoyment/growth of the community.

To each its own :)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop comparing Pavlov and Onward. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 09:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're two different games. 

We got it, Pavlov  is fast paced and more arcadey while Onward is more slow paced and you need to actually spend a lot of time in it to learn how to be good.

There's space for both, no need to bash one or the other. Sometimes this sub is filled with comparison trends (better Raw Data or Sairento? Better RecRoom paintball or Battledome? Better Battledome or Hover Junkers? And so on).

Let's just enjoy that we have choices, can we? :) it doesn't have to be a battle of titles!

Bonus info: for people who don't know, Pavlov was a Russian physiologist known primarily for his work in classical conditioning. The famous 'Pavlovian reflex'.

EDIT: grammar.

EDIT2: Maybe I should say, stop saying one is better than the other. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 09:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool man! Can us mortals play it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We do! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that, while Joystick vs. Trackpad is currently a matter of preference, time will prove the trackpad superior, for the fine-tuning it provides and customisation options. 

The current Touch controllers are very good ergonomically speaking, but you can see they're Gen 1 (they needed to port the consumers from a known  device - gamepad - to a totally new one). 

I'm sure Touch Gen2 it's gonna have trackpads, as Vive Wand Gen2 is gonna have open/close hand sensor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  for a suprise

Yeah but tracking man. That's the real deal. We know HMDs are gonna become better and better, the real *wow* idea of the Vive is how precise tracking is. No wonder PSVR will use something similar in the future! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HYPE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God I was worried too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 09:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be so reasonable on reddit!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can send you a copy of my book. For free.

Check it out [here.] (https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/31568483-of-life-death-aliens-and-zombies) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 13:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God. Number 9. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 12:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/floorplanbot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FloorPlanBot, help me! (big living/office redesign) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 12:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 07:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there! Thanks for answering and congrats for the app!

I've seen it and used it, but I can apparently make only rectangular  rooms - I've my living room which is like two squares overlapping in one corner, making it irregular.

Is there any way to make irregular rooms?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool,thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VR Home - can I create / import custom houses? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kudos to the dev for the app, it's pretty funny already, and if he keeps updating it, it's gonna be legendary :)

I've seen that I can create a standard rectangular room, but I was wondering if I could create a proper house to map mine 1:1. 

I'm in the middle of changing the furniture's placement and would love to test-run it in VR!

Anyone knows if that works / how it works / is it planned?

thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup the answer is fine. I was trying to give perspective to your comment after the answer :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It didn't load it yesterday, it works today. Looking forward to seeing more of it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Story is pivotal for me! I hope you guys will satiate my thirst! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 10:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it should be nice to be abe to tag the players - i.e. Veteran, private, commander etc - so you know what you're getting into, or can balance the teams.

Onward has a great community, but I'm starting to see a behaviour where more experienced people are giving shit to other players and are not talking to them, which is sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 10:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe OP lives on the beach and doesn't want to buy stuff. Which is a pretty valid argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 09:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Thanks for sharing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't seem to play the video! :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Voyager apart (which contains the exact position of Sol) our radio signals would be too weak/noisy to pinpoint exact location.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detached is out with tracked controllers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link:http://store.steampowered.com/app/436230/

The devs made a post about the game being available on Oculus Store. Steam page says controllers are supported. 

For whatever reason, I can't seem to buy it!

Anyone tried it?

Edit: added some info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely a great time to be alive! In 20 years we'll have who knows what tech, possibly a starter colony on Mars, hyperloop travel - but: my feet will still stink! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still, we assume that another advanced civilization uses radio frequencies - they might be using something else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know they called it the Dark Forest theory! It is indeed explained in the book by the same name by Liu Cixin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They know a rough position, not enough to pinpoint us. the voyager, on the other hand, has the exact earth coordinates referenced with the closest 13 pulsars of our quadrant (if I recall correctly - please correct me if I'm wrong!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What /u/messisfoot says!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We could definitely point our radio telescopes towards that and listen, but let's not get out hopes up ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game theory (and prominent scientists) suggest otherwise. Better not to broadcast our position. 

The universe is a Dark Forest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fine-tuning and options that a trackpad provides is technically superior to a thumbstick, and that's why Valve selected the trackpad as an option.

I'm sorry to hear it doesn't work for you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, there's some pre-made ones that are already pretty cool, but if you do hang out in a space like that one for more than just a dip, you'll definitely want to customise your avatar as much as possible.

I like AltSpace VR, but I think VRChat has a more Cyberpunk feeling to it - it seems like a early version of the OASIS from the book Ready Player One.

I was looking into making the Avatar myself as well :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same! I'm playing Dishonored 2 (I loved the first one), but it feels boring. I can't seem to play any first person game on flatscreen anymore. 
I have on queue Telltale Batman, MadMax, Mass Effect - but if I have more than 30 minutes to spare, I'll fire up VR even just to hang out in VRChat.

the RecRoom quest has been the most fun I've had with videogames since I played Duck Hunt back in the days.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a writer and would love to help, given the right team/setting. PM me if interested! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> some areas should be cached automatically after you visit them - that, or Google Earth VR is hogging my HD with 4GB of nothing :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, the pleasantness of strangers on the Internet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the club!. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet, but it'll be out soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. However he was talking about latency and refresh rate and resolution/DPI. 

The main tech is AMOLED and the mura effect is a direct consequence of having to pass electricity over the pixels at all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if they use the same tech for the panels, then it's gonna be present </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, the electric engine is old! :)

The problem of its non-adoption until now was, of course, production and storage of energy over long distances.

Wait... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 12:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 10:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you add to the list "all the people that voted Trump"?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 10:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Netflix executives are held captive and that's their way of trying to tell the wide public they need to be saved! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 10:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more I think about it, the more I believe AR is gonna be very detrimental if used in everyday situations. The sense of being present, which is already altered so much by constant notifications from your smartphone, social networks etc is gonna fade even more. we're gonna be ever-connected, tied to a digital now which is different from the real now. We'll be with friends in a place, but we'll be looking at notifications from "friends" from another place. 

I had a smartwatch and sold it after ~1 year - this tether to my smartphone was more detrimental than useful.

On the other hand, AR for specialistic jobs is gonna be awesome - surgeons, mechanics, engineers, being able to cross-reference information directly in their field of view, amazing! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 10:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he would create a stone-walled garden, tied to its own hardware, but it would be totally different from Oculus. 

Apple would create a proprietary SDK, with a proprietary game engine which would receive regular updates. The HMD would be plug and play, and the experience would be top notch.

Then you'd need to shell out a lot of money for the Apple VR HMD SE Pro every year, but that's another story :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 10:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. We're looking at smartphone gen1 - expensive, kinda slow, but mind-blowing. 

Fast-forward to 4-5 years, I can't imagine the quality of VR headsets / content! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 10:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game alone, maybe not. 

But Onward, Arizona Sunshine, RecRoom, The Solus Project, Elite:Dangerous, The Gallery:Call of the Starseed, Vertigo, Budget Cuts...

VR is "expensive" but it's something so unreal that (for me) it's worth it already.

Plus, Fallout 4 VR... :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, VR telephones you into another world, but AR creates a bigger separation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I think you're right, I'm sure they'll apply reasonable pricing, both for old and new owners.

Having said that, it's a matter of developers time - they'll price the game accordingly to how much time they sunk into it. After all, those devs would be working on the next $60 game if they weren't working on VR's wet dream ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not judging, just asking for options. What if I had only one arm? That would make the game unplayable. 

Simple as that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might be a full-priced release, and within reason. I mean they are reworking the whole game mechanics, tweaking the physics, for a niche market. 

Even so, there's no reason to complain. You bought your Fallout, you got what you paid for. No taking advantage of. 

To me, it would be like complain if I owned a PS4 game and had to pay full price for the Xbox version. 

They might do a paid DLC for the existing customers, but it wouldn't expect it to be cheap anyway!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did the same calculations! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the devs see this - please do implement more locomotion options! Locking your game to one option only greatly reduces the enjoyment of the community. Look at Arizona Sunshine (the devs promptly implemented trackpad locomotion) etc.

PC gaming is all about options :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cool, thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! Honestly, if I were a dev, I would smooth out the game dynamics as much as possible, create a basic story-line (2-4 hours of gameplay) and maybe a "wave mode", and release it for any price between 19.99 and 29.99. 

No Early Access, just super-smooth, with the promise of a free co-op multiplayer DLC if the game sells well enough.

At this point, you can then expand the storyline with paid DLCs, and bring it to a 15-hour-story game with multiplayer, co-op etc for a total of 50/60 bucks, which honestly is super honest.

I would love to hear what are some Devs thoughts on my plan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this game about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't be envious, working without a boss it's not for everyone. A lot of people burn out because their sense of responsability goes way, way up if there's no one to tell them what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 40$ is a right price for me for a high quality VR game, given the current state of the market. I've paid this price for Arizona Sunshine, would pay again for high quality content! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Murphy bed is your solution </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Locomotion options? 

(it looks great! If it has a solo campaign with 5-7 hours of playtime and the price is right it's an instabuy) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VR port =/= VR Game.

RE7 is the only VR game listed here. Alien Isolation, FO4 in VR were gimmicks. That's why Bethesda is taking time to re-build FO4 for VR. VR is not just stereoscopic view, it's the whole rommscale/controller/mechanics combo. You need to rework a lot of your game to make it work in VR. I'm actually impressed that FO4 was announced for VR, it shows that the medium is here to stay.

If Bethesda released it as a new game for $60, they'd insta-sell to 90% of the Vive population which is ~420k people. This equals to 22 Million dollars roughly. 

If they go the rout "you need original game + 30$ DLC add on" they'd still make 11 Million dollars + new sales of an "old" game. 

That's good money, so this will show other AAA studios that VR is already a sustainable market for small hits. But it takes time. 

2017 is gonna be a good year; 2018 VR is gonna become "mature" for a more widespread adoption. 

2020, we'll have OASIS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so tempted to buy this, but I game mostly alone (and sometimes with 1 friend), would I have fun anyway? OR is multiplayer strictly mandatory? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same - you should try RecRoom Quest Mode, it's super funny. 

Also, VRChat has some interesting aspects to it (it "feels" very cyberpunk) and there's a couple of shooting games but if you're trained with Onward people are gonna hate you because you'll kill them all the time :)

Looking forward to Fallout4 VR! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup if you do it for Elite, then you can reduce in-game SS to 0.65 and up SteamVR to 1.7/1.8 (equals 1.2 SS). I did that a while back and yes the clarity is much higher.  

The suggestion implies that Steam SS is better than the E:D engine one. 

It's a while I don't fly my Eagle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude! Now what does mine say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HTC Vive is HMD of choice for for 24% of devs (up from 6% last year); 40% of PC devs are planning a VR game (GDC data) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 12:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 12:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 11:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which means you're always in reprojection. 

Which is fine if you don't mind it, but it's not perfect. I have a 970 and supersampling is off the table :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 10:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Starvr has impressive specs. Can't wait to see some.reciew/comparisons, but I'd wager Vive 2.0 (mid2018?) would feature similar specs. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 10:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's pre-fab, do you know what company did this? Or it's a totally self-built project? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! BTW, it looks sick af ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks guys, it makes sense. I'm actually waiting for a 1080ti :) still, I believe that to help widespread adoption of VR, optimisation and inclusion for "lower" end cards is pivotal! Please do work on optimisation as much as you can! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask you how's the performance? I have a 970 and lately most of the games I'm trying are badly optimised - so much so that I asked three refunds in one day. 

I know 970 is the entry level and I plan to upgrade, but plenty of games are well optimised and run smoothly at low settings. I hope you'll have a 'performance mode' for us entry level guys,smooth performance = take my money! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the complexity in Onward is the strategy part. Newbies just go in and start running and shooting and they get killed in less than 60 seconds. 

It takes a bit to understand that every movement has to be calculated or you'll die. Luckily the community is great so if someone really wants to learn, they just need to tell they're new and people will take care of it. 

On a side note, there's some usual players with a rifle stock that are very good at running around and killing everyone before getting killed. They're like the commandos. I am truly amazed by their aim and ability to spot me from the other side of the map. 

Time to make a NoobTube! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think supersampling helps a lot, especially in Elite:Dangerous.

Of course this gen will never have the resolution quality of even a 1080 monitor. But honestly, I believe that the sense of immersion makes up for it. AAA games will just add polish (can't wait for Fallout).

Side note: I like cars but even racing Sims in VR don't do it for me. Project Cars I've abandoned soon, while Elite kept me playing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, I don't play MilSim  games, never did. It's the community that made me come back all the time. 

I'll be in later. Hit me up if you see me (DarioKan) and please remember to always keep open comms with your teammates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
