<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4797</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay and so? You seem like you are making "argument winning statements" to somebody these isn't having that argument.

If your are trying to drop a bombshell that once in a while an innocent person is killed or executed, I'm well aware.

I'm not saying it doesn't happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No i'm not fine it. I would imagine not many or any people are
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supposedly none really aside from being an actual *death sentence to die for your crimes.

Edited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supposedly none really aside from being an actual sentence to die for your crimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the reality of it? Yes this is a thing that happens. 

Am I okay with it? No not particularly, i'd seek reparations from the state if it happened to a member of my immediate family member.

But i'd like to think that as we move forward and that the more technologically advanced less innocent people will convicted of crimes they didn't commit. 

Not perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people deserve to die for crimes committed against innocent American citizens.

In broad strokes, child rapists, mass murderers, terrorists, serial killers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The General on the ground made the decision to use MOAB not Trump.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile the VEEP and his wife and kids are going to Seoul, Tokyo, Jakarta and Sydney to meet with Foreign leaders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  she used noise to blast at reporters to keep them from hearing what she was saying. 

She or the people that put on the event and were paying for it didn't want anybody who wasnt paying to be there to hear anything?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because /u/CristDied4You is obviously making comments with an agenda, this is evidence by what they are saying and the account age and karma are indicators of certain types of users, be it troll or bot IMO.

I am suggesting that this user based on the information i see has an agenda they are trying to spread by trying to suppress legitimate news or criticism of this ignorant Congressman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just be the longest serving congressman in the U.S. House of Reps, be a champion of defense, especially the Marines and Navy, throughout 2 world wars and chairman of the house armed services committee. 

Sounds a bit safer than having to die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 11:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rolltide.al </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 11:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a 7 hour account with negative karma.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 11:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Endgadget and Ars Technica, two major tech websites aren't real news sources for tech news and political commentary including like this?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I would not have wasted my click.

OH NO A SINGLE CLICK! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like having sex with his mother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breaking news is just new news that is coming out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean going from a Rep in Kansas on some committee to CIA director is a massive jump in intelligence he has access to and what he really knows.

I think he changed his mind, i think anybody who goes from those jobs to the other and basically see's the other side of the coin would </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Wolf Blitzer is their breaking news anchor.

Shep Smith does it for Fox and Brian Williams does it for MSNBC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Hagrid towering over Dobby the house elf](https://gdb.voanews.com/5561ACF5-7BA8-4420-9E1D-90E42C655377_cx0_cy4_cw0_w1023_r1_s.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leonardo DiCaprio on stilts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me know when we have more facts about what happened. I don't react to things like this based on my feelings on what i think happened.

I like to know what actually happened first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It stands to reason that dropping the largest non-nuclear weapon we've ever dropped on the region is indiscriminate a

So why are you overreacting based on 0 evidence of anything other than a big bomb was dropped in a 2,000 square mile province of a country.

I find such ovverreaction based on a 1 sentence news report ridiculous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Indiscriminately

You realize that ridiculous hyperbole and overreaction does more harm than good? And frankly makes you look exceptionally ignornant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   in an indiscriminate fashion

How do you that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucked up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so whats the problem then? enemy of my enemy is my friend right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is al-Qaieda fighting ISIS in Syria? Like the "enemy of my enemy is my friend" is a true statement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so what's your point?

You're all pissy that there is a theory or a conspiracy that Trump conspired with Russia?

Are you going to ignore all the other "Russia thing(s)" about Trump and Trump people that as a public official we have the right to know if he expects to be a leader?

The only conspiracy is the Trump himself colluded with Russia or had contact there is no proof only speculation of that. But there is plenty of proof Trump officials had contact with Russia by way of Russian officials and lied about it.

Why did they lie about these contacts? Why can they just be honest about literally anything?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Russia thing is a conspiracy theory

What about it is a conspiracy?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the media baseball team The NYT and WaPo are the pitcher and catcher. Maddow and Tapper are your 1st basemen and shortstop. Shep is all the way out in right field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but with all the new pressure

Is it all that new though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why do you think that would have happened in NY?

NY is well known for the amount of closed doors it has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Double down syndrome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tillerson and Putin never were going to have a discussion meeting in front of the press in the first place.

The discussion is always behind closed doors. The handshake and meeting was what everybody was waiting for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael Steele leaks stolen steel into Lake Michigan tributary  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> should be laying groundwork 

We can't though. Christie will just close that piece of infrastructure too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does she meant the Holocaust Center? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Child birthing hips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is SUNY Buffalo.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was too raise money for scholarships and stuff too. And this year some outlets are bringing journalism students instead of celebrities due to Trump's attacks on the media.

Also I figure easy way to raise money is to  get rich people there.

I don't get the reason if complaining about industry people doing something to have fun with other industry people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robert Bentley was more disliked.

And well... He's not governor anymore so yep just now Christie is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Russia is the Russian Federation made up of Russia and various other small republics that make up the landmass.

Chechnya is probably the most well known of these republicans due to it's past history of war and violence.

While yes it's technically part of Russia just like New York is part of the United States but Chechnya did something just in Chechnya independent of all the other states, republicans and regions of Russia.

I think they specfically say Chechnya because of this reason and that people have heard of this place before just as in the past week headlines have read "New York makes public school tuition free for students" rather than "United States makes public schools tuition free for students."


That's my thinking and why i would do the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> woah, thats like super eerie and kinda scary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Kushner lied in his TS clearence forms that's a huge deal

That was before the strike, those articles were sent out. My RSS feed got them. I saw it Reddit and facebook shared there, it was covered on at least CNN and MSNBC and i'm positive of.

 A US comressman conspired with the Whitehouse to stop a house investigation into the Whitehouse

Literally like 2 weeks of news coverage, covered the day he stepped down too, again before the strike. I know everybody covered that, shared online everywhere.

A Russian hacker was arrested in Spain today.

Yes and now what? From just the page on reddit it confuses and makes no sense to me and i'm very technologically literate i would say. 

But you sayd 0 articles popped up about the Russia prob, but is the hacker in Spain deal about the Russia probe or not about the Russia probe?

Did that not pop up on your "dashboard?"

Are your complaints more that the tv news networks haven't given ample time to that story today rather than it being on your "dashboard" even though i presume you saw it somewhere, on reddit or wherever else.

IMO with the Russian hacker in Spain, it seems to be the connections may run deep to other people and to the layman person would be rather complex for those who don't "get tech" aka older and or just technologically illiterate folks. So i think in that regard media people need to   simplify the story some way. To be like "Okay a Russian hacker was arrested in Spain. Why does Bobby in middle america need to know about this, why should he care about this, etc etc."

In that regard, it's not as simple for "mainstream" outlets i feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reported for Spam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want /u/RadBadTad and /u/the_rickiest_rick to know that due to you obnoxious behavior and nothing else I've reported YOU to the admins of Reddit.

You are breaking site wide rules for Spamming

https://reddit.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/articles/204536499 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need realize or at least acknowledge that more people in the USA will care more about the United States launching weapons into another nation than Devin Nunes stepping down from the committee.

For example i i dont understand why you are incapable of giving an inch or even bothering to see the other side. Do you believe that youre opinions are the only correct ones on this matter or something? Since you refuse to come halfway and i'll have to waste time either trying to drag it out of you or do the work for you.

So instead of doing any work, engaging in any worthwhile discussion you are more intent on hurling insults like a child.

If you can't be bothered to try to understand why something is the way it is and would rather resort to insult and shooting down first hand experience from people who are trying to explain it you, than you are not worth anybody's time in this discussion, argument or any future ones.

When you are ready to drop the hyperbole and the bullshit i'll be here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you like Russia probe articles about then?

More opinion pieces or something or reporting of facts that take time to uncover?

How will you react when Congress goes on recess and the hearings dont happen for a few weeks?

Will you complain then about no articles then as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your entire argument hinges on not giving any time to Nunes stepping down and the fact is that there was an entire day between news stories, you're argument is weak.

You lied about the time table, something easily verifiable for you.

Nunes stepping down from the Russia investigation was given all the news it needed. 

Did he step down? Yes.

Why? Because of xyz

Who is replacing him? These guys

There is no more information, story over. Lets wait for the investigation to continue.

There are far more important things in the world going on than the guy stepping down. It's not as big a deal overrall as some redditors like to make it seem. It seems like a big deal or like the biggest news story in the world because this is an echo chamber.

It was a big story, it was given the time it deserved and everybody was caught up and moved onto the next important world event.

Everything you question was discussed when the event was in the news cycle. If you missed it, you missed, you can seek out those opinions if you wish but that is on you. Do not blame anybody but yourself for not getting yourself up to speed.

It's 2017, the information is right there. I work at a major media outlet and i cannot stand lazy people who cant be bothered to seek out information they miss and blame everybody else for it.

Nunes stepping down was given the time of day it was deserved for the impact it had overall to the grand scheme of things. 

Neither side is perfect, media or the consumers. But as reddit finds out time and time again, not everything that is treated as biggest story on earth here is the biggest story out in reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well, about 5 minutes before the attack, Nunes recused himself from the HIC and Gowdy is supposedly taking his place.

Well that was an easily debunked lie:

APRIL 6TH (MORNING) - CNN Report tweets statement that Nunes if off and Gowdy is in

Source: https://twitter.com/jimsciutto/status/849981518269296641/photo/1

APRIL 7 (EVENING) - Morning Joe Producer tweets NBC News: US military has launched more than 50 missile strikes on al-Shayrat military airfield near Homs, Syria

https://twitter.com/JesseRodriguez/status/850154418486038528

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly if there is no new public news there is nothing to report or talk about beside the same thing over and over.

This goes for anything, if there is nothing new after a week or two it will fall out of the mainstream news discussion until new information comes to light that makes the conversation worth having again.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And i have reports saying Pentagon officials cannot confirm this story.

Really your quoted line should also be embolded as well.

There is no proof to anything here that isn't circumstantial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One blatantly pushed a democrat agenda and frames their stories to make that agenda seem to be the correct one.

One blatantly pushes a conservative agenda and frames their stories to make that agenda seem to be the correct one.

There is no false equivalency. If you are a right-winger who wants their opinions reaffirmed you go to Breitbart.

If you are a left-wing person who wants their opinions reaffirmed you go to Shareblue.

If you are any person that whats a news report of what happened with as little bias as possible, you do not go to these two places, period.

Shareblue might not have the vitrolic hate that Breibart has but let us not pretend one is better than the other. They are both bottom of the barrel "news sources" for people who want their opinions reaffirmed. Same for all the facebook pages that do the same b.s.

There is little difference between the two and where they are different, it doesn't matter to the point of the argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a Russian-made fighter jet bombed the hospital in what American officials believe was an attempt to cover up the usage of chemical weapons.

Is the Syrian airforce made up of jets that are all Russian/Soviet made aircraft?

Couldn't it have also been Syrian air force? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's argument is clearly based in content not fixes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should find out by this point how many EO's Obama signed compared to how many Trump has signed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subtle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maverick Garland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  action on a Supreme Court nomination must be put off until after the election campaign is over."

**The campaign ended on Nov 8.**

Biden proposed this idea because with everybody campaigning and dealing with the election it would be easier to wait until the election was over.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 13:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [Protests in Bolvar Province After Election Fraud Claims](http://normangeestar.net/2017/04/08/protests-in-bol-var-province-after-election-fraud-claims/)


##**FAKE NEWS WEBSITE**


DOMAIN IS REGISTERED IN UKRAINE!

https://whois.icann.org/en/lookup?name=normangeestar.net


==========

THE REAL NORMANGEE STAR'S WEBSITE IS DOT COM, NOT DOT NET

https://www.normangeestar.com/


=============

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case you were wondering if Andrew Cuomo was going to run for President or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus all these tasty taxes 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Play War Pigeons or Domination to get those melee kills.

I took me a few days each of playing to get all the kills for the new melee weapons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes Harry Reid's letter make all that more sense. They all had the dossier long before Buzzfeed published it. They knew what was going on long before it was a massive public story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on mobile but I can expand on some of you want when I get home soon. There are also more that I listen to but is say these are my favorites

This is news and politics

Pod Save America
Pod Save The World
Lovett or Leave It
The Axe Files

This is facts and history.

Whistlestop
Election College
Presidential --this one is over 
No Such Thing As A Fish
Backstory


This is Design

99% invisible
20k Hertz
The Sound Show
The Urbanist

Misc

I was the too
Gastropod
The Allusionist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Casuals and normies will be the death of us all  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like when anonymous people post on reddit and expect credit when is posted elsewhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McMaster will be on Fox News Sunday tomorrow so i expect them to discuss this further and get him on the record on tape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what's more ignorant...

You making it seem like it wasnt a thing 

Or people making it the only thing why she lost. Considering nobody talking to you of saying it's the main reason I'm going with the later.

The fact that you seemingly cannot move an inch on this subject and that you are right and everybody is wrong, there is no middle ground is exceptionally obnoxious.

Do you know why media didn't talk so much about Clinton's look? She's spent 20 years trying not to bring authentic l attention to it, not responding to bullshit about it, dressing the way she had dressed for years.

Yet somehow you manage to essentially complain the media shit on Trump's looks, that more people publicly shit on his looks.

Do you know why? Because it's been shown that Trump shits on the way people look. He seemingly doesn't care or mind doing it to others and receiving it from others. It's basically the treating others the way you want to be treated or least bring about to take what you dish out.

It's perfectly reasonable and true that people haven't liked Clinton because she's a women, people won't outright say it but pretending that it didn't help facilitate the dislike it hatred is as nave as saying Obama's skin color didn't play a part, consciously or subconsciously.
 
What your are basically doing is telling a women who has first hand experience seeing and being on the receiving end of misogny and telling her it didn't matter. That is astoundingly tone deaf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 15:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easily.

Not her fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 15:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's poor writing because it's a fake news website based out of Ukraine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 15:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ##**FAKE NEWS WEBSITE**


DOMAIN IS REGISTERED IN UKRAINE!

https://whois.icann.org/en/lookup?name=normangeestar.net


==========

THE REAL NORMANGEE STAR'S WEBSITE IS DOT COM, NOT DOT NET

https://www.normangeestar.com/


=============
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 11:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But she would make such a good progressive VP in 2020 right?

Please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing i can so easily find which state senators are on the fence, are for it, are against it.

Very Helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this a had thing?

Should something have not been done in response to illegal chemical warfare on civilians? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because threats against POTUS aren't the basis of the lawsuit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ##**THIEF JUSTICE OF THE SUPREME COURT, NEIL GORSUCH**

##**THIEF JUSTICE OF THE SUPREME COURT, NEIL GORSUCH**

##**THIEF JUSTICE OF THE SUPREME COURT, NEIL GORSUCH** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thief Justice of the Supreme Court, Neil Gorsuch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so wholesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its also not a bus its a Lada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vegetable?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody should bet on the Nazi blaming the Jew.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yess that's the word, yeah social science. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, if I'm attacked by an ignorant comment I'll explain myself fully and clearly.

I'm happy to engage and explain but attempting to paint any comment I make in any other light than that which I intended is unacceptable to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's not politics than what is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh no I didn't.

This is a joke. I understand that there are some reddit users will see a comment about Hillary and Trump that knocks them both but just see see red about Hillary.

You should loosen your collar.

You are aware that Trump is winning the reader to the bottom and Hillary lost with the most votes.

They finally have something in common. They're the biggest losers in presidential politics.

Maybe y'all ought not take shit so fucking seriously. 

Is hilarious that y'all are so up tight about Hillary that somebody who wholeheartedly supported her can't make a joke without some over zealous folks freaking the hell out over it. Chill.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your point?

You are the word  Hillary and your get triggered or something?

You see a joke about Hillary and I'm some Donald dick sucker?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like Hillary.

They are the biggest losers in presidential politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were always going to repeal Obamacare but you know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He edited his comment. It originally said Trump should watch his children "wither and die" from cancer. 

Why are you lying?

I didn't edit anything.

My comment originally said what it still says now.

This has absolutely nothing to do with being a conservative and everything to do with being out of touch and not caring about the harm one's policies will do to the citizens the President is supposed to govern.

If he doesn't fucking get it that people will suffer under these policies. Maybe he's stupid or blind to facts or just doesn't care. If he's doesn't care, if the President does not care that his policies will cause more suffering, harm and bad to people than good than he deserves to suffer.

*Here is an actual edit*

Yes, i hope something horrible befalls the President's family so then maybe he will fucking understand and have some god damn sympathy. Not because he's a republican or a conservative but because he is a poor excuse for a human being. For all the shit things he's done or said to or about people and for the policies he will inact that will hurt people, he deserves the karma for leading a horrible life.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they shouldn't. You need to pick your battles, thats why they are going to filibuster Gorsuch but all the Democrats save for Blumenthal voted to proceed Rod Rosenstein to a floor vote for Dept. Atty Gen.

Whats more important? A lifetime appointment to the court or the appointment of the Depty Atty Gen who couldn't say whether he would get a special prosecutor for the Russia investigation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and no. In general nobody does, but specifically here i disagree.

He doesn't understand the magnitude and the severity his policies have on people. He either doesn't get it or he doesn't give a shit.

If he wants to harm people for the sake of "small government" he needs to understand what its like to bury a child or know what its like to have a loved one with an incurable disease. Knowing there is absolutely nothing, no amount of money or prayer or goodwill that will ever make it better.

If he wants to make the American people suffer, he deserves to suffer too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And we think the national security adviser to Obama and the former UN Ambassador didnt have a good reason?

It didn't have to do with Russia. If they looked to be undermine the current administration's policies while Obama is still in Office, they needed to know that. Because that is not allowed.

I'd sugguest to everybody reading this to listen to the most recent POD SAVE AMERICA where people directly involved in the Obama administration discuss what Susan Rice could have done and why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump deserves to watch his kids wither away to cancer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The National Security Adviser unmasking names is not illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats; the party of states rights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really hit all the talking points there huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm starting to think page isn't a mastermin

His interview on Chris Hayes should have confirmed that for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We both know the independent prosecutor will be Jared </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keane 2020

....AND MY AXE^^elrod  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spicer: Betsy Devos' had a minor role in the Trump cabinet.

Press: But she was secretary of education.

Spicer: Yeah, exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know something is going to drop when Trump tweets

Because you know exactly what happened.

Washington Post reporters contacted the White House, Sean Spicer probably or the Communications/Press Office for a comment. Talked with Trump or WH people passed it on to Trump, he said no comment or didn't want to discuss it and then thinks about it knowing when it will be published and tweets about it the day or days before to control the news cycle.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is also a relevant fact to life:

##**THERE IS NO PROOF OR VALIDITY TO TRUMP'S CLAIM THAT OBAMA WIRETAPPED HIM OR """WIRETAPPED""" HIM** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, meme so spicy it could be press secretary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need 60 votes to end debate, aka the filibuster, and bring the nomination to the floor for a vote.

Since the Republicans currently hold 52 Senate seats, it means the GOP needs eight Democrats simply to schedule a final vote. (After the 60-vote threshold is reached, the nomination itself needs only 51 votes to pass.)


Given the degree of partisan polarization in the Capitol and in the country today, most observers expect it will be hard for Republicans to secure the backing of eight Democrats. So a procedural shortcut known as the "nuclear option" stands as an alluring alternative, since it would allow Senate Republicans to sidestep the 60-vote threshold for Supreme Court nominations.


The nuclear or constitutional option is a parliamentary procedure that allows the U.S. Senate to override a rule or precedent by a simple majority of 51 votes, instead of by a supermajority of 60 votes. The option is invoked by the presiding officer of the United States Senate ruling that the validity of a Senate rule or precedent is a constitutional question. The issue is immediately put to the full Senate, which decides by majority vote. The procedure thus allows the Senate to decide any issue by majority vote, regardless of existing procedural rules, such as current Senate rules specifying that ending a filibuster requires the consent of 60 senators (out of 100) for legislation, and 67 for amending a Senate rule.


In 2013, Democrats, led by then-Majority Leader Harry Reid of Nevada, finally gave in to frustration over the refusal by the chambers Republican minority to approve President Barack Obamas appointees, notably appeals-court judges. With the support of 52 Democrats, Reid succeeded in deploying the nuclear option, easing passage of several of Obamas executive-branch and judicial nominees.

Reid limited the scope of his maneuver to appointments below the level of Supreme Court justice; for the Supreme Court, traditional filibuster and cloture rules would still apply. The fact that Reid left that exception is what brought us to the current faceoff.


Going nuclear is not changing the filibuster overall. It's a shortcut to by pass it for the nomination of presidential appointees, Which Harry Reid first changed in 2013. To get rid of the filibuster and implement this "shortcut" all the way requires 67 yay votes, 2/3 Senate majority to fully change the rules of the senate.



http://www.politifact.com/truth-o-meter/article/2017/feb/03/6-questions-answered-about-nuclear-option-filibust/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   the new Tea Party Left

The Green Tea party </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably from behind, melee or bayonet charge

Or multiple attackers firing at it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 03:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matt and Jeff Harry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The should start The Climate Caucus.

If some reps formed a marijuana Caucus then this is possible too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got all of mine in flanking in war pigeons, switching between the m18 and the melee weapon in using to unlock the new ones.

Maybe turn the sensitivity down on the zoom your are using and take your time.

I found it all to be luck, I wasn't ever aiming for their heads instinctively except if I came up behind somebody sniping, I'd take the freebie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably defending the first sector in Verdun operations. Ive unlocked a few things from that game and gotten the weekly medals from there too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 12:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or we can just stop at James Mattis.

President Mad Dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wont be surprised if in the future Democrats try to make the National Security Adviser a Senate confirmed position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://wiki.gamedetectives.net/index.php?title=Battlefield_1

https://www.vg247.com/2017/02/21/battlefield-1-how-to-unlock-the-hidden-dog-tag-a-beginning/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should be banned under the guise of being a source that is notable for fake news and highly distorting facts passing them off as true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes Peter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is far more exciting when you misread the title as

Amish starts hashtag: 'Trumpstablishment' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of Kushner's plans are six-pointed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is going to win plain and simple. 

Have we not learned this phrase has no meaning in American politics anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright well you are dead-set on having this conversation for some reason. Not what i intended to discuss but fine, it'll be quick.

Frankly, i don't really care. I think your comment is an overreaction that the (D)s lost, whether it's Sanders or Clinton. You feel betrayed by the people, the politicians, whatever. It doesn't matter and i don't care. In the political world that is ancient history. .

There is more important things to do, to apply pressure to than worry about the delicate sensitivities of people who don't like Hillary Clinton.

If she wants to come out, speak out, be part of this supposed unified front than I am smart enough to not say no and if she has something to say, to rally the people now and for 2018 than i welcome it.

I have neither the time nor patience to deal with the what your selling, sorry.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck are you talking about? 

My initial comment was regarding

I don't hate Hillary but I personally think it would be best if she stayed in the woods for some time to come.

When I replied to you saying you had an overreaction based on

She is dead weight dragging the country down.

I don't want to waste time commenting on things that are irrelevant to what I am saying. I don't believe i could be anymore clear on that now or before. When nothing i speak of is about any specific weakness or issue Clinton had in the campaign.

Like I said, if you want to rehash the primary or talking about what Clinton's weaknesses or issue in the campaign were find somebody actually having that conversation to do it with. That was never my point or path. Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm well aware of her issues as a nominee just as much as Trump's or Sanders'.

But they specifically not relevant to this discussion and will not engage in that side conversation further.

If I wanted to rehash the Democratic primary i would be posting in /r/SandersForPresident  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats an overreaction but nothing anybody says can or will change your mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And Jill Stein had no legitimate chance of beating Donald Trump, so a vote for her wasn't a vote against Trump, it was a vote for the Greens.

Semantic b.s. excuses is what that is.

Plain and simple there were plenty of ways to vote against Trump.

Literally vote for anybody that isn't him than you think would do a better job.

but she can't give that to people without inflaming others

Literally nobody can, not in 2017.

This is politics. Adam Schiff is getting a smear campaign because of what he says about Trump by Republicans for instance.

Any Democrat that says anything will inflame others.

At a certain point you weigh the options. Is inflaming ignorant Rs and Ds worth rallying everybody else with the capacity to think critically?

Is speaking out or acting out for the greater good better than sitting idly by or quietly by while policies are rolled back or enacted that will hurt people?

I don't think so. 

Anything that can rally people now to act now and act in 2018 is what we need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   There were many people voting against Trump and the only way to do that was vote Hillary

To be clear Jill Stein was on the ballot in all 50 states

 She needs to at least give the election some time to breath.

It's been 6 months since the election.

One of the most important parts of the presidency is nearly over, the first 100 days.

How much more time does this administration and election need time to breath? 

They get the same amount of time to breath as every other administration.

From election day through the first 100 days of the administration. That's how it's been covered for a long time now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And she did, throughout the transition and much of the first 100 days.

Trump's honeymoon is over, frankly it never started.

As the former candidate she allowed for a peaceful transition of power, she did not try to undermine the election results in public comments, she has let Trump try to govern, give him the time to be President and enact or change policies.

We all have. 

But it's a continual face-plant after face-plant on issues and policy be it by the WH or the Republican congress. When it's not a face-plant it's a rollback on regulations or policies that appease the ignorant and reward the corporations or the wealthy all while trying to spin as if it will be beneficial for Joe the former coal miner.

Rallying the people to apply pressure to congressman is exactly what Elizabeth Warren and Bernie Sanders have been doing. Hillary Clinton 'ought join the likes of them now that the first 100 days of the Trump administration near their end.

To what end do you expect somebody who has the history of public servitude as a Democrat to remain silent on a Republican administration that is dismantling policies that:

A) This D supports

B) Does more harm than good, or is at least projected to do


If politics or any topic/hobby/issue is what you lived for would you be quiet because a bunch of gullible people believe everything negative they read about you all while the people in charge of your topic/hobby/issue make it worse for people and the people agree that it's not good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could but i have a very good imagination </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah its only misleading to people who want to play semantics but not to people who know what Trump means. But we all know Donald Trump doesn't have a good relationship with subtleties, semantics and speaking good.

This "thinking out loud" or "asking rhetorical questions" he'll never get an answer to are his bullshit way of throwing his weight around to rile up his base to attack people and groups to do or do not do certain things.

Lets not pretend Trump isn't asking them or telling them to stop covering Russia and do the wiretapping bullshit.

Sean Spicer does it.

Trump surrogates do it.

Trump does it. He's done it in the past, he's done it today in these tweets.

Just because he literally doesn't say "NBC stop." doesn't mean his meaning is any different, or the implications of his "question." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and Gary Cohn got a 5.6 million dollar cash bonus from Goldman in 2015

and Hope Hicks salary from Donald J Trump For President was $140k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
