<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject185</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [But do you drink?](http://static2.hypable.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/game-of-thonres-tyrion-lannister-i-drink-and-i-know-things.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use the coffee table as a raft! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://podbay.fm/show/536258179 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 07:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aS GOOD AMERIKAN ZITIZEN, AM DURE THIS IS TRUE STORY, DA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My tuxedo cat does the same thing. The phrase I use is she's "going full meerkat". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second the motion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the Mexican food is pushed out as poop, it's not sending the best. It's sending the squirts, the splatters and some... I assume, are good shits. But we are going to build a wall of TP around my asshole. AND TACO BELL IS GOING TO PAY FOR IT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Machinist planning to move to Seattle? I think you'll have some options...http://imgur.com/a/xiXh6

https://www.indeed.com/jobs?q=machinist l=seattle%2C+WA sort=date </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Housekeeper here - I changed the sheets the next morning. The rest of y'all literal mother fuckers are welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That poll may have just been a ploy to milk the faithful - 

Source code looks like the survey data not even collected, the only purpose of the page is to direct ppl to donation page. Anyone confirm? https://t.co/NxXUtUKZvK  mdash; Rogue POTUS Staff 

https://twitter.com/RoguePOTUSStaff/status/832812922434895872 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop I can only get so erect. Get to watch that and then read the next morning Trump is permanently gone? MMMM-HMMM! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And given his apparent overwhelming desire to "get even", he could stand there for a half hour calling out everyone in the room by name, saying whatever he wanted to say about them, and they would have to sit there and take it.

Some part of me - and it's a part that admittedly even I find disturbing - would like to see that. It would take a whole bottle of rotgut whiskey to get through but damn that would be fun to watch in a "Christians vs. Lions" sort of way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Hell, I'd take ~~Jeb~~ JEB! over this

FTFY - remember, that's his initials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you're seeing is a side effect of partial abortions. Some people undergo this procedure during pregnancy. The entire fetus isn't destroyed, merely the brain which, as we all know, is just for cooling the blood so is nonessential. These hot-blooded individuals then go on to promote the rights of men to tell women, well, everything - see "mansplaining" for more details on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 10:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rogue POTUS Staff says that the survey appears to be pure bullshit and is just a way to get people to donate - https://twitter.com/RoguePOTUSStaff/status/832812922434895872

 Source code looks like the survey data not even collected, the only purpose of the page is to direct ppl to donation page. Anyone confirm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm the first person to want alien life to be true.

Right there with you so I was hoping this would be worth looking at. The I saw the source was The Mirror. Yeah, no. Might as well be Weekly World News or Breitbart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that it's unpresidented just means it would fit with the trump administration perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be cool with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it will be as effective as Michael Moore demanding that the election be invalidated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not right. That's not even wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL. But, no, seriously - would you like a First Class Handbasket or will you be going to Hell coach class?

Oh, who am I kidding, all handbaskets to hell are coach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have your remedy for them feels:
http://s2.quickmeme.com/img/f4/f4dce7e45418340e76a37eff74fbb580a6b0a78757787c67d52d0bf18a3023c1.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. We are going to be seeing a bunch of political careers implode before this is over. My fondest wish is that Chaffetz is among them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This administration is running like a fine-tuned machine

The name of that machine?

The Samsung Galaxy Note 7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't say that I like Kasich - hell, it seems most of Ohio doesn't even like him - but my respect for his integrity grew 3 sizes when the news dropped that he rejected the offer. That would have been a lot of power and with the cover of, "What, I'm just the VP. Go talk to the boss if you have issues on his policies." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #ToxicTrump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But not Cheney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/R5NU9oE.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, be nice. He worked for a good 30 minutes on that zinger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  (but a pizzeria anywhere in ~~Denmark~~ the non-Muslim world would go bust REALLY fast without bacon or ham)

FTFY

SOURCE: Pigs are made of delicious meat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he can try - http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/donald-trump-russia-leaks-fake-news-claims-quote-a7584516.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we have Beyonce flanked by Adele and Lady Gaga as the Greek chorus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he's smart, he asked his senior staff who would be the best candidate for Deputy Director, promoted that person to the position, and is now deferring all decisions to the Deputy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, he'd outsource that to Russian hookers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He is probably the most incompetent government official I have seen in my lifetime.

Given your flair, I'm assuming you've dealt with CA DMV workers which makes your statement even more profound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or he'll keep doing crazy shit that gives them lots to cover thus increasing their subscriptions? 

I should buy shares in NYTimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but do they have a good place for picking up some power converters? I could use a couple new ones for these moisture vaporators. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You're aimbot sux more than yer mom, newb!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nor the brightest crayons in the shed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drumpf and Dumber </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 07:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking about that watching the news tonight. The gloves are off now, MF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 07:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone get HBO on the phone. They can get at least 3 seasons out of this easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just one of the many reasons I hate Mitch McConnell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, yes. Then I ask them to name one country which has successfully based their system of government on Libertarianism and enjoy the fireworks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rodeos? Check.

Oil? Check.

Big ass trucks? Check.

You're all cleared. YEEHAW, pardner! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was [Jeff Sessions](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/wonk/wp/2016/11/18/trumps-pick-for-attorney-general-good-people-dont-smoke-marijuana/?utm_term=.8fd917ffd5fa), our new Attorney General. Good thing he doesn't have the DEA under his purview.

[Oh, craaaap](https://www.justice.gov/jmd/organization-mission-and-functions-manual-attorney-general):
 The mission of the Office of the Attorney General is to supervise and direct the administration and operation of the Department of Justice, including the Federal Bureau of Investigation, **Drug Enforcement Administration**, Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives, Bureau of Prisons, Office of Justice Programs, and the U.S. Attorneys and U.S. Marshals Service, which are all within the Department of Justice.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ...if you make the ultimate sacrifice in defense of your nation, it may take years before your work and death is ever even acknowledged, never mind commemorated.

Exactly why the wall in CIA HQ that Donnie metaphorically pissed on while CIA workers had to stand and listen is considered sacred ground. I bet if he knew what he was going to unleash in the IC community by doing that, he... nah, trump isn't capable of self-reflection to that degree. Godspeed, Mr Drumpf. I love where this track is headed.

Sadly, though, I had the "over" on impeachment. That's $100 I'll never see again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  572.77 rubles

Shit, that's not even 8 euros. My integrity, being a rapidly dwindling resource, is worth way more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about the 1 person who you most hate. Go kill that person. When the police come to arrest you, point out that Al Capone killed a lot of people  but he wasn't arrested for that. So as long as you aren't evading taxes (what they did get Scarface for) then you shouldn't be prosecuted.

Just because someone else in the past got away with something illegal, immoral or unethical doesn't mean that everyone is excused to behave as badly as they want. If we're only going to enforce laws that no one has ever figured out how to weasel out of, then we might as well just stop having any laws at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  At this moment, we are four days away from Trump's inauguration. The FBI agents and analysts who monitored the calls, as well as some NSC officials in the Obama administration, along with a few senior Justice Department attorneys, all knew with certainty that the content of the calls contradicted Flynn's account of them. The transcript of the Dec. 30 call proved as much.

For reasons unclear to us, Comey did not believe that Flynn's misrepresentations amounted to a sufficient national security risk on January 16 to spring FBI investigators on the Trump team, or even on Flynn. Perhaps he felt that doing so right before the inauguration would have been too unseemly.

Nope, cannot for the life of me figure out what James Comey might want to shelter a high-level Trump staffer. Nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is showing how the Deep State really works </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While imagining your opponents are all cuckolded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then Ryan overdoes his workout, has an aneurysm and McCain becomes Prez. Out of loyalty, his VP pick is ... Sarah Palin.
http://ichef.bbci.co.uk/wwfeatures/wm/live/1280_640/images/live/p0/3l/cp/p03lcphh.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I didn't want to sleep tonight anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [Madeline Albright](http://static4.businessinsider.com/image/544979c469bedde52d26408b/madeleine-albright-had-the-perfect-response-to-conans-dirty-joke-about-her.jpg)

That makes me moist.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not an accident. He was briefed on a good bit of this before he left office.
http://www.cnn.com/2017/02/14/politics/donald-trump-aides-russians-campaign/index.html

President-elect Trump and then-President Barack Obama were both briefed on details of the extensive communications between suspected Russian operatives and people associated with the Trump campaign and the Trump business, according to US officials familiar with the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 19% of a half-trillion dollar oil company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And wouldn't it be a brilliant move, if that were your plan, to openly defy a decades-old arms treaty by deploying new cruise missiles explicitly prohibited by said treaty and have one of your spy ships leisurely sail up the entire Eastern seaboard right past the Capitol? Just to show the rest of the world that the US isn't going to do shit about it.

Because Putin knows Trump can't do shit with the threat of whatever is hinted at in the dossier being released. That tape is more than just a couple of whores pissing on Obama's old hotel room mattress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manafort doesn't know what every crack whore knows. All you have to do is ask, "Are you a Russian spy?" Because if they are and you ask, they have to tell you otherwise it's entrapment.

Rookie mistake there, Manafort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 23:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 23:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had the skillz to draw Trump as Klink shouting "BANNON!" at Bannon in that trademark Bob Crane bomber jacket. The Drumpf hair vs. Werner Klemper's bald head would be a challenge.

OOOh, and in the background, a young Richard Dawson in POW fatigues but in front of the Family Feud gameboard with the category "Who Has Ties to Russia" and the revealed answers are Manafort, Page, and Flynn but #1 answer is still hidden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 23:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to read the full label:

Every day mouth wash

Alcohol free

There are still days left. You need to keep washing your mouth every day. Once there are no more days left, then you will get alcohol free. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But...but.. we're not so innocent - [Dear Leader said so](http://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2017/02/05/trump-putin-oreilly-innocent-sot-harlow-sciutto-nr.cnn). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On their asses right into Leavenworth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's fragile. Very fragile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, russians paying trolls to flood social media with pro-Russia comments? [That's just crazy talk](http://www.businessinsider.com/russia-internet-trolls-and-donald-trump-2016-7)!

OK, maybe not so crazy but I'm sure they'd never [try that again.](https://www.google.com/url?sa=t rct=j q= esrc=s source=web cd=1 cad=rja uact=8 ved=0ahUKEwikzLj4vZDSAhVV92MKHVTnCFYQFggcMAA url=http%3A%2F%2Fmediamatters.org%2Fblog%2F2017%2F01%2F24%2Freport-trump-supporters-are-trying-manipulate-french-social-media-artificially-boost-far-right%2F215105 usg=AFQjCNEHZK9diX_S0zWoaRJLl7I1OB2x_A bvm=bv.146786187,d.cGc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a disservice to the article but it does include an chart of some key players and how they connect. 
http://static4.businessinsider.com/image/589e484e6e09a81c008b6931-1201/bi-graphicstrumps%20connections%20to%20russia%20v02.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, now. Maybe WH Counsel told Trump while he was watching TV and was only pretending to listen. That happens with my wife and me all the time. But then I'm not POTUS and it's less important stuff like, "My sister is coming to visit" or "Your mother died." You know, minor stuff. Not, "Your National Security Advisor's ties to Russia have been discovered and DOJ is investigating." So, different orders of magnitude but same principle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How any Mormon voted for him without a massive cognitive dissonance is amazing to me.

Which is exactly why 21% of Utah voted McMullin. They sure as Hell couldn't vote for Clinton but trump was just as bad. Yeah, throw away vote but it seems a good many Utahans voted their conscience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 09:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The word you are looking for is Breitschart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT?!? I didn't even know he was sick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I will - how much does it pay? 

/s - for anyone who needs that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At which point Tom Clancy permanently retires because there's no way he could ever top that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not easy to read but this is the best attempt at connecting the dots I've seen.
http://www.businessinsider.com/trump-russia-ties-michael-flynn-dossier-2017-2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well, this leak has accomplished what the Senate ~~Democrats~~ Republicans didn't.

FTFY. Republicans are in control of the Senate and the House.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will multiple Blue Ribbon Panels to determine why this is all Hillary's fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If [Juliette Kayyem](https://twitter.com/juliettekayyem) is right, the penalty is whatever your lawyers can bargain for in return for turning against your co-conspirators:
https://twitter.com/juliettekayyem/status/831352384001540097

Flynn is out. 

Petraeus is meeting Trump tomorrow. 

(you are welcome)

(btw, this is not over. Senate Intell should give Flynn immunity ASAP) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, just thinking how tiny it looks. 

Trump's hand, that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I volunteer to personally waterboard some drugs with the aid of this barbaric device:
https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/0/0f/Bong.svg/200px-Bong.svg.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is mental illness funny? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Under the press release, over the (presidential daily) briefs." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Bellicose statements like these (that would sound better if shouted in militaristic German)...

Best I can do [via Google](https://translate.google.com/?bav=on.2,or. bvm=bv.146786187,d.cGc biw=1920 bih=950 um=1 ie=UTF-8 hl=en client=tw-ob#auto/de/the%20powers%20of%20the%20president%20to%20protect%20our%20country%20are%20very%20substantial%20and%20will%20not%20be%20questioned.):

Die Befugnisse des Prsidenten unser Land zu schtzen, sind sehr umfangreich und werden nicht in Frage gestellt werden.

("The powers of the president to protect our country are very substantial and will not be questioned.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Jeffrey Sandusky is one of the six adopted children of Jerry Sandusky, the retired Penn State defensive coordinator whose 2011 arrest and 2012 conviction on 45 of 48 counts of child sex abuse crimes rocked the university and led to a major spotlight on pedophilia in Pennsylvania.

Headline doesn't make clear that he isn't a biological son. My money is on getting rather unpleasant details during the trial of what life was like in the Sandusky house when those kids were growing up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was OK with her stuffing in that handful of gum. But when she reached in and pulled out the half-chewed gum wad, I was simultaneously amused and revolted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 questions:

1) Are you going to be here all week?

2) Should I remember to tip my server? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jerry Sanduskys son arrested on child sex assault, porn charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean like these 2 tweets from a (purported) rogue White House staffer?

https://twitter.com/RoguePOTUSStaff/status/831130748224667648

Sanction talk is missing the big picture. Flynn tapped for a reason. Boot him, POTUS will just replace w/ another conduit to Putin.

https://twitter.com/RoguePOTUSStaff/status/831128774976602112

Regarding Flynn, he's not going anywhere. Pence/Priebus camps may hate him by now, but POTUS is committed. And they think they know why.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ivanka's ~~measurements~~ birthday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 09:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bam Ding Ow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 09:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least you aren't a literal 5-headed dragon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...we wouldn't be in this mess. So, still an imperfect world but slightly less imperfect than this one. 

OK, yeah, that doesn't exactly roll off the tongue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Holiday greetings. As one does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is your conscience... "OH HELL NO!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grazie for reminding me of a time when Bunga Bunga parties were the big scandal in world politics. Ah, simpler times, my friend - simpler times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially the 75 miles that goes through a Native American reservation. They've already indicated that they aren't at all keen on the idea.

https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2017/jan/26/donald-trump-border-wall-tohono-oodham-arizona-tribe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 07:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serious, some times the only thing that keeps me going is "OK, I'll go through this shit once and then I'm out." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, because you understand the legal system SO much better than 3 circuit court judges.

Idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda his job, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where'd you find a mannequin of Steve Bannon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "US" = Americans who put the country before their political party. But you wouldn't know anything about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just moved here 4 years ago and picked it specifically so that our daughter could go to WHS. She's hugely interested in Theater Tech and Butchart has done an amazing job with their drama program.

Plus, 130 wineries within 15 minutes doesn't hurt (until the next morning.)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be more likely if it was out here in Woodinville. We get bears wandering through all the...

OH! You mean **NSFW** [this kind of bear](http://images.fineartamerica.com/images-medium-large-5/bed-time-story-bear-pictureart.jpg) **NSFW**. My bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bear in mind that he's one of the [Keating Five](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Keating_Five). If you want someone capable of taking a principled stand on anything, you need to find a different senator because McCain ain't it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never know when your going to have a bear wander through. Just ask DeVos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
