<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8724</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Lifting His Federal Hiring Freeze </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> from the [Wikipedia ](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chemical_warfare#Nazi_Germany) article on Chemical Warfare - Hermann Gring said the reason gas was not used in Normandy had to do with horses. The Wehrmacht was dependent upon horse-drawn transport to move supplies to their combat units, and had never been able to devise a gas mask horses could tolerate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL When asked why nerve gas was not used in Normandy, Hermann Gring said the Nazis were dependent upon horse-drawn transport to move supplies to their combat units, and had never been able to devise a gas mask that horses could tolerate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spicer: Hitler 'was not using the gas on his own people the same way that Assad is doing' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. asks G7 ministers why it should care about Ukraine conflict </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eric Trump: Syria missile strikes prove there's no Trump-Russia connection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ivanka Trump encouraged my father to launch air strikes against Assad in Syria after chemical weapons attack, says Eric Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the New York Times White House correspondent woos Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump pushes laughable claim about a leading congressional Dem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 13:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eric Trump: We Might Be Here Because of Nepotism, but Were Not Still Here Because of Nepotism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell moves to change Senate rules to ensure confirmation of Trump's Supreme Court pick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert Reich: Four (or Five) grounds for impeaching Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Defends Bill O'Reilly: "He Shouldn't Have Settled" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no Google street view of that address for some reason, did they just skip some of the private streets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should Fox News Really Fire Bill OReilly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damnit... I forgot to mention their neighbors in the title, Herbert Osborn and Maxwell Osborne </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Peter Parker's address is an actual home in Queens New York, and is owned by the Parker family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today in Conservative Media: A Scarier Nuclear Option </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
