<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8373</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tamarack Peak Pac Waterproof Boot - $24 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone 6 keeps dying randomly even after a battery replacement and iOS restore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few months ago, my iPhone 6's battery level would jump all over the place and die even when at 60%+ charge. I took it into Apple, they told me my battery was at it's end, so I replaced it myself. 

After that, the battery drains normally again, no more skipping around. However, it would still die at about 40%. Then, I wiped my phone and restored iOS and then backed up my phone, but it will still die randomly. 

What else can I try?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the response. 

That laptop looks promising. I currently have a 128gb SSD in my current laptop I could just switch over into this Acer. That would work, right?

Also, how often do laptops in this price range go on sale? I'm not in a rush to buy another laptop, so I can wait for a good deal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Replacing my 5 year old laptop. Trying to decide between Chromebook(+Linux maybe) or Windows. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * **Total budget and country of purchase:** 
$350 USA (will spend a little more if it's worth the price increase) 

* **Do you prefer a 2 in 1 form factor, good battery life or best specifications to your requirements for the money? Pick or include any that apply.** 
 Good battery life, thin, and small SSD (128gb or smaller), no HDD. HDMI port

* **How important is weight to you?**
 Weight is of medium importance. I'll mainly be using it at home, but it would be nice to take it places sometimes. 

* **Which OS do you require? Windows, Linux, Mac.**
 Windows or ChromeOS/Linux

* **Do you have a preferred screen size? If indifferent, put N/A.** 
 N/A

* **Are you doing any CAD/video editing/photo editing/gaming? List which programs/games you desire to run. If you have no requirements, put N/A.** 
 No video editing, I have a dedicated desktop for that. I just need something to shop online, check emails, watch movies (local files), watch YouTube, things like that. I do very light photo editing from time to time. 

* **If you're gaming (leave blank if you put N/A above...), do you have certain games you want to play? At what settings and FPS do you want?** 
 N/A

* **Any specific requirements such as good keyboard, reliable business grade build quality, touch-screen, finger-print reader, optical drive or good input devices (keyboard/touchpad)?** 
 If possible, good, thin build quality would be nice. I don't need touch screen or fingerprint read or anything fancy like that. 

* **Leave any finishing thoughts here that you may feel are necessary and beneficial to the discussion.**
 I'm looking for light, thin, and snappy laptop that will be good for light usage. I have a dedicated video editing/gaming desktop at home, and I use my laptop for small stuff, like watching videos and shopping online. 
It seems like a Chromebook would suit my needs, but, I do watch a lot of movies on my laptop from local files (non-streaming). I don't believe I would be able to do that with the ChromeOS. I've read a bit about installing Linux on Chromebooks, but I'm not 100% sure what Linux would allow me to do exactly, since I've never used it.

Does anyone have advice on what I should be looking for? Any advice and/or recommendations are appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 02:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I built an editing rig last year with a i7 5820K using the ASRock x99 EXTREME4. 

http://www.asrock.com/mb/Intel/X99%20Extreme4/

It's got a lot of blue on the board. I'm not sure what your budget is, but it seemed to be on the lower end for x99 motherboards. I paid about $150 for it during a sale last year in November. No idea what the prices now,  but it's blue and x99 haha 

Good luck on your build!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll send him an email today and I'll keep you guys updated on what I find out! Thanks for the advice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! And yeah, I think it's all been sitting in a box for over 20 years. I just ordered some neatsfoot oil off Amazon for all the leather. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A family member passed down my grandfather's old Canons from the 1950s to me for Christmas. They're in unbelievable condition! Asking for help dating and IDing them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/w0WUf

I recently started shooting film for fun, and this Christmas, my cousin told me he had something for me, and brought out this big box that my grandfather had passed down to him in the 70s sometime. The cameras are almost in perfect condition, it's unbelievable. My mom always told me my grandfather was a bit of a perfectionist, and I guess this proves it. Apparently he took great care of all his possessions.

According to this site: http://global.canon/en/c-museum/series_search.html?t=camera s=film y2=1960 sort=old
It looks like the first camera is possibly a Canon IV or III. I can't really tell the difference. The second camera looks like some variation of the Canon II. I'm not sure about that one either.

If anyone has some info on these cameras or could point me in the right direction, I'd really appreciate it! Would there be a better subreddit for this post? (I posted to r/cameras already) I may try posting on r/vintagecameras, but that sub doesn't seem too active. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently started shooting film for fun, and this Christmas, my cousin told me he had something for me, and brought out this big box that my grandfather had passed down to him in the 70s sometime. The cameras are almost in perfect condition, it's unbelievable. My mom always told me my grandfather was a bit of a perfectionist, and I guess this proves it. Apparently he took great care of all his possessions.

According to this site: http://global.canon/en/c-museum/series_search.html?t=camera s=film y2=1960 sort=old
It looks like the first camera is possibly a Canon IV or III. I can't really tell the difference. The second camera looks like some variation of the Canon II. I'm not sure about that one either.

If anyone has some info on these cameras or could point me in the right direction, I'd really appreciate it! Would there be a better subreddit for this post? (I posted to r/canon and r/cameras already) I may try posting on r/vintagecameras, but that sub doesn't seem too active. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A family member passed down my grandfather's old Canons and accessories from the 1950s to me for Christmas. They're in unbelievable condition! Asking for help dating and IDing them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently started shooting film for fun, and this Christmas, my cousin told me he had something for me, and brought out this big box that my grandfather had passed down to him in the 70s sometime. The cameras are almost in perfect condition, it's unbelievable. My mom always told me my grandfather was a bit of a perfectionist, and I guess this proves it. Apparently he took great care of all his possessions.


According to this site: http://global.canon/en/c-museum/series_search.html?t=camera s=film y2=1960 sort=old

It looks like the first camera is possibly a Canon IV or III. I can't really tell the difference. The second camera looks like some variation of the Canon II. I'm not sure about that one either.

If anyone has some info on these cameras or could point me in the right direction, I'd really appreciate it! Would there be a better subreddit for this post? (I posted to r/cameras already) I may try posting on r/vintagecameras, but that sub doesn't seem too active. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A family member passed down my grandfather's old Canons from the 1950s to me for Christmas. They're in unbelievable condition! Asking for help dating and IDing them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently started shooting film for fun, and this Christmas, my cousin told me he had something for me, and brought out this big box that my grandfather had passed down to him in the 70s sometime. The cameras are almost in perfect condition, it's unbelievable. My mom always told me my grandfather was a bit of a perfectionist, and I guess this proves it. Apparently he took great care of all his possessions. 

According to this site: http://global.canon/en/c-museum/series_search.html?t=camera s=film y2=1960 sort=old

It looks like the first camera is possibly a Canon IV or III. I can't really tell the difference. The second camera looks like some variation of the Canon II. I'm not sure about that one either.

If anyone has some info on these cameras or could point me in the right direction, I'd really appreciate it! Would there be a better subreddit for this post? I may try posting on r/vintagecameras, but that sub doesn't seem too active. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A family member passed down my grandfather's old Canon cameras from the 1950's to me. I'm having trouble dating and IDing them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 23:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked this. Great job!

I have a question: I've never tried doing any kind of whip/pan transitions, and was wondering how they're done. Is it a matter of panning/whipping quickly at the beginning/end of your shots? Or is it mostly done in post? or a combination of both?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 06:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I've done is fix one of the downtube shifters, put new tubes and tires on it, polished some of the components and degreased/oiled the drivetrain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much should I sell my 1984 Centurion Comp TA for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 04:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/h1ypQ

(Don't judge the saddle position. I had just gotten the bike when I took this pic!)

I recently fixed up my dad's old 1991 Bianchi Virata, and have decided to part ways with my 1984 Centurion Comp TA. How much should I list it for on Craigslist and Facebook? I live in Southern California, and also right next to a college town.

The bike is 50cm, and in very good condition. Full Shimano 600 SIS groupset. The tires are Continental Ultra Sport ii's, with under 100 miles on the tires. The bike is very clean, and rides great. 

I've seen some people saying that Comp TA's in good condition are worth anywhere from $200-300. Not sure how much to ask for mine.

Please let me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] Some clips from a new park I got to skate while I was home for the holidays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 22:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info. I'll compare them.

My girlfriend doesn't want anything bigger than 13.3" unfortunately. I tried to convince her but portability is one of her top priorities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 22:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that laptop looks awesome. The discount is insane. 

Would be able to tell me anything about the difference in processors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need opinion on hP Envy x360 for girlfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 03:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been doing a bit of research on laptops for my girlfriend. She'll be using it for general browsing, video streaming, and graphic design (Adobe Illustrator/Photoshop).

I finally decided on this one: http://www.costco.com/HP-ENVY-x360-13-y013cl-13t-Touchscreen-2-in-1-Laptop---Intel-Core-i7---QHD%2b-.product.100317294.html

Right now, it is $200 USD off at Costco, making it $1000.

-  i7-7500U 2.7 GHz
- 256 GB m.2 SSD
- 16 GB RAM
It also has a touch screen and the ability to be used almost like a tablet, which are features that she really wants, as well as thinness/portability. 

Is this a good deal? I haven't been able to find another laptop with this high of specs that is this cheap. She also really cares about how it looks. Are there any other laptops that would be a better choice?

Max budget is $1000 USD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 21:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What state do you live in? I got mine replaced for free under the CA PZEV 150K mile warranty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 05:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the response. I think I may be able to manage on my Comp TA. I'll have to use some P clamps to attach a rear rack and panniers. My only concern with it is the gear ratio isn't the greatest for climbing hills. 

I'm beginning to think that this Cannondale might be more work than it's worth, considering it won't be that much greater than what I already have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need advice on 1985 Cannondale ST500 for $150 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Picture]
(https://images.craigslist.org/00o0o_l9h4okTA2Ya_1200x900.jpg)

Seller description: 22 1/2 inch Cannondale for sale with padded seat and back bike rack. 15 Speed. Chips in paint on frame but great bike and good tires! Light aluminum frame.

I think the bike is smaller than what they have written. I've been emailing them a little, and the owner is 5'7", and said that it doesn't feel too big. Keep in mind that I'm 5'6", but I'm not exactly sure what the perfect size would be for me on a vintage touring bike. I currently have a 50cm 1984 Centurion Comp TA and I'm very comfortable on it. Should a vintage touring bike be the same size? Larger? Smaller? 

How good of quality is this bike? Seller is asking for $150.  

I'm looking at vintage touring bikes to go on a 6-7 day ride from San Francisco to Santa Barbara and was wondering if I'll need to upgrade this bike a lot or if can handle the job as is. 

Some people on bikeforums.net were saying that a modern 700c wheel will fit with almost no problem. If I were to upgrade the wheels and use an 8 speed cassette, would I need to change the derailleurs or anything else? I'm not too experienced in switching parts out on these older bikes.

Any opinion on the bike is appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A casual, everyday brown leather belt. I've been looking at Orion and ASimpleLeatherBelt. Any other recommendations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What state are you in? In California, I got mine (2008 Mazda 3) replaced under the CA PZEV 15 year/150,000 emissions warranty. Definitely worth it to check and see if your state has anything similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 04:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The video will be thrown into a huge mix of other videos on a loop that they currently have. The tv's right now don't play the music from the videos anyway, so I'm not sure why they insisted on me putting house music on the video.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 23:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question about music copyright and a video I'm making. Don't upvote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing a little video for a local gym where the video will only be shown on some tv's inside the gym, showing random workouts from a couple classes I'm filming.

Do I need to use royalty free music for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 08:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah basically, which is why I think the swap from a Ford Fusion is possible. My 2.3 block had FoMoCo printed on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 04:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not 100% sure, but it may have to do with availability. It blew my mind that these engines were so much cheaper than the Mazda 2.3s, and with way less mileage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 02:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Labor was $1400 at $100 an hour. So about 14 hours of labor. 
I paid $700 for the engine (including core and shipping from about 75 miles away) 

In the end I paid about $2100. 

It was either that, or replace the cylinder head, which would have cost me about $1500-1700 anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found out my 2.3 with 112K miles had a cracked cylinder head a month ago. I did a ton of research over at mazda3forums.com and found out it's relatively easy to swap in a 2.5L from a Ford Fusion, Mercury Milan, or Ford Escape. (Years vary) 

The used Ford engines can be found much cheaper online. I found one with 32K miles, for only $500. Whereas  used Mazda 2.3 engines with about 100K miles on them were about $1000-1200. 

I had my mechanic swap it for me, since I live in an apartment, and don't have the tools, skill, or time required for this job.

My mechanic ran into only one problem: the intake manifold adapter plate I bought from 2008Milan over at mazda3forums.com was a tiny bit too long and blocked the actuator from opening the intake flaps. 2008Milan was extremely helpful and sent me a new actuator from a local junkyard since mine had broke from the plate obstructing it. 

After that, the engine ran perfectly fine. I can tell it has a little bit more power. I'd have to get it tuned to take advantage of all of it, however. I'm not planning on doing that soon. I just got it back yesterday and it was so much fun to drive after occasionally borrowing my girlfriend's 2016 Toyota Corolla. 

Fingers crossed for no future problems! I'm really excited to see how my gas mileage is affected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Successful 2011 Ford Fusion 2.5L swap into 2008 Mazda 3 S GT 2.3L </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 03:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't find a decent car for that cheap.

Check out this guide: http://www.mazda3forums.com/61-powertrain-2004-2009-mazda3/647562-04-2-3l-swap-2-5l-successful.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swapping Ford Fusion/Escape 2.5L into 08 mazda 3 2.3L </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 03:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, my 08 3 with 112K miles has either a cracked head or blown head gasket. I've been doing tons of research, and after weighing my options, I've decided to pursue swapping a 2.5L Ford Fusion/Escape engine into my car for the following reasons (in order of importance):

* More reliable
* Confidence that the problem won't come back on my 2.3L
* Cheaper engine cost with far less mileage. Only about $500-800 with shipping for engines with anywhere from 40-70K miles.
* More power

I plan on keeping my 08 3 for the next 5-6 years, and after reading on a lot of forums, I'm not very confident that my current 2.3L will last that long, even if the head is replaced/gasket is fixed. (My local mechanic hasn't pulled my engine apart yet since we may just replace the engine.)

Here are my options:

* Replace the cracked head (using a used $200-300 cylinder head) or broken head gasket
     * Cheaper ($1300-$1500 with parts and labor)
     * No guarantee that the problem won't come back
* Buy used 2.3L
     * More expensive than all other options (Around $1100 for motor alone with about 100K miles + about $1000 for labor)
     * Fear that "new" 2.3L will die
* Swap Ford 2.5L in
     * Reasons listed above
     * $1600-2000
     * Possible compatibility issues

As I see it, I'm willing to pay the extra money to have a more reliable engine in my car since I want to keep it for awhile. However, I do have some questions, especially for people that have swapped the Ford 2.5L into their cars.

* How reliable is the 2.5L?
* Did you have any problems with smog? (I'm in California)
* What years from the Fusion/Escape motors can be swapped in? From the guides I've been reading online, it seems like anywhere from 2009-2012 are okay. 
* Is it worth it in my case to swap out the engine? 
* My 3 is AT, does the motor I buy have to be AT as well? 
* Do I have to buy the intake and throttle body adapter?

If anybody has advice, I'd really appreciate it. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
