<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4921</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dmitriy is the best tailor I've come across yet. 

http://www.yourtailorforlife.com/

He did major work on my suit and it looked amazing.  Very rapid too.  He's not cheap though, but you get what you pay for.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wavery, Union, De Kleine Duivel, 8 Bar, Frazier's, Club Charles, yes def the Crown and Rocket to Venus, Mount Royal Tavern, The Windup Space, Idle Hour, Snake Hill, Johnny Rad's, The Laughing Pint, Blue Pit, The Sidebar, Butts and Bettys, Spirits Tavern.....

Not all will have your other request for music, they're just straight up watering holes.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have to admit, our little guy is one handsome devil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daaaaaaaaaaaaaaaammmmmnnnnnnn, I never realized Reagan whooped who's ever ass he ran against that bad.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try running a sample of pure DNA through your purification protocols.  The purification could be the problem or you might be loading too much? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH yeah, undergrads mixing up the SDS/page tris glycine buffer for the tris-glycine transfer buffer.  Heh, their transfers still worked.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did an intership in pharma and it was AWESOME.  They made me synthesize a series of small molecules for a project that was put on the back burner (but the PI was still interested in it) along with purifying them and characterizing them via NMR, MS, and CHN.  It wasn't for BS either, they tested the analogs in their assays.  They even tested some of the best ones I made in animal models and saw efficacy.  Long story short, there were some successful hits in the series that I made, the company took notice and then opened up a whole discovery program back on the project I started working on. It went from me just working on it to a team of 20 people.  

Oh yeah, they were also paying me $20/hr (back in 2004 this was awesome money) and it ended up hiring for a full time gig. Yup, I did real science and learned way more in industry than I did in the classroom--modern synthesis, large scale synthesis, analytical techniques you'd never be allowed to do at my small uni because you always had to hand the sample off to a tech, learned the basic principles of pharmacology, animal models, hell, even what pharma thinks on a business level and what goals they need to meet on the sales front in order to keep the business afloat.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a child I hated carrots.  As an adult I love them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 07:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NextGen sequencer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's more like telling a person to starve or eat.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 03:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cryptography museum .... NSA campus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why exactly are people like Ryan panhandling?  A healthy 23-30 year old shouldn't be homeless if they cared enough.  Take up a labor job doing construction, learn a trade skill that pays a decent middle class income, make deliveries for FEDEX, drive a rig or a bus for the city, or work baggage at an airport.  If you were truly starving like that I feel like you could find at least SOMETHING to keep a roof over your head, even though it might not be the best living space.  Plenty of illegal immigrants for Christ's sake can figure out a way to get a job and keep a roof over their head AND they don't even qualify for a lot of emergency benefits.  

There are lot of pandhandlers that don't have mental illnesses, for example, all of the crust punk types that squat on the streets in Hampden.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 01:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of Love and Regret

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I get that Hampdenites love to hate 5/10 because it doesn't fit in with their alt scene, but 5/10 really wasn't that bad.  Actually I thought the cocktail they made was pretty good and the food was better than average bar food.  Def. not that bad.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indomitable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm....I mean I've only been there a handful of times over the years when I'm in that area, but I don't think I ever been disappointed to the point that I'd call it *the worst* restaurant in Baltimore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sip and Bite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philadelphia Flyers vs the Red Army (1976). Soviets end up quitting after the first period. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parkour is still not cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 08:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A company man or no tears for the dead is more Wick like IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 05:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is by far and away my most favorite reference on this topic:

http://www.nature.com/nprot/journal/v3/n6/full/nprot.2008.73.html

Not too much theory, short and just straight to the point with very clear examples.  A freshman in college should be able to understand how to do PCR analysis after reading that protocol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 08:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even describe in words how much Venice Tavern fits the bill you describe.  

It is so awesome and the best part is that they have low prices on all beers everyday and all day. Craft ones too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Analtech baby.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 06:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silk Road: Uzbek/Russian

West Indian Flavor: Trinidad

Mayuree Thai Tavern: Thai

Chopstix: Chinese  (basically the only one worth going to around Baltimore)

Kippo: Japanese

Maiwand: Afghan





Merengue: Dominican

Pho Saigon: Vietnamese

Aromes: French

Alma: Venezuelan 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rancid - I Wanna Riot [Punk] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should read Four Fish by Paul Greenberg.  It explains why some types of large fish simply can not be farmed and don't do well in captivity.  It's why Tuna are impossible to farm and will be extinct:

https://www.amazon.com/Four-Fish-Future-Last-Wild/dp/1455809608 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **I**mmigration and **C**ustoms **E**nforcement.  

I don't see what the problem of enforcing immigration is?  Doesn't every country do it?  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watch Chris Pronger clips when he had the puck.  Dude had epic, epic patience and vision which was why he was so good.  He'd rarely if ever make a bad pass or turnover because he'd wait and let the traffic skate by.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just don't brew it that hot in the first place.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Predator, Die Hard, Lethal Weapon, The Terminator 1+2, Aliens, Bullit...... Hello.  Action movies used to be very good in the 60s, 70s, 80s and 90s.  Then the shaky crap came out and assloads of CGI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The accountant had some good action too.  It wasn't very shaky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there goes a keeper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Guys, if you're up the creek today because you forgot it was VDay try going to your local hospital for flowers and a card. They're almost never picked over on VDAy and no one thinks about trying to go there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Food Hall:  Mt Vernon, Belvedere, or R House.  Trying to get table might be insane today.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still to this day, this clip has haunted me ever since I've seen it.  How someone as high ranking as General Westmoreland could say something like that is beyond me.  And for even more background, here's an old article:

NONE OF THE many newspaper obituaries about General William Westmoreland exhumed one of the most important things he ever said:

''The Oriental doesn't put the same high price on life as does a Westerner. Life is plentiful. Life is cheap in the Orient."

Westmoreland said that in the Oscar-winning 1974 Vietnam documentary ''Hearts and Minds." The quote so stunned director Peter Davis that he gave Westmoreland a chance to clean it up. In a 1997 guest letter to The Washington Post in response to criticism that he cherry-picked the quote to push his antiwar agenda, Davis said, ''When we filmed the interview, Westmoreland paused after making that statement, yelled 'Cut!' and said he wanted a retake because that wasn't how he meant to express himself.

''In the second take, the general began saying exactly the same thing but we ran out of film. We then gave him a third chance to amend his remarks -- much the way Ted Koppel gave Al Campanis of the Los Angeles Dodgers a chance to change what he was saying about nonwhite baseball players lacking the 'necessities' to be managers -- and Westmoreland repeated the statement about the 'Oriental.' I used the third take, since the statement was most complete."

http://archive.boston.com/news/globe/editorial_opinion/oped/articles/2005/07/20/the_westmoreland_mind_set/


He was given 3 chances to fix it or take his words back!  Insane.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hearts and Mind "The Orientals don't value life" General Westmoreland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 06:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm...sorry, dunno. You'll have to call him up or send a message to him.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 06:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're small though.  You need almost 2 to fill you up = nearly a $20 sandwich.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 06:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, it's OK.  If someone asks me to go, I'll go.  I too found it expensive and pretty good, but not really outstanding.  A sandwich for me and the significant other plus two beers or glasses of wine will set me back nearly $50-60?  At a food hall?  Damn.  We often go to Clavel during happy hour, can get two drinks and stuff ourselves on tacos plus and app for less than $40.  And get service.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 06:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DG Alterations.  Dmitriy did an OUTSTANDING JOB and was quick.  I had major, major work done to a suit--sleeves, length, pants hemmed, crotch work, and legs slimmed.  He did it in only a few days.  It wasn't cheap, but I consider it reasonable for what needed to be done and how fast he did it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since when did America STOP taking in immigrants?  That's what I thought.  It is perfectly legal according to all known international laws to police immigration and citizenship.  We certainly take in immigrants every single day--legal ones.  If quota systems are setup that's too bad, maybe other people in the world, besides those down south, need a fair shake at obtaining US citizenship too.

Germany has very strict immigration policies and it is quite difficult to become a citizen.  

Same for Austria and Switzerland.  The Swiss overwhelmingly voted to prohibit minaret construction on mosques as well; even they are allowed to restrict who comes and goes and what those people can and can not do in their own country.  

Sorry, but there's nothing wrong with enforcing the law.  Every country is allowed to do it.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't say I agree.  ANY and EVERY country absolutely has the right to restrict, monitor, police, and enforce immigration. Period.  That's part of the definition of autonomy.  I don't understand why other first world countries with much, much more stringent immigration policies like Japan, Austria, Germany, or Switzerland don't get as much flak as the US does for NOT accepting illegal immigration.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't work.  As long as rhino horns are worth $1k a kilo or whatever, starving people will poach no matter if they have to get into a gunfight with authorities--see the failed war on drugs for another example.  

THey should just start cloning rhinos and harvesting horns in order to flood the market to reduce prices and incentives to poach.  Or I wonder if it would be possible to release genetically engineered rhinos that produce a poison in the horn so that it can't be used.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, I also get a chuckle thinking about how many times Reeves had to wrap his junk and get into prone with tons of dudes while filming this movie in order to get the perfect take for a ton of the scenes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, buy the gels.  Casting is a huge waste of time and doesn't save that much money overall, especially if you start losing protein samples.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, was Winston making fake coins?  The part where Reeves walks in for the first time in JW2 to the Continental and Winston is meeting with the guy and he says 'amazing work' or something like that...It looked like he was making fake gold coins?  I have a feeling that's how John will get out of being excommunicated once Winston is caught. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the sight on Arnold's handgun in Terminator utilized a helium-neon laser that required up to 10,000 volts to work. The only thing the developer got in return were some shirts, a poster, and baseball cap. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are family movies and movies for kids these days so friggin spastic and moving at 200 million miles per hour?  Jesus Christ, do kids only have the attention span of 0.5 milliseconds these days?  

Compare kids movies these days to something like Aladdin, The Little Mermaid, or Beauty and the Beast, it's like hyper active schizophrenic on LSD, coke, and PCP are making movies for kids these days where all they do is shout, scream, and run around all over the place all over the screen for 85 minutes.  Not only do you see it in the Lego movies, you see it in all of the Despicable Me types of films or the Kung Fu Pandas etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WBs rarely look perfect.  It looks like it worked, you ab just isn't 100% specific.  Just report what you see and show the whole blot.  The western isn't your entire project either. You can do microscopy work to show changes in localization or you can even fractionate your cellular components and then run the western again to see if things change.  I wouldn't dawdle on this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is just a scribbled out tattoo that was done haphazardly in order to help keep identity a secret.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is completely illegal though to live in Baltimore without of state tags unless you are a student/military/etc.  There are a lot of cars registered out of state by younger people who drive their 'parent's car' or who continue to register back where they are originally from in order to avoid paying higher rates for insurance. That's completely illegal and is insurance fraud.  They are making everyone else who obeys the law pay more money for their insurance.

No one is saying parking on the street w/ out of state tags is illegal for visitors etc.  Out of staters who routinely park in Baltimore, even if they are students, need to have the red sticker in their window, if they don't they should be towed and fined.  What is being said, though, is that people who are legally defined residents of Baltimore who continue to register their vehicles out of state in order to avoid paying higher insurance should have their cars towed and should be massively fined.   People with out of state tags and even people with MD tags should also have their plates routinely scanned and entered into a database that is crosschecked with their registration and where they pay taxes. If their car routinely appears for weeks parked on Baltimore's streets and they have their car registered to a location out of the city yet they pay city taxes, that means they  are dodging higher insurance rates.  Immediately fine them.  Once people realize that , 'holy shit, Baltimore is getting tough on insurance fraud therefore I have to register my car properly at my address', we can accurately gauge how many cars are truly registered/driven around the city. At that point, each additional car registered over the first registered at the same address should face increasing registration costs in order to deter a single house that is renting out from brining in 4,5,6 cars since there are that many people living in them.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> another reason why i'm a recovering catholic.  i still don't understand how anyone gives them money.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 05:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enforcement of out of state plates getting towed/fined unless they have lawful excuses for not registering.  Routinely scan MD tags to make sure they're actually registered in Baltimore.  If they aren't, start fining.  Once you get rid of a large portion of cars committing insurance fraud by being tough on it, increase the price of registration for every car over the first one registered to a certain address.  There are tons of rentals that house say 4 people and one house puts 4 cars on the street that need parking.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Selective removal of Phenyls from a diphenyl phosphate in the presence of phenyl groups on main scaffold. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a professional chemist, just a guy who needs to do and does chemistry.  I basically have my main scaffold which contains a phenyl group and which has a primary alcohol.  My main goal is to add a phosphate group to that alcohol.  I've come across established procedures for doing something similar where diphenyl chlorophosphate is used to add the diphenyl phosphate to the alcohol.  

My main conundrum right now is how do I selectively remove the phenyl groups from the phosphate while not disturbing the phenyl elsewhere in my molecule.  Almost all procedures I find use platinum oxide and hydrogen to remove the phenyls from the phosphate.  My only concern is that PtO2 and H2 will reduce the benzene ring that is elsewhere in my molecule.  Will that happen?  Is this solvent dependent?  Any ideas, if so, on how to selectively remove the phenyls from the phosphate while not disturbing my main scaffold which contains a benzene ring (assuming H2 is used)?  Any help is much appreciated, thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 05:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems extremely low, esp. for the outrageous Col in that area.  No way I'd work for that.  To put this in perspective, I made $60k 2 years out of college w/ just a BS in the pharmaceutical industry.....and that was all the way back in 2006. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hexanesalcohols </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mad respect for 0 politics as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The scoreboard for the Superbowl is blue vs red. This is like Democrats vs Republicans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only is AI much more advanced, think about materials.  What if we make machines that literally *never break* because the materials that they're made out of simply will always fix themselves?  There won't even be jobs for repairing them either.  

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mLwKZ43Dl7E

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think we're going to see bioprinted organs in our lifetime.  A complex organ like a liver is made up of a crazy amount of different types of cells that all have to interact with each other in a harmonious symphony.  At this point it'd be simply easier to clone a human and harvest their organs, ethics be damned! 


Bladders, skin, stuff like that is easy because you can get away with using only 1 or just a few types of cells that don't need to respond to all sorts of different types of autonomic or somatic responses, hormonal cues, etc.  We are way, way, way far away from ever creating a functional complex organ with a printer.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, some good ideas, thanks.  Incubation is done at 0C for 1 hour in PBS+5% BSA (published protocols, 0 degrees is for what I assume to prevent natural turnover of the glycans).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, there's probably already been hundreds, if not thousands, of reviews already on which miRs are altered in disease.  


You could try searching a bit harder for something even more cutting edge, such as trying to review the 'epitransciptome' regulation of miRs.  DNA isn't just methylated, but we know now that even the transcriptome is as well.  And your review could focus on miRs.  I could see difficulty, however, with the fact that it is still quite new so there may not be a lot to review, but on the flip side it is cutting edge and you'd be one of the first:

http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v519/n7544/full/nature14281.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So 1.) assume only 1 person makes 1 million dollars.   2.) assume that you can't sort everyone by how much they make you only have a list of names and then have to look through each person to see how much they made.  How do you find the person who made 1 million the fastest?  Do you just start from the top and go all the way down to the bottom of the list or is there some nifty trick and 'algorithm' you can use no matter what to find X information the fastest in a list of Y length? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's say you were given a list of 1000 people and you had to find the 1 person who made a million dollars, is there a 'quickest way' to do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they're still making 200% profit off of just colored sugar water.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 04:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, we tried that initially, but the problem too is that the sialidase doesn't always recognize the sialic acids because we treat cells with unnatural sialic acid precursors.  Like what Carolyn Bertozzi does.  I mean I've done lectin experiments before and got them to inhibit but the data is all over the place for SNA.  

And why are we trying SNA binding to unnatural SAs?  Well there had been published literature that has done the same thing and showed that the SNA lectin at least still bound to cells treated with unnatural precursors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 04:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just some cancer cells : bxpc3 + capan2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 01:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful OP.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone work with lectins? These things are a huge PITA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simply trying to do  binding to the surfaces of cells using FITC conjugated lectins followed by FACS.  I've done this a TON, but all of the sudden am having huge problems.  I know you need to preincubate lectins w/ inhibiting solutions to have a properly controlled experiment, but now every single time my inhibited controls for SNA lectin almost always gives a higher fluorescent signal than the actual sample.  Literally almost every single time (n=20+).  The inhibitory cocktail I'm using is 200mM sialic acid + 200 mM lactose + 20 ug/mL fetuin + 20 ug/mL glycophorin.  

I know lectins have a bad reputation for being extremely difficult to work with, but any ideas as to why almost every single time I'm seeing stronger signal in my inhibited sample vs my real sample would be much appreciated.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I never realized how priviledged we are to have an AWESOME dishwasher that makes your stuff look brand new every time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally reminded me of trading places:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DKtjBqJ4NxA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.  It is absolutely a must try.  Their doughnuts are by far and away the best in the entire city.  Old school style and no frills with stupid experimental flavors and gimicky things like bacon strips etc.  The plain doughnuts they have w/ coffee are amazing.  

Other things like the peach and blueberry cakes are awesom, imo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there is a severe shortage of platelets and that a big reason is because platelets only stay good if you store them at room temperature and they only last 5 days. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens to biosimilars if/when ACA is repealed? Any pharma insiders have insight into how pharma is feeling? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My basic understanding is that the ACA created the pathway for biosimilar submission through the Biologics Price Competition and Innovation Act (BPCI).  So what happens to biosimilars and the billions biotech has dumped into it if Trump repeals ACA? Could biosimilars possibly change to bioSAME? So many companies would be screwed then...or do experts and lawyers within pharma expect that even with ACA repeal the biosimilar mechanism would still exist as is ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Crime in the Cancer Lab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drug price increases since 2010 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are the scariest government spooks ever revealed to the public? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good cooking times to make awesome homefries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And to further ELI5--if you aren't familiar with diffusion--imagine you have an ice tea drink that you'd like to sweeten up.  You throw sugar into it BUT the catch is that you aren't allowed to shake or stir it or anything.  How long will it take to sweeten your drink?  It will slowly over time sweeten up, but it takes a while.  That's diffusion working, heat transfer through fluids with convection type of heating behaves in a similar way.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different types of energy.  Convection is limited by diffusion.  Microwaves have far greater depth of penetration and spin all of the water molecules in food.  The resulting kinetic energy of the spinning molecules gives off heat.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How does Google blur out images of nearly 100% of license plates and peoples' faces in Google Maps street view? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it can be mind warping out times to think how they're able to do it when every inch of the entire country is almost perfectly blurred out for license plates and peoples' faces.  Sometimes when I'm bored I'll just virtually drive around the city to places I've never been and through extremely rough areas of the city I'd never ever wander to just to see what it is like, but if there are cars that are parked in alley ways and side streets for which there Google Maps won't let you go down, somehow they're still able to get the cars license plates blurred out. How do they do it?  I can't imagine a human has to go through that much data to blur out every single license plate.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL of the Rajneesh movement which had over 2000 followers in Oregon in 1984. They perpetrated the single largest bioterror attack in US history, were guilty of other things such as murder, illegal wiretapping, and massive immigration fraud. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 07:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> itch on the bottom of my foot that I can't scratch or relieve when I'm wearing a boot that is a pain in the ass to take off. 

also itch ear and sinus canals/itchy back of the throat due to allergies and which is impossible to scratch.  my god is that torture.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saw this film through its digital release.  It was solidly entertaining IMO.  In fact, I've seen ever DC animated feature to date, and more often than not, DC's animated unit gets it right, especially when compared to its horrendous live action movies they've recently released.  I mean yeah, there's some misses wrt the animated films--e.g. Killing Joke etc--but DC's animated features work on far less of a budget while producing better films overall on average.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice League Dark (2017)--solid entertainment. Why can't DC seem to get the same quality of writing for its live action films as it does for its animated features? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mighty soviet empire couldn't invade Afghanistan.  Taking the country the size of another United States is virtually impossible.  Likewise, it would be incredibly stupid and nearly impossible for the Chinese to take the US because it is simply too massive, too far away, and there are more guns than people in the US.  That means military leaders will resort to things like biological/chemical/nuke weapons, mass carpet bombings, and a stupid amount of destruction and death.  It is a can of worms that shouldn't be opened.  Period.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prob because it gets annoying real fast to have to deal with 20 people bothering you every 5 minutes.  Pay someone else to deal with them.  The body guards might actually be more trained than him in self defense techniques.  Size isn't always everything.  Most US Navy Seals aren't huge guys and don't look like Arnold Schwarzenegger.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's amazing how history constantly repeats itself and how no one ever learns from the mistakes all throughout history.  

The bing cherry was invented by a Chinese immigrant --Ah Bing.  Bing traveled back to China for a visit, but unfortunately due to the Chinese Exclusion Act of 1882, he was prevented from returning to the US.  The Bing cherry is now loved by millions of Americans every year and is nearly a billion dollar crop.  

People like my dad were also banned from immigrating to the US alllllllllllllllllll the way until 1965.  He arrived in the United States with nothing in his pocket except $20.  His first job was a busy boy and dish washer at a local restaurant, and his only means of transportation back then was riding a bike.  He'd often have to ride long distances in the rain or snow.  Needless to say, he eventually went to college, became a nurse, owns a home, and sent his kids to college.  Oh yeah, he also drives a FordF150 and rides his Harley nearly every single day.  In fact, I don't think he's ever bought a car that wasn't an American brand.  

Who's more American, my dad or DT? If it were left up to people like DT, my dad would have never been allowed to immigrate and buy American products.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it just me or have Baltimore's streets gotten epically bad over the past year or two? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are there so, so many unfinished repairs everywhere in the city?  It seems like almost every street now has those large metal covers over top of construction projects that were repairing something down below.  Some of those metal coverings have been there for months and months and I've never seen anyone working on them since.  Have you driven to East Baltimore recently?  It is insane the amount of congestion and construction on the streets throughout Highlandtown.  And I know people have already been complaining about the massive jams in the center of the city due to road construction.  Why does it seem like the road repairs/construction projects take an epically long time to finish and fill the holes with pavement so that they can remove the metal slabs?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically the Raiders want to only pay $1 to rent their $1.9 billion stadium every year.  2/3rds of the stadium is funded through tax payer dollars. They're also demanding that they are able to keep 100% of all the revenue.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raiders submitted stadium lease proposal to Las Vegas, and they're asking for a sweet deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To this day, I still can not believe I sat through this whole movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That assumes there are rational players in the game though. Do you want to test that theory with a leader like Kim Jong Un?  And what happens when one country obtains some type of advantage, either through advance missile defense, military AI, etc. etc?  Someone will think they can win and unleash hell.  I'm sure the men behind the curtains in all countries have been busy calculating ways and thinking of strategies/technologies to beat MAD for going on the last 60 years.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do they catch these criminals sometimes?  Are they sifting through hordes of cell phone information to look for the same phone that was in the locations of all of the robberies near the same time they occurred? Do they have that technical capability and big data analytics yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Modern high speed rail comfort </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All Pipeline Incidents, 2010 to Present </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 04:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Connie Chung goads Newt Gingrich's mom into revealing to the world how he really felt about then First Lady Hillary Clinton in 1995. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, trying to respond to multiple inquiries here:

--I've used Corning 10-layer hyperflasks before (so basically a flask w/ 175 cm^2 x 10) for one of the cell lines before and only obtained about 80-100 million cells when it was fully confluent, meaning I'd need multiple flasks 10-layer flasks, and if I have to do that with 7 different cell lines it becomes a nightmare.  

-Some won't grow in suspension and just die while some of the lines I've never worked with before, so I have no idea if they'll be happy in suspension or not.  I'm just going with ATCC guidelines and they all adhere.  

-I have enough space for 7 of those flasks.  I'll just remove all of the shelves in several incubators and put them in there.  

-For one of the lines, a fully confluent 15 cm dish will give ~10-15 million IIRC.  I don't think I can grow 20 dishes for 1 cell line and have to do that 7x.  The problem too is that each cell line uses different media so then I'd have to spend a huge amount of time filling up dishes with different types of media and then trypsinizing all of them.  If  I could just pour an initial stock of cells into a large quantity of media and pour it into a multilayer flask, it'd save an inordinate amount of time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, imagine AMLO gets elected.  Wonder what America would do or how Americans would feel if AMLO takes the anti-American fervor all the way to allowing Chinese and Russian armies to base themselves in Mexico, house missile defense systems to shootdown US nukes in Mexico, or station Chinese and Russian navies at ports in Mexico.  

Trump could be an epic disaster in the making.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need to grow ~500 million cells for each of 7 cell lines, recommendations for flasks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Thermo has these offered:

https://www.thermofisher.com/order/catalog/product/140000

w/ 6000+ cm^2 area.  Does anyone else have experience growing cells on this kind of scale? What kinds of flasks did you use?  My cells are adherent.  I'd like something that works well and is the most economical.  I contacted Thermo for a quote, but I I know it is going to be extremely expensive per flask.  I was wondering if I could save money somewhere.  I'd like to grow the cells in 1 shot too and not have to grow multiple flasks for each cell line because the logistics of working with that many flasks becomes a nightmare for one person to handle.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of these engineered cell strategies also only work against blood cancers and rarely ever against solid tumors.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 05:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This shit was potent as hell IIRC.  Remember kiddies, we didn't really have the internet back then when we were playing Kings Quest, Space Quest, and Police Quest.  SHIT WAS HARD back then.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Dylans has A+ oysters.  They've super fresh and healthy.  Great flavors.  Quite expensive; some types of oysters can cost $3.5/ea.  so just a dozen oysters + 2 drinks might set you back close to $70 after taxes and tip.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fear not, they may be facing extinction, but they're rapidly evolving to beat the cancer that's decimating their populations:

://www.sciencemag.org/news/2016/08/tasmanian-devils-are-rapidly-evolving-resistance-contagious-cancer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Farmers in the United States Have Been Feeding Their Cattle Red Skittles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate lobster rolls with mayo.  Mayo should not be anywhere near lobster.  

Do you pour A1 sauce all over an amazing steak too?    The southern style lobster rolls....yes please.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caturday this past week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 06:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When talking about company policy one guy mentioned that employees had to clockout everytime they went to the bathroom.  

Nope, I ain't working for anyone who feels compelled to track how long my shits take and how often I need to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He always does this as soon as we home after leaving the house. He's not tricking anyone either, he absolutely wants his belly rubbed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 07:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you know what else is surprising?  He's *still relevant in fantasy*.  Yes, some of us play fantasy hockey, but Jagr is currently owned in over 65% of ESPN fantasy leagues.  

That's incredible.  That would be like owning Bretty Favre now and having him still be relevant to your fantasy football team.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And oh man, he totally owned style in the 90s:

http://img.blesk.cz/img/2/full/1421634-img-sport-hokej-jagr-straka.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is an absolute machine.  He makes pro sports players in leagues like the MLB and NFL look like a fat joke.  The workouts Jagr still does in his mid-40s today make 18 year old rookies and players in their prime puke their brains out.  A fucking monster and specimen whose DNA should be studied with absolutely unimaginable strength, speed, and endurance.  Oh, and he still bones 18 year old models:

http://sports.yahoo.com/blogs/nhl-puck-daddy/jaromir-jagr-blackmailed-with-scandalous-model-selfie--doesn-t-care--report-172338281.html

And then when they try to blackmail him for it he gives 0 fucks.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, you should read the story of what SC Edison did to their workers with H1Bs:

http://www.computerworld.com/article/2879083/it-outsourcing/southern-california-edison-it-workers-beyond-furious-over-h-1b-replacements.html

It's an outrageous abuse of the system.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Senate bill seeks sweeping H-1B changes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is insanely packed.  No where to park in the area.  Uber, bike, or bus.  Anything but driving.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muscle cancer in general.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 12:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the longest time until around the turn of the 20th century we used to only think of life and disease in terms of DNA and proteins. Almost all proteins that float around in your body aren't just proteins, they're actually GLYCOproteins, and it was that prefix we ignored for a long time because it was simply 'too hard' to understand the language that nature was talking to us in with sugars.

One of the first hallmarks ever discovered and which almost always accompanies cancer are altered patterns of sugars on the surfaces of cancer cells and secreted proteins. We know that a cell is sick or stressed based on what outside sugar pattern looks like.

PSA is actually a glycoprotein. Although elevated PSA may or may not give an accurate diagnosis, we could potentially vastly improve its accuracy by looking at specific glycoforms of PSA and not just the protein quantity itself. Because sugar patterns are altered in cancer, looking for very specific glycoforms adds another dimension to improve the accuracy of PSA. In fact, the importance of the sugar world to biology and medicine is starting to finally catch on and they're trying hard to improve PSA test accuracy by now including the protein + the sugar:

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/23318363

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4893645/

http://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/pr500575r

Finally, MRI, like the article states could be used to diagnose cancer by looking at a tumor's sweet tooth. For example, highly advanced and more experimental methods related to MRI are actually now starting to try to image the sugars themselves on tumors completely label free:

http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms7719 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 05:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh and if you're looking for a bakery there are some on Rockville and Silver Spring which are in the direction of Makoto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 05:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Maryland?  Well, Makoto in DC was crazy good.  You'll definitely blow a hole through your wallet though($200+ ea... that included sake pairings and maguro/ toro upgrade IIRC) w, but if you don't care I have to say it's the best in the area we've ever had.  OK, it's not technically still MD if you want to nitpick. Whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 23:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm good idea. I have extra lysate and will do a secondary only.  

1.) Blocked with 5% BSA in tbst (.1% tween) for 2 hours.  

2.) 1:1000 M2 in TBST + 5% BSA overnight in cold room.

3.) Wash 3x10 min TBST

4.) Hrp 2ndary in TBST +5% BSA (1:5000) for 2 hours.  Wash 3x10 min TBST.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 05:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't comment on other molecules per se and only carbohydrates because that is my area of expertise, but there is a growing cache of evidence linking diet to disease (OK that by itself isn't surprising) but which we now understand a bit of the mechanism.  Carbohydrates and carbohydrate metabolism are absolutely involved in almost every major disease we know.  For example, under periods of 'diabetic' like conditions or state of 'high' feeding, cells have to get rid of excess glucose, and one example of what they do is alter the structure of their extracellular matrix (basically the stuff that surrounds cells, this is ECM for short).  The ECM consists of huge polymers of sugars known as glycosaminoglycans (GAGs).  I won't go into all of the details, but we know that types of GAGs are super important for developing things like atherosclerosis.  Under diabetic conditions your cells produce a special type of GAG that retains LDL (the 'bad' fats you always hear about).  Your body tries to clear LDL with immune cells that end up forming what are known as 'foam cells'.  These keep piling up to cause a plaque that gives you a heart attack, but the main important thing to recognize here is that sugars and carbohydrates are extremely important for this mechanism related to heart disease.  

In some other examples, bacteria need to break through the ECM barriers in order to spread to other regions of the body.  Snippets of the ECM can elicit an immune response and cause inflammation--which you know about because you all have gotten fevers before.  Under chronic diabetes and high fed diets, we've seen cells produce the same types of ECMs that can elicit inflammatory responses, meaning there is some plausibility to the idea that consuming a ton of sugar could lead to a chronic inflammatory state through promotion of immune stimulating ECM components (which again, are sugars). 

Inside of the cell is even more interesting.  Although many in the scientific community haven't heard of it, we discovered nearly 30 years ago the phenomena that tons and tons and tons of proteins inside of your cells are actually modified by a special sugar known as N-acetylglucosamine (GlcNAc for short).  When it is on a protein it is called O-GlcNAc.  After a lot of effort, we've finally started to understand a bit what O-GlcNAc is capable of doing, which is everything from regulating how proteins are shaped, regulate how they fold, how they signal, how long their half lives are.....basically O-GlcNAc is involved in every aspect of the  physiology of the entire proteome just like phosphorylation is.  A protein complex called RNA poly II decodes your DNA to read your genes.  Well, RNA poly II doesn't bind to DNA and read it right unless it is covered O-GlcNAc.  In fact, your chromatin is heavily covered in the O-GlcNAc sugar, meaning sugar is all over the place in and around your DNA (we can stain for this and it'll light up like a christmas tree).  We now know that O-GlcNAc is involed in regulating your histone code, modifies virtually every single transcription factor (including for example all of the core Yamanaka factors that regulate pluripotency), it is found on proteins that regulates DNA methylation (epigenetics)...the list goes on forever.  You name a cellular process, O-GlcNAc and sugar is probably involved.  

But what does that have to do w/ diet?  Well, GlcNAc is produced by a branch from glycolysis known as the hexosamine biosynthetic pathway (HBP).  In otherwords, GlcNAc production is directly tied to glucose metabolism, which is ultimately tied to nutrition.  In periods of high feeding, you might have guessed it right, the HBP will produce an overabundance of of GlcNAc which will go on to alter the patterns in the way your cells O-glcnac modify proteins, which then goes on to change allllll those physiological processes I mentioned earlier.  It is entirely plausible that fasting can lead to increased lifespan, because at least for carbohydrates we know that a molecule like GlcNAc and phenomena like O-glcnac is absolutely involved in aging and stress:

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/27259471

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/18185980

http://www.pnas.org/content/107/16/7413.full.pdf

TL;DR:  At least when it comes to high sugar consumption, there are many plausible mechanisms through which a lower calorie intake diet could promote longevity since we know sugars are involved in everything from heart disease, cancer, and diabetes, to basically regulating everything about how your cells work, including many areas related to aging and stress.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just remember these two fact for the rest of your life:

Women--you have 1:3 odds of getting cancer in your lifetime
Men--for you it is 1:2.   

Look to your left, look to your right.  One of you will have cancer.  Just remember that when you vote in politicians who want to limit the access of affordable healthcare for people.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  I go to Asia alllllllllll the time.  The airports in the East absolutely blow western airports out of the water. US airports are a joke compared to Singapore's and S. Korea's.  ICN is amazing.  Like others have said, free showers, free internet, great dining establishments, ice skating, and garden to walk through, free city tour.  I almost always fly Cathay, Singapore Air, or Korean air when I go out that way, even if it costs a bit extra because they are so much better.  I want a little more comfort and don't mind paying for it if I'm going to be traveling for nearly 24 hours straight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Agents Arrest a Former Guatemalan Soldier, who worked in the mail room at Johns Hopkins, Charging Him With Massacring Civilians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 04:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm, they were never trained on the hazards and smells of HS?  It smells literally like ass, and it it were in that high of a concentration down there'd they'd easily be able to smell it and detect danger right away if they were trained.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, they had good martinis.  They weren't doing good business at their old place before they moved?  They definitely should have never moved.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, Philly for starters.  They took a HUGE chunk out of my yearly salary:

https://beta.phila.gov/services/payments-assistance-taxes/business-taxes/wage-tax-employers/

even though I lived outside of the city in a neighboring town.  It was like getting a $4k raise once I moved to another job outside of the city.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This also works well with other desserts such as strawberry shortcake.  They've serving desserts like this for a while now in Asia.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh Justin Sane....met him before in real life after a festival.  Was pretty nice, but gettin' old.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found it surprising Baltimore allows this.  Other cities I've worked in took a chunk out even though you lived outside of the city.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, if you want more entertainment, watch GG Allin on Springer:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ALGGreM9d7E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhhhhhhhhhhh the 90s.  Kiddies these days.... you don't know what it was like back in the days when we had people like Tipper Gore.  We used to have violent video games without M+17 ratings.  The good 'ol days when we could outrage parents with gangsta rap and shock rock.  I remember the parents being horrified at the atrocious level of violence in Mortal Kombat 1, yet parents these days would probably let a kindergartner play it because the graphics are so laughable now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
