<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9554</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being in the military. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 05:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cat loves empty toilet paper rolls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 05:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was in grade school in the 70's, the made us wear these glow in the dark pins/stars for when we're waiting for the school bus. I wonder if those were painted with radium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 05:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember using those in Buster Brown shoe stores in the early 70's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 13th Warrior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dune. It's built to run on a 386 or 486 but it is still fun as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mach 3 razors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use to drive 60 miles round trip for work. I also got the extended warranty as well as tire insurance. The tire insurance has saved me a lot of money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We called it the "Poop Snake" and it was wonderful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bangladesh's 'Tree man' has his hands back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did this once at a Cleveland Cavaliers basketball game. Everyone was yelling and having fun when suddenly the people behind me started gagging and coughing and swearing. It took everything I had not to start laughing.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People gasp when I tell them I drink a pot of coffee by 1100 and then have one more cup later that afternoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so glad that in America, the pressure to drink or attend work events where drink is being given is non-existent. Actually, if you show up to work stinking like alcohol, that's grounds for dismissal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 05:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where in the article does it state that the PD tried to bury it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 03:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, thank you for the answer. I really loved this movie but couldn't help but wonder about this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 02:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my day but...

I still drink a pot of coffee in the first hour of waking up.

And when I take my 54mg of Concerta?

It takes me 3 hours to drink that pot of coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about Pandorum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 02:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, while the survivors were in the crazy cooks home, they were discussing that the monsters were actually mutated humans due to the type of nutrition they were receiving via feeding tube. But at the end, we find out that they have actually landed on a planet. So, the question I have is are they mutated humans or or actual creatures from the planet they landed on and they are going to be hunted as soon as they touch land? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the term Baloney Pony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you a man or woman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the battle for Mosul, grenades rain down from ISIS drones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought price gouging was illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 19:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the snow fell silently onto the slightly heated ground with only a slight hiss, the brother wrecked the pussy.

I know I'm following up on a gold comment, but wanted to try my hand at it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great short film! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, the guys firing from behind the van were the bad guys or the cops? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is remarkable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this in Corpus Christi cause I've seen some fucked up shit on the road down there... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about sweet and low? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 02:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wilma Smith? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 01:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh. This scene would've ruined it for me. First off, they aren't going to jump with flair sand a smoke trail. Secondly, they aren't going to jump into a storm cloud with lightening. No way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 22:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And people bitch about the US's environmental laws. Seeing shit like this makes me happy that we have the intrusive laws that we do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 22:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go to her most recent post, she was one of those idiots who dyed her hair gray.  http://mommyslittlesunshine.blogspot.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 22:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you see the comment where one lady wrote the name of her "47" month old? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in the 50's, my grandfather was putting shingles on the roof of his barn. While doing it , he slipped and rolled off the roof. On his way off the roof, he hit the curved lip on the edge and it knocked him out. He then fell 30 feet and hit the ground. My mom found him laying there, unconscious with his pipe still in his mouth. Nothing was broken. I guess when he was knocked out he completely relaxed which saved him.
Although he didn't have any broken bones, he was lucky because his landed only inches from a cement pad...and he was incredibly sore for a few weeks afterward. He was so sore that my mother told me that they had to tie a rope to the bedposts by his feet so he could pull himself up in the morning. They did call the ambulance and he was taken to the hospital just in case. After the ambulance had put him into the back of the vehicle, it wouldn't start back up so they had to use a tractor to pull it so it could pop the clutch and start it. Also, it was his favorite Corn Cob pipe.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 14:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Melatonin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 03:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she had already had a few strokes and had almost died prior to this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 12:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say the early 80's. The haircut of the guy in the middle is very 80's along with those sunglasses. The guy on the left looks like Luke Wilson from [The Royal Tenenbaums](http://www.vulture.com/2013/10/how-wes-anderson-made-the-royal-tenenbaums.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Full metal jacket!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 04:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 04:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to Facebook and look up "Ghosts Of The Eastern Front". They have some amazing pictures. I grabbed that one from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: For-profit schools skirting federal law with GI Bill revenue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 04:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck, when I was in college this kinda shit didn't bother anyone. For all they knew, you were getting laid. Everyone having a damn cellphone is scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any fish in that water? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yummy pistol! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found on the Easterm Front </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 01:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 22:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is. That's the fun of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My father and a friend, missing the big one - 1960 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 22:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like Ketchikan and even Metlakatla. Summer comes and the seasonal workers/fishermen come in and the population increases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me and my ruler, 1979 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 19:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 05:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I was the second coming of Christ as a lover. Naw...I'm more like the third coming of Christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 05:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, was this essentially hand carved using an exacto knife after you finished with the dremel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 17:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a Christmas Day Miracle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 17:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of modern day France. Unexploded WW1 artillery shells are found almost every day (to include mustard gas shells). The farmers leave them on the side of the road for the bomb squads to pick up and dispose of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Town Of Augsberg Evacuates on Christmas Morning for discovered WWII Bomb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 17:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indians, Edwin Encarnacion agree to contract </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 17:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 04:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I just watched it again. Damn, what a fucking scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lisa Gerrard is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Sweet Hereafter. [Ian Holm telling the story of his daughter Zoe and the spider](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=8Wjy1mpt_Gg). What a remarkable scene. This is the type of scene actors die for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in 7th grade (1979) when my brother and I went to a matinee showing of Dr. Zhivago. I didn't know much but found I enjoyed the movie and did know that what I was watching was a far superior movie to what i normally watched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always thought that she and Anna Torv should play sisters in a movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 21:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was in 3rd grade (1976) teachers Approached my parents about me being  on medication. My father didn't believe in it. I was finally diagnosed when I was 28. My father saw my teacher from 6th grade a few years ago. When he told her what I had accomplished in life she said "I'm so glad he made it"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 04:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I do that all the time! My ex wife says she feeds off my energy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 04:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 02:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She draws like crazy and is pretty good for 6 years old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1st grade daughter is ADHD and I have some questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 00:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello All. First, let me introduce myself. I am a 50 year old man who has always had ADHD and am more ADD now. I've always that that issue of never really fitting in and as a result, my self esteem has always been pummeled,

Now, my 6 year old daughter has also been diagnosed with ADHD (she has both) and possibly some minor anxiety issues. Her mother and I are now divorced and I see every weekend. When we go out to do things, it always breaks my heart because she tries so hard to make friends but is always kinda shunned. And she gets really sad about it. My ex-wife also speaks of it and compares her to me and how she doesn't want my daughter to have those same alienating experiences I had.

So, I am asking for advice on how I should encourage her or make her feel better. I should know, but I'm only trying to learn.

TL;DR Daughter is ADHD, doesn't fit in. Asking for advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't know. He's never followed them and he's close to 75. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm afraid not. Mine father lost it when it tangled in the chain sprockets of a Hay elevator.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 02:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which one of them lets out a loud, nasty fart? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad lost half of his right middle finger in a farm accident when he was a teenager. He likes to make it look like he is shoving upnhis nose when he is aroundnkids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking asshole hehehehehe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And My Heart Sank....From The Dankness Of The Catacombs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 23:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also yelled "We die in Alleppo, you die here" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has now been confirmed as killed in the attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young studs modeling the hot new fashion trends - 1978 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 16:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always think of the movie "North Dallas Forty" when thinking about how players are treated as a commodity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 14:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use the Garmin Vivofit and I find it works quite well and has a great strap. It also has a battery that is good up to a year. The sleep function has to be manually activated when you want it To Track your sleep so that's also a nice function. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 04:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/nocontext </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 04:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upskirt!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 04:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's he doing today? Any problems with his memory? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 04:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankfully, that one had water running down it for an easy glide... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone remember those old Metal slides at the water parks? Me, age 6 - 1973 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 04:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Then this one](http://www.napolidavivere.it/2015/10/21/il-testamento-di-pietra-visita-teatralizzata-alla-cappella-sansevero/) will really blow your mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 04:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever seen [The Veiled Christ](http://www.napolidavivere.it/2015/10/21/il-testamento-di-pietra-visita-teatralizzata-alla-cappella-sansevero/)? I've been in this museum multiple times and the illusion is remarkable. It looks like a thin sheet is placed over Christ. Hell, you van even see the stigmata. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the resulting war years brought a better idea of combat tactics that have revolutionized how police or military act during combative periods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And, I think, you qualify for AARP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Partying hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 02:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, is the Monday, Tuesday and Wednesday this week or next week? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does he just not like walking on that tile? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what pigs and goats are for. They use them for military training. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you a pimp? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone else notice the comment under the picture at the top of the article?

"Rectum? I destroyed it, mate! Photo: Imperial College London" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I guess I was lucky where I went to school. All my classmates were my age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kid is 16 but in 7th grade? How old was the girl he was seeing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the webpage for little Diomedes school system.

http://littlediomede.bssd.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was to keep rabbits out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always loved "Citizen X" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever been to Naples, Italy? Those old churches have piles of bones out... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The movie came out in 2015 but I saw it on video in 2016 so I'm going to say the gruesome, brutal scene in Bone Tomahawk. The whole time that they were imprisoned was tough on my nerves but that sudden brutal violence took me over the edge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be able to find a Yellowpages at a time when they aren't used anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 23K points? I thought there was an algorithm  that tamedmdown points </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 20:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cedar Point Mean Strek or was that Geauga Lake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 01:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C-17's Rock. I didn't even bother with the hammocks. Straight to the floor with my sleeping bad and sweatshirt. That plane gets cold as FUCK at altitude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 01:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That guy is going to freeze his ass off in those shorts when they get to altitude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 01:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today's version of "3 O'Clock High"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 01:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad News Bears (1976)

Carmen and  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 01:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alien. I still remember that feeling of amazement while watching it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 03:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was once having sex with a lady dodgy style and it was hot and very wet. I slipped out and when I slid my dick back in, she screamed and curled up in a ball and started crying. I'd slid it in her ass by accident and she was so wet, it just went right in. She didn't stop crying for 20 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Grandpa Wagner selling and giving away Christmas Trees, mid 1930's. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 21:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 06:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know but I will say that my ex-wife had told me many times that I was oblivious to both men and women flirting with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the scene at the hospital, what was the old lady saying to Bill Murray that was causing those two younger ladies to laugh so hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 15:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of a lucid dream I recently had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you not love his performance in Kalifornia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You feel the need to speak when you don't need too. I understand that many times you feel uncomfortable whether it is due to silence or to much speaking. Don't just say something to say something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 03:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She won a Golden Globe for her role. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 00:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you mail it back in? There should be a mailing packet attached to one of those handles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quentin Dean (In The Heat Of The Night) 1967 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 06:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I was mis-informed. That being said, the US Army is a federal force. Federal military is legally not allowed to participate in state police actions (National Guard can). How can, what you are saying, be legally justified? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US Army and the US Army Corps of Engineers are two completely separate entities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US Army and the US Army Corps of Engineers are two completely separate entities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 03:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of your drawings are amazing!! Wow!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 04:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this video but why no gate at the stairs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 00:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never heard it compared to an Oceans 11 movie, but that makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 00:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During the State Of The Union address. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 00:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that as "Mr Bojangles" and wondered what was wrong with you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 00:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comfortably Numb -Pink Floyd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 03:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What book did he choose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't feel bad, I never put that together and I watched them both and thought Samantha was hotter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a can of Miller or Schlitz? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, although this shot is awesome, I prefer the cinematography of the airplane dogfights. It is remarkable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Navy ship I was in (USS Inchon) had pulled into port in Spain and I went to see the movie with a friend who spoke Spanish. The movie was in Spanish and he translated it for me for about 1/2 the movie and then he fell asleep. 

I was amazed at the action although I didn't understand a word.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 23:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The movie came out? Is it on Netflix or something? I read the book and damn it was good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 23:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reminds me of Trumps expression after the meeting with Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 23:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The final scene in [A Midnight Clear](https://youtube.com/watch?v=H9qZQoBMc7I). The video I posted is a tribute video to the movie. Jump to 4:15 for the final scene. The look of exhaustion, defeat, and sadness is overwhelming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 02:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where the hell is security for those troops? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 23:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy motherfucking shit. I just laughed hard for 2 minutes.

/u/poem_for_your_sprog this story would be perfect for your talents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of that equipment or uniform items might be associated with human remains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That just amazes me. It's probably nothing new for you to find those while I'd be so excited and happy to find something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 20:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [A Midnight Clear](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0102443/). The whole Third Act had me in tears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One problem with this picture. Trump doesn't
Go the White House till tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. I was never put in one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's at about 1:10 of the video.

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=ZQYt4io0Btw

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What bar in Cleveland? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me and my family, around 1977 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 12:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 12:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I aim to please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
