<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2846</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 09:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would rather help a new lifter than be an inconsiderate asshole like you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's talk about hating on other players. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 09:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It frustrates me soooo much when players start to sabotage, harass, and spam surrender because of a member on their team. You don't like their build? Stop playing pvp then, everyone builds a little different. You are mad because they keep dying? Then get in lane and support them instead of running around trying to gang and last hit  characters. One of your teammates is just really bad? We have all had bad games, and you have probably had some pretty terrible games too.

This game is fun, but let's learn a little respect for others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 09:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 245 is a respectable total for someone my size, and more than most folks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 08:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TM? Good luck dude! Playing in the top league is impressive, hopefully you make it back to the states and we see you hooping it up in the NBA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or how about the Audi one? Equal pay is liberal propaganda now? How laughable is that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the part that kills me. The irony is lost on them that we fought fascism abroad less than 100 years ago and now there is a president whose rise to power almost mirrors that of Hitler. 

My great grandparents are rolling in their graves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trailblazers Instagram nailed the comment on this ha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this one hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was their set list? I'm guessing you were at The Complex? Incredible concert!

I remember it being:

Jungle Youth

Something To Believe In

I Got

Titus was Born

Firelight

And I don't remember the order of the others except their encode, which was freaking awesome!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 09:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was actually a study done on this that showed no extended adverse mental or physical trauma on the woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 09:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was right wing, Christian conservative. Went on an LDS mission, and realized that 1. I spent the last 2 years teaching that we have agency, and that some laws do take away agency to make personal choices, and 2. There are so many people on this Earth who don't share even close to the same belief system as me.

The thing that solidified it for me was a quote by Joe Biden about him personally being pro life, but advocating pro choice because he wouldn't impose his belief on others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just overloaded this semester. I will be fine, college is supposed to be hard, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 06:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need facts! Show us facts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 06:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think both of you need to bring some sources into this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they were doing like 95 lbs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am cleaning 245. Enough to know that when your back is bowing, and your elbows are at your side, you are going to hurt yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When to step in on form? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently watching two guys attempt to do cleans. Their forms are damagingly horrendous. Like, they will be hurting tomorrow and possibly for a few weeks. When is it OK to step in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Battlefield 3 anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hinnom, TX. Bon Iver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about to melt down. I have 3 midterms and a paper, on Wednesday, Thursday, and Friday. The worst part? All science classes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was another post today about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. They monitor these threads though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Epic, this is one of the best ideas you have had! Develop this more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keto diets aren't healthy for type 1 diabetics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know about mountain Meadows, I know about the quase permanent militia, but the fact remains that the early saints were pushed around because of broad intolerance across numerous states and territories. 

I mean, the whole extermination order, mobs in Illinois, Ohio, Missouri, the burning of settlements, killing men, women, and children, rape, the list goes on and on about the persecution they faced because of intolerance.

And don't forget the March of the Union Army into Salt Lake, the ignorance of multiple sitting presidents on the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roslyn was on a playlist my dad made for my sister. Liked the song, but was oblivious to the band. Then my buddy told me to check out Skinny Love. Loved it, and I had a habit of buying full albums and listening to the entirety of them. This was like 2009. Have listened to them since! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if he set the moon free. Or something of the sort. And by freeing it linked the Fae and the Normal world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh child... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heritage, religious or not, is pretty important on how we comport ourselves, and being able to look back and see what our ancestors went through makes us a little more empathetic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator Hatch making me proud! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote him an email about this last night! How could would it be if that was the reason ha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just posted a link. The best way for a detailed map is to look up your representative and play around with the map on there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you seen Utah's Congressional districts? They are completely absurd! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 08:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Salt Lake is divided at I 80, North Salt Lake is coupled with most of southWest Utah, and everything in South Salt Lake is with Provo, Orem, Payson, Nephi, etc. Completely ridiculous!

Edit: A link for you troubles.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Utah%27s_congressional_districts?wprov=sfla1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cala boca porra! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump's hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 09:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/gallery/soT3ULY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, let's stop this drain the swamp thing. At least with this guy we get an old statesman republican instead of these younger neoconservative assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a personal email from him not too long ago, he made some specific comments about what I related to him, and probably copy/pasted the rest of it. 

For what it is worth, I like this guy better than the other dude we have in office who is basically butt buddies with Ted Cruz. Hatch is an old school Republican, which is kind of nice considering the younger neocons are all batshit insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Threat level midnight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's just back this up for a sec. Given the situation that this thread is, I think it is pretty clear why I have been insisting that the Word of Wisdom has one very specific interpretation, based on modern revelation. This is a core doctrine. It is so important that it is in temple interviews, and the prophets have given us a very specific definition for what it means.

The gospel is wonderful, and amazing, and everyone is welcome to interpret a plethora of scriptures, modern revelation, and personal revelation as they see fit, and that is what is great about the church. 

If this thread was discussing how we feel about commandments, or cultural differences in what is acceptable to ingest, then maybe I could see these comments being appropriate. This thread is an investigator who is trying to do what the missionaries have taught them. 

Giving advice that directly goes against what the doctrine means and advocating things like lying in TR interviews, or to the missionaries, and continuing the ingestion of substances prohibited by the WoW, and thus, leading the person away from what is being taught, is apostasy. 

You can have your own qualms with what it acceptable or not, and that is between you  and the Lord, but what the Church teaches on the subject, and this subject in particular, is black and white. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come to Church! There is nothing wrong with you attending. Just realize there are set commandments that dictate what is acceptable and what is not. And those tenants are not likely to change. Doesn't mean we won't welcome you, but asking others to accommodate your personal decisions in spite of what a set rule of beliefs for the church is asinine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because people do it doesn't make it right!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's not ok. These people have problems of their own with doctrine (which is cool, live your life howver) are not willing to admit it to themselves. 

The church has set guidelines for what is right and wrong. There are a lot of people here trying to rationalize their choices by quoting scripture and trying their own interpretations to it. On other scriptures, that is fine. This particular scripture, the Prophets God has ordained have said is meant to mean coffee and teas made with the tea leaf (black, green, white and oolong), hot or cold.

No where do they say anything about caffeine, mate, hot chocolate, or anything like that. It's just a fuss made by members. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your views aren't in line with set doctrine of the church, that's fine, it's your decision, but that is what constitutes apostasy. Just sayin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have ever been on a mission, you shold know what the WoW means. There are quite a few things that are open to interpretation, this isn't one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are trying to blur the lines for yourself and justify your habits on this one. 

I get that substitution is not much better, but when you are asked by the bishop about obeying the word of wisdom as interpreted by modern day prophets, you will not be breaking it by having soda or caffeine. 

As far as tea, it is the tea leaf that causes any sort of problem in the word of wisdom.

Caffeine was never the problem. It is the other things and ultimately obedience that is the bottom line of the word of wisdom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, and that is really the bottom line.

People have their own takes on the gospel, but in reality, there are certain things that we shouldnt drink/eat, as outlined per the missionaries lessons and the scriptures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I transfered from BYUI. Best decision of my life. Just come, you will enjoy it way more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wowowowow. Don't bring Sacramento into this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the Twilight from 4 to 9 where it is warm but you get a chilly breeze is perfect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 08:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any comments on anything you aren't a big fan of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 08:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which every character now has. It seems like only another Ult should be able to cancel it, ie twin blasts minigun, Khaimeras cull, etc, that way you don't get utterly destroyed because grub used his pull and the his Ult on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else annoyed with how easy Gideon's Ult is interrupted? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 08:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like even a stray hit from a melee character can stop it. It would be nice if only.ultimate blocked other ults instead of any random ability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meta? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, never knew this. The real LPT is in the comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 09:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Portland is an interesting team to work this trade with. I doubt they would part with CJ, but Harkless/Crabbe, plus Plumlee and a pick? That fills 2 voids in the rotations and levies a future for the Kings. That may seem low, and it is. But what else do the Kings really have to offer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 07:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High ave is right off the freeway and soooooooo close to downtown. It is my back yard, and there is already a lot of crime because the apartments around here are income restricted. Not to mention it is going to be a men's shelter. 300 homeless men 1 wall away from an apartment complex in a neighborhood that is already known for high crime rates is not a solution.

Putting the burden on the rest of the county would help. Also, not letting other states ship homeless folks here, or cleaning up the downtown drug trade in an actually effective way. Or building more affordable housing so families who are homeless can afford to rent in SLC where they work.

The citizens are getting the shaft so developers can make money, and there is no where to go. Everywhere slightly convenient or close to Trax is a small fortune just to rent, and there are a lot of complexes that are maintaining high prices and keeping apartments empty.

Let's address the other problems first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denny's is the ER of the food world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only thing open past midnight in a log of places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out the gospel topics section under church history in the scripture app. There is a lot of discussion on polygamy and early church history that I find enlightening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Upload the highest quality you have! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 06:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My soda? MY DIET DR. KELP?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 07:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree, but this is some beautiful and historically significant land. There is plenty of space in Utah for commercial use, but let's keep out of the beautiful part of utah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 07:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it was just a crap ton of random land, I would agree with the dude above. This is beautiful wilderness though. If they want land. Cache Valley, Beaver canyon, anywhere between beaver and cedar or beaver and Nephi are huge open spaces that no one is doing diddly squat with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to church, played video games with my dad, had dinner with my wife, then had some awesome sex! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After emailing Orrin Hatch, I would not mind having him as our president. Old, and a staunch Republican, but a seemingly likable guy. He has a plan to replace Obamacare, and I think could lead the party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 20:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Erin, throw me the scissors!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 08:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was, they ad libed a lot of this movie! Which is why I think you get the little comments and jokes. Gives the movie such an awesome feel! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 08:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Zeke, breakfast! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 08:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This band has some awesome music. Check out Mongo push, dance all night, cabin by the sea, spread too thin, lay me down. Soooo good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 08:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hands n my favorite animated film of all time, bordering on favorite movie ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It..... sounded cooler when I didn't know what it did. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is jokes, but in all seriousness, cities rarely have a basketball hoop. Last time I saw one was in a city that had a complex donated by the world record long jumper or something in like 1976? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 23:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I actually have the 1060 book. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 23:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to grab it from home. Tomorrow in the union around 11? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need the recipe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has said multiple times he loves the city and fans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said he wants to stay in Sac. No one ever hears it but the dude has repeatedly said he doesn't want to leave. He wants to end in Sacramento. 

Give the program another 2 or 3 years. They will make a lot of progress, I could even see them taking the 8 seed this year. Obviously the team needs some work, and some moving around, but they aren't in a *terrible* spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one, it's marked. 10 bucks and it is yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 04:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrible image. I laughed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that, and hopefully it works! I'm all for shelters, I just don't want the activity seen in Pioneer park to migrate south more than it already has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They claim the area is residential, but it is all industrial! If they are going to put it somewhere, at least put it in a neighborhood instead of off an industrial road.

Also, the crime in the area is already bad, it will only get worse from here on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It works just fine in my laptop. I even tried my 64 GB one from my phone, and it gave me the same message. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shelter is on high ave. I live around there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just got a letter from the city.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 05:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new homeless shelter is going up behind my apartment complex. This is already a shitty neighborhood, why not just completely let it go, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> K 100 D Memory card error </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i just inherited this camera from my brother, babysitting it for him while he is away for awhile. He took his SD card with him for a point and shoot, and so I went and bought a 32 GB SD card. It shows a memory card error everytime i boot up the camera. As far as i know he was using a similar capacity SD card. Any ideas on what to do?

I assume the camera is updated, firmware-wise, he has used it for awhile now. Even if it werent, i dont have a cable to use to hook it up to a computer.

Ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 05:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that the classical definition of a tragedy? We pity the character at the end of the story. I don't think the story is a happy story, especially with what the magic tree said and how that affects people's lives. Any way it ends, I think I will enjoy the last book, but it will be sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, yes, but there is a lot more than just that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 13:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has said, on numerous occasions, that he wants to be a king for life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 13:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think most people in general would argue that Westbrook deserves it over Curry. He is having a historic season. Curry is great, but Westbrook is a god  this season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 12:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course you do. All you Celtics think the guy is leaving for greener pastures or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 08:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boogie wont leave if he has any say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What a night for Turner ehh? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 07:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he is worth what we paid? Idk. Crabbe though, kinda disappointed with him. :/ what were your thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 06:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only part with Pam I didn't like was the part with the camera man. That just really got on my nerves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's city street sidewalks like around the trax at ballpark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like a terminator to kill terminators! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know someone who list his family when that happened. He happened to be in Lima when it happened, but his family was at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing that bugs me is that no one plows the sidewalks either. I have to walk through a mountain of snow to get anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 20:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should just implement a single payer system. I would gladly pay more in taxes if it meant not having to stay awake at night wondering if we will be able to afford medicine to keep my wife healthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator Lee voted to dismantle the ACA today. Ifor you disagree, it might be good to send a letter or phone call his way. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 11:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ACA means a lot to me. My wife is diabetic, and without the ACA, insurance companies can discriminate against her or choose not to cover anything related to her diabetes. My wife's life and health hang in the balance with this legislation.

If anyone you know has any chronic health problem, you should probably consider writing in for their sakes. Things like asthma, cancer, obesity, a family history of heart disease, a family history of dementia or other mental problems, Major depressive disorder, painkiller addictions, the list goes on and on.

One person alone cannot change much. I already wrote to senators hatch and lee. I, and many others, need this community's help, so if you have 5 minutes, shoot them an email. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 10:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm Dirty Dan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I speak for us all when we say that we need a link to your playlist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely understand that, and I'm glad.you have found a safe place to vent your frustrations. I'm really not talking about r/exmormon. I'm talking more about the fact that once a month there is a thread on the front page with tons of Mormon hate.

I'm fully aware that some times we as members of the Church, have a persecution complex, but I think it is safe to say Mormons are generally disliked in this community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey folks, just wanted to say thanks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 10:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This community doesn't carry the toxicity that some other subreddits carry, and is a shining light at times. 

Sometimes it feels like all of reddit is against us, but I'm glad this group exists and I'm happy I'm a part of it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 09:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
