<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 19:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to one of the more shitty pants sizes! Most places will limit you to 32x34 (too tight) or 34x34.

Congratulations, though! 175# is amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 00:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't reply to /u/black_angus1, you posted a top-level comment instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 22:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! Super impressive, but what was the second song? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 18:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But people live longer now, and are chubbier. Sounds like being fat makes you live longer!

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 16:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey its me ur brother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 15:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an incredibly unhealthily skinny guy who recently started showing up at my gym. He's about 6'2" and probably 150 lbs.

I know he's there to get fit, to put on some weight, and to make himself a better person. I respect the fuck out of him.

Most people go to the gym for themselves, not for other people. Go a few times, get a bit warmed up, and just do it. You can do it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 03:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You posted this to /r/mistyfront, not exmormon. OP didn't see this, FYI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 03:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Ultimate Guide to Shin Splints](https://www.reddit.com/r/running/comments/y7l3f/the_ultimate_guide_to_shin_splints/) from /r/running. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 17:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you invite two Mormons to go fishing? If you bring one, they'll drink all your beer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 16:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, hon, let's play some association games. In the OP:

OP's sister was **cheated** on, but SIL is **pregnant**.

In dash's comment:

Kevin has **cancer**, but it's Michael's **birthday**.

So, let's look for the similarities!

Someone has **something shitty**, but someone else has **something good**.

THAT is the point here. Cheif never said that cheating = cancer!

And, frankly, if you can't understand this, reread your last sentence.

Have a great day, pumpkin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 15:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might need to learn how to express yourself better. You said "Cheating happens every day" and "its not the end of the world." For both of these statements, you can insert "cancer" for "cheating" and the meaning remains the same. You did **not** say "cancer is worse than cheating."

Maybe if you learned how to adequately say what you mean, you wouldn't get showered in downvotes.

xoxoxo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 14:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, cancer happens every day, too. It's also often not the end of the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 15:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Illegal eviction, unfortunately. She probably needs to give him 30-60 days notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 23:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was exactly it!! Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 18:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, your super busy, too. Exhaustion doesn't help. Your hormones may have changed, but a simple blood test will reveal any problem. 

Outside of sex, do you masturbate? Look at porn?

Definitely bring this up with your therapist, and definitely with your PCP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 18:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could it be depression? I feel the same way when I'm depressed. I know that I *should* find a woman sexy, but I just *don't*. 

There are lots of other possible explanations, but that's my experience. Ask your therapist, definitely. /r/sex might be helpful, they have a part of their wiki dedicated to lost libido.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does this happen? Not all gif/webm/gyfs do this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 16:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple hard drive to Windows? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 03:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,

I have an apple hard drive that I can access in Windows via MacDrive 10. I can see all the folders, apps, etc.

HOWEVER, when I try to open any of the pictures (found through Users-[user]-Pictures-Masters-file, all the .jpgs say that the size is 0 bytes.

Am I doing something wrong? Where are they located on the drive?

Thanks for your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 22:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bok means book in Swedish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GZCL UHF calls for "legs up bench." What does that mean? Legs up in the air? Up on the bench?

Is this a safe exercise, and if not, what would you replace it with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 20:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand you won't be able to reply to everyone, sorry about the downvoters.

However, "stunts like this, his for-profit site," sound an awful lot like Deseret Book and the GAs profiting directly from their religious involvement. Do you have an issue with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 20:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm on a cut, how many calories does pre-denaturing my protein save? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 16:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I must have missed where Jeremy was the one who leaked it.

Per the uploader [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/exmormon/comments/4fkt3a/video_leak_jeremy_runnells_court_of_love_is_now/), Jeremy had nothing to do with the leak.

Do you have evidence to the contrary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 16:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is certainly evidence that God is real, just not such that you accept as being proof

What kind of evidence are you talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 14:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pulled 315x2 on DL!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 23:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See also: Ben Carson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 23:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll talk to them and authorize it. 

Major  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 02:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmm, been itching to try out the new ban hammer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 01:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> o7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 18:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yet my fat is around my mid section nowhere else.

[Lopez-Jimenez said that rather than relying solely on BMI to gauge obesity, we should be looking specifically for excess fat and whether its **disproportionately lodged around the midsection,** since both factors are associated with **poorer health outcomes.**](http://fivethirtyeight.com/features/bmi-is-a-terrible-measure-of-health/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 20:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, the church is sexist, racist, and homophobic. Those are it's core doctrines. The abuse he talks about stems from the "prophets, seers, and relevators." It's deep-baked.

I'd like to invite you to go over to /r/exmormon to see literally thousands of stories just like OPs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 17:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a woman? [This](http://strengthlevel.com/strength-standards/female/lb) puts her to "advanced" for all 3. It's pretty impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 17:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *her numbers

From [this](http://strengthlevel.com/strength-standards/female/lb) reference, she's "advanced" for all 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 14:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints, aka the LDS church, aka the Mormons, is absolutely based on lies.

The LDS church has not had the good fortune that Christianity or Islam has had, having a few thousand years pass. The Mormon church is recent! In recorded history! There's tons of documented evidence that all lead to the same conclusion:

The Mormon church is based on bullshit made up by an adulterous fraudulent con-man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 13:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, definitely. I'm from there and /r/mormon. /u/faman09, you'll find thousands of folks who know exactly what kind of shit you're talking about.

Congratulations on leaving, sorry that it's so shitty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 16:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nimble! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 12:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *facepalm* That's the point. Dog attacks are a fucking legitimate issue. I am making fun of your ignorance.

Educate yourself. Do you prefer the [Mayo Clinic](http://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/post-traumatic-stress-disorder/basics/causes/con-20022540) or [The National Institute of Mental Health](http://www.nimh.nih.gov/health/publications/post-traumatic-stress-disorder-easy-to-read/index.shtml)?

You can develop post-traumatic stress disorder when you go through, see or learn about an event **involving actual or threatened death, serious injury** or sexual violation.

and

PTSD is a real illness. **You can get PTSD after living through or seeing a dangerous event**, such as a war, a hurricane, or a **bad accident**. PTSD makes you feel stressed and afraid after the danger is over. It affects your life and the people around you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 12:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, who cares about war veterans? Sure, the saw some shit, and maybe did some shit. But it was years ago! It's over. It's done. Move on. Jesus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 01:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to like them when I was little. I think it was only because my fingers were small enough to have one on each finger, and I could twiddle my fingers and it was funny. Now I've got big hands and the novelty is gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 22:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, then it's not a bodyweight exercise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 22:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Muscle is muscle is muscle" implies that you could get to the 1000# club just with bodyweight exercises, which sounds like bullshit. You have to have progressive overload of your muscles. You will naturally hit a ceiling if you rely only on bodyweight.

Can you find me a bodybuilder who uses only bodyweight exercises? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 21:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At-will work can bite the employer. My employer can drop me any time they please. They could drop me because I don't like olives.

Similarly, I can drop them anytime and just quit. Further, by law, OP's GF has to be paid. The whole "by 1" bullshit is just a power play. Screw the pissed off boss. She's earned the money, and should get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 16:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 14:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, reddit doesn't do links or images like you tried to do (i.e. [img]xx[/img]). You should do:

    [words describing here](link.com) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 18:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha right? He's very excited about his call, but if he's going for baptisms, he'll have a hard time. He's going to a big city, it's absolutely beautiful. Hopefully he'll get more out of it, other than "I haven't baptized anyone therefore failure." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 18:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, yeah, I've already started planning care packages.

The CD player is a great idea, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 18:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, that's a great idea. My dad has a couple and loves them all. What about an LED camping headlight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My brother is going on a mission! Gift ideas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 18:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother is going on a mission to Scandinavia!

I didn't go on a mission, so I was wondering if you have any suggestions of good gifts to give him pre-mission. I'm pretty firmly atheist, but I love my brother and will support him in anything.

What has come to mind so far is an external battery pack (charging phones/ipads on the go), comfy socks, and good-quality headphones or earbuds.

Do you have any suggestions? Price isn't necessarily an issue.

Thanks for your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My brother is going on a mission! Gift ideas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 17:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother is going on a mission to Scandinavia!

I didn't go on a mission, so I was wondering if you have any suggestions of good gifts to give him pre-mission. I'm pretty firmly atheist, but I love my brother and will support him in anything.

What has come to mind so far is an external battery pack (charging phones/ipads on the go), comfy socks, and good-quality headphones or earbuds.

Do you have any suggestions? Price isn't necessarily an issue.

Thanks for your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My brother is going on a mission! Gift ideas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 17:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother is going on a mission to Scandinavia! 

I didn't go on a mission, so I was wondering if you have any suggestions of good gifts to give him pre-mission. I'm pretty firmly atheist, but I love my brother and will support him in anything. 

What has come to mind so far is an external battery pack (charging phones/ipads on the go), comfy socks, and good-quality headphones or earbuds. 

Do you have any suggestions? Price isn't necessarily an issue.

Thanks for your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 20:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both are raised to be wary of outsiders, both are raised to be completely reverential and unquestioning of authority, both think their leaders are protecting them from outside resources.

Weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 03:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we drawing direct comparisons between North Koreans and Mormons? I mean, I guess Monson is the "Dear Leader"... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 02:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't turn into *gold* gold, just goldish-silver. It should be noticeable if you put it next to a new white gold band, or next to platinum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk to your doc about taking prophylactic acyclovir. It has basically no side effects, and had greatly reduced the outbreaks, and length thereof, of cold sores in my fiancee and me. 

It's also super cheap, which is a plus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does the audio not match the video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 16:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've done the "Send Gmail As" in the stupid one. I also linked the accounts. However, when I reply to a forwarded email from my stupid account, the receiver has "Stupid on behalf of [myname] professional." Is there a way to change that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 16:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh, the send Gmail as in the stupid one? Because I tried in the professional one but it didn't work.

How do I link accounts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Replying to forwards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 16:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a gmail I've used since beta. I was a young kid, so the email is dumb, let's say "stupid@gmail"

I also have a professional one with a more formal account, "firstname.lastname@gmail".

I'm forwarding professional to amateur, since that's my main. However, if I reply to the forwarded from amateur, it has a sender as "stupid@gmail". Is there a way to reply from stupid@gmail, but the receiver would see it as firstname.lastname@gmail?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gmail forwarding with amateur and professional emails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 16:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a gmail I've used since beta. I was a young kid, so the email is dumb, let's say "stupid@gmail"

I also have a professional one with a more formal account, "firstname.lastname@gmail".

I'm forwarding professional to amateur, since that's my main. However, if I reply to the forwarded from amateur, it has a sender as "stupid@gmail". Is there a way to reply *from* stupid@gmail, but the receiver would see it as firstname.lastname@gmail? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
