<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7881</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The WSJ quoted a GOP official that said there were two officials unmasked and that Rice requested the unmasking of one.  That request wasn't for Flynn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's another Trump official's name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd want to hear it from something other than Drudge but that would be a massive deal.

Edit: Alexander suggests he keeps it.
https://twitter.com/PeterAlexander/status/849654583517487104 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Precisely.  Don't think that I'm buying a word of this explanation from the exec.  I'm not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean what could go wrong?  It's not like he's been asking for immunity so he can testify or anyth...shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be true if Bannon were anything other than a raving megalomaniac with a stated intention of destroying the administrative state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, but I don't see how they do that without admitting that the whole executive had concerns with him even being in the position in the first place.

And if they did, that means they heard the Yates warnings, had concerns and *still* ignored them?

This makes no sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't read that much into it.  Just "oh fuck, we gotta say *something*" flailing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so they knew Flynn posed some sort of risk that needed to be checked then?

Bold strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it means they have no idea what to say.

That's openly admitting major concerns over Flynn's loyalties within the executive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm saying Flynn went hours before the NYTimes dropped this: https://www.nytimes.com/2017/02/14/us/politics/russia-intelligence-communications-trump.html

A repeat with Bannon wouldn't surprise in the slightest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know how the Susan Rice story has another Trump official's name waiting to drop?

Yeeeeah... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Complicated.

He's pushing for much more French involvement but has previously had a focus on diplomatic resolutions.  That said, he's been speaking more forcefully of late and picked up Le Drian, the defence minister, as an outspoken supporter.

I've not caught a direct response to this from him yet and my French is crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed.

Very curious to see how the UNSC response goes.  If it weren't for upcoming elections I'd half expect European involvement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conventional not chemical, not that it helps the dead, injured or those treating them any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Steal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best bit is it appears that the target may have been someone else and that *that* story isn't public yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd be messy as hell to intervene but this has turned into something on the order of Bosnia.  I'm generally pretty doveish but there comes a point where quiet needs to be won by force of arms before peace can be discussed.

That said, NATO please if it's going to be anyone. God help everyone if Trump wades into the mess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britain: An Economy on the Brink </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leahy: We Should Go AfterWar Criminal Assad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll: Voters recoil from government shutdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vacancy: Right Wing Nutt Job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pauline Hanson's plane was bought by Bill McNee, former One Nation members say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's interesting to note how someone so beholden in the party room holds so much sway in Menzies House.

Money can't buy you everything but I guess it can buy you some things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amnesty calls for release of refugee Loghman Sawari in Papua New Guinea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 10:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2000 tickets sold was the number given to every media outlet by Think Inc yesterday, check almost any story.

The venues booked were Festival Hall in Melbourne, the ICC Darling Harbour Theatre in Sydney and the BCEC in Brisbane.  You can get their respective capacities off their respective web pages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 09:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Di Stefano really should be given a spin off in my opinion.

Him, Sainty and Workman are doing some pretty incredible leg work but where the tone doesn't bump it down a peg the association does.

Then again, maybe I'm just a crotchety old bastard and they're actually getting through to people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 09:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sold 2000 tickets to venues that seat conservatively 4 times that number?

lols indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, go easy on her.  It's not often that speaking tours fail to meet ticketing expectations *that* spectacularly.

Nothing like a bit of bitter sniping in rags like the Mail to salve a bruised ego. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps relevant for anyone who still has to travel, the EFF's guide for handling data at the US border.

https://www.eff.org/wp/digital-privacy-us-border-2017

They're pretty active about updating it as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No entry for US citizens without full tax records. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The irony being I'd probably trust the objectivity of Buzzfeed Australia's politics wing over Massola's output in recent years, regardless of tone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chemical attack in Syria poses profound questions for Donald Trump's leadership </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turns out he's not orange, he's yellow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And several of his predecessors along with him.

I wish I could get the missing links on our refoulement of Sri Lankans under Gillard for example.  The ends of the chain remaining have a lot of blood on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Our core values" meaning News Corp's, not Australia's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top teacher speaks out about youth prison system in crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me either but she'd be hard pressed not to be an improvement over Day, let alone Day's pick of Rikki Lambert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Qualified lawyer, ex Ernst and Young Kenya, worked for the SA Auditor General's office, legal aid volunteer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ABC story with updates as they come in here: http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-04-05/bob-days-election-ruled-invalid-by-high-court/8417204 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting.  That means FF aren't going to be able to name a replacement in all likelihood.

I can think of worse people to be in the parliament than Lucy Gichuhi if I'm honest.

Edit: Green speaketh - https://twitter.com/AntonyGreenABC/status/849418763392827392 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amnesty International report says billion-dollar offshore centre contracts should be made public </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda apt when those allies are led by Trump and May.

Horrifically reckless, but apt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turnbull's hoping to I'd say.  Brandis apparently thinks he's still got a shot at the courts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turnbull delays London appointment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prolonged isolation of children is torture.  Well and truly, established internationally and now *repeatedly* levelled against incarceration of minors in various forms in and by Australia.

An entrenched national blind eye to the scope and scale of our human rights failings seems a pretty pathetic reason to sugar coat either accusation or act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really.  I'm just curious why you, and you're far from alone to be fair, are so willing to deflect or distract from international criticism of our human rights record that'd you'd tie yourself in knots like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunno how you got the complete opposite from that. 

I read what she said and you quoted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet you argue her point for her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australia's rate of Indigenous child removal 'unique', UN investigator says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2000 tickets sold for the whole Australian leg of the tour per every media outlet when the venues booked were Festival Hall (2000-4500 seats), the Sydney ICC Darling Harbour Theatre (2500 seats) and Brisbane BCEC (4000 seats)?

Yeah, I'd say the "security issues" were more financial security.

Unsurprisingly, the hordes here have taken a different tangent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're lucky if they're at the bottom of the comments. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bit of both on the voting front.  A *lot* of discontent about the Liberals courting the far right from people who've voted for them many, many times at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've worked various ends of the refugee resettlement system for getting on towards 20 years.

My point is be careful of putting much credence in stereotypes, doubly so ones a generation old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 12:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I'm inclined to think that it's almost worth upvoting Quandrant articles for the self-satirical value.  Or perhaps as a warning unto others.

Sometimes.  Almost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barwon Prison youth unit 'incapable' of being lawful', court hears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It always rather irks the local conservative pollies when I point out my best fundraising *and* my best temp and crisis housing offers are now consistently drawn from Melbourne's inner south and east.

Elsternwick, Caulfield, Toorak, Malvern, Camberwell and Balwyn is my goto little arc these days and frequently are even out numbering family arrangements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Nations Peter Georgiou joins Liberals jet set </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Full Clint Watts: Trump Campaign 'Picked Up On' Kremlin Lines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 14:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liberals

budget

deliver

Ha Ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theresa May 'would go to war' to defend the sovereignty of Gibraltar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 12:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The majority failed to act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As it was DOON, so it is JAON. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schumer and McConnell

http://hosted.ap.org/dynamic/stories/U/US_NEWS_SHOWS?SITE=AP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL that the right to free speech now apparently includes the right to use a business' platform to monetise your bigotry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Government suspends its YouTube advertising, amid concerns about where revenue goes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 06:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll be called Fuego A Waco at the rate we're going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 06:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bishops central role in the fiasco is draining what respect many in the government may once have had for her. The perennial deputy Liberal leader can forget any ambitions she may still harbour to replace Turnbull should he fall or quit. The messages coming through from angry Liberals were things like: What the hell was she doing? Choosing her outfits for her next overseas trip? And: What about her staff? Were they absent on coiffure training? Not kind or pretty but a taste of the exasperation consuming MPs. It is not only the opposition that is lampooning Bishop for fashion diplomacy.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turnbulls muddle kingdom fails on extradition treaty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sky News axes Outsiders from schedule after sacking of Mark Latham </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bannon's care of [Jester Actual](https://twitter.com/th3j35t3r/status/847961984431771648): http://s3.amazonaws.com/storage.citizensforethics.org/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/31234502/Bannon-Steve.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In August, Federal Savings Chief Executive Steve Calk was named one of 13 economic advisers for the Trump campaign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicago bank tangled up in intrigue over ex-Trump aide Manafort </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Flynn: new evidence spy chiefs had concerns about Russian ties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a fun link.

https://www.washingtonian.com/2013/05/29/what-you-should-know-about-jim-comey-obamas-choice-to-lead-the-fbi/

As a federal prosecutor in Richmond, Comey started Project Exile, which federalized local gun cases and delivered harsh sentences to those convicted of weapons charges. Comeys prime backer in that project? The then-deputy attorney general, Eric Holder. Comey was so proud of his Richmond work that a gun confiscated in Project Exile hung in his office as general counsel at Lockheed Martin after leaving the Bush administration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ivanka Trump complained when the media called her adviser. Now shes officially an adviser. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At a very high level?  Tough economic times, a portion of society feeling left behind and a visible and sufficiently marginalised ethnic "other" overlapping those same struggling suburbs and doing better at it than the white population, or at least that segment of it.

There'd be an argument to be had that the rough ends of groups like Melbourne Sharps provided relatively fertile ground for the racial politics to be applied on top of what were originally basically apolitical groups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The archetypical, enduring face of it in Australia would be [Jim Saleam.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jim_Saleam)

The Australia First Party remains a going concern and Saleam's been acting as a mentor for Reclaim Australia with the splinter groups co-opting various adherents to various degrees toward their various heads.

Going back a bit you've got the big upswing of far right groups in the late 80s and very early 90s of which Romper Stomper and the various bits of literature surrounding that film go into in fairly great detail.

Before that you're back to National Action and the National Socialist Party.

If you want to go WAY back you could look at Australian nationalist and anti-semitic groups stretching from pre-WW2 right back to the last quarter or so of the 1800s.  A history of The Bulletin might be a good starting point there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually this one's a pretty big deal.  If Tony's sniping, he's sniping over a major foreign policy matter.

If he's *not* sniping, Turnbull is struggling to maintain even a semblance of respect for human rights within the current government.  Even less so than Abbott managed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump actions boosted Russian effectiveness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll have to do some stuffing around with schedules but it *should* be doable so long as they can orchestrate it properly.

Interestingly, SkyNews are saying they've got their deal with NXT as well in return for "measures on gas and electricity". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr Abbott told News Corp those sources had "grievously misled" journalists, adding "I regret to say that you cannot trust senior Government sources at this time".

No sniping... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tony Abbott says he was warned against China extradition treaty when Prime Minister </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A failure replicated in part or entirety in every state and territory in the country, and a few beyond.

What we learn from this royal commission needs to be applied in every place Australia deprives a child of liberty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kathy Jackson: Police to lay more charges against former HSU boss, court told </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Company tax cuts will NOT pass Parliament before the budget - the House of Representatives has just adjourned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what is he in the sheets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good.  Of particular note the reasonable victim test stands unchanged.  The potential gutting of that provision was far more egregious than the headline wording change.

On to debating the procedural changes which have reasonably broad support.

I'll laugh my fucking arse off if, after all the bluster and vitriol, Brandis and co. end up handing the AHRC the power Triggs has been seeking all this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bit of viral marketing for a new Viacom show going by the whois. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This proved a deeply, deeply unpopular decision in WA.

It won't sway everyone but when you're already surviving by a few percentage points it doesn't have to swing many. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don Dale ignored rules for 'at risk' kids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 07:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's going to be some very, very uncomfortable Coalition MPs in marginal seats when this comes to a vote in the house.

Marvellous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graham on Nunes Controversy: 'It's a Mess' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victoria leads the way on family violence, but Canberra needs to lift its game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cashless Debit Card causes social and economic harm  so why trial it again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Nunes-White House question, assessed minute-by-minute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in someone who receives and sells stolen goods?  Kinda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interior secretary Zinke says Mexico border wall might not fully be a physical wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A SCOTUS Obamacare Ruling May Doom Trump's Sanctuary Cities Crackdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little England at the rate you're going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's also an alternative timeline where Mark Latham becomes PM and something other than losing to Howard triggers the same fragile insecurities turning him into the stark raving lunatic prick we see before us today.

Only in public office and setting a national policy agenda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't have a very good grasp of what free speech means.

Why change the timbre of the entire Australian free speech debate over this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Local Infowars franchise.

***GOBLINS!*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That explains the resurrection of the @realmarklatham account.

Ross Cameron next would be too much to hope for wouldn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neoliberalism 'has run its course', says ACTU boss Sally McManus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bit of me wonders whether you just did.  A future one anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McManus' National Press Club speech is worth watching in its entirety when you can, for the tone of the address as much as for its content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Penalty rate cut: Opposition swings crossbenchers to block Government's penalty rates cut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Front page of the subreddit, not of reddit.

Stickies like this are excluded from /r/all and /r/popular etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://apps.washingtonpost.com/g/documents/national/read-the-letters-detailing-how-sally-yates-was-blocked-from-testifying-on-russia/2390/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 13:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well past due but very welcome.

You can remember the mistakes and the mistaken of history just fine without monuments standing in their honour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yuri Potapov and The Order of Zhukov </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 06:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been likening Mensch to The Lone Gunmen.

Kooky conspiracist?  Absolutely.  She's just also had an alarming record of turning out to be there or there about when it comes to the truth of things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Court rules in favour of Victorian man over NDIS payment of transport costs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 06:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Bolt Report breaches ACMA rules after running pro-marriage equality ad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the actual fuck is up with the ABC's reporting on this?

It's been absolute garbage even excluding Uhlmann's particularly mendacious output. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your handy guide to political newspeak - David Marr </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After his health care defeat, Trump's two options are bad and worse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Labor to block Australia-China extradition treaty amid human rights concerns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AG Dutton, he has experience in law enforcement after all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All of the untrue things Trump said in his Time interview about truth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toddler in Chief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [trump_irl](http://i.imgur.com/VHaCTmh.gifv) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the post again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This got the cover.

http://time.com/4710614/donald-trump-fbi-surveillance-house-intelligence-committee/

With this print

http://time.com/4709920/donald-trump-truth-time-cover/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally I'd agree but there's something to be said about letting a torrent of stupid that spectacular erupt unimpeded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now remember this. When I said wiretapping, it was in quotes. Because a wiretapping is, you know today it is different than wire tapping. It is just a good description. But wiretapping was in quotes. What Im talking about is surveillance.

Beyond satire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Read President Trump's Interview With TIME on Truth and Falsehoods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian bank sends threatening letter to computer scientist who called for Trump investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if you'd shift Damian Drum?  His division politics has a few rankles when it comes to the Libs and I'd wager the locals would be pretty supportive of the inquiry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christensen's still threatening it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe listen to what Khan said instead of what a Trump kid tweets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Banking inquiry: Nationals senator to cross floor and vote against Government to support Greens bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> False.  Leak's lawyer sent a letter *refusing to make a formal submission* and demanding some sort of public platform.  Triggs' testimony on that fact before the senate stands, despite all the bleating from News Corp.

Again, Leak was too busying trying to grandstand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's *exactly* the type of scum who radicalises them, just a different brand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention that many of the draft plebiscite proposals failed to even make it to equality.

"Do you approve of a law to permit people of the same sex to marry?" is *not* equality on both gender grounds and the ability for the government to establish separate legislation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the vicious vitriol that necessitated millions in mental health care expenses to be budgeted *and* with the ability to try and desperately stack participation to ensure a "No"?

I can see why Dutton's a fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Dutton backs voluntary postal plebiscite on marriage equality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A stain on the AFP who have been outed as merely political tools.

Again.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The QUT students won their defence, Bill Leak refused to even offer a defence, *twice*, because he was too busy trying to grandstand.

If you're talking about vexatious litigants, the AHRC and Triggs in particular have been pushing to have more discretionary powers for the Commission in that regard since she took on the role. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you do if it stopped?

I'd start it again, Brian.

:D

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  Correctional services in name only. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fairly depressing read and perhaps a reminder that these are problems with the our standard of care for those in our youth justice system Australia wide, not just in some pocket of abuse comfortably removed from wherever you might be.

Hopefully these formal findings are the impetus the Andrews government needs to finally take the now long-standing concerns seriously.  The frankly uncaring attitude towards both rights and outcomes displayed by Lisa Neville over recent months doesn't exactly inspire confidence in that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Same Four Walls - Inquiry into the use of isolation, separation and lockdowns in the Victorian youth justice system [PDF] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About that....

http://www.newsweek.com/pizzagate-trump-russia-clinton-podesta-comet-ping-pong-pedophiles-david-seaman-572578 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My suspicion is they'll retire it around the time iOS, hopefully iOS 11, integrates it into the core operating system.

It's useful as it is, baked into iOS with system wide APIs it would be amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to be blunt but what utter bullshit.

This is a tested law now over 20 years old with established case load and judicial precedent from the nations highest courts.

The meanings, standards and thresholds of the extant wording are well established, long applied and tested repeatedly by appeal.  It is not sufficient to hand-wave away the exclusions of 18D in order to argue a point of constitutionality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll probably be to deflect more.  It *should* be for him to recuse himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eric Garland goes into some quality Twitter ranting on the subject in this thread

https://twitter.com/ericgarland/status/844553799335366657 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Devin Nunes's Curiously Selective Memory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That, and in this instance that money's likely to disappear into a Cayman shell company while the whole project goes tits up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simply causing offence isn't the bar however.

18C is only fulfilled in the case of "profound and serious effects, not to be likened to mere slights" by virtue of the decision in Creek v Cairns Post Pty Ltd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 18C doesn't criminalise anything, it's not a criminal law.  

Furthermore, whilst freedom of speech is a right that must be protected, 18C enshrines a human right of its own (ICCPR Article 20) and with far more discretion and exclusions offered than it strictly might. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no relevant federal definition of harass.

There's multiple, differing definitions at a state level.

There's an Australian Law Reform Commission report from a couple of years ago calling on the need for a Commonwealth Harassment Act to resolve the problem.

The closest analogue law likely to be drawn upon, New Zealand's Harassment Act 1997, would set the term as a superset of the existing 18C wording, including offensive material. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link?  I've not caught it in the AFR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 10:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excuse the Twitter link to a paywalled article but this is huge news and just breaking as of a few minutes ago.

This guts the government's economic agenda.  Completely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Turnbull government is preparing to shelve the bulk of its $47.8 billion company tax cut. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 10:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Not a hypothetical': Shorten slams PM over changes to race hate laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 10:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take 'em how I can get 'em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's mostly just political optics.

There was public outcry over Syrian refugee movements when this intake was announced and ministers were able to pretend they were prioritising Christians to a degree sufficient to fool the Daily Tele crowd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Media and/or judicial scrutiny has been the go to method of getting action out of the immigration department since the Howard era unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a surprisingly common taboo worldwide in places, or communities originating from places, with poor quality health care.

You start with a situation where cancer has an incredibly high mortality rate and the disease gets directly associated with death, both by the individual and communities more generally.  People don't want to deal with the stigma so they try and ignore things to the last minute by which point they're often past the point of treatment and the whole cycle becomes self-fulfilling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sword of Damocles hangs over Turnbull </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, Commissars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their agenda probably doesn't include their commentariat providing an impressionable president with more than enough rope to hang himself with.

Consider this turning on the parental controls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox drops analyst who said UK could have helped spy on Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are CPUs even available for the iMacs yet?

Like much of the stagnation from Intel really hurt with these machines and I wouldn't be surprised if they waited until the USB C issues got sorted given the current teething issues.

I feel the pain though, I'll throw money at the screen the second the next update is announced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And deservedly so.

My concern is whether Australian society more broadly will follow suit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, "and" would infer that all conditions must be met concurrently.

The way our courts treat part a is simply to handle the test as a single test.  Any combination may be satisfied but the court is not obligated to describe how and why a particular aspect of the circumstances of the case that meets the standard of the reasonable victim test relates to an individual word, eg. humiliate.

It's considered unnecessarily verbose, open to vexatious nitpicking of decisions and is a circumstance replicated throughout our legal system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should add, the test under part a is singular, not compound.

The phrase "offend, insult, humiliate or intimidate" is taken as a block, not individual assessments around each word.

On top of that, there's a fairly significant threshold established under Creek v Cairns Post Pty Ltd requiring "profound and serious effects, not to be likened to mere slights".

That said, yes I'd say that's where we disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The latter would likely fall under Division 4 of the Disability Discrimination Act, particularly as the act includes a disability imputed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the act is reasonably likely, in all the circumstances

This is the section that invokes the reasonable victim test.  Basically any complaint under 18C must satisfy that a reasonable person would be insulted or offended, that 'person' effectively being an anthropomorphism of the standard of the courts established through case law and instruction.

The frequently cited example in the context of the Racial Discrimination Act is taken from Corunna v West Australian Newspapers, a case over a derogatory cartoon over the return of the head of Yangan from the British Museum.

In that case a combination of a demeaning portrayal of a significant figure in Yangan, a demeaning and derogatory representation of another religious figure, treatment of the subject of death in a manner widely considered offensive within the relevant indigenous communities, intimate details of ancestry of individual people involving rape and a perceived diminishment of their race by consequence *and* an unsupported and stereotypical view of indigenous people taking advantage of government assistance all culminated in the reasonable victim test of the case being satisfied.  Not the impact on a specific individual but transgressing on a standard of the court.

In that instance, despite satisfying the reasonable victim test and thus "failing" under 18C it was still deemed that the cartoon was presented in good faith and thus satisfied the exclusions under 18D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As for the RDA in it's current form, i think it is seriously wrong that you can be prosecuted for words you have said that someone has interpreted as being insulting/offensive to them based on their race.

But you can't.

The current implementation of 18C isn't about proving whether or not the complainant was insulted or offended.  It's covered by a reasonable victim test.

Disturbingly it appears Brandis intends to make good on gutting that provision along the lines of the Abbott era drafts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The extant protections of the racial discrimination act, particularly when coupled with an AHRC empowered in the manner it has been seeking to deal with vexatious litigants.

More generally, incitement to discrimination, hatred or violence on grounds of race, faith, sex, sexuality, disability or age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a suite of federal antidiscrimination legislation consisting mainly of the Australian Human Rights Act, the Age Discrimination Act, the Disability Discrimination Act, the Sex Discrimination Act and the Racial Discrimination Act.

As for the existence of Section 18C specifically, it's the federal instrument implementing our obligations under Article 20.2 of the International Covenant on Civil and Political Rights which states:

Any advocacy of national, racial or religious hatred that constitutes incitement to discrimination, hostility or violence shall be prohibited by law.

Our implementation already offers far greater discretion and the exclusions of 18D that a strict implementation of the ICCPR wouldn't permit.  We also fall short in that the religious aspect of the ICCPR right is only federally protected for ethnoreligious groups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The left never stopped caring about freedom of speech, it does however seem to have a far better grasp of the fact that "freedoms to" are coexistant, complemented and contrasted with "freedoms from".

As to why this has been labelled a right wing issue, I would suggest it's because largely only a very vocal subset of Australia's right, and particularly far right, discourse that feels in any way constrained by the law.  The why of that would unfortunately appear to be the obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 10:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non-racist?

Don't buy it.  After all, shitdrummer said... ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only the guardian...

http://www.theage.com.au/federal-politics/political-opinion/racehate-law-changes-gesture-politics-from-the-people-who-claim-to-be-above-it-20170321-gv2vri.html

http://www.theaustralian.com.au/opinion/columnists/greg-sheridan/gesture-politics-the-stuff-of-dreams/news-story/19a05470e9478a41bb2aa59f327645d8

https://www.themonthly.com.au/issue/2015/december/1448888400/megan-davis/gesture-politics

http://past.oxfordjournals.org/content/203/suppl_4/9.full

http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/middleeast/gaza/11020629/Scotlands-biggest-city-accused-of-gesture-politics-as-Palestinian-flag-raised-in-Glasgow.html

http://nypost.com/2008/06/13/gesture-politics/

http://www.nytimes.com/2005/01/23/magazine/the-triumph-of-gesture-politics.html

Oh dear.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May it continue to do so for the others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dogwhistle, an intentional shaming of Turnbull, just fucking crass or a combination of the above.

Take yer pick.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don Dale: Teenagers mistreated after tear-gassing win lawsuit against NT Government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coalition's 18C overhaul a hollow and operatic outbreak of gesture politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to see a protest and particularly encouraging to see the tone of it.

Think Inc are starting to set a bit of an editorial line on this of late.  Curious to see whether it continues.

Edit:  Cheers for the racist PMs cowards.  Its always a pleasure getting an inbox full of vitriol from you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watering down race hate laws at the behest of the far right, and on Harmony Day of all days.

The harass switch is a pointless nothing.  The destruction of the reasonable victim test that they're proposing along with it however is far from nothing.

I wonder if Malcolm ever thought he'd be humiliated this completely when he signed on to join the Liberals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not when it's a superset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nauru detains two detention centre guards after revoking visas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New ABC chairman set to be Justin Milne, NBN board member and ex-Telstra exec </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even the "contradiction" Pezzullo raised was weak as piss.

"The arrangement struck with the Obama administration included **an aim or a goal of 1,250 persons**," he said.

"So honouring the agreement would take you into that ballpark."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Immigration Department contradicts DFAT on US refugee resettlement deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we just stick our heads in the sand, ignore an encroachment on the human rights of others because we'll have bigots bleating about free speech when their "martyr" can't even be found to have acted in good faith?  This is how you intend to protect a human right?

Wallpapering over racism and bigotry isn't dealing with it.

Again, what is your alternative protection? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And your alternative?

We've the protection of a human right enshrined in this Section.  Would you prefer a strict interpretation of Article 20 of the ICCPR with no judicial discretion or exclusion?

The existing law provides ample opportunity for defence with the oft referenced failures being Bolt failing to meet even the broad exclusions of 18D and Leak failing to even attempt a defence of his actions under it.

Empower the Human Rights Commission to quell vexatious cases, *as they have been requesting for years*, and I fail to see the concern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no definition of harassment at a Commonwealth level.  There's multiple differing definitions at a state level.

We just had an ALRC publication highlight the need for formal consolidation of disparate law with a Commonwealth Harassment Act as a specific proposal.  The closest examples we'd have are the UK and NZ 1997 Harassment Acts.  Both deal with individuals and the latter at least *still* covers offence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or be stupid enough to take a clause their own side was criticising as too vague and making it vaguer.

Harass is an extremely nebulous term. Particularly at a federal level and even more so when directed at groups as well as individuals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arguably an even *more* nebulous wording than the current, especially when applied to a group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now let's see if Broadbent and Laundy are willing to cross the floor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 07:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's been more than a few News commentators tying themselves in knots over this awkward little conundrum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Private mobile phone numbers of nearly every federal MP accidentally published online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 05:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
