<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8211</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may also increase survivability in general. In my game we use PF rules and max HP. Which means that actually killing players is very hard, so long as the squishies don't try to act as front-liners. At that point it's their fault anyway. For example, a 5th level barb with a respectable, but not great 16 con would have to take 91 damage to drop dead. At 5th level that's plenty of buffer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did toy with the idea of making drinking rules. I like theorycrafting. Decided even thinking about having actual drinking rules was pointlessly overcomplicated.

What I did come up with, in case you actually want to see it, is: 1. A bunch of DCs for different alcohols. 2. Con check vs DC+amount of previous drinks(in last 24 hours) or suffer penalties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I basically started from the end backwards... the end of what would, if left to run its course be at least a 2-year regularly scheduled campaign...

I'm pretty sure I'll have to retire first before I see a satisfying resolution of the endgame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A multi-scope Mass Effect game.

Basically a combo of ME, StarCraft, FTL, Star Citizen, homeworld and galactic civilizations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH, I'm pretty damn happy with Mass Recall.

This does make me wanna warn everybody to got and get Mass Recall before Blizzard takes it down when they try to push this remaster.

What I do eagerly away though, is the D2 remaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear god, as a player do I hate that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A) NONE of these are particle physics.  
B) It is not reasonable. Heck D D doesn't even have a concept for acceleration.

Do not look too deep. For the shapeshifting bit... well, speed is a defined property in D D momentum is not. Therefore speed is preserved, seeing as how that makes things more interesting.

See, this was an example of the proper reasoning. "What is more plausible/realistic/fitting" is faulty. "What is more fun and dramatic" is the correct attitude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose there's a chance it might not be, but the channel suggests he was just a random dude with a drone in the right place at the right time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We live in a glorious fucking future where that's the kind of shots delivered by citizen journalism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 52 hours.... what a casual. I'm 4 months in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a moment. About 3 months of my life when I did nothing but play all the classic bioware RPGs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean [this](http://www.wizards.com/dnd/files/WildMagicTables.rtf) one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drama I don't wanna deal with. Why I made up the deck of many silly things. Gives things like bad bedhair, a tan or cake... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. Otherwise known as exposure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rolling shutter. Image is scanned progressively. By the time the scan reaches another part of the image, the propeller has moved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading Dresden now.

TBH, it would change literally nothing. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zelazny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, and horses are better than violins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol... my slider is disabled at the off position and on top it says "some settings are managed by your organization".

It must have gone the way of the dodo via one of the group policies I set up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That riff at "To love the earth is our desire"... it reminds me so much of another song, but I can't for the life of me remember. I think it's a classic rock song. It's killing me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That moment she said "Hit it sisters!"... I knew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why'd you have to remind me... 2018 is so far away......... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would never happen as it is not enforceable, but one can dream... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a song on when I opened this. She synced perfectly to the beat of the song. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Redditors are tan on the inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason this reminds me of Welcome to the Jungle. :)

As long as they don't take themselves too seriously, it'll be a fun movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have... but only on vanilla Civ4:BTS... not yet on the megamod I'm playing. I was close once... but then the SSD with my 6-month old savegame perished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take notes, make checklists and compile 5-year plans.

I'm in the middle of a game right now. At war with 3 nations. My turn consists of 15-20 distinct agendas such as winning a war on 2 fronts, keeping a lid on the 3rd, spreading religion, securing resources, building up my navy, expanding to the islands on the other side of my empire, constructing a comprehensive road network, so reinforcements get to where they're needed faster, using spare workers to improve my core cities, exploring the world, managing 3 distinct blocks of cities producing different things and trying to stay afloat financially, without completely tanking my research potential. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're misattributing the problem here. His is not a character, just a stick figure for him to act his impulses within the game.

But I agree, the real issue is irritating to suffer through, both as player and DM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to use that once for placeholder text on some CMS stuff I was doing. It was funnier to look at while I was working on the task. I was sadly told to stop when some business people began enquiring why the staging server had become... so meaty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gonna go with Stab-over-IP, but it turns out in this sub I am clever neither with my references, nor with my abbreviations. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also refused to lock down my devices. Even now they have an unlock, just because it is enforced by the VPN credential storage.

But then again I also don't trust "the cloud" at all. I use KeePass over LastPass and I handle everything myself. My cloud is my machine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using obscure rules is not, I repeat, NOT the same as getting them completely wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About half of my characters have been the opposite gender. It's not very relevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your name doesn't happen to be Durkon, does it? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, BC breaks once in a blue moon are healthy for an ecosystem. It allows you to ditch all the baggage that's accumulated over the years.

'course, as it relates to something as low-level like actual silicone, I might be talking out of my ass here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The paradox part comes from the physical bit contradicting the mathematical bit. There. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no... however shall we survive that 20% deficit you claim is there... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, you know... just double the playback speed of OP's video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... what's the opposite of that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Client-side validation... silly Xiaomi. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *dakka dakka dakka dakka* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome thingie. The visor is a great touch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a personal thing. Fan of smaller parties. For me 5. 4 is barely playable, 3 best party ever. 2 works, but lacks the characteristic party dynamic, 1's not a party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me, I'd be miffed by that particular rule. But then again if I was in that campaign I'd have already done my best to convince you to get rid of it before it even began.

On the DM side I would have handled it by simply not having such a stupid house rule.

So yes, there is a bad call, but it wasn't made here and now, but in the beginning of the campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone please explain the beginning bits? What did they say to cause the "get the fuck out"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes people's minds linger on that, as OP said, "short bit of tasteless humor". Makes it more likely for [Drew](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UBVV8pch1dM) to get involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would indeed be great, but that last sentence doesn't really carry enough information to verify this is the case. But it is a reasonable implication. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still not how physics works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One-shots galore! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if Obama himself received them from Richmond Valentine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FemShep looked weird to me too... you get used to it. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plausibly? Giant meteor crash. There is nothing terrestrial that can wipe out microbial life in that short a timespan. By giant I mean something large enough to be spherical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand them. I still confuse vegan and vegetarians. I laugh at the meme-worthy examples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instrument flying is a required skill for all commercial pilots flying passengers, I believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really isn't.

It was meant as an attempt to shake the lazy, knee-jerk simulationist attitude towards a game that is in no way simulationist. Trying to transpose these isolated chunks of real-world trivia onto the universe of D D is... sketchy at best. Silly and absurd at worst. For crying out loud, in the rules there exists no concept for even something as fundamental as acceleration.

Don't get me wrong, discussions like this to try to find out where the line in the sand is drawn are amusing, but someone has to point it out for the sake of the great mass of people who'd just go right ahead and build their sand castles out of wet sand otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Draw from life. Literally the most basic piece of advice any art student will get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The strength of gestalt is in getting 2 sets of CLASS FEATURES. I have no idea where you're getting that 1.5 EL figure, but right now this is at most 1.1 EL. If you're being generous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of what makes a good character is knowing when and under what circumstances they are willing to break their code, discard their ideals, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got ways to go, but a neat start. You seem to also need plenty of practice with perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't explain the system very well.

Is it buy 4 out of 5 of any class? If yes, then it is essentially gestalt, without the second class's class features. I.e. gestalting with an NPC class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to apologize. I'm not into that PC bullshit.

But it is important knowing where the source of racism lies and to what it is applied.

An elf refusing to marry a human because of their short lifespan is, fundamentally a form of racism, justified under the circumstances. An elf shopkeep refusing service to a human for the very same reason is uncalled for bigotry(a briefer lifespan has no bearing on the ability to purchase goods). This is probably not a very good example, but I hope it conveys the point.

Using humor to deal with questionable subjects should be allowed, but that's about the only reasonable blanket statement one can make. Anything more requires context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 12:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fond of the lovecraftian paragon myself.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 11:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you say "but are not racist"... well, the overview from the sidelines begs to differ.

Figuring out exactly what racism means(to you, to them) would do you good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 11:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Physics and biology in D D works in such a way(DIFFERENTLY FROM REAL LIFE) that no one suffers hair loss, unless required by plot.

There we go :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 11:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of [this](https://imgur.com/a/qBDce). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since a couple of weeks ago I am eminently happy to be part of the group that got that reference. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burning Wheel also has some concepts that apply.

But dear god, will this fall on deaf ears in this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 10:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your intuition is going to get the resolution part extra wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The misuse of the word "theory" has been is one my largest pet peeves in science.

There is a great video I always refer anyone suffering from this misconception to: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1uzsuCFUQ68 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 09:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quality real life ragdoll physics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just 5e? It has meant squat in all editions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah... yes. :)

I seem to be watching you on dA. Probably why this looked familiar :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Colville

P.S. Also, don't be a creative scrooge. Allow your players to influence the world and the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I've already seen this. Who's the artist? Was it posted anywhere else recently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **It is literally illegal by the rules.**

Any playable character must have at least 3 int. You cannot play an animal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stargate. Course the pilot episode was a feature-length movie so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nat 20 auto success skill checks.

"I jump to the moon." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not really. I generally decide the absolute difficulty of the task. Working on the chance of success invalidates the mechanics entirely.

But this is still just a game and if you are intent on making it silly, you will succeed. In fact it's disturbingly easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From your post you've already shown you're perfectly aware of the problem, which means you know what to discuss with him. Just sit him down and tell him this isn't a book. Or a play for you to be his unwitting actors. Try to explain in whatever approach is reasonable for him that the MAIN idea of this game is player agency in the world, not opportunity to bear witness to the DMs fancy. That is what books, movies and stage plays are for. This is neither...  
You get the point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DC X:

Have a bonus X-1 or greater? No check. Auto success.  
Have less than that. Check.  
Have less than X-20. No check. Auto fail.

Tada! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 09:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, for projects on that scale that's probably a CHEAP way to stay ahead of the curve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of us are unable to afford all the gaming platforms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't have to care before either. It just got slower as you went along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But PS4, so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Equating D D gold to IRL gold is a pretty big assumption.

Might wanna look into trade goods as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH I don't mind waiting 10 minutes for a game. If I'm queuing I have time to kill. I can easily just watch an episode or the youtubes while waiting, but this auto-region-reset is annoying as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/DnD/comments/5wxt9k/im_struggling_to_contextualise_some_of_the_stats/dedq69z/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incidentally I have my own campaign VCed. It's weirdly useful organizationally.

Also saved it when my drive went up in flames.

I'd help, but you know... I'd rather work on my own setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You presented a false equivalence drawn from a faulty assumption. I merely pointed that out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to note that the system from the article is not a system where 25 is the max. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the article is filed under "D D 3.5", so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't suppose you wanna substantiate those claims with actual references? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh... No. There is no max stat in 3.5 so your comparison falls flat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be surprised if that worked TBH.

Btw... git and github work just as well for collaboration on project like these just as easily as for more technical projects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going wherever you please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also /r/hardbodies :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manowar - Dawn of Battle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THERE CAN BE ONLY ONE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shepard indoctrination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way the rules say... duh.

In both cases. Though if the PCs get to that point they will have royally fucked up somewhere along the way. In general best to avoid inglorious deaths like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On turn, you can talk all you want, within reason. Out of turn you can respond or say up to a sentence or two yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adapted in the sense that it's not explicitly turn based, just behind the hood. Things like initiative and rounds are hidden from plain view. There was also an extra skill for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
