<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9815</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That night be a deal breaker. Like I want to be a hipster about it not a purist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe we can swap him back for Neshek? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These hats are so dope. But the shipping on their site sucks. 

Although some on ig commented that having the eyes be baseballs would've been cool too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shitposts only kill subreddits. true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A [problem](https://www.reddit.com/r/running/comments/67ftn3/super_moronic_monday_your_tuesday_weekly_stupid/dgqfrjs/) that this sub has helped me with in the past! 

I also discovered my Battery Park [Turkey friend](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zelda_(turkey)_) died because of your comment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [serious] In terms of plantar fasciitis is seeing a doctor helpful? When I had it 2 years ago, my GP ordered xrays on my foot to confirm what I kind of already knew. I didn't follow through because time and money constraints, but is that helpful? I did also feel super unmotivated to run and took basically a year off for it to go away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you gotta bend to the will of the people but this chaos has made me realize why r/running was my favorite sub before. All the things people are complaining about, including posting struggles, *unique journeys*, either come up in one of the daily threads or are shared in the race reports. People are wack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many people don't know this but Brooklyn has it's own kind of coyote. They're called *red-tailed hawks* and we as a city have set up a system to have them watched and monitored at [all times](https://patch.com/new-york/west-village/watch-live-nyu-hawks-welcome-baby) 

We are ever ready for coyote attacks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Running my 2nd half marathon ever. Feeling under trained. Again. I'm worried I'm going to kill myself and then feel unmotivated to run the rest of the year. (I'm already signed up for another half in November.) 

How do people run marathons though. I'm dreading 13.1 miles with training.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which the Department of Health conveniently ignores. There's some weird stuff out there about bodega cats http://www.wnyc.org/story/bodega-cats-their-own-words/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Persistence Hunting   Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based off the life changing experience reading Born to Run by Christopher McDougall, I knew that in addition to training for my next marathon I needed to make a change in my diet. 

Persistence Hunting! What was it? Was it for me? Could I successfully change my diet and lifestyle by spending hours stalking my prey until they finally died? What would that look like? 

As I live in Brooklyn, this proved challenging. To simulate the deer/antelope stalking experience, I began to spend my Saturdays on stalking missions. Each week my goal was different.  I would jog a considerable distance and then pop into a bodega. In the first one I would find my target: strawberry frosted poptarts. I allowed myself the briefest look, just close enough to motivate me to continue on, then I would extricate myself and continue my stalking mission. 

The next bodega I allowed myself a touch. 

Until finally I collapsed next to the friendly bodega cat, feeling their dry tongue licking up my perspiration, and I would cave and buy the pop tarts. 

Someday: real antelopes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you also post this a year ago? because it's funny either way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I smell collusion!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is such a weird bot. All of the posts are just running* related links but like zero commenting or interaction? Plus this pinterest post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there is maybe one troll in this thread and it's the only one that OP responded to because the *troll* gave them what they wanted to hear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a joke that I made personally a week ago. but some legitimate (maybe?) comments I saw yesterday in the GDT about him. I'm all about Marwin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do they do albums straight through for PF laser shows? Or is it just a grab bag?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when I finish 5ks that's what I tell myself: that was close enough to a half. Mission accomplished! I don't know why I don't get a medal for my 5k finish though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know we are doing the no-mod day thing here, but this is just straight up a website. No review. No experience. 

No advertising. Any user who wishes to giveaway an item or link users to a poll/survey must receive approval from the moderation team with adequate notice BEFORE making the post. Please do not submit threads solely for the purpose of collecting/raising funds for your event or to help you pay for your entry into an event.

Where are you mods! (and or automod!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm running a HM in two days and do not feel ready despite putting in 25 mile weeks leading up to it. You can't really spontaneously decide to run 13.1 miles. Don't be afraid to walk. Cardio isn't a substitute for running because running is hard and takes a physical toll on your body and legs. None of the activities you listed has the same level of sheer impact on your legs or feet. 

It's going to be hard and probably suck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that maybe it's a bit harsh to keep bullying people into the daily threads, but you'd think if people were genuinely interested in sharing an accomplishment--which this definitely is, they'd do it in the appropriate place after being told it exists? Instead of deleting the post and complaining about downvotes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know that you drop your core players during a slump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have you know some of us in r/Astros think Marwin should be sent down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may be my favorite Jeff Sullivan answer yet 

 Jeff Sullivan
10:00	Can you imagine being a Mariners fan?
Can you imagine being a Padres fan?
Can you imagine being a Marlins fan?
10:01	Last year the Mets made the playoffs. The year before they made the World Series. It's not so god-damned sad to cheer for the Mets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Astros Have an Outfield Shift </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump now agrees with the majority of Americans: He wasnt ready to be president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE MARINERS ARE WHAT THE ANGELS WOULD LOOK LIKE IF YOU SUBTRACTED MIKE TROUT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE ONLY TEAM IN THE ALW WITH A WINNING RECORD! TAKE THAT DIVISION! WE'LL NEVER GIVE YOU ASSHAT IN THE STANDINGS. THE BEST YOU'LL GET FROM US IS HATASS

Edit: because I said the same thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what would it take to get u/AstrosOfficial to participate in a GDT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> atm Tyler can also play 3rd. So him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prescription drug abuse and/or Mormons? Thumbsucker.

 
Keeping Jim Carrey and Kate Winslet apart irl and in their memories? Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind 


Aliens from South Africa? District 9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've somewhat done the same but I think I've just retrenched in my own beliefs (not exactly retrenched, just angry at the GOP). Specifically [Strangers in their own land](http://thenewpress.com/books/strangers-their-own-land) just made me angrier about the whole situation. I'll look into these you linked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this entire thread is verboten.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well we are gonna knock 'em off then!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for this particular post if this person had framed it as "does anyone run with their parents? Have great stories running with them or involving them and running?" I could see it because it fosters discussion but tbh it looks like they just wanted post karma. The Achievement Thread is great and helpful. And you can just reap comment karma there. I don't really get what the big deal is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [538](https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/why-cant-the-rockies-hit-outside-the-rockies/) just started up a new weekly baseball column/article. Which it's just a column but with all ESPN's layoffs it's weird to see them adding original content on one of their platforms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Trump Has Done | FiveThirtyEight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> now I don't have to go to climbing, or health, or aww to get her insight anymore!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Run longer, mix in speed work. 

Edit: Just to add a little more. I picked up Hal Higdon's Marathon book (and still haven't finished it) and he talks about general training for a Marathon/half and a lot of your running will be long and slow. not to mention those long slow runs will help you burn fat better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in immigration and grew up along the Texas-Mexico border. Both parties have dragged their feet on CIRA is where my party affiliation apathy started. Otherwise it's hard to be a Republican when you work in Social Services and I don't particularly feel like a party affiliation benefits me. I generally vote Dem, but as a NY I have almost no desire or need to primary for the big elections. So it's a combination of things?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Devil's advocate: this would fit pretty nicely in the daily achievements thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whoa neat I'm tight knit friends with the mods because I prefer it the other way? Sweet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is there a place to see the comment that spurred this? I miss the stickied comments and am hating the clutter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> joined! I have a three mile run from my bus stop to home so this will be good to motivate me not to skip any days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess for example how does it respond to a national language? if at all. does it include any theories about immigration? I know it says that it doesn't include xenophobia et al but I want to know how it responds to varying culture? Does it incorporate it under a civic relativity? Does it just suggest those people have opted out? Nationalism has such a bad taste, I'm curious what the clear differences are. Or if it's just as simple as you're describing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you are also looking for a quick read *Bird Box by Josh Malerman* was terrifying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for introducing me to Liberal Nationalism but I also don't understand its scope. Alt-Right Nationalism in a sense is defined by xenophobia and enthnocentrism, but my cursory research shows that LN doesn't include that component. Is it a philosophy beyond just Pride in Nation and Inclusion for the citizenry? and how does it incorporate multiculturalism into its tenants? Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you show up to the draft?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without Altuve and Springer. and a slumping Correa. But yeah I'm bummed about it too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eye test but Harris feels underutilized this year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except Devos role is specifically a multiple inning swing man. I'm not blaming either Fiers or Devo. Lindor is just good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kemp can play LF passably. And IF. Tucker is a DH. White can only play 1B </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if they bobble and drop them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiers has to throw a no hitter every game or tbh he needs to be cut  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some Yankees fans were saying id end up hating McCann. If anything I like him more and more as the season goes on  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peacock is out of options and has been pitching well. My guess is Hoyt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Musgrove gave up 4 runs in one inning his last start. I don't know if Fiers is the clear man out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean Grasshopper flair  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its probably the beard, that shit is intimidating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My app says it was a slider? I was wondering if it just didn't break at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean that was me but I wasn't advocating for it just saying if you had to send someone down at the time Marwin seemed the most likely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/AstrosOfficial what's the solo HR record for the 'Stros cause Marwin is coming for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clean inning by Fiers, messy one by Kluber just like we all thought non sarcastically  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think RES is your only bet. But I don't know if it blocks so much as ignores.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fangraphs Eno Saris suggested today that after such a great performance in the WBC Correa might be dealing with underreported injuries again this year that are affecting his performance. If that's true, why not just give him a couple games rest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Astros brought their top OF prospect in for a workout with Springer](https://instagram.com/p/BTZ2UKzA2lp/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I would like to agree with you, I think the administration hasn't earned the benefit of the doubt to not act in a way that isn't just immediately challenged in court. They must have lawyers on staff who can give guidance, but they haven't exactly shown that they're going to listen to lawyers before issuing executive orders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except in the article where they point out that there is some contention among legal scholars over whether or not it is possible. 

In fact, the Antiquities Act does not address whether presidents even have the power to rescind national monument status, and legal scholars disagree on this point.

And both their sources surprisingly fall on the [conservative](http://www.deseretnews.com/article/865676704/Conservative-think-tank-concludes-Trump-can-rescind-Bears-Ears-Monument.html) side or the [liberal](https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/no-president-trump-cant-revoke-national-monuments/2017/03/29/35e53336-10cd-11e7-ab07-07d9f521f6b5_story.html?utm_term=.8a37eb26bc17) side. I don't think you can conclusively say he can't revoke status just yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well shoot this is a dope [hat](https://www.milb.com/hooks/news/hooks-new-look-for-dia-de-los-muertos-inspired-weekend/c-226854668/t-196093310) What-a-burger and neat MiLB hats, the only thing I miss about Texas  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tied with Eugenio Suarez! And behind only Mitch Haniger, Dallas Keuchel, and Dylan Bundy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Might Be The First President To Scrap A National Monument </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 games up in April and the only team with a winning record in the ALW, maybe they think these aren't as must win as later games will be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Complaint:** I'm running my second ever HM and my wife is going to miss this one too. At least last time she had a good excuse, this time she just has a spin class that's "really amazing." Running is  a super solitary activity for me, but it would be nice to have some cheering on. 

**Complaint:** Not that it matters, but I didn't notice before and  I don't think the race has medals. Just a t shirt. 

**Confession:** I missed a week of training and don't feel ready, but I'm going to leave it all out there. I feel better about this one than about my first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hal Higdon's Novice Half Marathon plan is great. It's geared towards just finishing. Higdon does recommend having a solid base of one year of running before attempting a Marathon but if your goal is just to finish it should work for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to MLB Statcast, Keuchel got 30 called strikes Tuesday night. They said it was the most called strikes for him in the Statcast era. The 30 called strikes were also the most by any pitcher this season

I want to buy in to the hype so bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dallas Keuchel is back to 2015 form for the Astros in 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure the Astros got special dispensation not to play April last year and went 77-61 for the year... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What I Would Pay Eric Thames </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That grasshopper is pretty jacked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Most-Changed Teams Since Opening Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mexico has one term presidencies and Nieto is up in 2018. You do have some bitter party battles for presidency though but his approval rating is so low atm its already like his party will lose the next one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the comparable now? I remember when they first started out could run for $20. Plus they always have their summer series which are like $5.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah lets do it. It'll be extra painful for me if Gomez comes out ahead. What stakes? I was thinking something Orbit related but couldn't pin anything down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geez that is a great price for those shoes. Can you recommend them? I'm getting close to the end of a pair of Sauconys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NYC Runs gives you Race Credits for volunteering. It's pretty great for the NY area. Their races are much cheaper than NYRR too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Editor: Hey man you have to write an article about how good the Astros are this year?


Reporter: Can't I just mention how much they sucked for three years? 


Editor: Work it in, I like that angle. 



Headline: Formerly Shitty Astros Only Good Because They Aren't In the NL Central </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DC Rainmaker has a good review of the [HRM](https://www.dcrainmaker.com/2015/11/garmin-fr230-fr235-review.html) compared to other brands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has got to be the lineup with the fewest players on the team from last year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you were asking for proof not suggesting their comment was proof of their existence. I don't know. I was just reading through and old r/baseball post about how u/MLBOfficial made team accounts for all the teams but only some used it. I think this is the Astros one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well shoot. I was trying to pick comparable not quite the stars of the team players.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how Odor is doing but I bet Yuli gets more hits during than series than he does </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> someday your time will end and the world will turn a callous back to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hard to compete with Devenski for fWar leader. 

Edit: leads the league in bWar at 1.8 (okay tied with Chris Sale) which people  tell me is better for pitchers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe they're finally sending down a bullpen arm /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Can Probably Blame Rich Hills Blisters on His Curveball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah it does. if you sit too close to the wall in the bleachers you miss like half the action in the OF. It didn't bother me too much, but I can see it knocking the experience a little bit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Anyone Ever Going To Sign Doug Fister? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was trying to focus on *bad* presidents this year; or barring that a president known for surrounding himself with contrasting opinions. But it's pretty hard to find good books about bad presidents. I'll add *The Bully Pulpit* to my list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Chris Carter used to be a walk/strikeout machine, but I don't know if he's had the playing time this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guacamole Gift Baskets!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This list seems really generic? I'm not a woman so obviously it's not meant for me (/s) but I just don't see anything that grabs my attention, outside of what I'm already incline to read like Roxane Gay, and Rebecca Solnit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to think of something witty to say but I don't want to scare them away!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poutine made in the United States </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DP experts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ensberg is the only MLB player in history to have won championship rings in College (USC '98), Rookie league (Auburn '98), Single A (Kissimmee '99), AA (Round Rock '00), AAA (New Orleans '01), and to have played in a World Series (2005, Houston Astros).

TIL The Astros just couldn't get the job done for Ensberg.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They even have the disdain/hatred for Catholics down on a subconscious level since the GOP courts fundamentalists/protestants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/baseball making me realize I'm really sad/jealous we don't have a u/AstrosOfficial in here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I had too high expectations for The Color of Water because I didn't like it at all. Or rather I found it really boring for what could be an interesting topic, and generally something that I would eat up. I remember feeling that he wasn't presenting his situation in such a way that it either felt unique or offered up some insightful takeaway. Also colored my reaction to his follow up novel about John Brown.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it sounds like you can buy crack, just don't be a dick about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump wants a review of national monuments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bleacher seats are so cheap though. And the view is great. Plus if you bring some Mets fans with you, they'll ignore your team paraphernalia and just bitch at the Mets fans. 

Source: Astros fan who keeps his head down even when the Astros are winning against the Yankees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've found myself reading a lot of non fiction this year. Highlights so far are *Team of Rivals by Doris Kearns Goodwin*, highly recommend. In addition to being about Lincoln, America's favorite president, it's just so damn well written and interesting. 

I read *Evicted by Matthew Desmond* which just won the Pulitzer unless I misremember. It's about the housing crisis in Minneapolis. Great read. 

In the last couple years I think *The Spirit Catches You And You Fall Down by Anne Fadiman* was the best I read. It's about the social service response to a Hmong child dealing with epilepsy and the clash between Western and Eastern cultural practices. Highly recommend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beltran is a washed up has been, Reddick was terrible with the Dodgers, Morton is Fister 2.0 and is just going to get injured, Aoki who? 

Did I do it? I actually couldn't think of anything current season to complain about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tucker is playing so well right now, but he's pretty useless defensively.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Altuve and Teoscar. Nobody called the ball.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Singleton is still under contract? And in AA right now. Or you mean originally? Guess he thought he'd make more out of arbitration. In hindsight he was probably right  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Korean Eric Thames already broke Barry Bonds HR record so Yuli's basically a scrub 1B </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up watching Duncan and Robinson and tbh the other two teams didn't even register for me. But im not big into basketball  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spurs with the monkey wrench in the NBA though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ploy to get people to linger after work in Cleveland instead of going home  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but they got that weird Haniger cummy post. So that's uh a positive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
