<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8351</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once Again, the Republicans Are the Biggest Spenders of All </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A private prison company currently being sued for human trafficking expects to handle one quarter of President Donald Trumps immigrant detention.

 The company, GEO Group, contracts with governments around the world to incarcerate 100,000 people, and its top executives expressed optimism on a public shareholder call on Tuesday about how Trumps immigration crackdown will impact their business. Its indicative of a cultural overhaul taking place under the Trump administrationwhere well-connected multi-national corporations are poised to see significant financial gains because of tougher immigration law enforcement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Private Prison Company Is Getting Rich Off Donald Trumps Immigration Crackdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In an interview on the White House grounds on Tuesday with reporter Jake Turx of the Haredi publication Ami Magazine, Gorka claimed that he had met personally with Trump on Monday and got assurances hes not being asked to step down, Ami reported in a since-deleted tweet.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sebastian Gorka: Trump Promised Im Not Leaving White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Trump Tweeted: FBI Director Comey was the best thing that ever happened to Hillary Clinton in that he gave her a free pass for many bad deeds! he wrote. 

 The phony Trump/Russia story was an excuse used by the Democrats as justification for losing the election. Perhaps Trump just ran a great campaign? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump attacks FBI director James Comey before he testifies on Russia investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because Republicans know the more educated you are the less likely you will vote Republican. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't the republican party just die off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy in the background just saw the catch and it blew his mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not gonna hold my breath on this.

What do you want to bet Fox will have some pro Trump debate instead of showing this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  CNN said it would run the 30-second television spot, a celebration of Mr. Trumps first 100 days in office, only if the campaign removed a section that featured the words fake news superimposed over several TV journalists, including Wolf Blitzer of CNN, and others from MSNBC, PBS, ABC and CBS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN Refuses Trump Campaigns Fake News Ad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump and Putin Agree to Seek Syria Cease-Fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "There is an overwhelming majority ... not interested in changing the way the Senate operates" on legislation, McConnell said during a weekly press conference.

Huh, so what happened when you did it for SCOTUS? Fucking Turtle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So science is "guessing" now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some, but not all. She, in all honesty, ran a bad campaign too. She thought she had places (which she didn't) and went to others that she definitely had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "But I will step in line" he said shortly after. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump prods Congress on healthcare: 'I think it's time now' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, and Putin said he has never murdered anyone too....

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ivanka Trump Uses the Word Nanny Just Once In Her New Book Women Who Work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin says allegations Russia meddled in U.S. election are rumors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress is set to expand a school voucher program that was found to hurt student performance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What Trump said:

 I mean, had Andrew Jackson been a little later, you wouldn't have had the Civil War. He was a very tough person, but he had a big heart. And he was really angry that -- he saw what was happening with regard to the Civil War. He said, There's no reason for this. People don't realize, you know, the Civil War  if you think about it, why? People don't ask that question, but why was there the Civil War? Why could that one not have been worked out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps right-wing populism is built on historical amnesia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If it would be appropriate for me to meet with him, I would absolutely, I would be honored to do it, Trump told Bloomberg News.

 Clearly aware of the power of his declaration, he added: We have breaking news.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says he could meet with North Koreas leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dawdling Congress tests Trump's patience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  At the top of the list are two projects at the Chickamauga and Chattanooga National Military Park, both of which would cost about $78,000  almost exactly the amount Trump donated from his first three months of his salary as president.

 The records also suggest that Trump intends to deduct his donation from his federal income taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Civil War battlefields could get Trump's first salary donation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or cut planned parenthood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they are Putin's disciples and this is what he does with the government so they expect the same. The government pays for everything and then some. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am looking forward to my favorite Spice Girl - Shouty Spice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ivanka Trumps Passover Ski Trip Cost Secret Service $66K </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jared Kushners newest job: getting tech companies to love the White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering I said "that or a Russian bot" and "troll harder" but if your feelings got hurt by it I understand. We need to protect the conservative snowflakes out there that want safe places for them to just be an echo chamber for their ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha that is a big lie. Politics is not The_Donald with bans for people who have different views, troll harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had to create a new account to just get your voice out there anonymously huh?

That or you are a Russian bot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump and Sessions just want pointers on drug enforcement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have been a burden to the billions in this world too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps glowing op-ed about his first 100 days, with some badly needed context </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps invitation to Duterte is a sign of the times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> United Against Trump, May Day Protests Expected To Swell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Discards Obama Legacy, One Rule at a Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump starts dismantling his shadow Cabinet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippines' Duterte Urges U.S. Restraint on North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wednesday Was the Most Dangerous Day So Far of the Trump Presidency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jabba the Hut in human form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeff Sessions stuck in sanctuary city quandary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The EPA removed most climate change information from its website Friday, saying in a press release that language on the website is being updated to "reflect the approach of new leadership."

 EPA Administrator Scott Pruitt has expressed doubt about the reasons for climate change, saying in a CNBC interview in March that he was skeptical of the role carbon dioxide plays.

 "I think that measuring with precision human activity on the climate is something very challenging to do, and there's tremendous disagreement about the degree of impact," Pruitt said. "So, no, I would not agree that it's a primary contributor to the global warming that we see." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA removes climate change information from website </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is now talking about consolidating his power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump has galvanized activists on the left. Can they stay energized? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump asked Washington Post to run 2016 electoral map on front page to commemorate first 100 days: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate March draws massive crowd to D.C. in sweltering heat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The past 48 hours in Trump's bizarre, ever-changing North Korea policy, explained </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how much big pharma gave him... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judges take Trump at his word  and thats not been good for the president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Latest: Gabby Giffords criticizes Trumps NRA speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Latest: NKorea official calls US efforts a wild dream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Trump absolutely break up a federal court thats standing in his way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But just remember, he was approved by the Obama administration at the highest level, Trump told Fox News.

 And when they say we didnt vet, well Obama I guess didnt vet, because he was approved at the highest level of security by the Obama administration, Trump added.

 So when he came into our administration, for a short period of time he came in, he was already approved by the Obama administration and he had years left on that approval.
Trump added he respects Flynns past military service and has sympathy for the retired Army lieutenant general.

 I do feel badly for him, he said.  He served the country. He was a [lieutenant] general." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump blames Obama for vetting of Flynn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 winners and 4 losers from Trumps first 100 days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need to donate to him directly I see since the Dems don't care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many in China consider Ivanka a goddess now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will be the party song when everything comes to light with Russia and other shady dealings he has done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He said his primary concern with the agreement is that he doesnt believe countries like China, India and Russia are being held to the same high standards as the U.S., particularly with contributions to the Green Climate Fund.


 Its not a fair situation because they are paying virtually nothing and we are paying massive amounts of money, Trump told Reuters.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump hints he may stay in Paris climate pact </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven whoppers from Trumps first 100 days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps administration after 100 days: A second-rate salesman surrounded by con men and losers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is great for the gun lobby and terrible for gun sales </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fanatics believe hype over truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Im watching the news and theyre going on about a hundred days this and a hundred days that, and all I want to say is, Who the heck can count all the way to a hundred?  she said. Theyre acting like were a bunch of math geniuses.

r/counting needs to talk to her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Betsy DeVos says media shouldn't emphasize first hundred days because "It's so hard to count to a hundred" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instant Money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bet he will blame Obama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we should ask Flynn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where the key players from the 2016 campaign are now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA chief to skip Republican gala after ethics complaint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Strip Poker

_ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They already passed something that says state personnel cannot help the feds in marijuana cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shep Smith is a good man and does call out the stuff Trump does. I do have respect for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to change Trumps mind on policy? Be the last one who talks to him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half the country has forgotten was the President of the United States is suppose to be AND how it represents us on the world stage.


edit: words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In an apparent shift, Tillerson says U.S. willing to hold direct talks with N. Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump governs as he campaigned: impulsive, unpredictable and loud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, but I hear they are possibly imploding so that's always good news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I will also have to ask them if they want to go back to China like Xi told me to ask" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely, I loved that hearing yesterday. Very interesting and he isn't afraid of calling the people that perpetuated what happened as what they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Donnie you are out of your element](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ks072waMayk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You're fired!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need to learn to fight it instead of stooping to that level. We need to fight for democracy and what WE KNOW it is suppose to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling he does this so people go: "OMG THANK YOU Trump for not doing that because that was stupid!" and all he hears is "THANK YOU TRUMP" with the loud applause in the background. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are better gymnasts than the US Women's 1996 Olympic's Gymnastics Team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would they even do that? Get rid of the millions on ACA and hope that the people losing their insurance don't murder them before they get a different insurance out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well last night in Reuters interview he was a little sympathetic to little Kim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He's 27 years old, Trump said. His father dies, took over a regime. So say what you want, but that is not easy, especially at that age.

 Trump went on to clarify that he wasn't praising the North Korean leader.

 I'm not giving him credit or not giving him credit; I'm just saying that's a very hard thing to do, Trump said. As to whether or not he's rational, I have no opinion on it. I hope he's rational. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps empathetic comments about Kim Jong Un </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As many as 15 or so House Republicans have publicly said they will not support the latest GOP proposal, which was crafted among the White House, the hard-line House Freedom Caucus and a leading moderate lawmaker. That leaves House Speaker Paul D. Ryan (R-Wis.) and the White House an incredibly narrow path for passage. The speaker can lose only 22 Republicans on a health-care vote because Democrats have fiercely opposed any attempt to repeal the ACA.

We need some more Republicans to stop falling in line and look out for the people. We need 8 more to step out of line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House will not vote on Affordable Care Act rewrite, smoothing way for government to stay open </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Its a horrible deal. It was a Hillary Clinton disaster, a deal that shouldve never been made, Trump said, referring to the then-secretary of state who became the 2016 Democratic presidential nominee. Its a one-way street.

Bet you he wants to get rid of it because Hillary was involved. Just like he wants to wipe away Obama's legacy.

 South Korea is the United States sixth-largest goods trade partner, and the U.S. goods trade deficit with Korea was $27.7 billion last year, according to the Office of the U.S. Trade  Representative.

just....is Trump trying to piss everyone off on purpose or clearly stupidity?

 Weve told them that well either terminate or negotiate, Trump said. We may terminate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: We may terminate U.S.-South Korea trade agreement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This whole week has been a good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside Russias Fake News Playbook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Other 100 Days: 5 Decades Before Trump, the New EPA Truly Made America Great Again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Hickenlooper told host Chuck Todd on MSNBCs Meet the Press Daily on Wednesday that Sessions feels strongly that more people smoking more marijuana or doing any kind of drugs is unhealthy for the country. But Hickenlooper also noted that, in the meeting, Sessions did listen when he explained that there hasnt been a big spike in consumption nor a significant increase in teenage consumption since Colorado legalized recreational marijuana three years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colorado Governor: Sessions Finds Obama-Era Marijuana Policy Not Too Far Off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump complains Saudis not paying fair share for U.S. defense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh you sweet summer child </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got it working and am listening to it now. Thank you for the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  your wet dream of an impeachment null

Emolument clause...he is breaking it already and if the GOP had a spine this would've ended long ago.

[Already happening at Mar-a-lago](http://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/trump-secretely-met-2-colombian-ex-presidents-mar-a-lago-article-1.3083748) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That link is not working for me "No valid source found", when does it start? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could = Fucking WILL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is Comey's testimony since you seem oblivious to everything](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cm0DxSBjPXE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clearly never listened to Comey's testimony did you? Or you just do not care at all that a foreign nation meddled in the election and possibly(probably) colluded with it.

[Here it is so you can catch up to the truth](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cm0DxSBjPXE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clearly never listened to Comey's testimony did you? Or you just do not care at all that a foreign nation meddled in the election and possibly(probably) colluded with it.

[Here it is so you can catch up to the truth](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qHZ_j_Tim08) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget Ivanka hanging out with Putin's girlfriend on vacation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except Russia meddeling in the election is truth and not lies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 for those mental gymnastics!!

Strategic warning hahahahahah. Fuck I will message them for half the cost of those missiles for that "warning"

When did we have a missile that can strike just 1 person? Oh right, all life is not sacred to Trump supporters since if they are Muslim we can have collateral damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and here we go... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAHA...yea ok. He bombed an empty airfield because no one was there and it was up and running the next day.

Also: Trump happened to have stock in Raytheon, so he made some money wasting 60 million on a "show of force" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  because Republicans can't be relied upon to agree on what time of day it is, much less conduct an investigation on a Republican?

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It cost [$38,000](http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/328942-secret-service-has-spent-more-than-35000-on-golf-cart-rentals) for the FBI golf cart rentals so you tell me? That does not include their pay, air fare, security detail....so try again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, just no. FBI HAS information that the Russians interfered in our election. FBI HAS information that Flynn was getting money from Turkey which was from a Russian contact. 

What scares me and should scare you, is the fact that you do not see all the information around you and decide that a foreign nation involved in swinging our election is alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why continue wasting money on Trump's weekly golfing trips? Why waste money on making sure Melenia doesn't have to be with her husband? Why waste money on Jared and Ivanka taking trips all over the world and still doing their business dealings while on the taxpayer dime? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this points I do not think they will be safe in 2018 or 2020. Hell, 11,000 women have gotten into the political scene since Trump took office. Trump did make America great again by uniting people to care about their government and what it does and to FIGHT for their rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha you must've gotten a 10/10 for those mental gymnastics! 

If you need to hide in your safe place we understand it is scary for you but we will keep fighting for the truth because we love this country and want to see it move forward and not move backwards like it has been doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you need to hide in your safe place we understand it is scary for you but we will keep fighting for the truth because we love this country and want to see it move forward and not move backwards like it has been doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
