<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5070</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 17:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My only issues with android phones that aren't stock android is that they get very slow over time. At least thats what I experienced with the samsung galaxy s2 and s5. But that might've changed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it comes to coping with the panick attacks distracting is key, but I really don't know if it is even possible to get rid of this phobia completely. Personally I don't get triggered anymore when someone v* next to me as long as I know that it isn't contagious. So thats a progress but the fear v myself  is still as high as always. Good luck. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 14:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Gambia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 16:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already read that but I havent tried the node setup yet. Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greenlandic and Related Languages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 14:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **I already postet the exact same thing on r/greenlandic but maybe its helpful for some of you.**

It's not easy to distinguish the dialects of Kalaallisut/Inuvialuktun/Inuktitut/Inupiaq but I'll give my best, maybe this will help to get a better overview of the Inuit languages.

* **Greenlandic:**

**Kalaallisut** is the standart dialect of the greenlandic language and has it's origin in the western part of Greenland, it's virtually identical to the standart greenlandic. (50.000 native speakers)

**Tunumiisut** is spoken in east Greenland, some people see it as a distinct language but it's generally considered a divergent dialect of Greenlandic. (3000 native speakers)

**Inuktun** is spoken in the northernmost part of greenland (surroundings of Qaanaaq) and is a dialect of the Canadian Inuktitut and Kalaallisut. (800 native speakers)

* **Canadian Inuit languages:**
Unlike the languages spoken in Greenland most of the Canadian Inuit languages have in addition to the looped cursive Cree syllabics.

**Inuktitut** is by far the biggest language of the canadian Inuit languages, it has many dialects such as: Inuttitut, Inuktun, Qikiqtaaluk niginiani, Qikiqtaaluk uannanqani... (34.000 native speakers)

**Inuvialuktun** is sometimes considered as a dialect of Inuktitut and has several (sub)dialects such as: Siglutun, Inuinnaqtun, Natsilingmuitut, Kivallirmiutut... (2000 native speakers)

* **Alaskan Inuit languages:**

**Inupiaq** is distinguished in north Alaskan Inupiaq (Qawiaraq) and northwestern Inupiaq. (9000 native speakers) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 14:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly this didn't help. It still looks exactly the same. I am afraid I have to do the lighting completely differnet in order to make it work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HELP needed: I have an light emitting object that I want to be invisible in the render, but if I turn off the Ray Visibility of the emitting object in the properties panel The Object itself stays visible behind Glass. Link for better explanation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 13:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, nein das hatte ich nicht erwartet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 10:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are some very good tips. Thanks for sharing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 23:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the feedback :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 22:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah thanks. Didn't think about that. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that doesnt look good in the thumbnail but I just used the Image I rendered for my background. And on fullscreen its looking much better  

I uploaded another image that is is zoomed more in on /r/isometric where the chimney is also smoking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the lightrays at the windows I used a mesh with a volumetric scatter material thats shining slightly yellow and I just realized that this mesh is throwing a shadow on to the snow which isn't realistic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winter Scene [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isometric Winter Scene 4K [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you really have fever? I wake up sometimes with shivering, dizzyness and attacks of sweating. Most of the time it goes away when Im taking a warm bath and drinking tea to calm down. But I never had fever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 17:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are several excellent videos from Blender Guru covering this topic. [This](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O8i7OKbWmRM) is about compositing and its definetly worth watching if you haven't.

Nevertheless this is a great render already and I wish I could achieve things like this as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 15:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Texturing and modelling is very well done. But I think that theres too much going on in the picture. Too many colors and too many objects in the foreground.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 20:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to swallow the noro virus to get it. You should be fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 09:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. Adobe Illustrator? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 13:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leidln I dat amoi sogn dassma vorsichtshoiba nurmehr im dialekt redn damit fois des auf die frontpage kimmt koana von de amis mit eanam schuideitsch uns vasteht.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wahrlich </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 23:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They called the non TB 13" MBP the new Air at the Keynote. Im Afraid the Air wont get a refresh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 21:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such an amzing picture, looking like a William Turner Painting. Better resolutions available? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 20:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks good Idea  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 20:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The texture you see there is actually on the whole chair and node editing this was pretty difficult. In the final render its barely noticeable but at least I got some practise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Months ago I posted here an isometric drawing of the Rietveld Chair. In the last months I started learning blender, here's my first succes! :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 22:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 20:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I dont know how to make them brighter :( should I add an emission shader? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 20:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The colored wood texture on the chair is the part that was most difficult to me but the effort is barely noticable in the final render. How do I get rid of the fireflies where the glass is? And whats the best way to do the lighting in a scene like this (indoor, no windows)?

TIA :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First real render (not finished), your thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 20:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I finally got it. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have both textues in yellow and black but as soon as I choose while having the face of the object selected the whole object is changing into the chosen color (before pressing apply) I guess I will just have to mess around with the settings until it works but thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I do that It changes the whole mesh into yellow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putting diferent colors on different faces of a mesh with the same texture. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trying to model the rietveld chair but I am struggling on how to color one face different than the others of the same mesh. I couldnt find a solution on google, sorry.

Picture for better explanation: http://imgur.com/gallery/ehGKJ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 22:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot for replying. I also had times where my emetophobia was - not gone - but bearable. Currently - not so much.

It seems very likely that these incidents might be the root cause of your phobia. Thanks for sharing your story. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 18:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok thanks :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monitor for Rendering (Blender, Cad+T) and Gaming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Rig:

GPU: gtx 1070 (msi)
CPU: Intel i7 4820k (quadcore, 3,7 ghz)
RAM: 16Gb DDR3 1600mhz

I would like to buy the LG 34UC87C-B but I am not shure if my rig would be able to play games fluenty with said monitor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truly Beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gosh wheres the admin, again  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 14:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for taking your time to respond. I know what you mean by waiting for the inevitable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 02:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the response. 2 am here and Im still awake trying to cope with my panic attacks. Stay strong + </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 00:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you really had something you are not contagious anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 00:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had to make many many moulds due to my frickin teeth. Just breathe normally. They are nothing to get concerned about! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lifelong Emetophobia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 00:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had emetophobia since I can remember. But until today I never thought that this is actually something that has a name... Well now here I am writing to get myself calm. Some questions:

Whom of you knows why you have this irrational fear? I believe I have it thanks to a poisoning I had as little child and I guess seeing how my parents freaked out that I might die because a raw mushroom got me sick was the root cause. 

Whom of you got over it? Completely? I think I made progress myself. I for example dont care if someone next to me vomits as long as I know that its not contagious (eg Alcohol). Years back Id freak out If I even heard the sound or whatever, but even though thats a succes I feel like this phobia is going to follow me into my grave.

Currently I have little panic attacks at least once a week. And thats always when I try to sleep, always. 

I think that my stomach is actually very sensible which contributes to my emetophobia a lot. I have pyrosis way to often recently for example. 

Anyways I think that this sub is something I will keep an eye on. Because in real life I am very lonely with this fear. Trying to sleep now but I would be very happy if I get some responses. :)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. 

Now I only need two more monitors  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your percentage icon looks odd. Atleast on mobile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than an Apple-ish sounding Domain this is not Apple relevant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 14:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very cool I will try to do this myself. 
I love Snowflakes since I've read "about Grace". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Visit /r/longyearbyen if youre interested in svalbard :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to change the node as you said, current result: http://imgur.com/a/yePLs
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to make a good looking wooden material for my chair using the texture tutorial from blender guru. but the texture is too glossy overall and the normal map is only viewable if the lightsource is pointing directly at it (maybe due to wrong lighting) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> working on a chair render. wooden texture is looking wrong. please help :/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 19:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought the 6 with 16Gb on release. The screen cracked a year ago and I got a cheap af repairing set for 60 back then. Changing the screen worked but the screen itself is very cheap manufactured, I already had to "re-glue" by myself a month ago. 

Im using the latest software and It runs very well. The only issue is the battery life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 14:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cool :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I didnt know that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Good to know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
