<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2331</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, they're all 1-2 star movies, so I expect them to be pretty terrible, but they all seem quite good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Pikachu lunchbox and backpack :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, now you're just asking too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heavy Rain :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wet Dreams :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhm... I already do O-o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically every low-rated movie on NetFlix. Don't think I've found one I don't like, yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not giving a FUCK about what people think of me. If you aren't my boss, direct coworker, or something of the sort, I DO NOT CARE THAT YOU DON'T LIKE ME. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I intend to do the same. While my husband and I aren't religious, I want my child to have a choice in their own religion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory "not a recruiter". But take a shit ton of copies of your resume.

My SIL went to a job fair last week. I printed out 10 copies of her resume for her to take and pass out. She took ONE. Fortunately, the one she took ended up with her getting an interview for later this week. But I believe she really could have gotten more opportunities had she actually passed out more.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maaan, the lunchladies at school always look so school with their touch screen registers lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Myself. 

I find that I am a giving and generous person, but I will not sacrifice my own well being for anyone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and this is why I'm fat :(
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Said every man ever lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doing things for me without me asking. (housework, home improvement, etc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really a condiment, but I prefer not to have the bread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to write this as well, but I figured I would do it later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or crush the fucking monopolies. Only Verizon and T-Mobile get service at my work. As soon as I drive out the gate (approx 1/2 mil), I get LTE service with Sprint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being confident.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rasing Hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sister in law and I were driving from KY to CA and the alternator went out in her jeep. It was a Sunday in TN, so no regular shops were open. My dad called the truck stop shop about 20 miles up the road and explained our situation, and told us to head that way. I get there, they fix it, I expect to pay $120+ in labor. They did it for free. I gave the guy $20 before I knew I wasn't going to be charged, had I known, I would have given him more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy APPLICABLE math. I almost failed my algebra courses. Got moved to what was essentially dummy math, and got a 99%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a job that I love that pays me pretty well. I own my home. I have a loving and caring husband. I have minimal debt. My dog is awesome. My cat cuddles with me. Life is grand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 14:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a pressure cooker and its soooooooo great :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 20:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get deployed for approximately 3 months at a time, so in theory, I'll have enough birth control to last me throughout. However, my deployment timeline doesn't always line up with my prescription pickup. 

I have some genetic issues, so I need to be on a pill. I can't do the IUD or the Nexplanon. (nexplanon is evil, been there, done that). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My insurance covers my birth control, as long as I get it on their timeline. I gets 3 months at a time, and cannot pick it up until 70% of my pills are gone. I travel overseas for work, so I usually need to pickup more in order to have enough during deployment. If I pick it up early, I have to pay $100 to get 3 months. It's irritating, especially when mail can take up to a month, so it's difficult to have my husband just send it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 20:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I struggle with over washing my hair. I haven't washed my hair in 3 days and my dandruff is out in full force.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 14:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah lol. We got them this little cardboard box that has holes in it and they absolutely LOVE it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 05:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! I got my girls one of these and they ripped out the stuffing and slept in the seams lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 05:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't really had an issues with TWC. I pay $57.99 for 100mbps. I've had them for almost 2 years and haven't really had any issues. Meanwhile, ATT wanted to give me an AMAZING deal of $50 per month for 3mbps. Yeah, okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 14:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cat does this too. I don't LET him outside, but he'll dart out the door and just roll in the dirt and low crawl. Then he darts back in the door because of said dirt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 19:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a black lab/hound mix and she's the complete opposite of destructive lol. She has a squeaky porcupine toy that she's had for like 2 years and all it needs is a bath lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 16:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just described my marriage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My SIL's MIL started selling this shit, so she signed my SIL up to become an ambassador. It's Plexus. I bought some shit from her, just  to help get her started, because I'm that kind of person. The shit I was taking made me TERRIBLE. I was moody as fuck. She hasn't ordered any more and gave up trying to sell it. But we all told her in the first place it was a waste of time and money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 19:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I love when my company books me hotels right near the airport. I have terrible anxiety when it comes to figure out transportation lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 14:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm considering this for my sister in law. She needs quite a bit of work, after not having gone to the dentist since 16 (she's 23). She needs her wisdom teeth removed, as they are cracking her molars, a root canal and crown on one of said molars, many small cavities filled, and some stain removal. She recently had 3 crowns done and that maxed out her insurance and cost me $1600 in copays </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 14:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, my dentist told me that most of the work the Air Force did for me is probably going to have to be redone at some point. I don't think he's trying to make money off of me, since he's not really pushing the issue at the moment.

If you get married and get your spouse the dental insurance,  good luck with that one. The current plan only covers $1300 of work and the copays are astronimical. My husband maxed his coverage out in 2 visits for 5 cavities, with about $400 in copays. Sister in law maxed it out in one visit for 3 crowns, with $1600 copay. 

When I got my wisdom teeth out, I had to get them surgically removed, so I got sent to a specialist. Many people I know have lasting issues from the military stealing their wisdom teeth, so I lucked out on that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> totally. never having to shave again? and being smarter? HELL TO YIZAH! plop a wig on the head, tattoo the eyebrows on, GTG~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I travel and deploy for work, so I bought an MSI Apache... I've had it about a year now and it's been great. I have to make sure I have a hard surface for it, but that's usually pretty achievable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything by Digital Daggers... Everytime I play them, they're pretty well recieved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 13:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 13:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gawd, I could barely pass high school chemistry :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 13:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I feel like I need PPE to watch this gif :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 13:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Counting calories didn't really work for me. When I started counting carbs, I saw better results. When I was counting calories, I was noticing that the things I was eating, while allowing me to meet my calorie goals, were LOADED with sugar. (yogurt, granola,fruit). So I guess I'm trying to ask, whats the point of watching your calories if they're all...bad? If thats a thing. purely anecdotal here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 13:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I SEE WHAT YOU DID THERE HAHAHA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 04:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first drivers license had the same last 4 digits as my moms social  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 04:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband makes juice, so we have tried every combination we can think of. High nicotine, low nicotine. Pure vg pure pg. half and half. 75% of one 25% of the other. Just can't get the satiation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cigarettes. I have been struggling to quit. I've tried gum, patches, vaping... I can't try chantix with my line of work. I've heard that makes you crazy anyway, so I don't know if I want to. I plan on having kids in the next few years, and don't want to battle this addiction while pregnant.

My genetics make me more susceptible to breast and ovarian cancers (BRCA1), and I really don't think smoking is helping the situation. I wish it was as simple as just not smoking for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Futurama, Family Guy, Cleveland Show, American Dad... I love these shows so much. I watch one series, finish it, start another, and continue the cycle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this? GREYS ANATOMY?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a phone extenstion at my work that is the last 4 digits of my social security number. I've always found that funny lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in Vegas at a BackStreet Boys concert. I was in Vegas for training through the Air Force. I ended up sitting next to a young couple, and we start chatting. I tell them where I'm stationed (New Mexico) and a general idea of what my job is. He then tells me that his best friend from high school (also from new mexico) was in that same career field. He tells me his name and it turns out that he's the guy I went through training with. Small world/small air force </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is absolutely nothing wrong with not wanting a disabled child. I am 100% in that boat.

A child is your LEGACY. I see nothing wrong with wanting that child to be of mental/physical capacity. 

Nothing against those with disabilities, but if I knew my child would be doomed to a life of pain and suffering, I would abort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thanks. Didn't notice the abbreviation thing... did that part last night and everything else this morning lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it. Removed the objective and fixed all that. thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 23y/o stay at home mom, re-entering the workforce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long story short, my sister in law has been a stay at home for a while (mostly due to a jealous and controlling husband), and is now looking to start working again. It was quite obvious that she didn't know how to write a resume. I cringed when I looked over it, honestly. I did my best to re-write her resume and cover letter. 

I was wondering if you guys could take a look and give me some criticism. My resume skills are sub-par, so be gentle. The jobs she is applying for is a food service position at my company, so I'm hoping I'll be able to pull some strings any way. Thanks in advance!

[Resume Here](http://i.imgur.com/7AtWEnQ.png)
[Cover Letter Here](http://i.imgur.com/8JLWgk8.png)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve Earl - Better Off Alone [Blues/Country] (2015) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 19:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 14:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend that makes fun of me because I'll say something like "What the fuck is this guy behind me doing?" he responds with "why do you worry about the people behind you?"
 This. This right here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 02:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aha, it really did. It mostly came from the fact that she was lying about shower/doing laundry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 02:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime I use any soap that says it's supposed to be ph balanced, it wrecks my soul.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 14:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, there was this girl I was in the military with who ABSOLUTELY REFUSED to shower or do her laundry. She actually got kicked out for being stinky.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 14:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh dear god. I used summer's Eve once and got BV. That was the worst experience ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 14:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I managed to quit while I was overseas (mostly because there was only a vaper there). My husband also quit while I was gone and I thought we were home free. then we went on a road trip. We lasted 12 hours into the trip before we caved. Been trying to quit since then and there's just too much temptation around me. I go overseas in October, so I'm going to try again then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 13:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will say I feel slightly better that my half a pack a day habit isn't that bad compared to what other people are saying lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 13:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ill kill you next" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I don't know if it's a first sergeant in the army. I'm prior Air Force so that's all the knowledge I have haha. He's actually up for reenlistment right now. We don't think they will let him because he's got a lot of mental health shit in his record, making him non deployable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I say that, I mean that for some reason they're all stuck up Dons ass. He was suppose to get an Article 15 a few weeks ago but he never shows up to work. There have been several instances where he should have gotten in trouble , and did not. Also, I've heard that basically every married guy in that unit is cheating on their spouse. I'm tempted to tell her to try anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have navy federal, and I'm pretty sure there has to be signatures for that one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was planning on going to JAG tomorrow for some advice. We are also aware of the cheating being illegal. She initially had no desire to get him in trouble with the military, because that would be taking things from her son. From what I've heard, his unit won't do anything about it anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [KY] Husband refusing money to his wife (Military) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there! Quick backstory here. My sister in law, Jo, recently came to CA to live with me and her brother, along with her son. Her husband Don, is stationed in Ft. Campbell, KY. Jo left  (more like he kicked her and son out) Don a little over a month ago, due to his cheating and unwillingness to work towards a fix. 

Jo has not yet found a job, due to unavailable jobs and her vehicle being broken. But, she has started college through the military spouse assistance. In the past month, Don has been paid twice and has easily sent her $400 each time. Fast forward to this past paycheck, (Friday-ish) Don does not pay Jo. Jo doesn't want to ask him because she is not speaking to him due to his nasty attitude. 

Jo still has access to the joint account, so she went in and transferred the money herself. She sent Don a courtesy text, saying that she transferred the money because she needs money to provide for their son. He comes back with shit like "I'm the one providing, you're just buying him shit." or "that's not your money to take". 

I understand Don's perspective, but since they are still married, does he have any right to tell her she can't feed her son? This morning Jo woke up to a text that Don was going to remove her access to all the bank accounts, because she used money from another account. My question is, can he do that? Especially with him being military, can he refuse her money/access to the bank accounts?

Just remembered that he is threatening to kick her off the car insurance as well. Wouldn't be surprised if he's threatened the medical as well. 

This whole situation is a cluster fuck, and there are a million more questions I have, but this is just the most pressing item at the time.

Thanks for any advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my coworkers did this in college. He now has a huge scar on the withdrawal point lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop with the onions :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 13:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a lil cutie! My not sure of the birth weight of my nephew, but seeing people tell how much their 2 year old weighs is... worrying. My nephew will be two at the end of september and he is FORTY pounds. I feel like that kid is just too big lol
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 14:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll add anyone who isn't trying to sell me Herbalife or ItWorks! -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 13:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only people that I have met that have my last name are black. I'm white. My dad jokes that we owned slaves. Entirely likely :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 13:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think any of my ingrowns have ever had pus... That probably doesn't feel too good :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 22:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had that god-awful thing in my arm for 9 months. I spotted the entire time. Never had a real period. I had horrible moods swings. I gained a ton of weight. Hopefully you have a better experience lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 22:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been too concerned about sitting on the seat. I usually wipe is real quick and then do my business. I'll probably piss all over myself and fall over if I tried to squat. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 22:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you sprinkle when you tinkle, be a sweetie, wipe the seatie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have portable wifi, but there is a data cap that has to last me till the end of the month. Also has to be used for all my other internet needs. I wonder if there are Pokemon in the middle of Iraq o.o  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also work overseas for a few months at a time, and Ill have no phone service, so once again, OUTCASTED!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol. Hunni has never been too drawn to the clean clothes. Our cat, however, loves them lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 16:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know they already have plans for their own pokewalker thingy, but I'm not willing to buy a pedometer when I already have a fitbit. My husband mentioned that measuring steps might outcast disabled players, but I'm sure there is a work around for that as well. I already feel outcasted because I have a shitty cell provider lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found the dog sleeping in the laundry basket this morning... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 14:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 13:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish that my Fitbit could sync with the game. I have shitty service at work, so no distance counted there. I go on walks everyday as it is, but the samn distance counter hardly fucking updates :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 13:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Djibouti, we could drink on base (2 drinks per day). That's all you needed if you were loaded up with ambien like I was XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 10:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, as long as you're not in relationship with him, I guess you're good XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 14:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, my old roommate was this way. He is actually and incredibly sweet guy, just a lil awkward. Basically, he will start talking with girls and things will go well for a few days/weeks/months and then completely taper off. Well, because they aren't interested anymore, they're "bitches! Sluts! Cunts! Whores! Fuckers!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 18:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was fortunate enough to never have suffered from their crack smokin lol. I didn't even know about it until my dad told me a few years ago. I remember being 13 or so and asking my dad to take me to block buster to get a video game, there was no hesitation lol. It was hard on my grandmother. My dad and stepmom got off the road for a few years and started a fencing business. They made great money but blew it all on crack. My grandma was in her mid sixties, working as a live in nurse to pay the bills. But, I never suffered or knew what they were doing. Always thought they were just smoking weed lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 05:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been like 14 years, now that I've done the math lol.  I'm 23, so yes she is my stepmom. She's a wonderful woman who takes has always treated me like her own child :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 14:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my stepmom haha. She's a great woman. They balance each other out. He basically saved her life. She was into drugs and shit too. They spent a couple years smokin' crack, got clean, and are currently doing great :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 13:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god, so late. My dad's a trucker. He picked up a lot lizard about 12 years ago... he married her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 13:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the post! You looked/look fantastic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 21:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my apologies.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 21:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's basically what I told her as well. I understand why she wants to do this, and I see it as a good thing, but at the same time, I remember the bullshit I went through. I told her she should join the Air Force, but she's considering the army as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 20:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The father is still an option, although with him being in, I know it's hard with childcare. I know her mother in law could possibly do it as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joining the military while going through divorce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 20:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 20:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So she should start looking for a lawyer over there and not CA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Divorce help! CA/TN/KY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 20:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi /r/legaladvice!

Bit of an odd situation right now. My Sister in Law just left her DBH(douchebag husband) and moved to California with her brother and I. When I say she left, he more or less kicked her out.

DBH is in the Army, stationed at Fort Campbell, KY/TN.  SIL just moved to Palmdale, CA. They were married for almost 4 years (Florida license). 

DBH cheated several times over the past few years. Ranging from simple conversation to sex. SIL has been very clear that she wants to work on the marriage. DBH has made it very clear that he is done with her and she is not welcome to her home (base housing at Ft Campbell). SIL wanted to make arrangements to stay because she also has his almost 2 year old son. (something like him stay in the barracks and she can stay in the house) But he did not want that. She wanted to file for legal separation so he would still have to provide for her while she got back on her feet. He did not want to do that either.

So now she is in Cali with me and her brother along with her son. DBH says he will be filing for divorce in a matter of days. He says he will be filing no fault or something to close it. He insists that she agrees to all his terms and does not get a lawyer. Well, we aren't that dumb.

What we need advice on is how and where and who to file with. If we manage to beat him to filing, is it possible to file out of state? We know she can't file in Cali because she hasn't been living her long enough. She wants to nail his ass to the wall. Child support alimony, etc. She can't really report him to his chain of command about the situation because they already know its happening and are only on his side. Plus, getting him in trouble will take money away from their son. Does anyone have an idea of where to find a good, cheap, lawyer in High desert area? We want this to be quick and painless.  If you need more details, I will add them as they are asked for. Thanks in advance!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 15:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, flew out of Ontario Intl (CA) and DFW and JAX and all just have PokeStops and gyms  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 13:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steamed Clams :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 21:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was another thing we were thinking. My husband and I want a truck anyway, so we're trying to convince my father in law to sell us his truck lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rental Trucks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 21:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there /r/ Trucks!

I apologize if this isn't a good place to post. Please direct me to the right place if its not. :)

I was wondering if there are any rental truck companies that will allow you to tow a trailer with their truck. I need to move my sister in law from Kentucky to California. A U-Haul moving truck is not an option because she has her son. We do not think her Jeep will make the trip, so we are exploring other options. Our current plan is to use the Jeep to haul a trailer with her things. If we can't get her Jeep into a driveable condition, I was wanting to rent a truck.

Do you guys know of any place that will allow this? Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 21:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was giving my girls a little piece of salmon to try and I had some of the juices still on my finger. One of them bit me! Right in the cuticle of my pointer finger. That didn't feel good lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 20:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We got a wheel for our rats and they don't use it. Apparently, the only time rats use wheels is when they're slightly retarded. (according to something my husband read) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 20:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the hammock that came with the cage set up for a while. Then they decided to chew through the straps lol. I still had a bed from whe n I had a guiena pig, so i put that in their cage... They chewed the shit out of it and now they sleep UNDER it. Rats, man, rats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 18:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey now! Beibs has been dropping some pretty good tunes!The Pretty Reckless is amazeballs _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 22:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really have no idea what the hell was going on here... didn't really seem that cringey? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 17:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The argument that I've heard about this (which I do not agree with AT ALL), is  "Why should your employer have to pay you because you decided to have a baby? Why is that their responsibility?" 

People want to sit here and complain about California taxes, but part of that is FMLA. If a family member gets sick, I can take time off and still get paid. If I adpot a child, I can take time off and still get paid. I can give birth, take time off and still get paid.

I also find it odd that in order to LEGALLY sell a puppy/kitten, it has to be at least 8 weeks old. US law doesn't require 8 weeks of maternity leave for a human mother and child. Ain't life grand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
