<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2868</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 16:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck Keith Owen, and fuck Ari Bolden. Even without this incident, both of them are fucking cancer in the BJJ community. 

Here's to celebrating how shitty Ari is, losing to a white belt in competition **in 2010**, like 5 years after he started putting out instructional material:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=buqR3s7EZeQ

EDIT 2: Here's a blog post from Keith: **"Can Women Really Handle Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu?"**

http://keith-owen.blogspot.com/2013/02/can-women-really-handle-brazilian-jiu.html

And his hilarious justification: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IrqFqdTG0cA#t=111 

Regardless of his intentions, Keith Owen is a piece of shit. He's only relevant as an example of the pathetic drama-mongering in the periphery of the BJJ community.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 14:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real question is, what color is the bar???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 03:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really cool. He has a really interesting style - very odd and unorthodox to watch, and yet he clearly moves like a natural. I can see why he has improved so quickly. The weirdness of his style reminds me of Telles for some reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 23:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This doesn't make me feel better about the situation, sadly. When he says "it is a motivational tool" it just really didn't sit well with me. It really does make it sound like a business-driven move. Especially when he says it's to keep kids focused on BJJ instead of football or baseball... that's just goofy. Still feels like a cash grab.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 20:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome insight, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 18:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I completely agree about Grow Home! I'm thinking about animation **quality**, not necessarily animation realism. Grow Home is exactly the example I was thinking about as some AWESOME animation. I hope procedural animation becomes the norm, because it just looks fantastic (though goofy in this case). Goofily awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's talk about Animation Quality! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 17:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently realized that one of the biggest things that destroys immersion for me ("pulls me out of the game") is poor animation quality. Especially if the game is otherwise visually appealing, crappy animations just ruin it. I've since read up on this and found that unless you can pay for quality Motion Capture, creating good animations from scratch is incredibly difficult. 

I know Dragon Age 2 has been beaten to death across the internet, but it's still the best example I can think of for this. Characters swing huge weapons as if they have no weight or even air resistance. To me, it ends up looking like a poor knockoff of anime. Worse though, the animations are jerky and abrupt, and don't seem to "loop" properly (ending where they next need to begin). 

What are some other decent games that suffer from poor animation quality? Does it matter a lot to anyone else, or is it just me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 14:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, this was embarrassing on all sides. Gracie Nationals is a fucking farce of a competition. This type of thing is common. Whenever I see the Gracie Nationals name on a video, I know some stupid shit will probably be involved. What a bunch of man-children all around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 18:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the details! I've seen so many instructionals that I really only watch them for new details at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 16:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Josh = confirmed baller. Always learning from your videos dude, thanks for posting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 15:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obvious cash grab.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 21:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truly living up to your username.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 17:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Government sheep downvoting you as a cover-up attempt. Nice try government! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 15:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite being an obvious troll, you're clearly on the autism spectrum and should seek professional help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 15:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please stop posting forever and instead get professional help for your autism spectrum disorder. Even if you're a troll, you're clearly on the spectrum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 14:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you brought this up. 

For folks who get to the purple or brown belt level, especially those who are not natural athletes, the amount of pain and (what some would consider) humiliation, and lapses of confidence that go into that journey are unbelievable. 

They will get beat up repeatedly in ways that might be considered humiliating in other contexts, but because of the culture of BJJ it's all part of the learning process. Think about the hundreds of times, big and small, these guys had to pick themselves up, bump fists again, and just keep going. 

The very act of tapping out, bumping fists and starting again is sacred; the heart and soul of BJJ. Those are the moments in which those poor-to-mediocre athletes are taking the biggest steps to becoming future brown and black belt monsters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 20:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are downvoting you because "amplitude" is correct for what he's describing: the arc/trajectory of a throw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 03:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, this is a great description. At the highest levels, it's really not about specific "moves" anymore.

Rather, it's about how fundamental move**ments**, used with the right timings and setups, complement each other and fit into a well-timed flow. It's about using the right tools for the right purposes at the right times. Scissor sweep is just one of those tools.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 16:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of OP's quotes:
 if I wanted to, I could have hurt him much worse

Maybe he deserved a little discomfort in return?

At least I had the balls to stand up to him...I was **so angry I temporarily lost control,** that's all.

**I went too far** not letting go after he went to sleepy land, but **this guy did deserve the dose of nyquil I gave him.** 

**I've been choked out myself more than once,** and I'd definitely take that over having my body slammed into the ground by a guy who benches twice my body weight.

I **lost control** and **couldn't stop** choking him.

OP: BJJ is an amazing sport/culture and can help people get through a lot of bad times in their lives (PTSD, etc.) But you have serious anger problems. When people train with each other, there is a social contract that says "my safety is in your hands." You really need to work out your issues before putting other people's safety in your hands again, because you clearly can't trust yourself. What your partners did, while extremely disrespectful, is pretty irrelevant here. The "justice" they deserve is a separate issue. You can control whether you put yourself in a position to hurt people again. I hope you will deal with your issues before you trust yourself with someone else's safety again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 04:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What everybody else says in this thread, plus: put your forehead to your own wrist. This just really solidifies the structure to make sure you're using your whole body to torque it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 19:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's totally legit as a setup. I like to use the C-grip choke from mount to encourage them to open their elbows, allowing me to get s-mount for armbars and mounted triangles. 

I like it because it lets me threaten them without letting go of my crossface.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 19:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, to get the omoplata from here, you need your other leg to be mobile to either 1) pull out for a traditional omoplata or 2) shoot deep for the Carni. 

Marcelo is pinning the guy's other leg to the mat just enough to prevent either of those from happening, so the omoplata will be too loose and easy to shake off. 

When I do this pass, instead of standing up, I replace my elbow with my same-side knee to pin his leg down even more. I have trained with sharp rubberguard players for years, I use this same pass every time and have never once gotten swept or submitted from RG.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 17:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, twist sweep is what you're looking for. See Ryan's Deep Half Guard dvd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 17:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, "Master" is some lame Lloyd Irvin shit he came up with to sell his pyramid schemes.

First name basis for my gyms. Otherwise coach is good, and professor is traditional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 17:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could be wrong, but I think those all fit the legal definition of "sexual assault." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 19:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you're wrong; to me it looks like his opponent has little grappling experience and his coach was giving pretty unhelpful advice.  

But people are downvoting you because every time somebody from 10th Planet wins something, they want to believe it proves the system is amazing. Just like every time someone from 10th Planet loses, the opposite faction wants to believe it proves the system is crap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 18:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That pretty much describes it. 

Some people have this idea that Helio invented leverage and then BJJ sprang out of him fully-formed like a child of Zeus. 

But actually, at least in part, the crucible that formed BJJ into the effective martial art we know today was brutal street fights in Rio in the 80s, including the rivalry with luta livre fighters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 18:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC, the purple belt in the "basketball fight" video does something similar to set up a pretty slick back-take - forearm in neck to make some space, then hip out to get around their arms to the back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This works really well in half guard too. If you switch your feet so your outside leg hooks around his ankle, you can hip into him which tweaks his lower leg outward. This kills his pressure and can allow you to come up on a single or to the dogfight position at least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question! I neglected a couple things in my first response. 

It's all about the push and pull. 

**The push:** If he leans back, you can literally just pop him in the shoulders with both hands (or hip bump sweep if you have a bigger opening). This makes him want to drop his posture. Alternatively you can just pop your hips into extension to make him feel off-balanced backwards. Imagine doing a deadlift against his body. Loading your hips like this sets up "the pull"

**The pull:**In your example sounds like his posture is already relatively low (but not low enough to put him in real danger) and refusing to move. This is where you want to pull. But you don't want to just yank him onto you. Some details:

* Always pull with your arms and legs at the same time, one big motion as if you're going to throw him all the way over your body and backroll

* If you popped your hips into extension as I described, you can do a much bigger pull 

* Don't just pull him onto you - when you pull him forward, you should hip out at the last second so he kind of falls "past" you. In other words, you pull him forward but then move yourself out of the way at the last second, so he drops into the "hole" beside you. This is where armdrags start to work really well.

* EDIT: One more detail. Every time you pump your hips to pull, you can subtly walk your legs a little bit higher up his torso toward his shoulders. I.e., unlock your feet and walk one foot over the other, then re-lock them just a bit higher. Your goal is to get the crooks of your knees up into his armpits. Setting up this "high-guard" is a good alternative when they're too sharp to fall for your arm drag. If you can get here, you're 90% of the way to a triangle, armbar, omoplata, or cross choke in the gi (and you can chain all of these together easily).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you didn't even make me tap

If he just cranked and broke something, that's on him. But if you had time to tap, you should have. Just because something is "bad technique" doesn't mean it won't possibly break you. 

Just yesterday somebody posted about his teammate not tapping to an improperly-applied toe hold. His big toe got torn almost clean off. Bad technique can still break you, whether you want to tap or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respectfully disagree with a lot of the advice in this post. A lot of people are basically suggesting that you try different hand grips to attack, e.g. to set up arm drags. 

I think this disregards OP's premise #1, which is that his opponent is already in good position, and e.g. his biceps are often controlled. If that's the case, your hands/grips are not the problem and won't help you that much. 

If the top guy is ABLE to stall, it's because you're not using your **hips** to break him out of good position before attacking. Don't try to attack your opponent when he's in good position; rather, deal with his good position first to open up an opportunity to attack. 

If I'm in good position and really want to stall in your guard, I'm going to see the armdrag coming a mile away. However, if you pump your legs and move your hips, I'm forced to open up to regain balance. When I post my hands or readjust my base for balance, THAT is your opening to attack. 

**So TL;DR: You're basically saying "my opponent is in good position, why don't my attacks work?" They don't work because he's in good position. So pump your legs, move your hips, and force him to post or readjust his base. When he opens up to adjust, that's when you can attack.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 21:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to suck at jiu jitsu. 

I still do, but I used to, too.

--Mestre Hedberg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 20:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, so you're saying grappling techniques actually work, and if you don't tap to them, your body will actually break? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 20:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **EDIT: CAVEAT:** This is just my observation on the evolution of BJJ over the past decade+ of training and multiple promotions. I think the respect for the tap that exists today is a GOOD thing. Just sharing some insights into how things have changed (for the better) and why the stuff you see in this video is more common than you might think, especially in Brazil. 

I agree, not respecting the tap is really the biggest problem here. Offering my humble observation: In the old days and more "old school gyms,"  tapping kind of meant something a little different. The meaning has really changed over time. 

Tapping these days means "I'm in imminent danger and I submit, please stop. If you don't let up **immediately** I will break or become unconscious. I withdraw consent." In that case, it is ABSOLUTELY not cool to hold the sub. 

In the old days, in certain gyms, if you tapped it kind of meant "If you squeeze ANY HARDER I will break or become unconscious." I'm not saying this is good, but you used to see people tapping wildly and their instructor would hold the submission right there. 

You'll see this in old Erik Paulsen videos for example: his uke tapping wildly and he just holds it. For a choke: if you're still tapping, you're conscious (or at least mostly conscious.) For a straight armlock, you have to go WAY beyond normal range of motion to really break. This is not true for a kimura - you can definitely tear your shoulder easily: black belts know this and probably wouldn't apply this the same way, but that's just speculation on my part. 

In promotions, when people tap, it's pretty common to see the instructor let up only slightly, but keep them in that position, expecting them to escape. 

I agree it's not cool - like what if I'm dying of an asthma attack? But I think it's not quite as bad as people's perception in this thread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 17:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be 100% honest, especially in Brazil the "gentleness" is not something you really see that much.

I'm not saying it should be this way, but it is. For good or ill, the roots of BJJ are more hardcore than people realize.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 17:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mostly agree, but quoting myself below:

 I have a few thoughts, but first want to be clear I'm not condoning any of this and I have no connection to Checkmat.
 First, aside from not respecting the tap, this is pretty much what my promotions have looked like across gyms. I trusted those training partners so it didn't feel like hazing to me. They are testing his limits in a mostly safe way.
 Not respecting the tap is not cool, but I don't think he actually got choked unconscious here - they were encouraging him to move and from my POV being pretty gentle. I might be missing something though. I think they know him well enough to know that he was safe. I saw them loosen up a bit every time he tapped.
 Finally, I'm not saying BJJ should be like this, but it definitely has been this way longer than it was not... if that makes sense.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 17:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Believe the hype, they are awesome instructors (especially with this submission). I find arm triangles EVERYWHERE now, and when I get the grip, it's usually just a matter of time (like Seph says in that video, "my work is done)". For your opponent, it's a terrible position and there's no reason they should ever able to get out: no matter how long it takes to finish it, you should finish or they die of exhaustion. 

You're right: I find the brace method works against 90% of people, especially when I have the time/patience to finish it. Their arm just can't hold back your bodyweight forever if you're just leaning into it. I do believe the brace is the "ideal" way to finish. If I remember correctly, Ryan says that Seph was the one who came up with the brace method also.

So, for me the limiting factor is my own grip strength, because I'm a pansy in that way. If time is running out or I feel like my grip can't hold for some reason, I'll try the "hand across" method to finish them a little faster.  

Similarly, I always try to finish the arm triangle with one arm and it works amazingly well, but if time is running out in a tournament, you better believe I'll do the old-school arm-triangle finish: lock my arms RNC-style, go to knee ride, and just try to neck crank them for the finish (it works). Ryan would say that's bad technique, and it definitely is, but even with my imperfect technique it realistically can end fights if time is an issue. Overall, it was liberating for me to learn Ryan's point that "bad" technique works some % of the time and in some situations. 

So, I agree you should definitely try to finish these with the brace method and bodyweight only, especially in training, because in tournaments with time running out you can always "add back" the strength/squeeze to complement your technique instead of using strength **instead** of technique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 17:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a few thoughts, but first want to be clear I'm not condoning any of this and I have no connection to Checkmat.

First, aside from not respecting the tap, this is pretty much what my promotions have looked like across gyms. I trusted those training partners so it didn't feel like hazing to me. They are testing his limits in a mostly safe way. 

Not respecting the tap is not cool, but I don't think he actually got choked unconscious here - they were encouraging him to move and from my POV being pretty gentle. I might be missing something though. I think they know him well enough to know that he was safe. I saw them loosen up a bit every time he tapped. 

Finally, I'm not saying BJJ **should** be like this, but it definitely has been this way longer than it was not... if that makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 16:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've watched the whole DVD and learned arm-triangles and ezekiels from both Seph and Ryan in person. This is also my favorite sub combo. 

My interpretation of their advice is that it's situational. In an ideal situation, doing Ryan's "brace" method will absolutely give you a tighter "noose" around the neck. Just because of the configuration and angles, it can give you a smaller triangle. 

However, there are times when the guy is just extremely sharp (or you just really want to threaten them quickly) and you're simply not going to get the smaller triangle. This happens e.g. if they are really strong and jacking their trapped arm down to their side. In that case, I will absolutely go with the "hand across" version and it works just fine. EDIT: I think this is why, in this video, Seph shows his version of the ezekiel when someone is grabbing their own leg as a defense. 

The other scenario in which the "hand across" works well is if you're more squared up with them, more like arm-triangle style, but have an ezekiel grip (this happens if they turn back toward you while you have the ezekiel grip). In this case, putting your hand across their neck can actually close up some space to help finish, but it will probably be an air choke.

This is why Ryan would say that the method Seph shows is not wrong, just different. 

**So bottom line TL;DR**: I always try Ryan's brace method first, because it can be more efficient sometimes (allowing me to use my body weight to tighten up the noose by leaning North.) However, if they're defending well and I want to threaten them right away, I'll go with the classic hand-across grip that Seph shows. Hope that helps.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 00:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it has been a bit boring but I think still efficient. What has made it seem efficient is that I basically never need to pay for or wait for stress relief in town. 

What DPS teams are working for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 00:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Medium runs are definitely the sweet spot. You're right, the stress relief from camp is part of what makes this economically efficient (so I don't have to do stress relief in town). 

And I can never carry all the loot from long runs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 00:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh thanks, I'll definitely try that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 21:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stumbled on this team when I was doing fully-dark runs with random teams of level 0 people - so it works right away!

in medium dungeons i was equipping them with 8 food and 2 shovels only (no torches or anything else) and ending most runs with almost 0 stress. great way to farm tons of gold and upgrades.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 20:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome details! You seem to always post exactly what I'm working on. 

Humble request: My training partners have some excellent top pressure, so even when I can get that elbow in, I find that they are often able to "float" on my elbow. 

So I can get the elbow in as a check, but often can't use it to get back to guard. **Can you suggest any follow-ups/alternatives to shrimping?**

Some things that have worked for me include backrolling over them (since they're so high up and my hips are free) or switching to an elbow-push situp escape on the other side (Marcelo style) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 18:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do fully dark for the ++crits. My strategy is pretty cheesy but really works: if I just keep stunning, it does low enough damage that I can keep monsters alive longer. If I draw out fights without taking damage to HP or stress, naturally I'll get more crits which lower my stress. 

If stress does get above a couple bars, I just camp and the Jester takes care of it (I almost never have HP damage to fix in camp because the strategy is so safe.) I think the Jester is really under-rated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 18:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh I will definitely try this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 17:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This option looks great - but the biggest use of the Jester for me is stress relief (lots of crits and the best camp skills for stress). Are you able to keep your stress low running this? I almost never have to do stress relief in the Hamlet, which allows me to bank ridiculous amounts of gold. I float at 90000 or so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 17:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's tough to establish a culture for new people right away 

But for the blue belt example: In the past I have had instructors who will berate the blue belt in front of the whole class for doing this to their teammates. 

Brutal but effective. In my home gyms I almost never see this, and when I do it gets called out HARD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 16:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is absolutely true. People who are very new simply can't be effective when going light because they just don't have a deep enough understanding of how the leverage works. 

And by "effective" I don't even mean "win" - I mean nothing they do will even appear to make a difference on the situation. 

Generally in training (aside from comp season) I'm never giving more than 50%. That being said, rather than agreeing to "go light," it's better to explicitly agree to flow roll where each person is giving up some ground to the other within reason. 

This is harder to "teach" but ultimately better for both people in terms of learning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
