<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject374</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of the agreement to receive compensation was for neither of us to mention the specific product, or the company who provided the items to test. 

I'm sorry I can't be of more help, my current warning is the best I could do.

I might convince Chrissi to show me her review submission and testing log, I think it would be okay to share that, and I know that there were details she didn't tell me that should be in her copies. 

That might prove to be more useful to those who are interested in buying the product. She's usually very in-depth in all of her work, and she understand skin care, health, and the entire process of product testing better than I do. I'll see what other information I can provide for you all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All recent products that don't have reliable reveiws.

Hundreds if not thousands of people test products before they are released, honestly it shouldn't be that hard to do a little research on your skin care items.

Risk a painful and gruesome process, or Google "suchandsuch lotion review" and spend ten minutes checking it out.

If there's hardly any reveiws, or they aren't positive, find a different lotion. 

I'm not saying boycott the entire brand, I've said in other comments that I wouldn't be surprised if this was an elaborate imitation product by another company who is using the Dove brand to get their dangerous product into the world. 

"No proof or evidence", damn son, is this not the internet? A well of endless knowledge? 

Also, I'd recommend any brand or older Dove product that doesn't make your skin fall off c: Go wild with the possibilities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You go girl 

Lol anyways 

So excited about this series, I decided not to post my story in the morning because you're too much competition. Very excited for part three ^-^
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you could get a similar effect with an apple peeler c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you never have to worry about experiencing something like this!

At least, until it happens with another brand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only been a few weeks since Chrissi teted the product, and up until about three days ago similar reveiws were constantly going up and down on the site. 

I don't think they're going to all this work to hide it for no reason, and there's no way that they fixed the product entirely since it was last tested less than a week from today. 

Honestly, Dove was the only "big" brand that she tested, I wouldn't be surprised if this product was a knockoff that some other company is creating to make money off of the Dove name, yet didn't make a safe product.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like her skin is great now, but I definitely don't think it's worth the flaky dead skin that becomes heavy and bloated after a certain amount of use and contact with water. 

I mean, if she didn't look like a hairless cat that had blood and clear liquid seeping from her skin for nearly a week, THEN it *just might* be worth it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides the one product, the pay was great. If it weren't for the amazing compensation I'm sure Chrissi would have just went searching for another company that was more reliable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd hate to see the result if Chrissi had a bad reaction to the shampoo... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't remember what the scent was, but it's probably safest to avoid any new releases from them that don't have reliable reveiws somewhere online. 

Good luck!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, it smells okay at least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, since her skin has started getting back to normal it's softer than ever. Maybe there's something to all these cosmetics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Don't Use Dove Lotion](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/66f7sa/dont_use_dove_lotion/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Use Dove Lotion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chrissi was the most ambitious person I'd ever met. When she had a plan, she followed through. Throughout our high school years I witnessed her impressive talent as I stood by in the role of best friend. 


She had her high school career laid out as soon as we started. I spent the summer before our freshmen year helping her estimate scenarios that might be impactful enough to affect the plan. She needed back up plans in case something went awry in the next four years. It sounds crazy, but it's not really as OCD as it seems. She just made a mental checklist about how to deal with things when they came along so that the high school experience would have less surprises and be more productive. 


High school worked out great for her. She managed to get a job during freshmen year, and kept it until after she had graduated as the Valedictorian of our class. I'd spent the last four years in awe of her ability to succeed at so many things, and graduation day was when I realized that I was in love with her. Besides her success she was beautiful, thoughtful, kind, and compassionate. She was always the first one to offer her help, and she always worked on everything with a smile. 


11 months, two acceptance letters from the same school, and an awkward declaration of love later, we were living in a small apartment together as a happy couple. I've never been happier, even though things can be rough at times. It was hard to find a decent paying job while attending college, and Chrissi had to quit hers because we'd moved too far away. 


It's been almost a year since we graduated,and we've only been in this apartment for a few months. I've finally got a job, but it just barely covers the rent and utilities. Chrissi had a great idea a few weeks ago though, since we need more spare cash until she gets a job as well. She decided to take an offer doing some product testing, mostly cosmetics.


It was simple enough, she'd get a package containing several products every week. She would have to keep a log of how the products worked for her and if she had any obvious reactions. After the specified time for each product, she would have to write a review and submit it to the company who ran the whole thing. She'd get paid depending on how long she had to test each product. $20 per product, per day. 


She received three products the first week, all of which were five day trials. Her idea was definitely going to help around the house, and the paycheck came as a direct deposit into her account each Friday. We were happy, and we finally were doing everything right. Doing well at classes, both earning money, no longer having to scrape by to live. Things had become pretty much perfect, until the second week of product testing. 


She only got two products, some type of lip gloss and a bottle of Dove lotion. I remember the day she got them very well because she had been so excited. 


I heard her exclamation of *Ohmygod* as I entered the kitchen, she was emptying a package onto the counter. Between unnecessary amounts of bubble wrap was a small makeup bag, and inside were her new tester products. When she pulled out the lotion she actually squealed. 


Look! *Look!* They got a new one, I love these lotions, she waved the bottle in front of my face as she bounced around the room. 


I don't think I've ever seen someone so excited about lotion, but she explained that this bottle claimed to be the latest version of the lotion she already used. Apparently it was some special scent as well-- who knows. She's always been prone to dry skin, so I could almost understand why having decent lotion was a big deal. The real odd parts didn't start happening until a few days later. 


The lotion was a 14 day trial, the bottle claimed that it moisturized more than just the outer layer of skin. It was supposed to go deep into several layers to leave lasting moisture throughout each day. Chrissi was excited about it, and she started using it the morning after she got it. 


It didn't seem to do much at first-- in fact, her skin seemed to be even more dry after three days. She told me it was normal, sometimes they didn't work right away or well enough. Regardless, she would be adding this information into her testing log and her final review. She hadn't had any side effects other than the dryness, so she had to continue using the product to receive payment. 


By the end of the first week things got worse. The dry skin was so severe in some spots on her arms that it flaked off occasionally. I had one memorable evening where she reached across the table for salt and I saw a small chunk of skin fall from her arm and into the gravy bowl. I didn't finish dinner that night. This was also around the time that she started complaining of the itching.


She felt *something* under her skin, or at least that's what I think she told me. She didn't make a lot of sense when she tried to tell me, and I got the feeling that she was keeping things from me. I know she wouldn't want me to worry, but it was scary not knowing the specifics of what was going on. I also knew that she didn't want me to start thinking of the hospital, she adamantly avoids it due to our lack of insurance and the cost of healthcare. 


She told me that the company would give compensation for the reaction when the trial was over, and that she just needed to make sure she kept all the information in her log and review. It seemed simple enough, another few days of dry skin before we got paid. 


Things didn't stay so mild though. I'd hear Chrissi whimper throughout the day when her dry skin rubbed up against something. She complained of being itchy, but she couldn't scratch because it made the dry areas raw. By the time we hit the morning of the last day she was a mess.


She put the lotion on for the final time that morning, and that evening she'd write out the last day in her log, then type up the review. Her skin was dry, flaking off, raw in spots, and she was still so very itchy. I was glad it was over, I hated seeing her suffer just to get paid. I thought everything was in the clear, we were done with the testing. Chrissi would be sure to avoid this lotion when it came out in stores, she would stick to the regular kind. 


That afternoon things took a turn for the worst. Chrissi was in the shower, and I was feeling playful so I decided to join her. I couldn't hear her over the shower until I got in behind her, but she was crying. I grabbed her shoulders intending to turn her my way, and was met with the worst experience of my life. As I gripped her shoulders the skin beneath my hands started to slide away from her body. I moved my hands away quickly, but watched in sickened awe as the skin fell away from her body and landed on the shower floor with a wet splash. 


She turned to me, and I saw the same fate had met the skin of her chest and stomach. She sobbed as she met my eyes, trying to explain through her tears that she had only tried to shower. She cried that it itched, and cried that it stung. I didn't notice until that moment that the water level in the tub had risen above my ankles, and looking behind Chrissi revealed that large chunks of bloated skin had covered the drain. Her skin seemed to be taking on the water too well.


I delicately helped her out of the shower, it was a painfully slow process. She had lost skin from her neck down, it wasn't all gone but it was a substantial loss. I noticed that she hadn't really lost her skin either, only layers of it. Her body was covered with tender pink patches, but she could stand the pain enough to pat herself dry. Within moments the patches that had lost layers were wet again. She touched a finger to a spot, the clear liquid substance seemed sticky. She cried again. 


I was at a loss for what to do. Here stood my girlfriend and lifelong best friend, and she was missing over 60% of her skin. Even as I stood there I saw spots of pink flesh begin to weep blood, it diluted and spread as it met with the clear substance that coated her. 


W-we should go to the hospital, I stumbled over the words as I stared at her deformed figure. 


She looked down at herself, visibly wincing at the extensive damage, I'll be okay. 


She claimed that the hospital trip would be a waste, her skin would fix itself. It was only layers missing, it would be fine. I decided to listen to the stubborn girl who was going to school to be a nurse, or maybe I was just compliant while in shock. 


We ended up wrapping her in a thin cotton sheet, but she mostly walked around bare. It hurt when things touched her moist and exposed flesh. She typed her log, typed her review, and posted them. She told them everything. I wish I could have seen the angered words that must have been at the end of her review. 


Within twenty minutes of posting she received an email from the company running the testing. They weren't happy with her review.


After a series of heated emails back and forth, this is what Chrissi has told me: If she deletes the review and signs a non-disclosure agreement, then she will receive a hefty compensation-- were talking *buy-a-house-and-car* compensation.


It's been almost a month and Chrissi is pretty much all better. There's been a large deposit in her bank account, and Chrissis review of Doves newest lotion is no longer on the internet. 


There's a reason I had to warn people though. This entire time I've been checking into the website where Chrissi posts her reviews, and I've seen 15 other people experience the same side effects as Chrissi. All of those posts were removed shortly after they were posted, and who knows how many have been posted while I'm not online. That's not the worst part of it all, because now I know why they're paying so much and having this kept so quiet. 


Today at the store I saw a familiar bottle of Dove lotion on the shelves. 

[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean by space-horror? I'm not very knowledgeable about space, rockets and such. Would a story about an astronaut stealing a souvenir from another planet, giving it to his daughter, and then having odd/awful things happen work?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, sorry for just sending my own, but now I know what to keep a lookout for. I know I've seen some similar to mine before. Have you tried r/nosleepfinder ? 

I'm spending time today reading, so I'll send you more links if I come across something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All things considered, I'm glad I heard this pun before I die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might readapt it to just be from the caller perspective, but [here's what I have already done with your idea.](https://www.reddit.com/r/cryosleep/comments/666beu/voicemail/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voicemail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I woke up that morning and was prepared for a completely lackluster day. I had nothing planned except for a visit to the doctor today. I rolled myself out of bed, the sunlight stung my eyes and I felt nauseous. Groaning in annoyance I got up and stumbled my half asleep body into the bathroom to drink some water and shower. 


I felt better afterwards, I collected my phone from where it charged on my nightstand and headed downstairs to make myself some coffee. The nectar of champions, I swear I drink enough that my blood, sweat, and tears could be bottled into energy drinks. I scrolled through the notifications on my phone as I waited for my liquid motivation to brew. 


I received the regular slew of harassment that I had been dealing with for the last three months. Emails and texts littered my notifications. An organization that called themselves New Kind has been persistently contacting me. They want me to become a member, apparently I have assets which would be of great value to them. I can't deny that some of their offers seemed a bit appealing, but they reminded me of a church-- or *maybe* a cult. 


The benefits to their members sounded great though. Full payment for approved college courses, jobs within the organization, the option for reduced cost housing, and the opportunity to have connections to the political world. The New Kind was apparently some sort of obscure government party that had yet to have a candidate in the presidential election. 


Though the benefits were amazing, it wasn't for me. If the interest of the organization was politics, it was not something I could do. I find politics tedious, and would loathe each day that I worked in a position in that field. I'm not sure what a member may stand to gain from joining without working. What would you even be there for? What were you a part of?


For months I've had knocks on my door, people stopping me in the street, and messages delivered by mail, phone, and internet. The people in this organization have been relentless in their attempts at converting me, and I have *no idea why*. I've been followed, chased, and had my windows knocked upon in the middle of the night. I've called the police, got restraining orders against people that they specifically caught, but it didn't stop anything. 


The police couldn't find actual evidence of any organization of any sort that existed by this name. All of the people who had been caught harassing me had been found unrelated to each other-- most of them weren't even from this state. Honestly, I'm terrified every day because of them. They are obsessively trying to convince me, and they are well veiled from the law. There was nothing I could do to stop it, and the daily bombardment became a routine. 


It still freaked me out of course, but there was nothing I could do except live with it. Maybe it would eventually stop. Maybe one day I'll stop seeing people standing outside my windows. Maybe I'll stop hearing whispers when the house should be silent.


After ignoring and/or deleting the messages from New Kind, I noticed a different notification. I had a voicemail, no missed calls though. It made me wonder,*can you even leave a voicemail without calling the person first?* My phone had been turned on while charging with the volume up, there was no reason I could think of that explained the lack of a call. But then I realized there was-- my phone has been known to have fairly poor reception, so it was likely that the call hadn't come through while it was acting up.


The voicemail was from a private number, but I smirked to myself as I hit play. *Like I'm dumb enough to believe this isn't about New Kind.* I rarely got voicemails, and never ones from private numbers. I assumed it was a new tactic for New Kind to pester me. I poured my coffee into a travel mug as a moment of quiet static came from my phone. I was surprised to hear an unfamiliar female voice, she sounded young-- maybe around my age. The surprising part was that she sounded scared, it was a stark contrast to the usual cheer which members of New Kind seemed to have an endless supply of.


*Listen. Claire White? This is for you. I'm going to tell you a story, to explain why you should never have children. My name is Claire Robins.*


I was a little surprised, and paused the voicemail to check the caller ID again. Stupid, I know. Private number, zero hints about who left the message. I figured it must be one of my friends instead of the creepy organization, since I don't give out my number to strangers. I took an annoyed breath before continuing the message. My friends knew that I wasn't planning on having any kids, no doubt this was some sort of joke to mock my standing on birthing children. I don't have anyone to help me out, and my own mother wasn't the best role model. I didn't want to have kids that I'd have no idea how to raise.


I checked the recording length of the audio, it would take a while to listen to. I guess my friends created quite the story to tease me. I grabbed my purse, my coffee, a set of earbuds, my keys, and my phone. I hopped in the car and shoved the earbuds into my purse-- I didn't need them yet. 


I took a glance around my neighborhood, a familiar dark car was parked nearly two blocks away. It seemed that some person or another from New Kind was always keeping an eye on me. I felt a sudden chill and looked away, something deep inside me told me I had made accidental eye contact with one of my stalkers. I'm not sure why such a thing still scared me so much. I tried to shake off the feeling of dread that ran through my body.


I plugged my phone into the cable attached to the car radio, and when I turned on the car I hit play on the voicemail. As I drove I listened, and the following is what I heard. Items in *this format, including brackets* are my own notes, to maintain minimal confusion for anyone reading.


The voicemail: 


-----


The easiest way to tell you this would be in the form of a story, but this story is true. I don't mean to insult your intelligence, but you need to take this seriously. You may not believe it at first, but I hope once everything is revealed to you that you will make the right choice. I hope I'm not too late to tell you. I think we'll begin with the moment I finally started working hard on my plan. It started with yet another mandatory news broadcast, I remember it all.


*Scratchy noise, possibly the recording device being moved. The voice coming through the speakers begins mid sentence, and is that of an older, but cheerful female. The sound was loud and distorted, as though the recording device was placed very close to a speaker*: 


**... Again we will see the light of day. Once again we will overcome the trials of famine, pestilence, and the ever-present threat of anarchy. Once again WE WILL SAVE YOU. These hard times will not dilute our determination to outlast our ancestors, we WILL prove that we have developed greatly as a civilization. This is the future! You are the future! Your children may be the first generations to experience the success of the New Kind! We ALONE have the power to make this world better, and total peace is nearly within reach.**


*I shivered as I listened to the recording that was part of the voicemail. New Kind. Was this some sort of advanced method to recruit me? I continued listening, unsure of how this related to them.*


**We are commencing the testing for this year in three weeks time. If you have never had this process explained to you, please seek assistance and information from a New Kind representative in your area. Thank you for giving your attention to this mandatory message--**


*Static noise, recording device being moved, followed by the other Claire speaking again*:


The message from Prime Minister Amari wasn't a shock, the speech that preceded her testing announcement was something we were used to. Our PM likes to recycle the same sentiments each time she addresses her nation. 


I vaguely wondered if the world had always been so corrupt under the surface, and if the fourth World War had just finally cracked the seal which held that darkness at bay. I wondered if other remaining nations did the same as us; I wondered if they even knew what we had done.


This is it though, this is me hoping to stop the madness. This is me recording what may be my last days-- I forgot to mention that when I started recording. It's hasn't been long since I set my plan into action, but if all goes well I won't be around to know. If things go wrong, well, perhaps someone from one of the other nations will find this audio device eventually. With respect to that I will explain what has been going on in the United Haven-- and maybe what the United Haven is. 


Be you Claire White, a far off nation, or a future member of the Earth who stumbled across this recording, *please* pay *very* close attention to the information I'm about to give you.


As we know there have been four World Wars.


* I narrowed my eyes at the road ahead as I heard the false words. There's only been two world wars, what nonsense was this other Claire spouting?*


People thought the third war was tragic, yet that was practically nothing. Only one country from back then faced the fate that a nuclear weapon brings about. That area was nicknamed the Land of the Damned for a long time. It wasn't even close to being inhabitable by the time we hit the fourth World War.


Everyone thought that humans had learned their lesson about the sacrifice that war demands when they killed an entire country, but apparently they had not learned enough. The fourth war saw the Land of the Damned expand greatly, and I was never taught the names of the many countries which used to stand before the toxic wasteland invaded.


There weren't many years between the wars, I believe I'm no more than five or six generations from where the Claire White I'm hoping to address is located. 


* My eyes involuntarily narrowed again. Was she claiming to be from the future?* 


My mother chose my name, it means something great in our society today. A giver of salvation. That's what they consider the First Ladies-- anyone named after them is likely the favorite child in the family. 


That brings me to the aftermath of the war. As far as our history texts have told us, the events that took place after the bombs were the most tragic tales in existence. More tragic than the initial death toll from the 27 nuclear weapons that were launched during the war. So many lives were lost in pursuit of the end of the war. Millions, maybe billions. At least, that's what we are told in the United Haven. 


When the war came to an end, United Haven arose. The leaders of it were ready, an entire organization of people that spanned throughout the decades had been waiting for society to crumble so that they could rebuild it in their own vision. 


Their vision is now our reality. They haven't completed it yet, but the methods they are using to achieve their goals are actions beyond what any human with morals could commit. We have cut all ties with outside nations, we are advised to ignore the fact that we aren't the only people on the Earth. If we ignore the outside, they will ignore us. That's exactly as it works too, we have zero interaction of any kind with anyone from outside of our nation. It seems to keep things peaceful-- at least between nations.


That means that most of our information about the outside world is passed down through family, tales of the past that no one could imagine happening today. I'm not sure why we couldn't imagine it, it's not as though this world has become any less cruel. Other information about the outside is given to us from the New Kind, like the history books and archived news broadcasts. 


From what I've gathered I can almost positively say that the United Haven is what used to be called North America. Though most of these antique maps show islands that have long since gone underwater. Our nation itself is not as big as one from the past may expect, every year the water rises a miniscule amount. We've lost many miles of coast land over the years.


Nuclear fallout has left most of the southern part of our country a wasteland, there are still many people who end up with radiation poisoning from being too close to the bomb sites. I honestly think the radiation is spreading, as though there's too much of it in the air to ever leave. It'll spread across the planet and smother us all while we sit unaware. Then again, who knows how they may have enhanced these weapons before the attacks. Who knows what deadly thing may have been unleashed. 


It's been years since the war, but no one has stopped being afraid. The people who don't seem afraid belong to the government. A government run by the New Kind. The New Kind are mainly women, generations who have hidden behind the scenes to develop a plan to make this nation great. Hundreds who knew that the war was coming and used it for their own gain. 


Oh, I forgot the tragedies-- these leaders have given us tales and evidence of the most depraved acts that were committed during and after the war. Communities who brought all the children around to the lakes, forcing them to drown in the toxic water. They were already poisoned from the nearby bombs, no one wanted all those children to suffer.


The worst part of learning about this part of the war was the video recording that came with it. It revealed women screaming as other women and men dragged children underwater. They were being held away from the children, obviously they did not agree with the majority of the community. Not only that, but the New Kind members who showed us these videos seemed very pleased as they watched the events unfold.


Other videos contained similarly soul crushing acts. People lit their homes ablaze while their families were trapped inside, groups of school children were led by their teachers to leap from bridges and overpasses, some videos showed people running mad through the streets. There was so much death, so much murder and suicide.


During the war rape and slaughter awaited in the streets, people were living without fear of consequences. *Were all dying anyways, why not?* Suicides, homicides, and crime as a whole rose. People were convinced that the world was ending, or they knew the war would take them in due time. No one wanted to sit around and wait for death.


I'm rambling I know, so let me simplify this for you. United Haven is a large country that is being governed by women and has isolated itself from the world since the greatest nuclear war in history. Society as a whole has gotten back to a relatively normal state. We have water, power, technology, and homes. We look normal. 


We aren't. 


Our government isn't run by peaceful matriarchs who want us to feel safe and free. The goal of the government is to maintain their positions of power, and control who will receive that power in the future. Men are treated as slaves and experiments, I'm fairly sure the researchers are trying to manipulate future DNA so that we stop producing boys. 


Children are monitored heavily, and disciplinary acts for any age are cruel and severe. The government is always watching for people who develop the right characteristics to be part of the New Kind. In fact, that's their preferred name. The women in charge want us to know exactly who controls us. Disobedience is not an option, we live pretending everything is fine. Pretending that the next town over isn't blackened shell that's been abandoned from the war, pretending that we're not afraid of the water purification devices failing, pretending that everyone who joins the New Kind is okay. 


There is no water supply that isn't contaminated, so abandoning our corrupt society is not an option. Much of the wilderness is contaminated with patches" of toxicity. Anyone who abandons civilization faces sure death. Live with them, or die alone in great suffering. The New Kind monitor their technology intently, anyone trying to leave the nations or disobey them is promptly dealt with. There is nowhere that they can't hear what you're saying. 


Yes, I know they're listening to me right now. *I KNOW YOU'RE LISTENING!*


-----


I flinched when her sudden scream came through the speakers in my car. The sound seemed to vibrate me to the core, as though this other Claire was sitting directly beside me. I actually glanced around the car as her message reached a moment of silence. I nearly laughed at myself, the amazing quality of this audio made her sound so close. I froze mid smile as I saw a car pull into the parking lot before me-- the same car that had been parked down the street from my home.


I paused the voicemail as I parked my car in front of the doctors small office. I collected my phone and purse, and glanced around. No one had left the other car, they rarely came up to me directly in public places. I let out a sigh at myself, I wasn't as calm about being constantly followed as I imagined I was. I tried to ignore my silent stalkers and entered the building. 


After speaking to the receptionist and confirming that my bi-annual check up was scheduled for 10am, I checked the time. I had ten minutes until my appointment, not including whatever extra time the patient already inside may take up. I sat in one of the hard chairs in the waiting area. Once I fished the earphones from my purse and plugged them into my phone I unpaused the voicemail, tensing in case the screaming renewed. 


Instead she continued in almost a whisper.


-----


I'm sorry That was inappropriate. I just get so frustrated about the state of my home. This entire New Kind organization is not a saving grace, they are monsters. They torture anyone who is not a part of them, they're secretive-- no one knew they existed until they decided to volunteer themselves as acting government until things settled from the war. I guess things never settled, or the rest of the population are too blind to see what the New Kind really are.


The testing, I forgot to mention that. It's part of the reason I'm reaching out to you, through everything I have learned in my desperate search for answers, you are a key element. There are hundreds if not thousands of other women in your generation that will help to strengthen the New Kind. Yes, I said *strengthen*. They already exist in your time, they're already recruiting. They've been around for too long. 


* My heart began to race as her voice picked up volume. She seemed so open and honest, as though she wholeheartedly believed in what she was telling me. Wasn't this what I was hoping for? Answers about New Kind? These were not the answers I was expecting.* 


Anyways, the testing examines your DNA and pinpoints markers that are found in the most loyal and successful of the New Kind. At this point almost every one of them contains every marker. These days they've only been examining pregnant women-- everyone else has already been tested. They've developed the technology to determine everything they need to know about a fetus. At least that's what they've told us, it doesn't seem to add up entirely. What is the *true* thing that their members possess which makes them desirable?


If you're pregnant with a child who contains all the markers, the New Kind adopts them at the moment of birth. You have no say in this. If they contain more than 40% of the markers but not *all*, you can raise them but they must attend a New Kind school. They will either develop to become low level members of the New Kind, or not. When they graduate at 18 you lose your child. You don't get to know if they were accepted into the New Kind, or if they were executed for knowing too much but not being good enough. If your child has less than 40% of the markers, congratulations, you get to have as normal of a family as you can.


This is where my issue lies. I'm going to be tested, and I know I'm pregnant. The chances of the baby not ending up with the New Kind are slim. I had a small indiscretion with one of the relatively high ranking men-- even the highest ranked man is worth next to nothing compared to the female roles-- their DNA markers ensure that members of New Kind have an almost guaranteed chance of making a New Kind child. 


Mother's that fight for their children don't last long, and there is no way to hide the pregnancy and avoid the test. They are everywhere.


I can't escape the fact that in a few months I will lose my baby. That day I heard the first announcement for the testing I panicked, I had discovered my pregnancy a few weeks prior. Hardly two months along by the time I remembered I'd be tested. Abortion is not an option now, and there is nowhere to go that they wouldn't see. They will kill me and anyone involved, so many people have already died. I can't be responsible for more, if my baby is a girl she could end up as one of the people who caused the state of fear we live in. 


The world ended and they reaped the suffering, bringing along their own form of it. I can't imagine what it takes to become one of them, but I wish they had never existed. This is why I sought you out, this is why I chose you out of all who I found. I was named for you. 


-----


I paused the voicemail when someone tapped on my shoulder. I glanced up to see the face of my doctor, he smiled. His other patient had left, and since my appointment started in less than five minutes he took me in early. 


The appointment was short, he did all the basic checks that I'm used to, and then I had to give him a urine sample, and a full physical with whatever tests that requires. I'm planning on applying for a nursing program at my local college, and they require me to get my own drug/physical tests and submit the results before I can be accepted. Not an issue for me, recreational drugs weren't my forte, I don't smoke, I'm fairly healthy, and partake in safe sexual interactions. He told me he could have the results back to me within a few days, and I left his office.


I didn't feel like listening to the rest of the recording on the ride home, I was too confused. There was a different car now that had followed me out of the parking lot, and I was more paranoid about it than usual. What if these people really *are* as awful as the voicemail said? Why do they want me? I had long since dismissed my initial thoughts about the message being a friendly prank. It was way too weird, and none of my friends are heartless enough to use my frightening stalker situation as fuel for humor. Honestly, I was entirely stressed out.


I spent that night fighting the urge to scream, tapping came from my windows and my phone rang repeatedly with calls from various members of New Kind. I shut off my phone, crawled into my bed, and turned on the radio to block out the people at my windows. I fell asleep shivering and crying beneath the blankets as the tapping turned to knocking, then pounding. 


By the next morning I was exhausted and curiosity got the better of me. I really wanted to know why I got that message, what was the point of it all? I had spent all night dreaming about a world in waste, where murderous matriarchs slaughtered those who opposed them. I woke up terrified, a sinking feeling deep in my stomach sat so deeply that it made me physically sick. After emptying my already baren stomach I sat down to clear my head, I couldn't pinpoint the deep sense of foreboding that ran through my body as I debated listening to the end of the voicemail.


I thought for a moment about deleting it, leaving it as something that did nothing but waste my time and fill my head with dark thoughts about the future. Maybe this other Claire had a good ending for the future she claimed to be a part of. She couldn't just be some random crazy person who happened to know my name and number, and then decide to call and ramble on about a dystopic future and the exact organization that has been making my life miserable.


I pulled up the voicemail on my phone and hit play.


-----


You are the mother of a First Lady. There were several before you and many after, but you are one of the most important keys. The First Ladies are the most revolutionary of the New Kind leaders. They bring the brightest ideas, the most controversial plans, and the most strictly enforced rules. They made the skeleton and nervous system which the body of the New Kind functions upon. They basically rule over all. 



A First Lady is automatically put in the running for Prime Minister. In fact, *everyone* who runs must be near or equal to First Lady status. Also, the Prime Minister must be a woman. Through psychological manipulation of the leftover population, they managed to rule and have their laws set as the norm. It's an awful time to be alive. 


Claire White, your daughter is going to be one of the greatest First Ladies ever to join the New Kind. Your name is sacred among them, as she chose to claim it as hers when she joined. There are several sacred names, all passed on by a First Lady. You choose your name upon joining, or your guardians pick your name if you begin young. My mother expected me to be eligible for the New Kind, but the name Claire is misplaced on me. I'm not enough for them, I'm glad I'm not.


Please Claire, I beg of you, please don't have any children. Avoid it at any cost. Your child will bring forth some of the most depraved actions that the New Kind have committed in secret. She will be so highly honored. Please, don't let her live.


-----


That was the end of the voicemail. I sat there and thought for a moment, wondering if this really was a joke. There wasn't really anything funny about it. It does nothing but enhance my fear of New Kind. Was this their doing? 


How does that make any sense? I mean, if confusing me was the point then they succeeded. I didn't know what to do with that information, I didn't have any way to prove it true or false. I tried to put it out of my mind that day, thinking about messages sent from the future puts a heavy weight on your mind. I took a nap and tried to ignore my daily dose of New Kind bombardment.


My doctor called me later that evening sounding joyful. No drugs in my system, I was good to go on the nursing course. After he filled me in on all the good news he had obtained from my tests, I went to hang up. He stopped me with a few words.


Why didn't you tell me? My wife could help you, she works at the hospital nearby.


My stomach dropped, but I didn't yet realize why, Um, what do you mean?


Your pregnancy of course! Did you forget that my wife offered to help you with prenatal care? I mean it was over a year ago, and you did say that children weren't in the plan, but-- 


I'm pregnant? I cut him off, stunned and on the verge of throwing up again.


Well yes, you didn't know? You should see someone about the baby specifically now--


Okay, bye, I cut him off once again and promptly hung up the call. 


I panicked, probably even hyperventilated. *What are the chances?* Seriously, what are the chances that I discover I'm pregnant the same day that a supposed message from the future claims my spawn will practically be Satan? 


I've been to several visits with doctors since then. I had no idea, but I'm nearly four months along now. It's been a few weeks since I got that voicemail. My friends have listened to it as well, and none of them are taking the blame. They didn't do it. 


I'm at a total loss, how do I deal with a warning from the future? What is the truth behind New Kind? How much of the truth did Claire Robinson actually know?


I think maybe that call was fake, maybe from New Kind. Maybe they were messing with my head because of my persistent denial. I'm still unsure, and I'm still afraid. I have one belief though: There is no way that I'm going to give birth to a child that will grow into an evil tyrant. I'm not hurting the world, I'm not a monster, and I'm not giving my baby up. I never wanted kids, but something about the life growing inside me has changed that. 


I want to raise a child, I want to give my care and affection, I want to teach, love, and inspire. I want to motivate, to be a shoulder to cry on, and a well of wisdom. Something about this baby demands that I be a good mother, it demands that I help my child succeed in life-- whatever life they choose. I have to give my child freedom, or as much as I can while New Kind monitors me constantly. I have to protect my child from them.


I'm not sure what to do yet, I'm not sure how to keep her away from them. What about the other mothers of New Kind members? I'm not alone in this. How do you protect your child from something that the future dictates will happen? 


Today marks the day where I fully believe I received that message from the future. This is my warning to anyone-- but especially women. Please avoid an organization called New Kind, please keep yourself and families away. Do not join them, no matter the offer. Do not trust them. I'm nearly at my breaking point with being followed, but I can't do anything. 


I might just give up and join them, I fear that they are waiting only to take my baby. I found out this morning during an ultrasound that I'm having a girl. The news made my heart sink, but it made my belief in my namesake complete. That message was true.


I can't do anything except warn others away. I'm not letting them take my daughter away, I'm not letting them corrupt her. In fact, after I post thing I'm going to answer the tapping at my window. I'm going with her, I'll join them if it means I can protect her. 


Maybe everything will be okay. 


-----


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/)








 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucked up and apparently read the first one wrong oops. 

[My Dog Won't Stop Barking](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/6665tg/my_dog_wont_stop_barking/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Dog Won't Stop Barking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been over three weeks since this began, and I think I'm starting to go insane. My girlfriend is acting insane, my friends are acting like *Im* insane, and my dog won't stop barking. Suffice to say I'm having a rough time lately, and I can't seem to figure out why. Before I get into the shadowy corners of my life though, let me start at the top.


I'd had a long day at work, and I arrived home late. It was around seven when I pulled my car into the driveway of the small bungalow which I call home. The house was a little pricey on rent, but it was worth it. This was one of the only areas that was a reasonable distance from both my job, and the college that my girlfriend attended. Kaylee lived a little further away from the school than me, so she spent nights with me if she had an early class the following day. I definitely didn't mind having her around, and she was friendly with my roommate. 


Sure, having a roommate isn't the best, but Jack is a really great guy. He cooks like a professional chef, and is insanely mature. He's become one a my best friends since we moved in together, and he always has his share of rent on time. Alabama was a fan of him as well-- Alabama would be my dog. A fluffy golden retriever, that dog means the world to me. 


My dog was part of the reason I was willing to pay more and share a house with a stranger. The house had a backyard, and there was actual *space* between the houses in the neighborhood. It was a refreshing change from the buildings within the city which pressed up against each other in a manner similar to having too many kids in one seat on the bus. Alabama appreciated the space out here, and the neighborhood was even nice enough to feel safe walking him at night. 


I had it all in this overpriced bungalow, and that night I had it all at once too. I was three steps north of exhausted when I walked up to the door, but that feeling was blown away as I registered the information in front of me. Alabama was jumping around my legs, apparently he had missed me today more than ever before. I noticed Kaylee's shoes by the door which made me happy, I'd been hoping to see her tonight. 


Alabama was pawing at the door while I took off my work shoes, he obviously wanted to be walked. I stepped into the living room to find my girlfriend, but I was momentarily distracted by a delicious scent that came from the kitchen.


Whatcha cooking, Jack? I called out as I walked towards him. 


You'll see when you eat it. Hold on, I'm busy. Kaylee's here. Tell her that it's almost done? He spoke quickly, he was very intent on whatever he was cooking. 


Not unusual for him, he makes the best food and that takes time. My own mother would envy the way that 23 year old could cook. Hell, I envied him myself. Two years younger than me and yet light-years older in the culinary department. I'll starve to death if I ever end up living alone. I headed over to the couch where Kaylee sat watching the TV with her full attention. I don't think she'd even noticed I was home yet, Pokemon was her absolute favorite show and she had no regard for the surrounding world when it was on.


I leaned over the back of the couch, gave her a peck on the cheek, and relayed the message from Jack. She nodded absently, giving me only minimal attention. I told her I was going to walk Alabama before dinner and she turned to me. 


You sure? It's getting dark, She sounded a little worried.


Babe, how many times do I have to tell you that this isn't your neighborhood? Seriously, it's totally safe here. I'll be back in twenty minutes tops, I gave her a wide smile, hoping it would ease her worries. 


She leaned up and kissed me on the cheek while telling me to stay aware of my surroundings, then she turned back to her show. She was adorable. Always worrying, anxious, but sweet. Sometimes she was absent minded, or she had trouble finding the motivation to finish things, but she was perfect to me. She may be insecure and not entirely up to dealing with the world each day, but she likes dealing with me so I count that as a win. 


I smiled to myself as I tied my running shoes, I had a relatively perfect life right now. My dark eyed beauty was sitting on the couch, holding a strand of shoulder-length black hair back so that it wouldn't interrupt her view of the show. She was so cute when she was lost in something she loved. My good friend and roommate was whipping up a meal that was sure to be both filling and tasty, and my dog was excited to see me. How could an evening be any more perfect? 


I leashed Alabama and we set out while dusk closed around the neighborhood quickly. The walk was pleasant, it was almost warm outside except for the wind that came every so often and raked nails of ice down my back. I shivered a few times, but the walk was helping to keep my body warm. Darkness seemed to be coming on quickly that night, since the streetlights had come on but children still played in the street. Checking the time revealed it to be just quarter after seven, and I wasn't surprised that the kids were playing in the growing dark. It was still relatively early in the evening. 


I didn't think much about the early onset of night, and the evening walk went as normal. I talked to neighbors, waved at kids, and watched Alabama sniff every object with extreme prejudice. Things didn't get strange until we rounded the corner to the back of the block. This street was connected to each of the fenced in backyards that belonged to the row of houses where I resided. Normally I would hear kids in their yards, or through open windows, and I'd hear dogs, couples fighting, neighbors chatting-- the street was silent. 


Being a 25 year old man doesn't make you brave or fearless, and I'm not ashamed to admit that I was a little freaked out by the dark silence. I noticed that night seemed to have fallen completely, but everything seemed so much darker than usual. My neighborhood look as though someone had been playing the with brightness and contrast controls on a television. Spots of darkness were absolute, and shapes within the darkness were practically indistinguishable. I didn't want to be outside anymore, even Alabama seemed wary.


Alabama may be only three, but he's smart. He was a puppy given to me by my childhood best friend, Ryan. Alabama was the only pup that his older dog gave birth to, and he was excited to have another dog that would live past the time when he lost Sandy. Sandy was the mother of Alabama, but she was old and constantly had issues which brought her to the vet. In a random twist of fate, Ryan met a girl who he decided to get an apartment with. No pets allowed. He gave me Alabama, who was still less than a year old, and gave Sandy back to his parents. Everyone was satisfied with the deal. 


Alabama has become very protective over my friends and I, so seeing him acting as though he was preparing for a fight freaked me out even more. I wasn't sure where the ominous feeling in the air had come from, but it weighed down on me heavily. I felt a moment of panic as I struggled to catch my breath while the sensation of being suffocated overcame me. I made a quick decision, as we neared the gate to my backyard I quickly unlatched the gate and brought Alabama into our yard.


I thought maybe the feeling would dissipate if we got off the street, but if anything it was only stronger now. I fell to my knees and clutched at my chest, I couldn't force my lungs to inhale. I heard Alabama whimper, and watched as he took tentative steps towards the corner of the yard. I couldn't see what awaited him in the shadows, but he stopped a few feet away from the unnatural darkness that consumed the corner. Then he barked, and suddenly the feeling was gone. 


I laid my back on the ground as I gasped for air, my lungs ached. I could still hear Alabama barking at something. I hoped that he was just paranoid and that he'd already chased off whatever had given me such a reaction. I have no idea what could have caused this, but I think Alabama saved my life that night. 


I told Kaylee and Jack about what had happened when I returned, but they didn't believe me. Apparently I hadn't arrived home until after 9pm. Somehow I had been stuck in my yard suffocating for over an hour, yet it seemed like only minutes. I didn't bring up the subject again, they were upset about my late return. I felt bad, but so incredibly confused. What happened back there? 


Later that night I woke to the sound of barking. I had hoped to put the strange incident from behind the house out of my mind, hoping it would never happen again. The barking gave me a moment of panic, and I clutched at my throat as though it would prevent another round of oxygen deprivation. Nothing happened after the barking, except more barking. By the time I had realized I wasn't in danger and should check on my dog, I wasn't the only one awake. 


I ran into Jack in the kitchen, he was staring through the glass sliding doors trying to locate whatever Alabama had been barking at. I looked myself and saw nothing. Jack confirmed that there was nothing there, but the dog hadn't stopped yet. He stood in one spot, staring intently at one corner of the backyard. The same corner as before.


I knew Jack would be annoyed if I brought up my unexplainable experience at 2am, especially while the dog barked so loudly that it was deafening to stand in the kitchen. Jack and I moved to the hallway. 


What do we do about that? He asked.


Ignore it, or try to put her in another room so that she can't see out the back door? 


Jack wasn't one for directly ignoring things that had obvious solutions. We put the leash on Alabama and had to literally push him away from the door. I took him to my room and closed the door, he slept in here fairly often anyways. The barking stopped for the night and everyone was relieved. 


Four nights after that was when I decided that Alabama should stay closed in my room every night. Every time it got dark outside and everyone went to bed, he would start barking at the empty yard. At this point I hard shrugged off my weird incident as a panic attack. I had simply gotten myself extremely worked up for nothing, and it seemed to have caused a negative impact on my pet. 


We didn't get a single night of silence. The first night that Alabama spent entirely in our room started out nicely. We both went to sleep, Kaylee wasn't staying the night so I let the dog in the bed with me. In the middle of the night I awoke to his panicked barks. He was standing on his hind legs, his front paws held him upright against the window. The window that faced the backyard. I glanced out the window and sighed-- nothing there. I moved him into the bathroom for the night after nearly an hour of attempting to calm him had failed. 


Jack didn't look impressed when I found him in the kitchen the next morning. He suggested that I bring Alabama to a vet to get checked out, the barking was driving him up the wall. Maybe my panic attack had traumatized my dog, surely a vet could figure out the issue. That's what I did. A few days later he was diagnosed and given anti anxiety medication. 


We had to wait to see if they would help, and so the barking continued. It had been just over a week since this all began, and now Alabama wasn't the only one in the house acting strange. 


After he took the medication for the first time things changed. He stopped barking at the backyard, and began barking at a corner in the kitchen. I figured that just *maybe* this was progress towards fixing him. When I got ready to take him for his evening walk he freaked out. He *did not* want to leave the house. We ended up finally getting outside after much struggle, but when we rounded the block and passed by our backyard, he stopped to growl at our gate. I assumed the medication had side effects.


We arrived back at the house to hear yelling from the kitchen. Apparently Kaylee had shown up while I was out, and now I could hear her shouting Jack's name. I was confused by the scene when I went to check on them. 


Jack stood perfectly rigid in front of the stove, staring intently at an empty corner of the room. He nodded periodically, as though he was listening to someone. That someone obviously wasn't Kaylee, who was trying to snap him out of his trance. I had no idea what was going on, and as I stood there I watched Jack suddenly move.


After another nod he raised one hand so that it hovered over a pot of something that was boiling on the stove. Kaylee tried to grab his arm, I tried to get across the kitchen to push him away-- we weren't fast enough. Jack's hand plunged into the boiling liquid, and he stayed emotionless for several moments. Kaylee and I froze, I suppose neither of us knew how to react. 


The seconds that passed felt like years, and when the screaming began I found myself stunned again. Jack pulled his hand from the pot, screaming in agony. He looked around the room as though he was seeking out the person who had done this to him. I stared at his hand, the skin was red and already blistered. It looked painful and grotesque. He ran to the sink and turned on the cold water, wincing as he let it run over his scalded hand. 


What the fuck? He stared at us, looking for an explanation about his injury. 


You just zoned out and stuck your hand in a boiling pot! Kaylee shouted, her face was pale from witnessing the event, What are you even asking?! 


Jack looked confused, What, really? I nodded when he looked to me, confirming Kaylee's version of events. I don't remember. I was just getting dinner ready, and then all of a sudden you were both here.. And my hand.. Fuck, I need to go to the hospital. 


None of us knew what to say after that. We didn't know how to talk about what happened, and we weren't even sure *what* had happened. Jack called a friend to drive him to the hospital since Kaylee had an early class and I was going to drive her. He didn't want us to waste our night waiting on him to get his hand checked out. 


Jack left, Kaylee and I watched TV like nothing happened, and Alabama barked in the kitchen. There was nothing else to do. At some point the dog stopped barking, and we took that opportunity to go to bed. We woke early to more barking. I assumed that Jack was home, but that wasn't the case. Upon checking my phone I found that he was spending the night at the hospital and wouldn't be home until the next evening. 


It wasn't long before the alarm was set to go off, but it was still an unpleasant awakening. I found Alabama barking at a corner in the living room. I sighed and went through the day as normal. Dropped Kaylee off, bought coffee, went to work, came home. Kaylee was there again, she had gotten a ride from a friend, and Jack would be home any time. 


I went inside only to hear whimpering from the dog, Kaylee was on the couch transfixed on something. 


Did you put Alabama in my room? I asked her as I sat beside her. 


She didn't respond, instead she just stared. Upon closer inspection I realized that her daze wasn't caused by something she was watching, she was staring into the empty corner of the living room. I didn't want a repeat of whatever happened to Jack, and panic set in. I grabbed her by the shoulders and shook her until she looked at me. 


What are you *doing?* She looked at me as though I had grown a spare head.


You were just staring off into space, did you hear me talking to you? 


I'm just watching a show, she sighed, Sorry, you know I'm not good at dividing my attention. 


It's okay hun, I didn't know how to make her believe that she had been acting strange, so I let that line of questioning slide for a moment, Did you lock up Alabama? 


She nodded, He kept barking at this corner, she gestured towards the spot-- the same spot that I had seen her staring at, and he wouldn't stop until I put him in there. 


Okay, I paused while I debated my next words, You know, that's the same corner you were looking at when I came in. 


I guess I'd annoyed her, because she took on an irritated tone while she denied my claim. I ended up dropping it entirely, it was going nowhere. This was the first of many similar days. 


I'd get home to find Kaylee staring at the corner, by the third day she was whispering to it. Alabama had to be put in a room any time we were home, or else he'd endlessly bark. After a few days Jack left. He went to go stay with another friend for a bit, he claimed it was just until the medication started working on Alabama. 


I felt like I was going insane. Kaylee was over every day, and she was speaking to the corner more and more. I couldn't make sense of what she was talking about. 


*Almost time, almost?* 


*Are you close? Come closer.*


*I miss you, don't go.* 


*The warm room, you can come.*


*Four more days?* 


It scared me, but every time I confronted her about it she claimed to have no memory of it happening. I was worried about her, but I wasn't sure what to do. I thought about asking if she wanted to go see a doctor about it, but I wouldn't live through a conversation where I implied that she's crazy. I figured that maybe the only way to help would be to provide her with proof. 


Unfortunately I haven't been able to get that proof. I'll come home and hear the whispering, but it stops when I enter the room. She's been acting totally normal around me, but when she's alone in the living room I hear her. I've been at a loss for what to do. 


I've tried asking Jack to come back and help me figure things out, but he refused. Somehow he came to believe that Kaylee and I were responsible for his burn, and that we weren't giving Alabama the medication. He claimed that I was insane and trying to intentionally drive him out of the house. Nothing I could say would convince him otherwise, he thought it was all just a tactic to freak him out and keep him away. He wasn't coming back. 


Now I need some serious help, because I'm not sure what to do other than leave. The issue with leaving is that Kaylee won't go. She hasn't left the house at all in two days, and her secret whispers have become more frequent. I found her whispering to a corner in my bedroom last night. 


*One more night?* 


*I'm so happy you're here.*


*I'll wait for you.* 


I haven't been able to put Alabama in my room since then, he's been barking at the new corner and whimpering at the bedroom door when we keep him out. 


I'm not sure what to do guys, but whatever my girlfriend has been whispering with will be here soon. 



[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one might work for you, but it also might not. It's *almost* a monster. I have a similarish one, but I'm not sure if it hits the mark for you either. I'll edit to add. 

[My Children Never Lied](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/592px2/my_children_never_lied/)

[This is a short story](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/5y4f6u/i_tried_out_a_dating_site/)

Andddd

[How To Drive A Boy Crazy](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ux2ut/how_to_drive_a_boy_crazy/)

Let me know if any of these are close to what you want, I'll let you know if I remember/find similar stories c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried so hard to contact anyone who can help expose them, but they are hidden too well. I can't breach them from the outside, but perhaps from the inside I can make a difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm with them I can watch her, I can tell her what could happen if she followed their path for her, I could intervene. They can't steal my child if I volunteer to give myself to them, I'll always be able to keep an eye on her.

I can't explain the immense feelings I have as my daughter grows inside of me, I *have* to do this. It's what my baby needs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit o.o 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's my opinions: 

Loved your Hell series, that was really awesome! There's a lot of ways to do a series, you could go anthology style but since you said that the first series would be *required* reading, I'm not sure if it's the same.

I'm currently doing an anthology type thing, and though it's not required to read the original post, things make more sense when you have everything. 

What I've been doing is linking all related posts at the bottom of the original post, and then I'm going to just have the link to the original and most recent related posts on the future parts.

Because it's not a traditional "must read in this order" series, I never flagged it. You can read one part and walk away, or you can dive in and find all your heart desires and await more. Also, there are four confirmed posts that relate to each other and all of them have done very well. They don't have a singular title though, because I wanted it to be apparent to anyone new to the story that there is no set start point. This is also why my links are at the bottom of the stories, so that you're not deterred by the fact that it's part of a bigger picture. 

If you want it to be an entire spin-off series, I'd give it a title that hints back at  "How to Survive In Hell" so that it might attract fans of the first one, but still have a relatively original title for the new series. 

Orrrr, if I'm way off track and you mean one singular post set in the same universe as the Hell series, then definitely a unique title. If you want it to be able to stand alone without *mandatorily* the series, then I might suggest not relying too heavily on huge plot points from the original post and instead being vague when something like that happens. Enough to maintain the immersion, but still make a reader who is unsure of what you're referencing curious to learn more.

**TLDR;** If it's not mandatory to read the series beforehand, then link it at the bottom. If it is mandatory, link at top. 

-----

Also, I think the dentist story is cool c: For nosleep or somewhere shorter? And the other advice you got about it was great c: 

Sorry I'm super excessive with words
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Workshop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I propose that more of us who enjoy the sub try to put in an hour or two per week/every few days/whenever to help out in r/nosleepworkshops so that we can help others get out more content that would be great to read on the sub.

We should become more involved in the place that could birth legendary tales. It would be nice to read a great story and say, "Hey, I helped this user with this/a story and this is an amazing product they've created!" 

Plus it's not super active, so if more of the regular nosleep people join in, we could all help guide some more quality content into nosleep! 

Just a thought c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I plan to write the shit out of this soon, for cryosleep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you link the first part of your story, please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first one seems like you could definitely make it go interesting places, but the second one was a little confusing.

 I'm not entirely sure what's going on or how the narrator is posting when they're repeating a day over ten years ago. (But I may have just missed something). 

Your writing is good IMO, there's the minor mistakes like not capitalizing the letter i at one spot, and little typos that are hardly even noticable.

I definitely think it's a good start! Good luck on your stories c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be interested if you're looking for more people c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would make a neat story ohmygod  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point, only if you were to become a Shade or you attract attention from one of them and they decide one way or another to involve you in the Shade world. 

You could make a friend who wants you to know the world as it truly is, or you could accidentally anger the wrong person and end up in literal pieces days later. 

Edit: Oh and as for learning more, there are a lot of people who have posted on here speaking of either guests at the hotel, or the same types of Shades we've had as guests. They're unlikely to identify them as Shades though, as I believe that is a hotel nickname.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as she's told me, "a little bit of this and that".

From what I've learned while being here she's obviously some part Shapeshifter. When I first got here I learned the Latin name that was given to her by other Shades, which translates roughly into "Charming Mutt".

She has said before that she is the only one of her kind, and that her mother was slightly different but also a very unique creature. 

From everything I've gathered by talking to her and seeing her own posts online this is what I've got:

Some part Shapeshifter (due to body changing) 

Some part Siren/Other water creature (She usually takes her victims underwater to consume their souls, as far as I know. As well as the hypnotic quality her singing has. 

Some part Demon. (She's clever, sly, and incredibly convincing. Her eyes occasionally turn into inky black pools, a trait I've seen only in Shades that are some part demon.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet cover!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I played around with your idea!](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/64g5ks/ive_been_speaking_with_my_shower_head/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've Been Speaking With My Shower Head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not quite sure where to start when I describe what happened. I suppose the easiest thing would be the day it all began. 


I had just finished unpacking everything in my new apartment after living there for several weeks. The place wasn't great, it wasn't the closest to the fun spots in the city, and it certainly wasn't in the nice part of town. It was old, and honestly kind of run down. Twelve stories high and at least one of the two elevators was guaranteed to be out of order on any given day. 


The nearest stores included a convenience store, a pharmacy, and a pizza shop. As far as I was concerned the apartment had two key upsides: the price was decent, and those few stores on the corner would do me fine when I was too busy to take a twenty minute bus ride to a real grocery store. I had a great first few weeks at the place, the violence in the area was a little alarming but I felt safe enough while in my apartment. 


That started to change one night. I was in the shower when I started hearing a strange distorted sound. It sounded almost like a man sobbing. I turned off the water so I could hear better, which led me to the discovery that the sound was coming from the shower head. It stopped for a moment before I heard a long sigh and retreating footsteps. Suffice to say I was a little weirded out. 


I thought that perhaps sound travelled easily through the outdated plumbing. For a while after I wondered vaguely who I may have heard through the pipes, but I ended up forgetting all about the incident. It didn't stay off of my mind for long though, because I had a similar occurrence a few days later. 


I could hear muffled noises again and shut the water off to listen in, I don't know what made me so curious. I was disgusted to realize that the sounds I had previously thought were sobs were instead groans. I could hear some guy getting off. I didn't bother finishing my shower, I felt odd from so deeply invading someone's privacy. It's not like I intended to listen in on that sort of private moment. 


I sighed at myself, I wouldn't have heard so much if I hadn't been listening in. I pushed it out of my mind promising myself that I would ignore it from now on. I tried, but it seemed that whoever was in the other end of the pipes decided otherwise. The voice in my shower started talking to me. It got more and more frequent, like he suddenly realized that I could hear him and decided that he should bother me excessively. 


It started with him just pouring out random stories about his day, I could hear him speaking but no other voice replied. It's like he was talking to himself, or talking directly into the pipes to see if anyone would reply. After hearing his voice on and off for a few days I decided to respond to his conversation. That ended up being a mistake, as soon as he knew someone could hear him he would *not shut up*. In the beginning I didn't even respond constantly, but I eventually learned that his constant chatter was almost pleasant when he had someone to reply to. 


I figured he was nuts, talking to some random female voice through the pipes each day. I suppose I seemed insane as well, because I started talking back every time. I had conversations with my shower head daily, the voice on the other end seemed so kind and reasonable. It was an odd way to make a friend, but I'm not a very social person so I take human interaction where I can get it. The man in the pipes described himself to me, not much older than myself and he sounded really nice. He was so humble, it threw me off that someone met in such an invasive way could be such a good person. 


We didn't always talk, some nights I would hear the sounds from the shower head and know that he was busy. I could hear conversations, I couldn't make out the words when I heard them, but I heard distinctly different voices and could understand the gist of the conversation by the tones they spoke in. I heard a lot of girls visit him, almost never the same female voice twice. I'm a little ashamed to admit that I felt kind of jealous. *There is this guy that I talk to every single day who is seemingly perfect and lives in my building, yet he's with fifty girls that aren't me.* 


It was a petty thought, he could still be a creep who happens to get a lot of action. He could be some sort of stalker. Hell, he could even just be playing movies to make me wonder about what I'm hearing. I didn't start wondering if I was truly going insane until he told me I was. That night I was sitting in the empty bathtub with a blanket, talking to my friend through the shower head. The conversation was entirely normal until it wasn't. 


You know you're crazy, right? The voice laughed through the pipes. 


What do you mean? I questioned. 


You're insane, talking to an imaginary voice that comes out of your shower head every day.


I thought over his words for a minute, Are you fucking with me? 


I'm not a real person. I'm a voice in your head that you're desperately clinging to so that you feel less alone. You're alone. There is no one on the other side of the pipes. You're all alone. 


I didn't reply, and he didn't say anything more after that. There was no more voice coming out of my shower head. After having constant conversations for nearly a month I felt conflicted. Was I really going insane? Was it possible that I made up a man speaking to me through my pipes? 


The nights passed almost quietly for a few days, it seemed that only an eerie noise made it's way through the pipes. I couldn't begin to describe it, but it creeped me out. Each night the sounds coming from the pipes only seemed to get louder, and I woke up horrified several times at the odd noises coming from the shower head. I heard them in my dreams sometimes, the haunting quality of the sound coming out of my bathroom made the perfect soundtrack to change any pleasant dream into a nightmare. 


After nearly four nights I finally got irritated enough to contact the landlord about the noise. I questioned if the pipes carried sounds from other apartments, or if there was some sort of error when they renovated the building before I moved in. I was sick of the chilling sounds I heard each night. 


I was told that he didn't have the answers to my questions at that time and he'd come by and look into it, but there was nothing he could do about it until morning. That night had to be one of the worst, the noises seemed almost like howls of pain and it became the soundtrack to my home all night. I heard a noise that sounded almost like distorted laughter, and for some reason found myself truly afraid. 


I turned on the news to drown out the sounds from the pipes, and hopefully calm myself down a bit. The news was relatively calm, except for a small update on an ongoing story. *Young women in the city continue to go missing. Police have no suspects at this time, and have been unable to find any links between the victims. More on this after weather and the break.* 


I sat there stunned as the weather report played in the background. I couldn't help but feel incredibly paranoid about the sounds I heard from my shower head. I changed the channel before the story came back on, I didn't want to make myself worry any more than I needed to. I was up until nearly dawn channel flicking, afraid of the nightmares that would plague me when sleep finally hit. 


I ended up sleeping most of that day away, my body was exhausted from being so freaked out the night before. I awoke to the sound of knocking at my door. It was mid afternoon, a time when I would normally be wondering what I wanted to make for dinner. I was practically half asleep when I answered the door, and I was entirely unprepared for what awaited me on the other side. 


I spoke to two police officers that evening, instantly becoming fully awake and alert when they explained to me why they wanted to ask me questions. There was a man renting out the apartment below me, an apartment which appeared to contain rain barrels that collected water from a few sources in the building. They believed my house was one of the sources. 


I told the officers about everything I heard through the shower head, but didn't find out until days later what I was technically involved with. 


The man renting the apartment turned out to be the son of the owner of the company which did all the updated plumbing for the building. He also happened to be the person who oversaw several pipe installations that drained used water from the bathtubs into the barrels in his apartment. Due to evidence found in the apartment, they believed he may be involved with the girls who have gone missing around the city. 


Over the last few weeks I've seen his face on the news, he honestly is very attractive. When people who knew him described him it seemed he was exactly the kind of person I'd assumed when we had conversations through the pipes. I felt a little guilty for having been attracted to a guy who might be a serial killer. I don't know why he said all of those things through the pipes. 


They never told us why he was collecting the used water from various apartments, and they haven't caught him yet. 


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the guests used to be human, so they enjoy speaking with someone who is still human but is aware that they are not. They don't have to pretend to still be human and can feel at ease talking to someone who is living the way they would had if they hadn't been changed. 

Some of them are humans who have been dead for quite a while, so they enjoy updates on the world through someone who is still living in it as a human. 

The singing is another thing that is also commonly requested by those Shades who were once human. They request a natural human voice to sing things they haven't heard out loud for any number of years. Most of the other employees have some sort of voice "modification" that humans don't, so they don't always produce the desired effect that a guest may be looking for. 

There are many Shade guests that have human visitors or companions with them at the hotel, but the majority of our human guests are entirely unaware and kept away from our Shade guests. Different floors and everything. 

There are a select few human guests who are already highly aware of the Shade presence in the world, they are kept especially safe from any harm other guests may do, and they are not subjected to the memory removal process that other guests go through.

Most Shades that I have encountered don't actually hate humans at all. Some of them like them a lot actually, they like to watch human lives play out and see what we deem important in our lives. They like to learn about us, live with us, or they need us to maintain their own lives. They aren't all murderous, and they don't all eat to kill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During my break I just tried to live life normally. I worked on getting regular sleep, but I still had nightmares about things from the hotel. I received a message from the Good Shade each day asking if I had decided to leave or stay. 

I tried to spend time with my friends, spent a few nights out on the town with everyone. I was just so paranoid. The stories I'd heard from the hotel made it impossible to rule out any of the strangers around me as Shades. 

I didn't want to go back to a life where I wasn't aware of how much danger surrounded me, so on the last day of my break I let Mister Smith know that I'd be coming back for another quarter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Delivery](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/649wuc/a_delivery_to_the_good_shade_hotel/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Delivery](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/649wuc/a_delivery_to_the_good_shade_hotel/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Delivery to the Good Shade Hotel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently working my second interval at this hotel. Every interval is three months, and during the time off you have two weeks where you can decide to stay or quit. I haven't really thought about quitting since back when I first started, I honestly really enjoy working here. It has really opened up my life and allowed me to witness and experience a world few ever see. A world where we're aware of the Shades.


I didn't take a lot of time to think about quitting during my break, I was too excited about all the things I was learning by working here. I'm nearly to the end of my second three months, and something just happened that I'll definitely be keeping in mind when I have the chance to quit. 


A few nights ago everything was going as normal-- or at least as *normal* as it can get around here. I was sitting at the front desk talking to Alphaeas most recent persona, Chiara. Beautiful as always, she was petite and 53. She sported olive toned skin, and highlighted deep auburn hair. She smiled sweetly from behind the desk as I came back from helping a guest. 


Hey Tyler, Mister Smith needs you to do him a favor, She told me, her bright blue eyes widened as she waited for my reply. 


Sure thing, is he in the office? I asked. 


She nodded at me, and seemed to be trying to hide her amusement. I guess she knew what I had to do and found it funny, or she knew how confused I would be when I received the task. Either one would be exactly in her character. I tried to prepare myself so that Chiara couldn't laugh at me, if I just handled the job and got it done well enough then she'd have no reason to chastise me when I returned. 


Mister Smith did not seem impressed when I entered his office. He gestured for me to have a seat and began speaking after a sigh. 


I'm sorry to have to ask you, Mister Stephens, but all of our other employees are tied up, and with a guest we have scheduled to arrive this evening Alphaea must remain at the front desk. 


Alright, I replied hesitantly, What do you need me to do? 


There is a delivery for the hotel that needs to be picked up. You will drive there in one of our hotel vehicles, exchange vehicles at the delivery pick up location, and return the delivery to the hotel, He stared at me as though this was the most serious matter on the earth. 


I can do that, I told him. 


There are some requirements. You cannot look in the delivery vehicle to see what you are carrying. You are not to unlock the back of the vehicle, and please do not ask any questions about what you are collecting. 


I nodded, moderately concerned about what it could be that I was delivering. He told me what car to take and gave me the keys, the GPS was already set to show me the way to the pick up location. Chiara wiggled her fingers in a goodbye as I walked by the front desk to leave. She had a knowing smile on her face, but I didn't want to give her the satisfaction of admitting that I was freaking out on the inside. 


The car was plain and silver, the kind if car that you see absolutely everywhere. The drive towards the delivery was quiet and dark. I had nothing but time to think on the hour and a half long drive. *I could be picking up guests. I could be picking up raw meat, or large dead animals. I could be picking up corpses.* I panicked the entire way there, I had no desire to find out what the consequence would be if I were to peek at what I was delivering. 


Arriving at the location of the switch brought me to a small dirt road in a dark wooded area. Suffice to say this did nothing to ease my worried mind. Two suited men exited the Uhaul truck that was parked there. As I stood outside in the cold one of them instructed me to drive as I would normally so that I would not be pulled over. They got in the hotel car and left. 


It took me a few moments to clear my head and remind myself to ignore whatever it was I had to deliver. I steeled myself for the journey ahead as I got in the driver's seat and noticed that the GPS in the truck already had the destination set for me. *This is a simple task. They've made it so easy for you.* I let out a breath that I didn't realize I was holding as I started the truck and drove away. 


I tried to distract myself from the task at hand by listening to the radio, but no stations were coming in clearly. The voices distorted by static would somehow manage to slip their way into my already hotel ravaged nightmares. The car was quiet, and according to the GPS I was only about 15 minutes away from my destination. Unfortunately that was when I started hearing noises coming from the back of the truck. 


Banging, muffled shouts, and crying. A panicked thought crossed my mind, *I'm delivering live people.* I sped up, my delayed start must have messed up the schedule set for the passengers to sleep. I didn't know why they were being delivered, if they were human or Shade, and I didn't want to know. I couldn't come up with any peaceful reason that I might be taking a shipment of people to the hotel. I knew that these people likely wouldn't enjoy their stays at the Good Shade. 


It was none of my business. I got back to the hotel at record speed, and Mister Smith awaited me by where I was instructed to park. He asked some follow-up questions to be sure I hadn't tampered with the delivery, then sent me on my way. I was sure Chiara could tell I was freaked out when I sat behind the desk. I couldn't stop thinking about what I'd done, *am I a criminal now? Did I just commit human trafficking?* 


Hey, earth to Tyler? Chiara waved a hand in front of my face. 


I snapped out of my panicked state, Um, yea? Sorry.


How was the drive? She asked with an eyebrow raised at me. 


It was okay, I replied vaguely, still trying to avoid her mocking me. 


Great! She smiled widely, An incoming guest has requested a human bring the bedding to the room prior to arrival. 


I nodded, and she gave me the room key and directions, Room is U12-54, the requested bedding is located on the storage floor, U1. Take the second elevator, don't be too long.


I hoped a simple walk to place some bedding for a guest might calm me down, but Chiara had an odd look on her face when she gave me this task. She knew something I didn't know-- as usual. I used the card to get down to the underground storage floor, a place I had never been previously. The floor looked just as nice as any of the ones that actually housed guests. It was clean, well lit, and looked like a regular floor overall. The one major difference to this floor was the set of doors to the left of the elevators. This led to the basement laundry room and linen storage. 


I grabbed a small cart to place the bedding in and loaded everything I could possibly need to make a guest's bed. As I was leaving the room I noticed a group of people coming out of the storage elevator located at the back of the hotel. I recognized several hotel employees who seemed to be escorting these people into different rooms on the storage floor. I willed the elevator to get here faster and take me to the guest room, I didn't want to think about where those people came from. 


After I got back into the elevator and headed down to the guest room things went smoothly. I got the bed made in record time, spent less than a minute on the storage floor to return the laundry cart, and made my way back to the front desk with confidence. Chiara looked exhausted. 


You okay? I asked her. 


She sighed, High-maintenance guest tonight. We'll probably be giving a lot of requested room service tonight.


I wasn't concerned about it at that point. It wasn't the first time a guest had requested a human to deliver their room service since I'd been working here. Requested service meant great tips for escorting a person, food, or items to a guest. It wouldn't be so bad. The night was fairly uneventful until we began receiving room service requests. Chiara had to provide escort for me to the room each time, it was hotel regulation. There were a few simple requests for drinks and such, but every so often there would be a request to bring up a friend. 


Each time the guest requested a friend, Chiara made a call and another employee would escort in a person. We would then take that person to the guest. This happened three or four times during the shift, and I became concerned when none of the people returned from the room. I couldn't imagine what this guest might want so many people for. The worst part was, I recognized those people as part of the group I had seen entering the hotel through the service elevator. 


The delivery was eating me up inside, and before the shift ended I had to ask. Chiara and I were sitting at the front desk waiting for another request. 


Did I deliver people to be eaten by guests? I blurted out into the otherwise quiet lobby. 


What? Alice laughed, Obviously you're aware that you did deliver people, but not specifically to be eaten.


I stared at her, she was acting as if this should be obvious to me. 


She rolled her eyes, They either owe something or have done something and are being brought in for the hotel to take care of, or they were requested by a guest to be delivered for whatever purpose they wish.


I had no idea how to respond to that. How does the hotel *take care of* the people who have done it wrong? Also, *whatever purpose* does not rule out people being eaten. The rest of the shift kind of went by in a blur, I was exhausted from the continuous nightmares that working here afforded me. The stressful shift did nothing but add to my exhaustion and I went by the last of it on autopilot. 


It's almost time for me to go to tonight's shift. I remember Chiara saying one thing while I was zoned out, one thing that stuck with me. One thing that might always remain true. 


Youve been here for what feels like so long, yet you still hardly know anything about the Good Shade.


-----


*Related:*


[My first day at the Good Shade](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/6104g9/the_good_shade_hotel/)


[First Hotel Holiday](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/61xh3y/our_hotel_celebrates_the_strangest_holidays/)


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [April Fools!](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/643jli/i_thought_it_was_an_april_fools_joke/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Thought it Was an April Fools Joke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was sick of the day, of the cold and the rain. I was tired of the coworkers pranking each other in honor of a childish holiday. Work was chaotic with everyone acting crazy, and I ended up leaving early for the day. No one seemed to care, the day was already lacking in productivity. 


I thought it was another April Fools joke when I got to my house to find my usual parking space filled by the car of my best friend. I silently thanked living in the middle of nowhere for the unlimited parking space it provided. I parked in the driveway and entered the house, steeling myself against any pranks that might await me. 


Instead I heard the noise of muffled groans coming from the master bedroom. For a brief moment I hoped harder than I ever had that a joke was being played on me. Maybe she was pretending to be some stranger and they'd both pop out when I went in the bedroom and laugh at me for thinking something mischievous was going on. 


They didn't notice me in the doorway, and I backed away from the room where my best friend straddled my boyfriend. I felt sick to my stomach, and absolutely enraged. I walked quietly to the coat closet and pulled out the shotgun we kept in there. I walked back into the bedroom as I loaded the gun the way my boyfriend had shown me. 


They noticed me standing in the doorway as I aimed the gun in their direction. Alexis panicked and pulled the sheets up to cover herself. 


Ricky, what the fuck? She glared at him as though *she* was the one who had been cheated on. 


He looked around the room at a loss for words for a moment, Katherine, I told you this morning we were *through*.


He looked both angry and afraid as he stared at the gun in my hands. I thought over my stressful morning, lazily swinging the gun back and forth to point at them each one at a time. Alexis spoke again. 


Kate, cmon. This is a joke right? You *had* to see this coming--


Whatever other words she had planned to say died on her lips as I pulled the trigger. Tears ran down my face as I watched her traitorous body slump over. The shot shook my small frame, and I was shocked that I remained standing in place. I leveled the gun again to point at my boyfriend. 


He pleaded for his life, claiming he'd do anything I wanted. I had him spend the next few digging a grave for Alexis, and it was dark by the time he dropped her body in the hole. I still held the gun, and I aimed it at his back as he let her body fall. He stumbled into the grave with her, screaming in pain as he landed. He had just finished his whimpering by the time I filled the hole in enough to cover his head. It took a while, but I once again was thankful for being so far from neighbors as I shoveled dirt. 


It was nearly 4am by the time I got the grave filled in. I roamed through the house to find the keys to Alexiss car. I drove it until I was out of state and in a dark alley. I removed the plates and left the keys inside the car. I had to take a bus back to the town nearest to my house, and it gave me a lot of time to think about what I'd done. 


Over the last few months I had noticed Alexis and Ricky becoming friendlier towards each other, but I didn't think much of it. On the morning of April Fools I had been sitting at my desk when I received the texts from Ricky. 


*I can't do this anymore. I'm tired of pretending.*


*Katherine I'm leaving, for Alexis.*


*We all knew this was coming, could you respond?*


I ignored the texts, I figured they were a joke and didn't want to complain about it while I was dealing with everything going on at work. By the time I got home I had forgotten about the texts, but seeing Alexis's car in the driveway had renewed the feeling that I was part of an elaborate joke. 


I thought it was a joke until the moment I saw them in bed. Then I broke, it wasn't a joke at all. 


It's been a few days and I find myself wishing I had known it wasn't a joke. I would still be alone, but I wouldn't have to stare at the patch of dirt behind my house that holds the bodies of my two closest friends. 


What can I say? I've always hated April Fools Day. 


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I did a spin on your idea!](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/63vpqt/it_all_started_with_a_game_of_would_you_rather/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It All Started With A Game of Would You Rather </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It all started with a friendly game of WYR. For those of you who may not know, Would You Rather is a game where you pick something you'd rather do out of two options. They can be simple and innocent, sometimes they're sexual, sometimes they're boring, and sometimes they're just plain weird. 


I was in an online chat room talking to some friends when one of them brought up another room. It was a room entirely for games of Would You Rather, called *RatherIndeed*. A group of us decided to head over and play, it was something to pass the time. 


They started out weird but it made the game interesting, the bot in the room shot out questions to each player one at a time. It was like any other game of WYR. I don't remember everything about the game, except that it didn't last long with all of our joking in between questions. 


*Would you rather have your body only intake liquid in the form of grape soda or MelloYello for the rest of your life?* 


*Would you rather have to sing every word you say or never speak again?*


*Would you rather witness the death of someone you love or blind yourself?*


*Would you rather have every piece of meat you touched rot, or never be able to eat meat again?* 


*Would you rather have horrifying predictions of your friends dying every time you tried to sleep, or never sleep again?*


We all made random choices from the compilation of weird selections, but I remember it being funny to see everyone explain why they made the choice they did. We laughed about how ridiculous it would be if we were to find ourselves in a situation where we actually *had* to make such insane choices. 


We only had enough time to go once through everyone in the room, by then half of us were tired and other people in the main chat room were starting to leave as well. We all left *RatherIndeed* entertained but also a little weirded out, some of those selections were apparently made for complete psychopaths. I went to sleep that night and had awful nightmares about some of the options from the WYR game. I ended up waking an hour before my alarm and spending the entire day exhausted. 


By the time I got home from work I was too tired to sign in and chat, I decided to take a nap but that ended up being shorter than intended. I woke up about an hour later and figured I had time to pop in and say hello while I made dinner. Emily was on video complaining of an annoying cough she was developing, Glen was flooding the text chat with some nonsense I was too tired to actually pay attention to, Alex was complaining about something being wrong with the lunch he bought earlier, and Kristy was nowhere to be found. 


It was an average night, despite the absence of Kristy. We all chatted and joked around until we got tired or busy and left the room. Over the next week things got weird for everyone. I could hardly sleep, each night I had nightmares that I couldn't fall back asleep after. Each night that passed resulted in me sleeping less and less. 


Every day in that I came into the chat room everyone seemed worse as well. Emily had gone from a mild cough to a painful and violent one that shook her entire body, her throat was raw from the force behind each cough. Glen had some type of flu, he couldn't keep any liquids down. Every time he had a drink, he violently expelled it seconds after he swallowed. Alex began thinking the meat he'd had at lunch last week had somehow been tainted and was now ruining other meat for him. He couldn't stomach any meat, it all tasted spoiled. Kristy still hadn't come back to the room. 


We asked Alex about her, since they were engaged but still living long distance. He showed us their texts from earlier that day, he seemed concerned. 


*A: Hey babe, you okay? Haven't been talking much lately.*


*K: I just can't look at you! I don't want to see or talk to anyone right now.*


*A: What are you talking about?* 


*K: I keep having these dreams of you and all of our friends dying.* 


*A: I'm sorry honey, is there anything I can do?*


*K: Stay away from me.*


*A: How am I supposed to do that? For how long?*


*K: I don't know! Forever maybe. I can't stand looking at you.*


*A: I'm sorry*


*K: It's not your fault. I'm sorry, I'll talk to you later? I have an idea about how I can fix this.*


*A: Okay, I love you.* 


She hadn't responded to the last text, and I felt bad for him. I wasn't sure why she would be acting so odd. Kristy and Alex are the most perfect couple I've ever known, surely this wasn't her pushing him away. None of us really knew what to tell him about the texts except for the standard, *I'm sorry, it'll be okay. Tell her we miss her.*


Everyone was so miserable, we hardly participated in the regular group chat with everyone else. We all ended up fading out early, promising to say hi again the next day. I didn't sleep at all that night, the nightmares came immediately as my eyes closed. 


When I signed into the chat the next evening and was exhausted and irritable. My mood perked up when I saw Kristy was on video, the room was happy to hear from her again. She spoke excitedly to everyone, and several of us joined her on video. I noticed that Glen was drinking several two-liter bottles of MelloYello while he was on video. 


Dont you think that's a bit excessive? I asked him. 


Its the only thing that hasn't made me sick, He explained.


I suggested he see a doctor about bring dehydrated, and the night continued on pleasantly. Everyone was happy, but Kristy began complaining of a pounding headache. When we suggested that she go lay down and rest, she replied very sadly. 


I just wanted to make sure I got to see everyone at least one last time.


Everyone started questioning what she meant, but instead of answering any of us she clutched her face in her hands and started screaming. 


I don't want to see this anymore! She cried out as she dug her nails into her eyes. 

Before anyone recovered from the surprising change in mood, Kristy grabbed a pen from the desk she sat at. There was a moment of stunned silence as she hastily drove the pen towards her face, and the sickening sound that came through my computer's speakers will haunt me forever. Panicked messages came rolling into the chat, and several of the people on voice and video call screamed. Kristy responded to nothing as she removed the pen from her eye and stabbed it into the second one. 


People called the police, Alex left to drive the three hours to her house, and everyone in the room who knew her in person rushed out to get to her. No one knew what to say as Kristy sat in front of her camera covered in blood and screaming. I left the room, I couldn't handle looking at her. 


I didn't sleep that night. The real life nightmare played over and over in my head. I couldn't understand what was happening. When morning came around I decided to pop into the room to see how the night ended. 


Apparently the police got an ambulance to Kristy, and Alex ended up meeting her at the hospital. She's still in there recovering and speaking to therapists. They think she's gone crazy. She keeps claiming that she wouldn't stop seeing her friends dying until she couldn't see at all. According to her she was right to do it. 


It's been days since then, maybe weeks. I can't keep track of anything, I don't remember the last time I slept. I can't function well enough to spend an entire day at work, but I've been keeping up with news about my friends from the chat. We've all paid visits to doctors. Emily has to go in for surgery, she got an infection that has actually eaten away at her vocal chords. They're going to try and remove the remaining infection before it spreads anywhere else. She'll likely never be able to speak after. 


Glen went to the hospital and they tried hooking him up to an IV bag, but for some reason his body didn't react well. Apparently he had screamed when the fluids entered his body through the IV, he claimed that it felt like fire burning through his veins. Before they could do anything to help he had a heart attack. They tried to bring him back, but he was gone. 


Alex visited his doctor about the meat making him sick, and the doctor couldn't find any medical reason that may have caused it. He suggested that Alex become a vegetarian, which was a disappointment to him but easy enough to do. It wasn't so bad for him. 


No matter how many prescriptions my doctor gives me, I cannot sleep. I can't stop hallucinating about my friends being torn apart. My entire life has become a waking nightmare and I don't even know what's real anymore. I'm going insane, everything is out to get me. All I want is sleep and it won't come. I'm losing myself. 


I've tried going back to *RatherIndeed* to see if anyone from there had a similar experience and was talking about it, but I couldn't find the room. 


I can't stop thinking about the choices we made, unaware of what we were deciding. 


Glen would rather only intake MelloYello for the rest of his life, Emily would rather never speak again, Kristy would rather blind herself, Alex would rather never be able to eat meat again, and I would rather never sleep again. 


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so excited to hear it :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so excited to hear it :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for narrating! We had such an awesome team who contributed amazing pieces to the story!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woo, congratulations everyone! Great round c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inspire me! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm out of the country for a month and a half, meaning I can't be online more than once or twice a day, so I have a lot of time to write. 

I was wondering if anyone would like to give me random prompts, literally anything even if it's silly. 

They can be as simple as one word, or as complex as you'd like. I will work throughout my stay to do *every single one.* Upon posting, I will reply to your comment with the link to the story. 

PS; A big hello and thank you to everyone who I've met in the IRC chat, you guys literally have made my days brighter and I'll miss every single one of you until I get back. You are seriously the most amazing, crazy, hilarious and kind people I've ever met! 

PPS: The posts from April Fools are hilarious, that was awesome mods!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Loyal To The End </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one has ever been a best friend to man the way dogs have. Loyal, protective and fluffy little creatures. Maybe not so little, like Doug and I. A man of nearly six feet tall and a fluffy Saint Bernard, we can be an intimidating pair at times. I'm Tim, by the way. 


Doug has been my best friend for a few weeks now. You'd think we'd still be in the adjustment phase both being fully grown, but we adapted to each other quite well. We know each other's feelings and routines. Life was great for us. 


There was one night that changed everything. I was half asleep in the master bedroom, the house was quiet. Doug left the room, he was probably thirsty and headed downstairs for some water. He must have tripped, because I heard a series of loud thumps. 


I ran out of the room to check on him. He lay crumpled at the base of the stairs. There were clearly several broken bones, blood leaked from a source I couldn't see, and I could tell from a distance that his neck was broken. My best friend Doug was dead. My owner, my human, the man who had fed me. 


I felt despair for a moment, I was his pet after all. But this accident meant I wouldn't have to hurt him myself. I shifted out of Tim the Saint Bernard, back into my regular human form. Doug was pathetic, lonely, and adamantly disbelieved anything supernatural. He would have lost it if he had lived until I made my move. His redeeming trait was the fact that he was very wealthy. 


No one hides things from their dogs, they're loyal friends, they *can't* rob you blind. Unless they're like me. 


Loyal until your end. Woof woof.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, and good luck c: Hope things settle down as you get into the swing of it all!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strange Things Happen in Louisiana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot to be said about small towns in Louisiana, but that's not important. Most people who aren't from around here don't listen seriously to the things I say anyways. They don't understand that I'm not crazy, lying, or stupid. I know what I'm talking about though, it's the type of thing that's *almost* considered normal around here. 


Let me start from the beginning-- the beginning of that day at least. It started out good, I stepped out of my bed and my foot landed on something cold. Lifting my foot revealed a penny-- heads up! I smiled to myself, *my lucky day.* I checked my mailbox as I was leaving and was hit with another happy surprise, the check from my tax return was sent to me earlier than expected. 


I stopped at a coffee shop on my way to work, and discovered that they had just brought back the delicious chocolate lattes they used to have. Better yet, the person in line before me had paid for everyone else in line! This morning was positively serendipitous, I'd never had such a lucky string of events happen to me. It didn't stop there. 


When I arrived at my dad's flower shop I was happy to find that we had received a new supply of bleeding hearts, it's been months since we'd had them in stock. My dad always forgets to order them, but they're my absolute favorite. 


Morning daddy! I greeted him while I inspected the bleeding hearts, You finally remembered? 


Sorry darlin, wasn't me, He shrugged, Seems someone had em sent for us.


I nodded happily, we've had locals do such kind things before. Working at a flower shop is always so nice and peaceful, everyone in town stops by to get flowers and ask about Mister Time. I work there with my dad and my sister Liz, a family run business as long as it's been open. 


I was flying through my morning routine of tidying, setting up arrangements and displays, and answering calls. I had thought my day was wonderful already, but then I answered a call from a familiar voice. 


Hello, Freeman's Flowers, how might I help you? I said cheerfully as I picked up the phone. 


Um, Elizabeth? Don't tell Anna I'm doing this okay? He said hesitantly. 


*He* being Damien Dappa, the boy I've had a crush on since elementary school. We were good friends, and I was a little surprised he mistook me for my sister over the phone. I was too curious to correct him, and Liz wasn't here today. 


Sure thing, this is Damien, right? I said. 


Mhm, do you guys have those heart flowers yet? She's been talking about them forever.


We just got some in today! I replied, probably sounding a little too excited. 


Great! Can you send them to her in a pot? I think she'd like it better if they didn't die. I don't want her to know they're from me though, 


Sure can, leavin a note? I asked. 


Yea, can you write I know how much you love these, D.D? 


I nearly laughed at his idea of anonymity, there was likely not another person in town with his initials, and if there was I had no idea who they might be. I confirmed his order, and let him know that they'd be sent out this afternoon when dad did the deliveries. By the time the call ended I was happier than a kid in a candy store. 


It was nearly noon by that point, which meant I had to go check on Mister Time. He was a *gift* of sorts, given to the shop when my mama was still around. She was special, and that part of her was sent into me when she passed. The cancer got her good, a tragedy for the whole town. Everyone loved mama, she was an honest and kind woman. She tried to get Lady Priestess to help her, she was so afraid after she told is Mister Time had shown her face, but Lady Priestess couldn't cure cancer. 


Before she passed only her and Lady Priestess could talk to Mister Time. Lady Priestess isn't her real name, but no one knows anything else to call her by. I swear she's been around longer than the town itself, but she's a mysterious magic practicer. She's the one who gave us Mister Time, she said she needed a break from caring after him. 


Mister Time is an oddity himself. He lay in an open casket in the back of our shop, and mama insisted that he loves flowers so we bring him a different one each day. He doesn't have a face-- not always that is. He lay there in his dark grey pinstriped suit, and the head above his shoulders bears the features of a mannequin. There's all the hills and valleys of a regular face, but the skin is seamless. No eyelids to blink, no lips to open, no nostrils to breathe. Sealed up tight. 


Visiting him is usually easy, I always leave with news that'll break someone's heart, but the town is comforted by knowing what's coming. Gives us time to prepare. The thing about Mister Time is that sometimes he lets me see a face, that's how he talks. He doesn't say anything, but the face he uses tells me everything I need to know. It's the next person who will die in town. 


He can't tell me how they go, or when they go, so all I know is *who* will go. He only tells one a time, the face repeating each day until the person no longer exists. Every time someone dies our shop gets a rush of traffic the next day. Everyone wants to be the first to hear what Mister Time told me. 



Besides Lady Priestess and myself, everyone else in town could only see the seamless face he wears. That's why he's here, Lady Priestess was tired of holding the responsibility. We can't stop telling people what he reveals, the town has gone crazy before over it. It's an accepted fact of life here, we always know who's next. I don't mind doing it, I've become fond of Mister Time. 


I brought him bleeding hearts that day, and greeted him cheerfully. I always spoke to him, just like mama would. I told him about the flowers, and how I'd had such a joyful stroke of luck that day. When I asked him about his day his response ruined my lucky streak. 


He wore my face. I asked if he was sure, but the face remained the same. I felt sick, and thanked him for letting me know before I left the shop early. I didn't want to spend my day telling the town that I was going to die. The longest anyone's ever lived after being shown is about a year. I'd be incredibly lucky to make it that far. 


I hid in my house all day, and when my flower delivery arrived I burst into tears. Bleeding hearts seemed appropriate for my day. Everything had gone from amazing to awful. 


I composed myself by the next day, getting back into my regular swing. I wanted to make the most of the time I haf left. When people asked about Mister Time, I told them. I got so many pity filled looks, but I ignored them. I wasn't going to be brought down by this. There was something I kept from the town, I didn't want to scare them. 


Each day since seeing myself in Mister Time, my visits got worse. This had never happened before. As each day passed the face he wore became more mutilated. I was shocked every time, it wasn't a progressive deterioration. Every visit brought a different form of horror. One day I had no eyes, another day featured my skin melted, and yet another showed my lips sewn shut. At that point I realized that I needed to tell someone about this. 


Lady Priestess was the only one I could go to, she was the only one who knew the details of dark magic. Calling her gave me a huge revelation. 


Lady Priestess? I asked when the call was answered. 


Yes child? She replied calmly. 


It's Annabelle Freeman, I'm sure you've heard of what Mister Time has told? She made a noise of agreement in response, I need help, I pleaded. 


I explained to her the horrifying things I'd seen. 


Ah, I've seen a similar case. Your mama came to me the same as you.


I was shocked, Mama had cancer, why would she come to you?


She saw similar such things, she told everyone it was cancer, but I'm the nearest to a doctor she saw. Somethin else was eating her from the inside, She sounded thoughtful as she said it. 


Can you help me?


I can do for you what I did for your mama, come see me, She hung up right after. 


I did end up going to see her, but for all her spells and rituals I've only become sick. I've asked her who will take my place with Mister Time, and she's told me that it will pass through the women of my family. When I'm gone, Elizabeth will carry on talking to Mister Time. 


I'm afraid though, Lady Priestess has placed some sort of spell on me. I can't directly tell anyone in town about her healing. I can't make my fingers write or type the words, I can't force my tongue to form them. My only saving grace is here, where no one in the town roams, where Lady Priestess would never find. 


She visits my home, I've become bedridden most days. Each day I see her she looks younger, just slightly. I feel myself getting weak, and I swear I've aged more each time I see my reflection. Something is *very* wrong with what Lady Priestess is doing. 


There's a reason Lady Priestess has lived longer than anyone in town knows. 



[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on mobile and I can see it o.o  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [There Was Something Wrong With Our Last Foster Child](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/62i82s/there_was_something_wrong_with_our_last_foster/)

**By Team: Oblivious Train to Nowhere** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orbit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst thing I have ever been

Was when I was a Princess

Because you were the King

My title never meant a thing

Bestowed me a crown, 

A gift to yourself

To prove you were kind

To everyone else 

It's all about you

It's all just a show 

"Look what I've done, 

I'm perfect, justly so!"

Anything you will do 

To boast your own name 

As for your children? 

They were pawns in game

"Pity me, for they left! 

Pity me, I'm alone! 

I did nothing wrong, 

They abandoned their home!" 

We're all pawns, we're all planets 

You are self-dubbed the Sun 

For without us in orbit

Narcissism hasn't won

Sit on your false throne 

Claim yourself as righteous King 

Believe the worlds orbit you

Though you're really nothing 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
