<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1073</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's a bullshit parody of Democrats that ignorant, hate-filled racists have pushed so that they can knock down a strawman, and you've fallen for it.

Why on Earth should we be tolerant and not call out ignorance, hate, and greed?  It makes no sense, yet here you are trying to argue it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahahaha!!!!

I'm going to let your comment speak for itself. An anarchist!

LOL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, so the alt-right is yet another conspiracy you people are pushing.  

Doesn't the need to make up reality ever make you stop and think that perhaps you've got it all wrong?  Even a little? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha!  Does it even remotely bother you that your comment made no sense when read in context?  No?

Sorry, do you know what the word "context" means?  I keep forgetting the intellectual level of the average Trump supporter - and you don't even appear to be up to the average.

SAD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you don't seem to feel any need to call out alt-right hypocrisy, of course.  Which is also hypocritical.

Also, the idea that calling out nutjob racists who are actively trying to destroy the planet is somehow intolerant is idiotic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How entitled alt-right snowflakes are!  You demand I answer your question when you didn't even bother to answer mine first.

I suppose rudeness goes hand in hand with ignorance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So instead of answering the question, you shit out more ignorance.  I guess you're proud of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL!  You literally called someone ignorant in your last post then came in here to criticize me for doing the same.  Hypocrisy much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very good!  It was not an argument.  It was a question.

Now that you've grasped one of the basics of English, maybe you can answer the question.

Are you proud of your ignorance or do you secretly feel ashamed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do right-wingers always believe they should have a safe-room bubble that floats around them wherever they go and protecting them from reading things they don't want to know - which is just about everything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost every penny gained from reversing environmental regulations will go to corporations, but workers could gain some tiny increase in wages depending on the situation.  That extra 80 cents per week certainly wouldn't make up for the extra taxes, property damage, and healthcare costs, of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you proud of your ignorance or do you secretly feel ashamed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep!

The real 'genius' (if you can call it that) of this deal is that it'll cost workers far more in taxes and medical bills than $35.00 per year to cover the cost of environmental damage to public roads and other property caused by things like climate change and acid rain as well as the costs and pain from increased pollutants in our water and air causing cancers, breathing problems, deformities, etc...

 All that to save less than a dime a day.  What an incredible con that scumbag has pulled on us! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jan. 20: Within moments of Trump's inauguration, nearly all references to climate change disappear from the White House official website. While there's nothing unusual about a new administration changing the website, the new language is telling. "President Trump is committed to eliminating harmful and unnecessary policies such as the Climate Action Plan and the Waters of the US rule," reads the new site's only reference to climate change. "Lifting these restrictions will greatly help American workers, increasing wages by more than $30 billion over the next 7 years."

I just thought it was interesting to note that in exchange for destroying our water and air, Trump offered each worker in the country a whole $35.00 per year! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Youve Probably Forgotten Half the Terrible Things Donald Trump Has Already Done to Our Planet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but he could shoot somebody and not lose voters.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Activism Won Net Neutrality - Can it Stop Trump's FCC from Rolling it Back? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that all depends on whether he's bought shares of Smith   Wesson recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump tells NRA: 'I am going to come through for you' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress to avert shutdown hours before deadline, vote for weeklong extension </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea crisis: Tillerson says US is open to talks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Glendale school board is attempting to break off in order to segregate itself from minorities.  This is the finding by the judge in this particular case.  That violates the prohibition created by Brown.  If the judge had not found that the reason for breaking off was due to race, then I'd agree there would be little recourse.  Furthermore, government entities do no have the right to act in a discriminatory manner against discreet minorities unless a need can be shown and the action shown to be as narrowly tailored as possible.  I don't think that saying the minorities would be blamed for not segregating fits those requirements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Separate but equal is not legally justifiable regardless of supposed good intentions.  IIRC, the belief that black children would be more comfortable with their own race was used to no avail in Brown as well.  I definitely remember it being a deciding factor in Plessy, which Brown overturned.

EDITED TO ADD:  Parents have a right to be racist, shitty people, public school boards do not.  I think that has been well established by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a nutshell, this decision states that yes, the rich, white community wants to shut out black kids - which the judge actually calls "deplorable" - then says go ahead and do that, even though it violates the precedent set by Brown v. Board of Education.  

The judge's reasoning?  The black kids will be blamed if she doesn't violate a major Supreme Court ruling forbidding "separate but equal."

Makes no sense and should be immediately overturned.  After that, the judge should be removed from the bench for racial prejudice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US to tighten sanctions on North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the whiners crying about the millions of non-existent "Bernie or Bust" minions who supposedly withheld their vote from Hillary spent half as much time actually supporting their shitty candidate, maybe we wouldn't have Trump in office right now.

Also, the crying is starting to look pretty pathetic at this point.  You chose a lousy candidate and she lost to an orange con-man despite cheating in the primary.  That's history.  Grow up and focus on something productive already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
