<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9866</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is a link to his Paleo art website.](http://www.simonstalenhag.se/paleo.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simon Stlenhag's art is stunning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may also recognize it is more difficult for the cat to take the food from its beak than it is for the dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article [*The life review experience: Qualitative and quantitative characteristics*](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/27840285) can be found in the journal *Consciousness and Cognition*.

**Abstract:**

**BACKGROUND:**
The life-review experience (LRE) is a most intriguing mental phenomenon that fascinated humans from time immemorial. In LRE one sees vividly a succession of one's own life-events. While reports of LRE are abundant in the medical, psychological and popular literature, not much is known about LRE's cognitive and psychological basis. Moreover, while LRE is known as part of the phenomenology of near-death experience, its manifestation in the general population and in other circumstances is still to be investigated.

**METHODS:**
In a first step we studied the phenomenology of LRE by means of in-depth qualitative interview of 7 people who underwent full LRE. In a second step we extracted the main characters of LRE, to develop a questionnaire and an LRE-score that best reflects LRE phenomenology. This questionnaire was then run on 264 participants of diverse ages and backgrounds, and the resulted score was further subjected to statistical analyses.

**RESULTS:**
Qualitative analysis showed the LRE to manifest several subtypes of characteristics in terms of order, continuity, the covered period, extension to the future, valence, emotions, and perspective taking. Quantitative results in the normal population showed normal distribution of the LRE-score over participants.

**CONCLUSION:**
Re-experiencing one's own life-events, so-called LRE, is a phenomenon with well-defined characteristics, and its subcomponents may be also evident in healthy people. This suggests that a representation of life-events as a continuum exists in the cognitive system, and maybe further expressed in extreme conditions of psychological and physiological stress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life Does Flash Before Your Eyes When Having Near Death Experience, Research Suggests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article [*The life review experience: Qualitative and quantitative characteristics*](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/27840285) can be found in the journal *Consciousness and Cognition*.

**Abstract:**

**BACKGROUND:**
The life-review experience (LRE) is a most intriguing mental phenomenon that fascinated humans from time immemorial. In LRE one sees vividly a succession of one's own life-events. While reports of LRE are abundant in the medical, psychological and popular literature, not much is known about LRE's cognitive and psychological basis. Moreover, while LRE is known as part of the phenomenology of near-death experience, its manifestation in the general population and in other circumstances is still to be investigated.

**METHODS:**
In a first step we studied the phenomenology of LRE by means of in-depth qualitative interview of 7 people who underwent full LRE. In a second step we extracted the main characters of LRE, to develop a questionnaire and an LRE-score that best reflects LRE phenomenology. This questionnaire was then run on 264 participants of diverse ages and backgrounds, and the resulted score was further subjected to statistical analyses.

**RESULTS:**
Qualitative analysis showed the LRE to manifest several subtypes of characteristics in terms of order, continuity, the covered period, extension to the future, valence, emotions, and perspective taking. Quantitative results in the normal population showed normal distribution of the LRE-score over participants.

**CONCLUSION:**
Re-experiencing one's own life-events, so-called LRE, is a phenomenon with well-defined characteristics, and its subcomponents may be also evident in healthy people. This suggests that a representation of life-events as a continuum exists in the cognitive system, and maybe further expressed in extreme conditions of psychological and physiological stress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have analysed accounts from people who have had near death experiences and identified life review experience (LRE) as a trend. LRE may occur because certain parts of the brain that stores memories are among the last to shut down when the body is close to death. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brontosaurus watercolor by superka_01 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to amend the title and say by "stable" I mean not a flat line on a graph. Hovering is still relatively stable.

Some populations that overshoot carrying capacity (K) can crash, which is an abrupt decline from high to low population density as resources are exhausted.

In my part of the U.S. (and many other parts of the U.S.), we see this with [White-tailed deer](http://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/mammals/w/white-tailed-deer/) (*Odocoileus virginianus*) populations in the winter. Without natural predators ([Grey wolves](http://www.nwf.org/wildlife/wildlife-library/mammals/gray-wolf.aspx), *Canis lupus*) to stabilize their numbers, the deer populations rocket up in the Spring and Summer and then due to starvation crash come winter.

Unfortunately, this not only affects deer but the habitats they live in. When one organism goes unchecked it can wreak havoc on the organisms they feed on, share resources with and even the soil and other [abiotic](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Abiotic_component) (non-living) resources around them. [Here is an example graph](http://www.msudeerlab.com/img/dynamics/dynamics6.jpg) of what an unchecked deer population does to the [ecosystem](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ecosystem). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carrying capacity is the largest population a particular environment can support long term if there are no changes in that environment. Natural populations rarely remain stable, but instead, rise and fall, hovering around carrying capacity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cat's Eye Nebula from Hubble [800 x 760] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crow feeds cat and dog a snack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Schmidt Insect Sting Pain Index </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The American Museum of Natural History in New York City. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rare critically endangered Rodrigues fruit bat pup born at San Diego Zoo Safari Park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [National Wildlife Federation's page](http://www.nwf.org/wildlife/wildlife-library/amphibians-reptiles-and-fish/spiny-softshell-turtle.aspx) on these cuties.

*Apalone spinifera* are found throughout most of central-eastern North America and as far south as Mexico. They will eat whatever fits in their little turtle mouths!

Some folks keep them as pets, you can see Reptile Magazine's care page [here](http://www.reptilesmagazine.com/Turtles-Tortoises/Turtle-Care/Soft-Shelled-Turtle-Information-and-Care/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The spiny softshell turtle is a sit-and-wait predator. They bury themselves under a layer of mud at the bottom of a lake, with only their head sticking out, and catch prey as they swim or float by. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hooded crow sleds down a roof on a plastic lid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Symbiosis can be obligate, where two organisms cannot survive without each other or facultative, where species live together by choice. They vary between mutualism (positive for both), commensalism (positive for 1, neutral for the other), and parasitism (positive for 1, negative for the other). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronauts, from the left, Gus Grissom, Ed White II and Roger Chaffee stand near Cape Kennedy's Launch Complex 34 during training for Apollo 1 in January 1967. [3000 x 2333] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiger Longwing (Heliconius hecale) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiger Longwing (Heliconius hecale) [OC] [1600 x 1200] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome! I'm very happy to clarify. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Archaeology is a subset of Anthropology. Anthropology is the overall study of humans (there are several subsets; cultural, linguistic, biological/physical, etc.) whereas Archaeology is the study of material culture or history of the past by looking at/unearthing physical remains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For more information here is NASA's article [*Junos Close Look at a Little Red Spot*](https://www.nasa.gov/image-feature/jpl/pia21378/juno-s-close-look-at-a-little-red-spot). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [I Ate] Omaha steaks hot dog on a potato bun with ranch Sunchips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASAs Juno spacecraft has spotted a huge anticyclonic storm in Jupiters high north temperate latitudes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never get tired of hearing about new species and how their lineages have affected organisms alive today. Their name means *Mighty traveler from Egg Mountain*. 

According to the article, if you just want a summary:

In the many-branched tree of lizard evolution, Magnuviator comes out as an iguanomorph. This is the broad  group that includes the anoles, basilisks, and iguanas that skitter around the American tropics today. But back in Cretaceous time, DeMar and coauthors write, the closest relatives of Magnuviator lived in Asia. The fossil stem from which today's iguanas and anoles sprung used to be spread in a different pattern over the planet, setting part of the foundation for what we see around us today.

Journal article *A new Late Cretaceous iguanomorph from North America and the origin of New World Pleurodonta (Squamata, Iguania)*.

Abstract:

Iguanomorpha (stem + crown Iguania) is a diverse squamate clade with members that predominate many modern American lizard ecosystems. However, the temporal and palaeobiogeographic origins of its constituent crown clades (e.g. Pleurodonta (basilisks, iguanas, and their relatives)) are poorly constrained, mainly due to a meagre Mesozoic-age fossil record. Here, we report on two nearly complete skeletons from the Late Cretaceous (Campanian) of North America that represent a new and relatively large-bodied and possibly herbivorous iguanomorph that inhabited a semi-arid environment. The new taxon exhibits a mosaic of anatomical features traditionally used in diagnosing Iguania and non-iguanian squamates (i.e. Scleroglossa; e.g. parietal foramen at the frontoparietal suture, astragalocalcaneal notch in the tibia, respectively). Our cladistic analysis of Squamata revealed a phylogenetic link between Campanian-age North American and East Asian stem iguanomorphs (i.e. the new taxon + Temujiniidae). These results and our evaluation of the squamate fossil record suggest that crown pleurodontans were restricted to the low-latitude Neotropics prior to their early Palaeogene first appearances in the mid-latitudes of North America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Article] This ancient lizard, Magnuviator ovimonsensis, reshapes the backstory of today's anoles and iguanas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warmer together </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best buds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crows make it in to Top 5 of Gold Coast bird count </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link to the full and free journal article](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002592) 

*Bigger Is Fitter? Quantitative Genetic Decomposition of Selection Reveals an Adaptive Evolutionary Decline of Body Mass in a Wild Rodent Population*.

DOI: dx.doi.org/10.1371/journal.pbio.1002592

**Abstract:**

In natural populations, quantitative trait dynamics often do not appear to follow evolutionary predictions. Despite abundant examples of natural selection acting on heritable traits, conclusive evidence for contemporary adaptive evolution remains rare for wild vertebrate populations, and phenotypic stasis seems to be the norm. This so-called stasis paradox highlights our inability to predict evolutionary change, which is especially concerning within the context of rapid anthropogenic environmental change. While the causes underlying the stasis paradox are hotly debated, comprehensive attempts aiming at a resolution are lacking. Here, we apply a quantitative genetic framework to individual-based long-term data for a wild rodent population and show that despite a positive association between body mass and fitness, there has been a genetic change towards lower body mass. The latter represents an adaptive response to viability selection favouring juveniles growing up to become relatively small adults, i.e., with a low potential adult mass, which presumably complete their development earlier. This selection is particularly strong towards the end of the snow-free season, and it has intensified in recent years, coinciding which a change in snowfall patterns. Importantly, neither the negative evolutionary change, nor the selective pressures that drive it, are apparent on the phenotypic level, where they are masked by phenotypic plasticity and a non causal (i.e., non genetic) positive association between body mass and fitness, respectively. Estimating selection at the genetic level enabled us to uncover adaptive evolution in action and to identify the corresponding phenotypic selective pressure. We thereby demonstrate that natural populations can show a rapid and adaptive evolutionary response to a novel selective pressure, and that explicitly (quantitative) genetic models are able to provide us with an understanding of the causes and consequences of selection that is superior to purely phenotypic estimates of selection and evolutionary change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early onset of winter triggers adaptive evolution towards smaller snow voles in Graubnden. These changes took place over only a few generations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link to the full and free journal article](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002592) 

*Bigger Is Fitter? Quantitative Genetic Decomposition of Selection Reveals an Adaptive Evolutionary Decline of Body Mass in a Wild Rodent Population*.

DOI: dx.doi.org/10.1371/journal.pbio.1002592

**Abstract:**

In natural populations, quantitative trait dynamics often do not appear to follow evolutionary predictions. Despite abundant examples of natural selection acting on heritable traits, conclusive evidence for contemporary adaptive evolution remains rare for wild vertebrate populations, and phenotypic stasis seems to be the norm. This so-called stasis paradox highlights our inability to predict evolutionary change, which is especially concerning within the context of rapid anthropogenic environmental change. While the causes underlying the stasis paradox are hotly debated, comprehensive attempts aiming at a resolution are lacking. Here, we apply a quantitative genetic framework to individual-based long-term data for a wild rodent population and show that despite a positive association between body mass and fitness, there has been a genetic change towards lower body mass. The latter represents an adaptive response to viability selection favouring juveniles growing up to become relatively small adults, i.e., with a low potential adult mass, which presumably complete their development earlier. This selection is particularly strong towards the end of the snow-free season, and it has intensified in recent years, coinciding which a change in snowfall patterns. Importantly, neither the negative evolutionary change, nor the selective pressures that drive it, are apparent on the phenotypic level, where they are masked by phenotypic plasticity and a non causal (i.e., non genetic) positive association between body mass and fitness, respectively. Estimating selection at the genetic level enabled us to uncover adaptive evolution in action and to identify the corresponding phenotypic selective pressure. We thereby demonstrate that natural populations can show a rapid and adaptive evolutionary response to a novel selective pressure, and that explicitly (quantitative) genetic models are able to provide us with an understanding of the causes and consequences of selection that is superior to purely phenotypic estimates of selection and evolutionary change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early onset of winter triggers adaptive evolution towards smaller snow voles in Graubnden. These changes took place over only a few generations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The site in France is called Abri Blanchard and has a sister site Abri Castanet. Both are considered among the oldest sites in Eurasia bearing artifacts of human symbolism. The slab bears a complex image of an aurochs (wild cows) surrounded by rows of dots. 

I love prehistoric findings like this, they are a window into our past and help us better understand how culture and spirituality arise in humans.

[Link to the journal article](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1040618216305766?np=y npKey=33ac1eac947448b503dc71cd9fe4f1061e469b975d0bdb2c446f4b26dc07d4c7) *A new Aurignacian engraving from Abri Blanchard, France: Implications for understanding Aurignacian graphic expression in Western and Central Europe*.

DOI: 10.1016/j.quaint.2016.09.063

**Abstract:**

In the excitement of the widely publicized new finds of Aurignacian art from Chauvet, from the Swabian Jura and from as far afield as Pestera Coliboaia in Romania, it has almost been forgotten that a rich corpus of Aurignacian wall painting, engraving and bas-relief sculpture had been recognized and studied before World War I in the Vzre Valley of SW France. Scientific knowledge of the chronological and cultural context of that early-discovered graphic record has been limited by the crude archaeological methods of that pioneering era, and the loss and dispersal of many of the works discovered. In 2011, we launched new excavations and a re-analysis of one of the key sites for such early discoveries, the collapsed rock shelter of Abri Blanchard. In 2012, we discovered in situ a limestone slab engraved with a complex composition combining an aurochs and dozens of aligned punctuations.

This new find, recovered by modern methods and dated by molecular filtration and Hydroxyproline 14C, provides new information on the context and dating of Aurignacian graphic imagery in SW France and its relationship to that of other regions. The support is not a fragment of collapsed shelter ceiling and is situated in the midst of quotidian occupational debris. The image shows significant technical and thematic similarities to Chauvet that are reinforced by our reanalysis of engraved slabs from the older excavations at Blanchard. The aligned punctuations find their counterparts at Chauvet, in the south German sites and on several other objects from Blanchard and surrounding Aurignacian sites. In sum, we argue that dispersing Aurignacian groups show a broad commonality in graphic expression against which a certain number of more regionalized characteristics stand out, a pattern that fits well with social geography models that focus on the material construction of identity at regional, group and individual levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anthropologists have uncovered a 38,000-year-old engraved image in a southwestern French rockshelter--a finding that marks some of the earliest known graphic imagery found in Western Eurasia and offers insights into the nature of modern humans during this period. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link to the journal article](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1040618216305766?np=y npKey=33ac1eac947448b503dc71cd9fe4f1061e469b975d0bdb2c446f4b26dc07d4c7) *A new Aurignacian engraving from Abri Blanchard, France: Implications for understanding Aurignacian graphic expression in Western and Central Europe*.

DOI: 10.1016/j.quaint.2016.09.063

**Abstract:**

In the excitement of the widely publicized new finds of Aurignacian art from Chauvet, from the Swabian Jura and from as far afield as Pestera Coliboaia in Romania, it has almost been forgotten that a rich corpus of Aurignacian wall painting, engraving and bas-relief sculpture had been recognized and studied before World War I in the Vzre Valley of SW France. Scientific knowledge of the chronological and cultural context of that early-discovered graphic record has been limited by the crude archaeological methods of that pioneering era, and the loss and dispersal of many of the works discovered. In 2011, we launched new excavations and a re-analysis of one of the key sites for such early discoveries, the collapsed rock shelter of Abri Blanchard. In 2012, we discovered in situ a limestone slab engraved with a complex composition combining an aurochs and dozens of aligned punctuations.

This new find, recovered by modern methods and dated by molecular filtration and Hydroxyproline 14C, provides new information on the context and dating of Aurignacian graphic imagery in SW France and its relationship to that of other regions. The support is not a fragment of collapsed shelter ceiling and is situated in the midst of quotidian occupational debris. The image shows significant technical and thematic similarities to Chauvet that are reinforced by our reanalysis of engraved slabs from the older excavations at Blanchard. The aligned punctuations find their counterparts at Chauvet, in the south German sites and on several other objects from Blanchard and surrounding Aurignacian sites. In sum, we argue that dispersing Aurignacian groups show a broad commonality in graphic expression against which a certain number of more regionalized characteristics stand out, a pattern that fits well with social geography models that focus on the material construction of identity at regional, group and individual levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Common Cuttlefish (Sepia officinalis) [OC] [720 x 431] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anthropologists have uncovered a 38,000-year-old engraved image in a southwestern French rockshelter--a finding that marks some of the earliest known graphic imagery found in Western Eurasia and offers insights into the nature of modern humans during this period. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very happy to teach, sorry it's not all cute. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red-bellied piranha (Pygocentrus nattereri) [OC] [720 x 431] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 00:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So relaxed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 00:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photo by Dorit Hockman, University of Cambridge, England

Featured in [this Wired article](https://www.wired.com/2013/10/nikon-small-world-2013/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chamaeleo calyptratus (veiled chameleon), embryo showing cartilage (blue) and bone (red) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog and crow play ball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ecologist swimming by.

The [North Pacific wolf eel](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wolf_eel) (*Anarrhichthys ocellatus*) is a species of wolffish (Family Anarhichadidae). They are found, well in the north Pacific ocean and can grow up to 8 ft long. 

While they look vicious and have a face only a mother could love, wolf eels are excellent parents! Females [lay up to 10,000 eggs](https://www.montereybayaquarium.org/animal-guide/fishes/wolf-eel) at a time and then coil around the clutch to protect them. They also mate for life.

As adults, they prefer crunchy food, such as crustaceans, sea urchins, mussels, snails and sand dollars. If they get a hold of your finger, you're going to have a bad day, but [they are known](https://aqua.org/explore/animals/wolf-eel) to be fairly [friendly to divers](https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/07/ce/23/1b/volunteer-diver-feeding.jpg)!

[They also bear an uncanny resemblance to Statler the muppet.](https://jackiehildering.files.wordpress.com/2013/02/statler-and-grandpa-wolf-eel-001.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ecologist swimming by.

The [North Pacific wolf eel](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wolf_eel) (*Anarrhichthys ocellatus*) is a species of wolffish (Family Anarhichadidae). They are found, well in the north Pacific ocean and can grow up to 8 ft long. 

While they look vicious and have a face only a mother could love, wolf eels are excellent parents! Females [lay up to 10,000 eggs](https://www.montereybayaquarium.org/animal-guide/fishes/wolf-eel) at a time and then coil around the clutch to protect them. They also mate for life.

As adults, they prefer crunchy food, such as crustaceans, sea urchins, mussels, snails and sand dollars. If they get a hold of your finger, you're going to have a bad day, but [they are known](https://aqua.org/explore/animals/wolf-eel) to be fairly [friendly to divers](https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/07/ce/23/1b/volunteer-diver-feeding.jpg)!

[They also bear an uncanny resemblance to Statler the muppet.](https://jackiehildering.files.wordpress.com/2013/02/statler-and-grandpa-wolf-eel-001.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

Well this isn't so much a space topic as a light/photon topic. Where I teach, and I believe most universities in the US, students of all majors are required to take a basic introduction to biology course. How light works, especially in relation to ecosystems/photosynthesis/trophic levels/color perception etc. is mentioned at least briefly. I go over it in my lecture when we get to each relevant chapter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would hope so, though many undergrads in my class who are non-science majors have no clue how this works. It's my job to not only teach them new material in college, but to also bring them up to speed on things they should have learned in grade school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Posing with Times Square Elmo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Energy radiates from the Sun and moves through space in waves within packets called photons. Photons traveling at the same wavelength carry the same amount of energy. Photons that carry the least energy travel in longer wavelengths; the those that carry the most energy travel in shorter wavelengths </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SpaceX Falcon 9 to Orbit by Tim Shortt [3528 x 2398] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm happy to clarify! Thank you for the follow. I'll have some microscope pics this coming week as I get back to the lab and hopefully some nature photos as well. If you ever have any questions feel free to PM me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mouse pancreases grown in rats generate functional, insulin-producing cells that can reverse diabetes when transplanted into mice with the disease. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> January 1986 - Voyager 2 Flyby of Uranus' moon Miranda [6588 x 6666] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photo by [M. Subirats, National Geographic Your Shot](http://www.nationalgeographic.com/photography/photo-of-the-day/2017/01/rocks-basque-spain/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spains Basque Coast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Chicken braciole with Parmesan cream sauce over sauteed broccoli </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Speaker Suggestion: Sylvia Earle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for taking the time to speak with us today!

Given we know so little about sea life at that depth it may be likely you see an undescribed organism. Are you expecting this? It's an exciting prospect. If so, what are the steps to describing and naming a new species? 

Which animal group is the most likely to be found/most abundant at those depths? New or otherwise.

How long does it take to reach your destination?

Thank you again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a new sub for me, thanks! A friend sent this one to me from FB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a sure fire day brightener! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I could tase you, but I'm lacking a charge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worth it to see this gif. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! There are also non-communal wasps as well. Attracting females is a must when you're not in a colony with a queen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great question I'm surprised no one has asked me before!

In the case of Orchid bees I knew about their proboscis, colors and their gathering volatile oils to attract the ladies. I was not aware of the Florida population or the parasitism, so thank you National Forest Service!

I have a general working knowledge of a lot of insects, arachnids, and birds because I've done research with them and I love them. I also have a degree in Marine Biology and grew up doing a lot of fishing and have marine scientist friends, so I'm alright with a good amount of marine life (at least to initially identify). I'm full of random facts. I read *all the time* and love nature documentaries. I also teach Climate Science, Environmental Science, and Biology and learn a lot to keep class interesting.

From this cloud I know where to look for deeper information to get a larger story for each organism I comment on. I'm also great at identifying organisms because I love taxonomy and the relationship between familial groups.

I try not to reference journal articles because that's a little much for the general public, but I usually know of a few websites that can back up the fact or two I remember, and then add on to it.

I do not have a great working knowledge of plants or fungi, they are much harder for me to comment on. I've got some field guides though and I'm reading papers in my spare time to broaden my general knowledge. I can't wait for Spring to get out in the forests and get hands on! My husband bought me a new camera for Christmas I've been getting used to, my Instagram feed @subject9866 is full of birds, so I'm excited for more time. I find a general knowledge of a lot of things gives me more to work from when doing specific research.

So TL;DR I remember a little bit about a lot of things then find my sources to create a broader picture. If I have done research on that organism I remember almost everything I've worked on, but still find resources because no one should have to take my word for it. 

If anyone says they know everything about a topic and especially all from memory, they are not being honest.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ecologist buzzing by!

I can't get over how absolutely beautiful these bees are! They come in a variety of jewel tones and honestly I bet they smell great to not only female bees but to humans.

[The United States Forest Service](https://www.fs.fed.us/wildflowers/pollinators/pollinator-of-the-month/orchid_bees.shtml) has a lot of great information on these beautiful bees.

* [Their proboscis (like a tongue) can equal twice as long as their bodies!](https://68.media.tumblr.com/022fc938d57e3bcb1536e596922b8741/tumblr_o9z8mo2Qox1qio57co1_500.png)
* Some orchid bees in the genera *Eulaema* and *Exaerete* are parasitic of other Orchid bees
* Orchid bees of genus *Eulaema* are as large as carpenter bees or bumblebee queens
* Along with 22 other species of introduced bees, an orchid bee (*Euglossa viridissima*) has become naturalized in several areas of Florida where it now routinely visits orchids, other flowers and scent resources.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The United States Forest Service](https://www.fs.fed.us/wildflowers/pollinators/pollinator-of-the-month/orchid_bees.shtml) has a lot of great information on these beautiful bees.

* [Their proboscis (like a tongue) can equal twice as long as their bodies!](https://68.media.tumblr.com/022fc938d57e3bcb1536e596922b8741/tumblr_o9z8mo2Qox1qio57co1_500.png)
* Some orchid bees in the genera *Eulaema* and *Exaerete* are parasitic of other Orchid bees
* Orchid bees of genus *Eulaema* are as large as carpenter bees or bumblebee queens
* Along with 22 other species of introduced bees, an orchid bee (*Euglossa viridissima*) has become naturalized in several areas of Florida where it now routinely visits orchids, other flowers and scent resources.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orchid bee males collect essential species specific oils from orchids using tiny scraping hairs on their legs. They then gather in lek display sites on tree trunks to attract females. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many boxes is too many? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 05:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ecologist rolling into my own thread.

The gif says sea lion, but this goofball is an [Elephant seal](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elephant_seal), of genus *Mirounga*. 

[Southern elephant seals](https://travelwild.com/resources/antarctica-wildlife/southern-elephant-seal/) are the largest species of the true seal. Males can be over 20 feet (6m) long and weigh up to 8,800 pounds (4,000kg) or more.

[Here's the full video.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kHfh_ie_h0s)

For additional information here is [National Geographic's page](http://animals.nationalgeographic.com/animals/mammals/elephant-seal/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Journal Article link](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1053811916307431)

**Highlights**

* Behavioral and psychiatric differences between men and women suggest that the human amygdala is sexually dimorphic.

* Systematic review of the literature identified 46 studies reporting amygdala volumes in 58 age-matched samples of males and females (6726 individuals).

* Meta-analysis of matched raw volumes demonstrates a moderate-sized sex difference and average bilateral amygdala volume about 0.3 cm3 (10%) larger in males, comparable to the 1112% larger overall volume of males brains.

* By contrast, meta-analysis of volumes normalized for overall brain size demonstrated no significant sex difference in amygdala volume.

* The frequent claim that the amygdala is proportionally larger in males was not supported.

**Abstract:**

The amygdala plays a key role in many affective behaviors and psychiatric disorders that differ between men and women. To test whether human amygdala volume (AV) differs reliably between the sexes, we performed a systematic review and meta-analysis of AVs reported in MRI studies of age-matched healthy male and female groups. Using four search strategies, we identified 46 total studies (58 matched samples) from which we extracted effect sizes for the sex difference in AV. All data were converted to Hedges g values and pooled effect sizes were calculated using a random-effects model. Each dataset was further meta-regressed against study year and average participant age. We found that uncorrected amygdala volume is about 10% larger in males, with pooled sex difference effect sizes of g=0.581 for right amygdala (=28, n=2022), 0.666 for left amygdala (=28, n=2006), and 0.876 for bilateral amygdala (=16, n=1585) volumes (all p values  0.001). However, this difference is comparable to the sex differences in intracranial volume (ICV; g=1.186, p.001, 11.9% larger in males, =11) and total brain volume (TBV; g=1.278, p0.001, 11.5% larger in males, =15) reported in subsets of the same studies, suggesting the sex difference in AV is a product of larger brain size in males. Among studies reporting AVs normalized for ICV or TBV, sex difference effect sizes were small and not statistically significant: g=0.171 for the right amygdala (p=0.206, =13, n=1560); 0.233 for the left amygdala (p=0.092, =12, n=1512); and 0.257 for bilateral volume (p=0.131, =5, n=1629). These values correspond to less than 0.1% larger corrected right AV and 2.5% larger corrected left AV in males compared to females. In summary, AV is not selectively enhanced in human males, as often claimed. Although we cannot rule out subtle male-female group differences, it is not accurate to refer to the human amygdala as sexually dimorphic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A meta-analysis of human amygdala volumes found no significant difference between the sexes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Southern elephant seal Travel Wild page
](https://travelwild.com/resources/antarctica-wildlife/southern-elephant-seal/) and their information from the book [*Population Ecology, Behavior, and Physiology*](http://www.ucpress.edu/op.php?isbn=9780520083646) Edited by Burney J. Le Beouf, Richard M. Laws

[National Geographic's page](http://animals.nationalgeographic.com/animals/mammals/elephant-seal/)


The gif says sea lion, but this goofball is an [Elephant seal](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elephant_seal), of genus *Mirounga*, the largest species of the true seal. 

[Here's the full video.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kHfh_ie_h0s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Southern elephant seals are the largest species of the true seal. Males can be over 20 feet (6m) long and weigh up to 8,800 pounds (4,000kg) or more. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowy owl meets a raven </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elephant seal pup rolls down a hill for a  time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photo by [Rahul Belsare](http://yourshot.nationalgeographic.com/profile/273250/) of National Geographic.

[His 500px album.](https://500px.com/photo/85587897/oriental-dwarf-kingfisher-by-rahul-belsare) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oriental dwarf kingfisher (Ceyx erithaca) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ecologist flying in!

What an absolutely stunning kingfisher, *Ceyx erithaca*! There are so many beautiful  birds in Thailand that they also call this one the [Black-backed kingfisher](https://www.thainationalparks.com/species/oriental-dwarf-kingfisher). As far as birds go here though, in my neck of the US, it's stunning! The [Rufous-backed kingfisher](https://www.thainationalparks.com/species/rufous-backed-kingfisher) (*Ceyx rufidorsa*) is sometimes considered a subspecies. [Check out how beautiful these guys are!](http://www.ourbreathingplanet.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/3-4.png)

They are found in found in Bangladesh, Bhutan, Brunei, Cambodia, India, Indonesia, Laos, Malaysia, Myanmar, Singapore, Sri Lanka and Thailand.

Kingfishers are forest birds usually found near lakes. Some specialize in eating fish, as it says in their name, but depending on the region they will also eat small mammals, reptiles, amphibians, and insects. 

They are cavity nesters and prefer [burrows in the ground](http://www.akellyphoto.com/html/wildlife/bird_gallery/kingfisher/Kingisher-Burrow-sm.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biofilms are communities of organisms living within in a shared mass of slime. A common biofilm found on humans is the plaque build up on your teeth! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello, Ian? Patrick here! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try to remember to post. It's adorable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries! The course is Climate Science for non Science undergrads and Climate Change is a huge part of it. We got into the ionosphere as well though I didn't put my notes up here yet. I can add them. They have to first learn how it works before we can get into how it's broken. :) It's going to be an interesting semester. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for abhix3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recent Submission history for abhix3:

domain submitted from|count|%
:-|-:|-:
[getintotrend.com](/search?q=%28and+site%3A%27getintotrend.com%27+author%3A%27abhix3%27+is_self%3A0+%29 restrict_sr=off sort=new syntax=cloudsearch feature=legacy_search)|12|67%
[imgur.com](/search?q=%28and+site%3A%27imgur.com%27+author%3A%27abhix3%27+is_self%3A0+%29 restrict_sr=off sort=new syntax=cloudsearch feature=legacy_search)|5|28%
[i.imgur.com](/search?q=%28and+site%3A%27i.imgur.com%27+author%3A%27abhix3%27+is_self%3A0+%29 restrict_sr=off sort=new syntax=cloudsearch feature=legacy_search)|1|6%

subreddit submitted to|count|%
:-|-:|-:
[aww](/r/aww/search?q=author%3A%27abhix3%27 restrict_sr=on sort=new feature=legacy_search)|5|28%
[science](/r/science/search?q=author%3A%27abhix3%27 restrict_sr=on sort=new feature=legacy_search)|4|22%
[worldnews](/r/worldnews/search?q=author%3A%27abhix3%27 restrict_sr=on sort=new feature=legacy_search)|4|22%
[politics](/r/politics/search?q=author%3A%27abhix3%27 restrict_sr=on sort=new feature=legacy_search)|4|22%
[gifs](/r/gifs/search?q=author%3A%27abhix3%27 restrict_sr=on sort=new feature=legacy_search)|1|6% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extends from the surface up to the numbers given. I can clarify in my original comment if it looks confusing.

Wikipedia -

The troposphere is the lowest layer of Earth's atmosphere. It extends from Earth's surface to an average height of about 12km, although this altitude actually varies from about 9km (30,000ft) at the poles to 17km (56,000ft) at theequator,

My numbers come from the text book I am teaching out of, I trust that more that Wikipedia and it's what my students will be going off of so those are my notes numbers. It does get lower near the poles, but on average that's the height.      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earth's surface to 16 to 18, from there the other layers extend. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well-preserved otter material of giant size, including crania, mandibles and postcranials, was recently unearthed from the latest Miocene lignite beds of Shuitangba in Yunnan Province.

Alive during the Miocene these giant otters were around for our giant crocodilians and other reptiles, and a myriad of other large and small mammals. 

[Full and free journal article](http://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/14772019.2016.1267666)

**Abstract:**

Otters (subfamily Lutrinae) are semi-aquatic predators in the family Mustelidae. Modern otters have a worldwide distribution but their fossil record is poor, often consisting of fragmentary jaws and teeth. Multiple lineages have developed bunodont dentitions with enlargements of molars, usually for cracking molluscs or other hard foods. Some lineages have evolved badger-like teeth and, as a result, were often confused with melines (Old World badger clade). Siamogale thailandica Ginsburg, Invagat,   Tassy, 1983 from the middle Miocene basin of Mae Moh in northern Thailand is one such species, whose fragmentary dental remains have thus far impeded our understanding. A new species of fossil otter, Siamogale melilutra sp. nov., represented by a nearly complete cranium, mandible and partial skeletons of at least three individuals, was recovered from the latest Miocene (6.2 Ma) lignite beds of the Shuitangba Site in north-eastern Yunnan Province, south-western China. Computed tomography (CT) restoration of the crushed skull reveals a combination of otter-like and badger-like cranial and dental characteristics. The new species belongs to the Lutrinae because of its possession of a large infraorbital canal and ventral expansion of the mastoid process, among other traits. A distally expanded M1, however, gives a badger-like appearance. In overall morphology the Shuitangba otter is closest to Siamogale thailandica. A previously described jaw (Lutra aonychoides) from the early Pliocene of the Yushe Basin in north China is also here referred to S. melilutra. No previous attempt has been made to provide a global phylogenetic framework for otters. We present the first combined morphological and molecular (nuclear and mitochondrial DNAs) character matrices of five extant (Pteronura, Lontra, Enhydra, Aonyx, Lutra) and eight extinct genera (Tyrrhenolutra, Paralutra, Paludolutra, Enhydritherium, Siamogale, Vishnuonyx, Sivaonyx, Enhydriodon) to better understand the evolution of bunodont otters. Parsimony and Bayesian analyses consistently recover an eastern Asian clade that includes forms from Shuitangba, Yushe and Mae Moh, all of which are referred to Siamogale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Article] Scientists Discover Prehistoric Giant Otter Species In China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raven rips up parking ticket in Yellowknife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mr. Darcy showing off his fluff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops, that order is lowest to highest!

I'm teaching an intro course on Climate Science this semester, so prepare for some Climate-related facts as we move on peppered in with the rest. I'll throw some of my notes in the comments to expand on concepts.

**Troposphere**

* Earth's surface to 16 to 18 km (52,000 to 59,000 ft)
* *Tropo* means to turn or change
* Layer closest to the Earth
* 80% of the total mass of the atmosphere
* Green-houses gasses are concentrated
* Tropopause separates it from the Stratosphere
  * Without the stability of the Stratosphere there would be no Troposphere

**Stratosphere**

* 50 km (30 mi)
* *Strato* means layers
* Gases here are layered and do not mix
* Contains most of the ozone within the atmosphere
  * Ozone absorbs UV light
 * Life did not spread from water to land until about 400 million years ago, with the development of the ozone layer
* Temperature increases with altitude as ozone absorbs UV light
* Air is thin here and does not contain moisture
* Supersonic jets fly here!

**Mesosphere**

* 85 km (50 mi)
* *Meso* means middle
* Increasing in altitude temperature decreases
* Coldest layer of the atmosphere, -93oC (-135oF)
 * Fewer molecules to absorb UV rays
* Weather balloons fly here!
* Meteors burn up here

**Thermosphere**

* 500 km (300 miles)
* *Thermo* means heat
* Increasing in altitude, temperature increases
* 1,000oC (1832oF) or higher
* Charged partials cause auroras
* Meteors and satellites fly here!

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The atmosphere consists of 6 layers. From highest to lowest; Troposphere, Stratosphere, Mesosphere, Thermosphere, Ionosphere, Exosphere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took this photo at the [American Museum of Natural History's](http://www.amnh.org/) Butterfly exhibit, in New York City, NY. 2009.

Here is the [museum's blog post](http://www.amnh.org/explore/news-blogs/on-exhibit-posts/the-butterflies-are-back) about the 2012 exhibit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great Southern White butterfly (Ascia monuste) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silly Sirs in Black and White </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [NASA's description of the photo:
](https://apod.nasa.gov/apod/ap170120.html)
On January 18 a tantalizing sunset was captured in this snapshot. Seemingly sliced into many horizontal layers the Sun shimmered moments before it touched the horizon, setting over the Pacific Ocean as seen from the mountaintop Las Campanas Observatory in Chile. Pink hues of filtered sunlight were created by the long sight-line through the hazy atmosphere. But the remarkable layers correspond to low atmospheric layers of sharply different temperature and density also along the line of sight. Over a long path through each layer the rays of sunlight are refracted strongly and create different images or mirages of sections of the setting Sun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Layer Cake Sunset by Yuri Beletsky [1200 x 803] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't downvote you, but that's very true! Ther a lot of animals with large (ha) penis to body size ratios. Ducks are 2:1, banana slugs are 1:1, African elephants I believe are also 1:1.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EVERYTHING. It's for grooming, man. You groom everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is pretty odd and doesn't happen often. Generas change because organisms end up being more or less genetically related than we originally thought. As for this, according to IUCN Red List:

This taxon was formerly known as *T. spectrum*, but, Brandon-Jones et al. (2004) argued that *T. spectrum* is a junior synonym of *T. tarsier*, and this has since been confirmed by Groves (2005). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very beautiful! Looks like Pink Burn Cup (*Tarzetta rosea*)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colorized by Reddit user /u/kibblenbits

Original thread by him from a year ago [here](https://np.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/370js3/nuclear_bomb_testing_1957_colorized_by_me/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colorized by Reddit user /u/kibblenbits

Original thread by him from a year ago [here](https://np.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/370js3/nuclear_bomb_testing_1957_colorized_by_me/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nuclear bomb testing, 1957 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nuclear bomb testing, 1957 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she's your pet it's nothing to worry about. They do it when they are afraid, she's probably just comfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Eastern box turtle Wiki](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eastern_box_turtle).

[National Wildlife Federation's page.](https://www.nwf.org/Wildlife/Wildlife-Library/Amphibians-Reptiles-and-Fish/Eastern-Box-Turtle.aspx)

I loved these guys when I was a kid. My father would bring them home, we'd keep it over night in the garage and feed it, then it'd go back to wherever he found it. Usually on the other side if the street it was originally crossing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eastern box turtles (Terrapene carolina carolina) have a high domed carapace (upper part of the shell) and a hinged plastron (lower part of the shell) which allows almost complete closure of the shell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi crazycrayon, your submission has been removed for the following reason(s)

It does not include references to new, peer-reviewed research. Please feel free to post it in our sister subreddit /r/EverythingScience. 



*If you feel this was done in error, or would like further clarification, please don't hesitate to [message the mods](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FScience message=My%20Post:%20https://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/5pjclf/quantum_bayesianism_qbism_quantum_interpretation/).* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Source Arkive page](http://www.arkive.org/spectral-tarsier/tarsius-tarsier/)

The [spectral tarsier](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spectral_tarsier) (*Tarsius spectrum* or *Tarsius tarsier*) is a species of tarsier found in Indonesia. Tarsiers have the largest eyes, relative to body weight, of any mammal! These large eyes help them gather as much light as possible at night, as they are mostly nocturnal animals. You can tell by the gif that they are insectivores, but they will also eat small lizards.

Tarsiers in general, are the smallest of primates. Their genus name *Tarsius* comes from their elongated tarsal or ankle region.  

Spectral tarsier young are fairly [precocious](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Precocial) (young are up and moving at a very young age, not like humans) and able to climb at just a day old and hunt alone by 26 days. [Here is a photo of a mother with her young.](http://s3.amazonaws.com/mongabay/indonesia/600/sulawesi-tangkoko_0991.jpg) They are pretty adorable!

[IUCN Red List](http://www.iucnredlist.org/details/21491/0) lists the spectral tarsier as vulnerable and is protected by law in Indonesia. According to [Ecology Asia.com](http://www.ecologyasia.com/verts/mammals/spectral_tarsier.htm):

The Spectral Tarsier only occurs on the central Indonesian island of Sulawesi and some smaller nearby islands including Peleng and Selayar. Two other species of Tarsier occur in other parts of Southeast Asia - these are the Western Tarsier, which occurs in Borneo and Sumatra and the Philippine Tarsier in southern parts of the Philippines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tarsiers have flattened nails on their digits, except on the second and third toes, which are equipped with a toilet claw used in grooming . </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brief summary:

The scientists have now studied three different parts of the divergent ridge (area where the ocean plates are slowly sliding away from each other) that crosses Iceland from southwest to northeast. The slow movement and separation of the ocean plates can cause cracks in Earth's crust, through which hot magma from the planet's interior rises to the surface. As a result, a large number of volcanos have emerged along the divergent boundary.

'The study includes data with extremely high precision. Data from 1967 to the present, together with the very best modelling software, have yielded the best picture to date of the anatomy of the divergent boundary,' says Md. Tariqul Islam, lead author of the article, which has been published in Journal of Geophysical Research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study will help find the best locations for thermal power stations in Iceland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mr. Darcy wishes to join me on the balcony </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [NASA's explanation of the photo:](https://apod.nasa.gov/apod/ap170119.html)

Like an illustration in a galactic Just So Story, the Elephant's Trunk Nebula winds through the emission nebula and young star cluster complex IC 1396, in the high and far off constellation of Cepheus. Also known as vdB 142, the cosmic elephant's trunk is over 20 light-years long. This colorful close-up view includes image data from a narrow band filter that transmits the light from ionized hydrogen atoms in the region. The resulting composite highlights the bright swept-back ridges that outline pockets of cool interstellar dust and gas. Such embedded, dark, tendril-shaped clouds contain the raw material for star formation and hide protostars within. Nearly 3,000 light-years distant, the relatively faint IC 1396 complex covers a large region on the sky, spanning over 5 degrees. This dramatic scene spans a 1 degree wide field, about the size of 2 Full Moons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Sirs and a Turkey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After weeks away from traditional roosting site, a large murder of crows have returned to UNB campus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More info about [Io](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Io_(moon).

Gzomodo's article [
A Moon With The Most Volcanic Activity Of Anything In The Solar System](http://gizmodo.com/a-moon-with-the-most-volcanic-activity-of-anything-in-t-1022062044). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jupiter's moon Io has the most volcanic activity of any body in the Solar System. It's lava lake, Loki Patera, is the largest in the solar system. On Earth the largest lava lake is the one inside Mount Nyiragongo which can grow to 2 km in diameter. Loki Patera is 200 km in diameter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Elephant's Trunk Nebula in Cepheus by Stephen Leshin [2048 x 1330] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Horned lizards](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Horned_lizard) belong to the genus *Phrynosoma*. At least eight species can squirt an aimed stream of blood from the corners of the eyes for a distance of up to 5 fet (1.5 m).They restrict blood flow leaving thier heads which increases blood pressure and ruptures blood vessels around the eyelids. This is not only confusing to predators, but the blood tastes pretty nasty to canine and feline predators. It apparently has no effect against predatory birds.

More on that from this BBC article [*If it has to, a horned lizard can shoot blood from its eyes*](http://www.bbc.com/earth/story/20151105-if-it-has-to-a-horned-lizard-can-shoot-blood-from-its-eyes).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horned lizards shoot blood from their eyes as a defense against predators.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ecologist flying in.

The term [*cuckold*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cuckold) comes from the [Cuckoo family of birds, *Cuculidae*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cuckoo). Cuckoos (and a few other species such as the [Brown-headed cowbird](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brown-headed_cowbird)) lay their eggs in other birds' nests. We call this [*brood parasitism*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brood_parasite). The host bird either doesn't realize the new egg is not theirs, or in some cases the cuckoo comes back and destroys the host eggs if they try to remove the cuckoo eggs.

The cuckoo eggs usually hatch first and the chicks start pushing the host eggs out of the nest ([Here is a video of a Common cuckoo ejecting a Reed warbler egg from the nest](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SO1WccH2_YM)). If a host egg manages to hatch the cuckoo will kick the chick out. The host bird will continue to feed the interloper until they are adults and fledge.

For more information here are a few articles:

* [*Cuckoos Don't Sneak Into Other Birds' NestsThey Barge Right In*](http://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/cuckoos-arent-secretly-jerks-theyre-just-jerks-180951916/)
* [*Nest stealing cuckoo birds are locked in evolutionary war with their would-be victims*](http://io9.gizmodo.com/5785233/nest-stealing-cuckoo-birds-are-locked-in-evolutionary-war-with-their-would-be-victims)
* [*Fairy wrens teach secret passwords to their unborn chicks to tell them apart from cuckoo impostors*](http://blogs.discovermagazine.com/notrocketscience/2012/11/08/fairy-wrens-teach-secret-passwords-to-their-unborn-chicks-to-tell-them-apart-from-cuckoo-impostors/#.WIP6IfkrKUk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corn and a hot dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Names Former Climate Scientist Erik Noble to NASA Advisory Role </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 22:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always best to see a therapist first and then go from there. There are books, but getting advice from a professional to form a basis is a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try making a self post in /r/Archaeology. I'm sure someone there would love to have a talk with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to the [full and free journal article](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0166346). 

General Statement on posts - Please read at least the abstract before drawing any conclusions from the news source. News often misses important or interesting points and to really understand what the researchers were getting at it's important to understand the journal article. This is of course meant in no offense to the article's writer, but it is a common issue with only reading the news source.



And as always, please direct all comments at the specific content of the original post, or the specific scientific article it is based upon and do not post anecdotal comments.

**Abstract:**

Numerous behavioral paradigms have been developed to assess tinnitus-like behavior in animals. Nevertheless, they are often limited by prolonged training requirements, as well as an inability to simultaneously assess onset and lasting tinnitus behavior, tinnitus pitch or duration, or tinnitus presence without grouping data from multiple animals or testing sessions. To enhance behavioral testing of tinnitus, we developed a conditioned licking suppression paradigm to determine the pitch(s) of both onset and lasting tinnitus-like behavior within individual animals. Rats learned to lick water during broadband or narrowband noises, and to suppress licking to avoid footshocks during silence. After noise exposure, rats significantly increased licking during silent trials, suggesting onset tinnitus-like behavior. Lasting tinnitus-behavior, however, was exhibited in about half of noise-exposed rats through 7 weeks post-exposure tested. Licking activity during narrowband sound trials remained unchanged following noise exposure, while ABR hearing thresholds fully recovered and were comparable between tinnitus(+) and tinnitus(-) rats. To assess another tinnitus inducer, rats were injected with sodium salicylate. They demonstrated high pitch tinnitus-like behavior, but later recovered by 5 days post-injection. Further control studies showed that 1): sham noise-exposed rats tested with footshock did not exhibit tinnitus-like behavior, and 2): noise-exposed or sham rats tested without footshocks showed no fundamental changes in behavior compared to those tested with shocks. Together, these results demonstrate that this paradigm can efficiently test the development of noise- and salicylate-induced tinnitus behavior. The ability to assess tinnitus individually, over time, and without averaging data enables us to realistically address tinnitus in a clinically relevant way. Thus, we believe that this optimized behavioral paradigm will facilitate investigations into the mechanisms of tinnitus and development of effective treatments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wayne State University Research Team Develops New Diagnostic Tool to Identify Tinnitus in Rats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are only about 60 left.

Brief summary:

An ambitious, emergency plan to help save the vaquita porpoise from extinction in the northern Gulf of California has been recommended by the International Committee for the Recovery of the Vaquita (CIRVA). The plan involves relocating some of the remaining vaquitas to a temporary sanctuary, while crucial efforts aimed at eliminating illegal fishing and removing gillnets from their environment continue. The emergency action plan will be led by the Mexican government and supported by a consortium of marine mammal experts from more than a dozen organizations around the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> International effort announced to try to save the world's most endangered marine mammal, the vaquita porpoise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brief summary:

An ambitious, emergency plan to help save the vaquita porpoise from extinction in the northern Gulf of California has been recommended by the International Committee for the Recovery of the Vaquita (CIRVA). The plan involves relocating some of the remaining vaquitas to a temporary sanctuary, while crucial efforts aimed at eliminating illegal fishing and removing gillnets from their environment continue. The emergency action plan will be led by the Mexican government and supported by a consortium of marine mammal experts from more than a dozen organizations around the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> International effort announced to try to save the world's most endangered marine mammal, the vaquita porpoise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers Characterize Wolf 1061 Planetary System </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a general message I post every time I link a journal article after approving a post. Sometimes it applies better to certain articles than others, but it is important to at least give the abstract a run as a lay person. Some writers do sensationalize.

I understand the audience of the sub, I've been posting here for years (other name). Again, it's a general statement to give the journal article a chance or at least the summary and see if both the news and the science lines up. I don't think you're giving the audience here enough credit on what they can glean for themselves by giving it a try.

It's also a reminder to stay on topic as comments tend to stray in most posts. Again, it's a general message, as this post is not getting too much attention right now. It's for everyone, I wasn't singling out your post or this particular news article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [spectral tarsier](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spectral_tarsier) (*Tarsius spectrum* or *Tarsius tarsier*) is a species of tarsier found in Indonesia. Tarsiers have the largest eyes, relative to body weight, of any mammal! These large eyes help them gather as much light as possible at night, as they are mostly nocturnal animals. You can tell by the gif that they are insectivores, but they will also eat small lizards.

Tarsiers in general, are the smallest of primates. Their genus name *Tarsius* comes from their elongated tarsal or ankle region.  All of their digits have flattened nails, except the second and third toes, which are equipped with a [toilet claw](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Grooming_claw) (also called a grooming claw, but toilet is pretty fun), used in grooming ([Source Arkive page](http://www.arkive.org/spectral-tarsier/tarsius-tarsier/)).

Spectral tarsier young are fairly [precocious](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Precocial) (young are up and moving at a very young age, not like humans) and able to climb at just a day old and hunt alone by 26 days. [Here is a photo of a mother with her young.](http://s3.amazonaws.com/mongabay/indonesia/600/sulawesi-tangkoko_0991.jpg) They are pretty adorable!

[IUCN Red List](http://www.iucnredlist.org/details/21491/0) lists the spectral tarsier as vulnerable and is protected by law in Indonesia. According to [Ecology Asia.com](http://www.ecologyasia.com/verts/mammals/spectral_tarsier.htm):

The Spectral Tarsier only occurs on the central Indonesian island of Sulawesi and some smaller nearby islands including Peleng and Selayar. Two other species of Tarsier occur in other parts of Southeast Asia - these are the Western Tarsier, which occurs in Borneo and Sumatra and the Philippine Tarsier in southern parts of the Philippines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spectral Tarsier Catches A Grasshopper  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking down on the Utah Valley by /u/orbojunglist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like Trump, but Baron is being a respectable and really sweet young man here playing with the baby. There's no reason to attack a child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study shows that cognitive behavior therapy (CBT) strengthens specific connections in the brains of people with psychosis, and that these stronger connections are associated with long-term reduction in symptoms and recovery eight years later. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 16:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study shows that cognitive behavior therapy (CBT) strengthens specific connections in the brains of people with psychosis, and that these stronger connections are associated with long-term reduction in symptoms and recovery eight years later. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 16:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 16:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to the [full and free journal article](http://aem.asm.org/content/early/2016/12/12/AEM.02289-16.full.pdf+html). 

Please read at least the abstract before drawing any conclusions from the news source. News often misses important or interesting points and to really understand what the researchers were getting at it's important to understand the journal article. This is of course meant in no offense to the article's writer, but it is a common issue with only reading the news source.



And as always, please direct all comments at the specific content of the original post, or the specific scientific article it is based upon and do not post anecdotal comments.

**Abstract:**

Tuberculosis (TB) is a disease caused by Mycobacterium tuberculosis or Mycobacterium bovis and still remains one of the world's biggest global health burdens. Recently, engineered polyhydroxyalkanoate (PHA) biobeads produced in both E. coli and Lactococcus lactis displaying mycobacterial antigens were found to induce significant cell mediated immune responses in mice. We observed that such PHA beads contained host cell proteins as impurities which we hypothesized to have the potential to induce immunity. In this study we aimed to develop PHA beads produced in mycobacteria (mycobacterial PHA biobeads, MBB) and test their potential as TB vaccine in a mouse model. As a model organism, nonpathogenic Mycobacterium smegmatis was engineered to produce MBB or MBB with immobilized mycobacterial antigens Ag85A and ESAT-6 on their surface (A:E-MBB). Three key enzymes involved in the poly(3-hydroxybutyric acid) pathway, namely -ketothiolase (PhaA), acetoacetyl-CoA reductase (PhaB), and PHA synthase (PhaC), were engineered into E. coli-mycobacteria shuttle plasmids and expressed in trans. Immobilization of specific antigens to the surface of the MBB was achieved by creating a fusion with the PHA synthase which remains covalently attached to the polyester core, resulting in PHA biobeads displaying covalently immobilized antigens. MBB, A:E-MBB and a mycobacterial vector control (MVC) were used in a mouse immunology trial, with comparison to PBS vaccinated and BCG vaccinated groups. We successfully produced MBB and A:E-MBB and used them as vaccines to induce a cellular immune response to mycobacterial antigens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great Southern White (Ascia monuste) [OC] [1600 x 1200] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 16:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Space Station Vista: Planet and Galaxy [4928 x 3280] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 16:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 01:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 01:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really they tend to burp more than fart methane.

[Journal article link](http://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/acs.jafc.6b04395)

**Abstract:**

Onion extract is used as a feed supplement for the diet of dairy cows, acting as inhibitor of methane production; however, its properties could alter sensory attributes of milk. In this work, we propose a method to evaluate the influence of this extract on milk properties, using propyl propane thiosulfonate (PTSO) as a marker. PTSO is extracted using a quick, easy, cheap, effective, rugged, and safe procedure and monitored by high-performance liquid chromatography with ultraviolet detection. The method was applied to milk samples obtained from 100 dairy cows fed during 2 months with enriched feed. In addition, a milk tasting panel was established to evaluate the PTSO residue that should not be exceeded to guarantee milk sensory attributes. It was established that a value of PTSO lower than 2 mg kg1 does not alter milk organoleptic properties. This fact makes onion extract an interesting alternative as a feed supplement to control the methane emissions without any influence on milk attributes.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists Feed Cows Onions to Make Them Stop Farting So Much Methane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [hooded crow](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hooded_crow) (*Corvus cornix*) is native to Eurasia and like it's other Corid relative is an intelligent and crafty species. They are similar to the [carrion crow](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carrion_crow) (*Corvus corone*) and where their regions overlap they produce viable hybrids.

They are very bright, like most Corvids, and have been known [to drop shells from a great height to smash them open and to pull in fishing lines to steal the catch or the bait.](http://www.bbc.co.uk/nature/life/Hooded_Crow). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hooded crow (Corvus cornix) unties shoe to steal pan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how I missed it. Sorry, OB!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He really did a lot to combat AIDS in Africa and was seriously passionate about it, even when NATO passed on helping. He wanted to make a difference. There was a great Vice documentary about it and they interviewed him; he was articulate, passionate and unapologetic for taking the leap. I didn't vote for him and disagree with most of his policies, but in this he was a good man. [Here's a clip from it.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ChCno7alwwI) He says in the beginning:

If your name is George Bush and you are from Texas, you are not supposed to love people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of awesome technologies to locate places of archeological importance now. There was a NOVA documentary last year about finding Viking villages in North America by using high resolution satellite imagery. Here's the [news article](http://www.ibtimes.co.uk/vikings-unearthed-documentary-uncovers-extent-viking-expansion-north-america-1553045). I looked for a link on NOVA for the documentary, but they no longer have it up for free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 23:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlikely. Religious activities is a very broad claim and they were pagan at this point in history, which was full of every day to seasonal religious activities performed by the poor and wealthy alike, sometimes in the home and other times as part of the community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 23:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's important to us to make sure all claims are verifiable! We love to learn as much as you guys do and all this can only be accomplished by real sourcing. :) We're so glad you enjoy the sub! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 23:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are very soft! And can be quite friendly once tamed. [Their babies are adorable too.](http://www.twrcwildlifecenter.org/site/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/baby-opossum.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Watson studies a model of DNA in 1957 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photo from Time Magazine's [*37 Weirdly Beautiful Old-School Science and Tech Photos*](http://time.com/3878525/37-weirdly-beautiful-science-and-tech-photos-from-life-magazine/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Watson studies a model of DNA in 1957 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Image Credit   Copyright: [Eric Coles](http://www.astrobin.com/users/coles44/)

NASA's [Astronomy Picture of the Day](https://apod.nasa.gov/apod/ap170107.html) page about the photo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sharpless 249 and the Jellyfish Nebula </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During spring of 2016 a number of large house terraces were identified by the archaeologists at Korshamn. Due to these discoveries high resolution geophysical surveys using ground-penetrating radar were carried out in September 2016. 

The survey revealed a major Viking period hall on the site, with a length of around 131 feet (40 m).

The results will be published in the international scientific journal *Archologisches Korrespondenzblatt* . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A large manor has been found at the archaeological site of Korshamn near the Viking Age proto-town of Birka in Sweden. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Virginia opossum (*Didelphis virginiana*)  [National Geographic page](http://animals.nationalgeographic.com/animals/mammals/opossum/).

They are also the only marsupials (pouched mammal) in the United States and Canada! They get a bad rap, but they are great animals and would rather avoid human contact. 

Females give birth to baby opossums that are about the size of honeybees which immediately make their way to her pouch. Opossums can give birth to up to 20 offspring at once, though most do not live and some never make it to their mother's pouch. It's a tough beginning for our little friends!

This great YouTube page was recommended to me. The Brain Scoop, so [here's a video from their channel about Opossums](https://youtu.be/wbf8nqMh0R0).

[Bonus cute gif](http://data.iwastesomuchtime.com/IW-111320160513356.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Virginia opossum (*Didelphis virginiana*) [Wiki page](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Virginia_opossum) and [National Geographic page](http://animals.nationalgeographic.com/animals/mammals/opossum/).

They are also the only marsupials (pouched mammal) in the United States and Canada! They get a bad rap, but they are great animals and would rather avoid human contact. 

Females give birth to baby opossums that are about the size of honeybees which immediately make their way to her pouch. Opossums can give birth to up to 20 offspring at once, though most do not live and some never make it to their mother's pouch. It's a tough beginning for our little friends!

This great YouTube page was recommended to me. The Brain Scoop, so [here's a video from their channel about Opossums](https://youtu.be/wbf8nqMh0R0). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opossums have 13 nipples, arranged in a circle of 12 with one in the middle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opossums have 13 nipples, arranged in a circle of 12 with one in the middle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daphnis is featured in this view, taken as NASA's Cassini spacecraft made one of its ring-grazing passes over the outer edges of Saturn's rings on Jan. 16, 2017. [1041 x 1041] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apollo 17, Final Crewed Mission to the Moon, Launches -- Dec. 7, 1972 [7096 x 5327] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Luna enjoying a warm sunbeam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 02:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full and free journal article [*How Ants Use Vision When Homing Backward*](http://www.cell.com/current-biology/fulltext/S0960-9822\(16\)31466-X).

**Highlights:**

* Backward-walking ants rely on celestial but not terrestrial cue memories
* Correction of direction based on terrestrial cues occurs after peeking forward
* The retrieved direction can be transferred into a compass frame of reference
* Ants can decouple their travel direction from their body orientation

**Summary:**

Ants can navigate over long distances between their nest and food sites using visual cues. Recent studies show that this capacity is undiminished when walking backward while dragging a heavy food item. This challenges the idea that ants use egocentric visual memories of the scene for guidance. Can ants use their visual memories of the terrestrial cues when going backward? Our results suggest that ants do not adjust their direction of travel based on the perceived scene while going backward. Instead, they maintain a straight direction using their celestial compass. This direction can be dictated by their path integrator but can also be set using terrestrial visual cues after a forward peek. If the food item is too heavy to enable body rotations, ants moving backward drop their food on occasion, rotate and walk a few steps forward, return to the food, and drag it backward in a now-corrected direction defined by terrestrial cues. Furthermore, we show that ants can maintain their direction of travel independently of their body orientation. It thus appears that egocentric retinal alignment is required for visual scene recognition, but ants can translate this acquired directional information into a holonomic frame of reference, which enables them to decouple their travel direction from their body orientation and hence navigate backward. This reveals substantial flexibility and communication between different types of navigational information: from terrestrial to celestial cues and from egocentric to holonomic directional memories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
