<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4858</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 11:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you exclude immigrants? And if you do what is the point of the numbers because by 2050 they won't be immigrants. Muslims are 5% in UK now it will only increase so who knows what organised religion in Europe will be like by 2050.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 11:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope ammunition is too heavy for them to reload either machine guns or artillery. They would be best for EOD (small nibble hands, lightweight so might not set off mines, tripwires would be closer to eye level so they would be more visible) or tunnel warfare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 11:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the Palestinians with Hamas. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OZTcYKwnehY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 11:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solution: All antibiotics should be prescribed by a doctor not a market stall (developing countries), no antibiotics for industrial farming so what you pay a bit more for meat (USA, China), finish your prescription stupid people (everyone).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 10:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uber tried in my city but failed the taxis are all good with great apps but hearing the stories from USA no wonder uber took off but how did US cities let their taxis get so shit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 20:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put a pull up bar on a door you use a lot. Do 1 pull up everytime you go under it. Then you will quickly find yourself able to do 2 everytime. If you do this as a matter of course and do your pull up sets as normal you will increase massively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 20:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IPMtMaUoLkA just watched this video on PST and suggest that you aim to exceed those "competitive" scores by quite a large amount. Screenings are there to weed out the wannabes. If you aren't beasting those stats you probably shouldn't be there. You should also probably stop taking creatine unless you are just getting massive/shredded for the beach. It adds weight and messes up your hydration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 19:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the elite teams of foreign terrorists trying to cripple USA infrastructure are not really waiting as sleeper cells otherwise they would have done it. Just as all the weapons smuggled past the TSA by testers show that there are not legions of ISIS trying to take down every flight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 12:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TTIP like TPP but with Europe. It is so controversial that the document is kept secret and the peoples representatives read it in a secure room unable to take notes. The plan was to rubber stamp it across the EU but it is so bad many politicians, both right and left, have condemned it and also spoken out about the lack of transparency and anti democratic process of implementation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 10:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know Dylan got better after going electric... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 10:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is roof actually "roof"? Is it code? /s
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 10:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL so many people don't know the difference between murder and manslaughter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 16:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mullet rights! you fascist!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 16:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it will look real nice when its done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 14:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 212,000 coal mining jobs were lost under the 1964-1970 Labour Government

43 per cent of mining jobs went in the 1960s under Wilson 

Here is the article from left wing perspective so no pro Tory fact picking. http://leftfootforward.org/2013/04/tory-spin-on-coal-masks-fact-that-80-per-cent-of-coal-jobs-were-lost-under-thatcher/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 10:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa there hos. Don't come here with your "facts" and "book learning" I have thoughts about Thatcher I have developed over many years listening to comedians and other people. Don't try to twist my mind with your so called "knowledge". Don't you know there is a narrative to maintain, your "historical facts" can't undermined the received folk wisdom, OK?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 10:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being gouged open and then watching as its inside are burnt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 10:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coal is one of the most destructive fuel available. Thank god the mines closed. Lucky for the environment the NUM tried to bring down an elected government rather than modernise the coal industry and save jobs. Also thanks to the old style confrontational unions of the 70s and 80s there was no future for any industry in the UK as we watched the death of ship building, car making etc. Nissan and Ford would have pulled out/shut down years ago without the change brought on in the 80s. The pragmatic unions that work with industry came about because the parts of the union movement itself realised nutters had taken over and perhaps working with Nissan to create super productive working environments was better for members than scheming for class war and striking at every opportunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 09:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was his evil ex wife winnie mandela who ran a gang and enforced strict control over her chunk of the black area by killing those who opposed her and her grip on local power. She was so vile that nelson did everything he could to distance himself from her and her attempts to exploit his fame after his release. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 00:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waiting with knives after class  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M_W9gbk-tIQ Edit: for relevance the song is all about group hating Becky but dv cos you hate the song thats fair enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 21:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no argument in my statement other than USA did not enter WW2 in response to Nazi death camps. At no point do I say we should have let the Holocaust happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 14:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realise Team USA only joined the war after Japan attacked them and they had loaned the anti Nazi forces so much money it would take around 60 years to pay it off? Nothing to do with Jews at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 18:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except often the drone attacks are done with the consent of the sovereign government of the area or are done in areas that have no central authority perhaps controlled by groups fighting over the remains in a failed state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 17:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are in the sun in a pub garden...get off reddit! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 11:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are mistaken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 10:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No actual occupation or genocide but Scotland was not completely untouched by the war. Here is an example https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clydebank_Blitz 
Of course the landscape was changed by gun emplacements and large scale beach defences and all military from Scotland. Arresting the guy for the prank on his gf is totally insane. With any luck the judge will dismiss the charge. But he might go to jail like the idiot junkies who put bacon on the door handles of a mosque and then got jailed!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 13:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they don't pay for it? It is free on the socialised health care system. So they title is click bait, dog whistle shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 18:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you twelve?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 20:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you have a solid door into your living space. Your front door should not be able to be kicked apart. It should need a axe to get through it. Once you have a solid front door make sure it has at least 2 locks at least 2 feet apart. Also make sure the door jam/frame is strong enough it wont splinter if the locks get kicked. Think about running a thin metal strip down the side that will hold the frame together to prevent kick ins. Be able to see who is at the door before you open, maybe a small window in the door or a spy hole or video camera. Maybe a door chain or something so you can open it a bit while still being safe. However THE MOST IMPORTANT thing is make sure you have a smoke alarm fitted and check it works and get a small fire extinguisher and fire blanket for the kitchen. Also window locks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 22:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Brit I find the fact that Americans actually have a Christian right political force to be amazing. The stuff Ted Cruz was into would make him unelectable to a town council outside of Northern Ireland. As far as the politics in the UK are concerned it is more of an ethnic thing rather than a religious belief thing so more like someone identifying as hispanic so some mexicans will vote for him rather than him saying I am Catholic so vote for me. Also politics is filled with british people of pakistani origin so are the universities, public sector and local councils. Despite what those trying for victim status say they are well represented and are as rich and powerful as  anyone else in UK. There are no parallels with the USA system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 22:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off Pope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 21:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is as Muslim as Boris was Christian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 12:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would be trying to hard - closet case detected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 11:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Spanish govt is just distracting its own citizens from its failings crap economy, massive youth unemployment and various other scandals. Wave the flag rile up some nationalism to distract the voters. The truth is in that part of the world many Spanish work on Gibraltar and many Gibraltar citizens live in the surrounding spanish towns and cities. Politicians are dicks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 12:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Artillery in battle is used on an area of ground rather than a specific individual target. So you might fire it at tanks to make them close down their hatches, try to damage their optics and radios making it easier for anti tank weapons engage them. Or use it on a piece of ground to direct the enemy into a killing zone. Or to suppress an enemy position while you move troops to assault it (or withdraw). It does all these things in all weathers whilst out of sight of the enemy and very cheaply compared to multiple layers of ground attack aircraft. Also good at providing smoke and illumination. Plus it is probably part of the ground troops own formation so is more likely to be there all the time when air power might not be. In a modern war it is still useful, even in counter insurgency where you probably wouldn't use multiple gunlines pre smashing the target area because of civilian casualties. You could put it in a remote location (very little maintenance or support required) and be able to hit enemy mortar, rocket firing positions that would be out of range of infantry weapons (even anti-tank weapons like Javelin). 

TL:DR Very useful. Artillery is cheap, all weather, out of sight, easy to maintain, a very good area weapon and very good at supporting ground troops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 11:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would bet that there is a requirement that smaller less physically strong soldiers be able to load it hence the crane but yeah it looks faster to pick up the shell and carry it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 09:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video from 2015 world cup. Link is article on race from red bull. 2016 race is in June.

http://www.redbull.com/uk/en/bike/stories/1331729311377/leogang-2015-dh-world-cup-results-video-highlights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 13:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet they did because few if any of the Japaneses scientists were brought to justice and most ended up in USA weapons programs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 12:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just kept moaning about not killing people. Even when fighting seemingly unlimited numbers of ninjas who go from completely invincible, to cannon fodder depending on plot requirements. Yeah pretty easy to stop caring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 11:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am big. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 10:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were using them as "sniper" weapons to kill individual Taliban in Helmand. Lots of missiles fired. Youtube and liveleak must be like fantasy porn for you;) Maybe some genius politician will suggest using western troops to establish "safe havens" in Syria or Libya then you will get to fire all you want!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 10:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep they had a riot and stoned some mountain guides just to protect their monopoly on rigging the mountain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 22:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half of Glasgow always knew there was a evil catholic plan...The other half were just too busy winning football games ;)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 15:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect you are not the dead at 54 type and are therefore not part of the "stereotype" referred to, so no need to apologise for any bursting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 17:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cash money and power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 14:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Climate tax on pets. http://www.leftlanenews.com/study-finds-dogs-have-larger-carbon-footprints-than-suvs.html    http://www.salon.com/2014/11/20/the_surprisingly_large_carbon_paw_print_of_your_beloved_pet_partner/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 14:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They never tried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 13:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, Science FTW. Unless global domination is the aim and given your military spending that might be easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 19:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The IRA did this, kidnap a family and make one of them drive the truck to the police station while handcuffed to the steering wheel. Proxy bombs. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Proxy_bomb     http://www.belfastdaily.co.uk/2013/11/07/patsy-gillespie-widow-i-dont-want-revenge-i-just-want-justice/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You are the Devil and are trying to defeat God by winning a cultural victory. 2016 has been a big year for you calling in David Bowie, Alan Rickman and now Prince. In the depths of hell you are deciding who to claim next. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 11:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 09:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This type of arrest would be illegal in most of Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 20:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be....oh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 18:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traitor. Treachery. Treacherous. Treason.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 18:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't even know what tax evasion is but don't let that stop your commenting and fb level political opinions. Bet you were right into russell brand last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 17:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toyota land cruisers crush land rover defender but the LR defender really is a hardcore off road vehicle fixable with a hammer. Had a defender get trapped in a river as the water rose, towed it out and the rocks had knackered the 4x4, we just knocked the drive shaft off and drove it as 2 wheel drive the rest of the way. Seriously robust but very basic. But like the rest of the wold even the UK has replaced LR with japanese imports for work vehicles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 15:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be because your own government asks them to drone them. Better drones than all out PAK army assault that levels entire valleys. Drone strike or infantry brigade with Artillery support? If I was an innocent shopkeeper in the swat valley the answer would be drones please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 12:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do sometimes wonder why USA is still a single country. It just seems they would be happier split up a bit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 11:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is happening but nothing to do with government more to do with corporate interests and the workplace thinking it should own peoples entire lives and everything they say. You boss wants your fb? For instance I see one of the biggest threats from big data comes from insurance companies getting access to health reports. Imagine not being able to get a mortgage or a job because of a bit of DNA and potential genetic risk. The terror Americans have about their credit rating and the impact it has on them, way worse than anything in Europe, is worrying. So I don't really think Govt spies are a worry, more the workplace owning more and more of our existence. 

Imagine if your boss could just buy your social profile because you might control a cash drawer. GCHQ will tell him to ram it but I imagine plenty of corporate security services would love to be able to data mine and sell all the stuff google and the rest of the internet economy has on you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 11:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crime statistics have been improving not necessarily the truth at street level. NO sex attacks in Cologne, nope none at all, nothing to see here...  
For a fairly lengthy but accurate description of how police fix crime stats at the behest of politicians see The Wire (season 3).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 11:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope because the stasi used the information to totally dominate and control the population, meeting with friends in East Germany and saying things like get rid of the state, I hate the government would quickly lead to serious pressure. Even if you think the evil western agencies have all the knowledge there are no consequences for the many who say get rid of the queen, tear down the state etc even reasonably violent protests only result in a handful of arrests and sentencing is fairly mild. People get longer in jail for putting bacon on the handles of a mosque than rioting in London. Imagine if you posted, I hate Gove save NHS evil Tories on Fb then the next day you went to work as a cashier or road sweeper and found you had been sacked and the council was maybe taking back your house that is how it worked under the stasi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 11:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No mainstream UK parties are strongly authoritarian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 00:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be the top comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 13:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manlet breaks neck playing ninjas on stairs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 09:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I can see is spider webs from hell. NO trippy time near that for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 10:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monoculture of commercial bees is also a big threat to bee populations and should be changed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 10:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might eventually give Hydrogen powered cars the edge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 20:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like he had a choice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 17:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Private companies will now do this for anyone that pays.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 17:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Spader in the TV show The Blacklist is astoundingly good. It is a fun thriller, campy, spy type thing but there are lines he says that are chilling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 18:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bloodbath of junkies and psychos, imagine Japanese Irvin Welsh crossed with Brett Easton Ellis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 14:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 40k is a lot for a car and should be taxed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 11:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep Muslims having to use Arabic is no different than the Vatican insisting on use of Latin, it is about control and subjugation. Islam is just 500 years behind the curve of progress.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 11:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had gold you would have it all. It seems no one else has noticed that the oil story was about to go off then the panama papers come out and everyone forgets about the oil papers! Oil story was about to show global oil rigging and corruption and links to global strategic planning etc then a story about Putin and the Chinese leaders stealing money come along. Conveniently very few Americans involved (probs because the use different tax fronts etc) so win win for whoever leaked it. I doubt it was a pissed off lawyer whistle-blower.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a load of bullshit. Take Scotland the last Pakistani murdered for racist reasons was murdered by another Pakistani because he was the wrong sect and insulted the prophet. Pakistanis are more at risk from religious violence in their own country than they are in the west which literally bends over backwards to help them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dog is the worst, he is already dying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 11:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but you have to be interested in running rather than it being a cardio component of your lifting plan. If you want to get better at running do it 2 or 3 times a week 5-7 miles once a week is not enough, you would be better doing 3 miles 2 or 3 times a week. Headphones on and a nice path/trail with no traffic then you get to zone out. 
But if you get that into running where after 30 or 40 mins you get that runners high and your body feels totally in sync and you feel you can push it; where it is only your mind that holding you back rather than pain in lungs/legs then you might be eating into those gainz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teenage Arctic explorers return from 10-day adventure eating raw narwhal skin. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 11:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 10:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also how was he able to not get droned for the last 5 years (he says last attempt was March 2011)? Perhaps because he is not on the list? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 12:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captain to XO - I love the way that blush highlights your check bones.
XO to Capt - Thank you sir, that scarlet makes your lips really pop!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 11:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect he has contributed more in taxes than you will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 17:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chuka just seems like the slimiest, lawyer/politician possible. So smooth and just far, far too slick. And Jarvis used to kill people in Iraq and Afghanistan so not sure how acceptable he is to the wider "community". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 17:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is going to sit in Russia for the rest of his life like several other former western spies who ended up in Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 14:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> History will judge Obama as wise and note this as a good move on his part. The often used phrase, "when the only tool you have is a hammer everything looks like a nail" couldn't apply more when he describes CIA officers who have only known hunting and killing in war zones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 10:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NI is totally different to the UK in the way religion is viewed, there are many, many protestants who like the evangelical right (def not catholic) in USA regard abortion as murder. This is not the case in England, Wales or Scotland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 17:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Design Apple products. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 16:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A spot of local bother nothing more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 16:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Americans, prepare to have your feedom minds blown away - In Scotland the chants can be so religiously offensive to the other side that the Scottish Government passed special laws meaning you can go to jail for singing during the game, on the way to the game or just singing anytime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 11:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I googled it and can't find any evidence of the RC church regularly ex communicating nationalist terrorists. Any links? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 20:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like distracting us from the oil industry scandal that was brewing. Oh but now we are all focused on Putin's corruption and a bunch of individuals. Nothing more about American oil interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 17:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The brightly coloured vests would have been too busy checking seatbelts are being used as you drive around at 5 mph inside the base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 12:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. Europe was ticking along making progress with virtually all religions becoming more and more chilled then all of a sudden, "FUCK YOU, ALLAH's HERE!!!!". For years if you said anything against Islam you were branded racist etc but the simple test I suggest to people is ask if Jews or Catholics were doing this would you be cool with it? I know why the left traditionally secular and anti-religion has embraced Islam but I don't understand it. Not all Islam is the same and there are branches that are chilled but unfortunately they are routinely killed by other Muslims for being more humanist. From Pakistan to Scotland Muslims that are similar to European ideas of religion and its place in politics are murdered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
