<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3122</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 04:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this approach. Perhaps even calling it something like "sports analyst" would give it a more palatable and "legitimate" feel to it for other people's ears. Personally, I love the whole "blah blah math" bit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 06:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Setting aside any discussion of the merits of your career since you don't seem to want to discuss that, it sounds like the people in your life are some mixture of concerned for your economic future and jealous of the perceived freedom you have because you don't have a "real" job. You could take one more crack at using evidence to sway their opinion, but it seems like there is a fundamental disagreement between you and them in terms of what an appropriate way to live your life is. They may never accept what you do, in which case you will need to find others who accept you as is and stop discussing work with these current friends (or cut them out entirely). As for your GF...well, she shouldn't have the option of benefiting from your money and insulting how you make it at the same time. :-/


Perhaps a good way to deal try approaching them is to show them how seriously you take handicapping. Don't show your current bank account figure, state something like "I spend X hours a week studying and handicapping football matches and average y dollars per week from my hard work." You've been at it for long enough that you have a solid set of results to use for support.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 03:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you're asking the right question here. You, and everyone here, already know that penis jokes are out of bounds in relationships unless you're out to hurt your partner. You are not overreacting. 

The better question here is "what can she say that will allow me to get past this?" You're going to have to communicate about it, that much is clear. What can she say that would make it better? "I wasn't saying that as a complaint. I love sex with you and think your penis is perfect for me?" That might do it. Short of that, I feel like you are going to have a hard time trusting her with personal things when you know she's so careless that she's attack your sexual ego in such an obvious way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Compensation Data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! I'm a researcher who does work on compensation and incentives. I'm looking for any data sources which contain information about compensation for public or private companies.  Thanks in advance for any information you may be able to share! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 04:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not getting where the family was trying to make a different point aside from their worry over the OP not having a LTR. It sounded like the entire focus of the intervention was the lack of a LTR. Even if his family was trying to say something more general about the OP's personality or behavior, they clearly didn't communicate that effectively.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 22:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up the term "economic order quantity" and you will find a basic model of inventory management designed to balance holding and ordering costs. Along with this model you can find statistical techniques for adjusting your EOQ safety stock based on variability of demand. It's a simple but effective way to think about inventory management.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 12:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something about your description of things bothers me. I think it's the way that you seem to gloss over throwing your sister under the bus by telling your aunts and uncles that you didn't get to visit them because of your sister a discomfort. This isn't to say that you shouldn't be upset about having been kept separated from your family. But blaming a young girl for that decision makes no sense to me. The blame for that falls squarely on your parents, who kept you away despite your asking them directly to take you on your own. Now that you've basically ratted her out and blamed her for not being as social within the group as you, you've destroyed any future chance she might have had at integrating herself within your family. In essence, you have achieved what your mother set out to avoid: you've permanently excluded her. 

Despite your protestations, I get a real sense that you resent your sister. Personally, I think this resentment is misplaced.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 02:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Follow TSwift's advice and shake it off! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 02:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a business-related field working at an R1. We have journal rankings which dictate our target journals. Tenure standards vary widely depending on tenure clock and institution. Where I am, they ask for 2-4 articles in the top 3-5 (depending on area) journals in your 5-year tenure clock period. Top schools might offer an 8-year clock and require 6 top 3-5 articles with 6 other high impact articles in the next tier of journals (e.g. Discipline-specific journals or "B+" journals). Teaching schools, by contrast, might simply require 5 articles overall without regard for the outlet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 00:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's clearly why he is trying to pay you under the table...any reputable payroll preparer will ensure you are paid overtime appropriately. Its not just more taxes, but more wages. What a jerk! You should start looking for a new job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 16:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. My advice is to recognize that part of his problem is, in fact, his sister and his feelings of being overshadowed by her. Why should he have to live in that feeling of he doesn't have to? It's easier to remove yourself from the situation causing those feelings and then deal with the underlying issues. 

He could see a therapist...that would be wise, actually. But why continue to work with her of she's a constant reminder of his less popular status? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 15:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is nonsense. He spends the whole post acknowledging that he feels bad because his sister is clearly great at the job. He also clearly acknowledges his jealousy. Why should he be grateful for a good looking sister? That's creepy and wrong-headed. Looks aren't everything! The OP clearly gets what's going on here and feels appropriately bad about it. 

The fact here is that the OP has a problem that lots of people have - he's got a sibling that seems to be overshadowing him. She's good looking, more popular, and at least as competent as him. The difference is that, unlike most people, he can't get away from his sibling and strike out on his own, feel his own success. Sure, he may love his sister and enjoy her company. But he's constantly having to face his own relative lack of popularity. He used to have a job he could feel some independent success in, but with his sister there even that has become less satisfying because she's clearly better than him at the job. Pus, she's gossiping about him being possibly gay? His sister...sounds needy despite having it all (on a relative basis)z

Are his feelings of jealousy and anger wrong? No. They're natural for someone who has probably felt overshadowed by his sister all his life. 

Are they going to go away? Also no. Certainly not when having to face them every day by living with her and working in the same place. 

I think the OP should at least find a new job. Don't discuss it with the sister, though...that's just looking for sympathy. Get the new job, give notice at the video game store, and move on. If that isn't enough to start feeling some independent success, consider moving out. Again, don't consult your family. They seem content to sacrifice his happiness to ensure his sister's happiness.  Once you are feeling more secure in yourself, OP, you can rebuild your relationship with your sister on more solid ground.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 06:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also think this is the way to go here. Basically, whatever middle school game of dominance he was trying to play with you is over and he lost.  Badly. You won, you both know it. Now it's just a matter of how you choose to win. 

Personally, I think saying nothing and treating him as neutrally as you can is not only the right thing to do, but also the most personally satisfying thing to do. He clearly knows what is going on and is deliberately avoiding your gaze because of it. If he brings it up, let him know that personal feelings have no place in the workplace. If he doesn't, he will have to deal with knowing he works for the guy he bullied and wonder when the proverbial other shoe will drop. Torment him with your success and good grace

Edit: Added a few words to make it clear I can construct a complete sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 05:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm talking about! Vindictiveness is underrated in my opinion, particularly when dealing with academic integrity issues. Teach that kid a lesson and make sure they learn it the first time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 17:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You already have the job and have shown your competence by passing the exam. The main draw of a "good" program is access to recruiters and alumni networks. You can get competent education most anywhere, however. 

When you go to apply for a different job, the hiring manager will look for two things: the letters "CPA" and your work experience. You only need credits. If the cheaper online program will count for those credits, go for it. Check and see if there are other, cheaper in-state options online first. Also, whichever school you choose should be regionally accredited.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 16:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did a season of personal tax for a small CPA firm. It was an interesting and fun experience. As you suggest in your post, one of the most fun aspects of the job was seeing people and getting to interact with them. It was clear that the CPA had a strong relationship with his clients. So long as you can deal with disorganized clients (more frequent in small CPA practices) and have personal sales skills, it can be a good practice to engage with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 15:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I see...you mean Ditto! How silly of me. I was thinking you all were talking about some sort of bug in the program (I.e. the ditto bug). Ditto makes a lot more sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 10:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you explain to me what is meant by "a ditto thing" please? I haven't heard this term before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 07:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a better person than me. I'd blow that friendship up by outing him as an asshole wherever I could. #SaltyFBPost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 06:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best press Niantic has gotten all week!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 06:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that's an interesting point about how much they're willing to let the client know. Niantic seems very concerned with people's ability to know where Pokemon are with any certainty. Even the original tracking feature requires effort to wander around and narrow down the range until you find them. Given that they've suggested the current version of the game represents very little of the full vision for the game, I wonder if they have a preference for the server-side version of things in order to facilitate some future product or micro transaction functionality. 

If they had wanted to use a client-side approach, I can't imagine they wouldn't have been able to do so. I'm not a tech person and I can clearly understand the concept after reading the comments here. I feel like the choice of a server-side model was deliberate and chosen to avoid cheating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 08:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment deserves all the upvotes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 22:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't respond to him at all. However, I'd definitely let her know that her dad was snooping on her phone when I talked to her next. She deserves that much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 18:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure isn't the same as sure sure. Independent confirmation, please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 18:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone confirm this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 18:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can't disable their Twitter feed or their App Store comments. Bombard them with your feelings there!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 02:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A year or two ago, I caught six students plagiarizing with TurnItIn on a single take-home exam where I told them twice that I'd be electronically checking for plagiarism and explicitly told them they couldn't collaborate. 

Cut to me hearing a fourth student tell me the answers were exactly the same because they studied together and prepared answers for those questions before the exam (not possible given the specific nature of the questions), subsequently losing my mind, and telling her off for lying to me until she cried. Students five and six took their F's gracefully without even showing up to contest them. 

Tl;dr: Fuck some students!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 02:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finishing a PhD is going to be very difficult without the support of your spouse. Is there something keeping your wife from contributing to the household financially while you continue your studies (eg cultural considerations, poor local economy)? If money is the main issue pushing you out the door, maybe there is something to be done given that you describe yourself as a superior student.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait...lotion? I picture hypocrites as being stuck with the dry rub. :-P

Seriously, though, your boyfriend is better off standing firm against his family and their nonsense now. If any possibility exists for a healthy relationship between them in the future, it starts with firmness now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be much higher on the list than it is...clearly the most horrifying joke I've ever actually laughed at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 02:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember that moment you describe here, the one where you know for sure you aren't straight. A therapist asked me to think about a a Victoria Secret mode and a Calvin Klein model and, after a few seconds, I just blurted out "Oh shit...I'm gay!" 

It took me an extra decade and a lot of heartache but I get where you're coming from with your realization. No matter what anyone says, it's entirely up to you and your comfort level and pace as to when and to who you talk to about any of this. It sounds like you have at least one friend who supports you and parents who love you and want the best for you. There's no reason to rush it, so take your time and enjoy learning more about yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 07:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They probably are just mentioning you since you don't have a profile. Luckily, Facebook is very easy to use and lots of people have posted helpful how-to posts online telling you how to use it. I would make a profile and write that post as others are suggesting. If you look at the profiles of people who are mentioning you, you'll appear as someone they might know. I bet the friend requests will come quickly. 

I am so sorry this all happened to you. Use this time when the spotlight is on you to tell people how their actions have affected you over the past year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 03:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't work at one, but I have several friends who do. One who works at CSU San Marcos make approximately 15-20% below market rate for comparable schools. Cost of living is well above average as well, with a Cost of Living Index of 136 compared to a national average of 100. 

California is pretty progressive in terms of open records laws. You might be able to find salary data for CSU schools online if you search.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 07:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on your source, failure rates for new restaurants are between 60% and 90%. The reasons for these new restaurant failures include ineffective management/leadership, among others. No experience and poor credit suggests ineffective management will be an issue. 

Ask your wife to search Google for "restaurant failure statistics" and slim the first 20 results. If that doesn't then her around, I'm not sure what will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like this approach. It sets up your brother to take responsibility for his behavior without you having to face scrutiny of your sex life. 

I'd also delete your post on that dating site temporarily in case his GF decides to go searching for who sent the email. If she'd recognize the writing when presented the post, she might recognize it automatically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 07:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 07:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're entrusting the care of your child to someone who has a history of ignoring sexual abuse? That seems like a first class terrible idea. 

Whatever you do, I think it's imperative that you find a way to get alternative child care even if decide to live at home.  

As for your mother, there isn't anything you can do there. It's up to you to protect yourself and your child since your mother is either unwilling o incapable of supporting you in that regard. Keep quiet if you must to preserve your living situation, but absolutely do not trust her with your safety.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 06:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really worrisome, man. Calling to make sure you don't come is really, really active exclusion. Most families are just passively exclusive as in they don't treat you well when you come along. 

Have you asked what your boyfriend plans to do in the long term if you decide to get married? Are other family members having their SOs excluded too? I'd hate to join a family that will never accept me...that places a big strain on the relationship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 22:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only way to get help for your problems from a therapist is to admit what they are. If you are as ugly as you think you are (which I sincerely doubt, by the way), the therapist already knows about it. You're telling the therapist puts you insecurity out into the world, however, and it can be a bit daunting to do that. Take the step anyway because you deserve to feel good about yourself no matter how you look! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 10:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with everyone else here who is telling you to cooperate with your mother and go visit the psychiatrist for a bit. I'm going to take a more practical approach, however, and suggest an incentive for you to go to see the psychiatrist. 

You've been spending time checking out pictures of guys online...a perfectly natural thing for a gay person to do at your age. Have you ever given any thought about how to move from looking at pictures to actually going on dates with real guys? If you don't love yourself as you are, gayness and all, how will you be able to go out and feel comfortable going on a date?

I've been where you are. I was a young closeted gay guy who looked at pictures and dated girls to try and hide. It wasn't until I couldn't take the lack of fulfillment anymore and went to see a therapist that I got the answers I needed to move on. Years later, I have a partner and love my life (well, most of it). But none of it would have been possible without someone non-judgmental to talk to about my feelings. A stranger, you see, is exactly who you want to listen to the embarrassing and worrisome secrets you don't want to tell anyone else. After all...who gives a damn what a stranger thinks of you? Right? 

So, in conclusion...if you won't go for your Mom, go for the makeouts it will help you enjoy in the future! Also, good luck to you!

Edit: It's not clear what religion you are from your post. As someone who has spent a lot of time in Church, however, I can tell you that the parts of the Bible pertaining to homosexuality are...well, let's say open to interpretation. There's a three chapter section of Leviticus where we've basically just kept some of the rules and not others depending on whether or not the rules make sense to our modern understanding of things. Why we have rejected the prohibition on wearing mixed fabrics yet kept the prohibition on homosexuality is beyond me and many other people. When someone is telling you to hate yourself and promising you eternal damnation, you get to give their words extra special scrutiny. I encourage you to do some research on your own and see what conclusion you come to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 19:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well...the math of it is relatively straightforward. I wouldn't be super impressed by his ability to pull that statistic out quickly, however. When you play games seriously, you encounter a variety of common situations and learn the associated statistics by rote. The player in question seems like he's a relatively serious player, so I'm assuming he just memorized the odds for various situations. Alternatively, as with poker players, you can learn tips and tricks to help you get close enough for situations which are common.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 05:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like this logic. One could look at slaves and say "Well, they got food and clothing...and the work gave them muscles and agricultural or domestic skills." It doesn't make it any less of a violation of their rights. #FreePikachu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 01:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hearing the way your boyfriend talks about your work, I'm reminded of the scene in Mad Men where Peggy and her boyfriend Abe break up. She's in advertising and he's a writer for a subversive underground paper bent on changing the world. In that moment, he says "your activities are offensive to my every waking moment."

He may not be saying it in such a confrontational way, but there is something sneering in the way he judges your work that is reminiscent of that scene. A good relationship has at its core mutual respect. That doesn't seem present here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 22:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, you're the asshole who keeps selling my email address and filling my inbox with garbage? Jerk! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 06:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because it's...not to be critical, mind you...irrational. It's hard to explain because to explain it, you'd have to appeal to all the crap and pressure they put on you about it. That wouldn't sufficiently explain it to them despite the fact that a therapist would probably "get" the problem instantly.  

It's not that you aren't intelligent, it's that you aren't interested. Their badgering had made it almost a point of pride for you not to be proficient in coding. I get it. I have a similar block with a certain foreign language that my father speaks. Even if I were fluent, I'll be damned if I let him hear me speak it. 

I feel like this is something you should be talking to a therapist about. It sounds like there are some family and relationship dynamics here which aren't particularly helpful to your career development. I doubt they're trying to be mean or anything...they sound like they want the best for you and are trying to achieve that with their suggestions. You need to find a way to say "no" and have it be the last word on the matter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 04:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to back you up here and say that coding-heavy statistical analysis is not required for all fields. Many programs, including STATA and SPSS, have point-and-click interfaces which you can use to achieve substantially similar ends as coding would allow. 

With that said, it sounds as if you have a bit of a phobia surrounding your use of computers and coding at this point. That's not surprising given all the pressure you've received to engage with those things. Nevertheless, it's going to be a hindrance to you in the future of you don't find a way to open yourself up more to specific kinds of computer-based experiences. Jobs are increasingly introducing technology, even those fields which don't traditionally do so. Try and examine this more objectively to see if there isn't something you can do to help yourself mentally with respect to computers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 00:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL I'm a bad person for laughing out loud at your "HEYOH!"

Of course, the comparison is very appropriate. He'd lose his mind, as would your family, if you said any of that. Don't let him do the same thing to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 00:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling bullshit on facts doesn't make them not facts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 22:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30-32? So you want her to wait another five years when you say you're already sure you want to be with her forever? That seems really silly!

She's pushing because she wants you to commit. If you like it then you better put a ring on it, because she's clearly losing patience with...well, whatever is going on in your mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 22:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't see a problem here, though certainly not for lack of effort in trying to find one. 

It seems like he took care to acknowledge the numerous people who provided input into the paper. It could be that one of the acknowledged provided enough of a contribution that they'd receive a co-authorship credit. However, by signing off on the publication of the paper as required by JAMA, those people have essentially stated that wasn't the case. Even if you think the President used the power of his position to bully one or more of the acknowledged into forgoing a co-authorship claim...well, that sort of thing happens in academia too. This doesn't make it right, of course, but it does mean that the President isn't necessarily a special case. I have no trouble believing that a Constitutional Law professor with an Ivy League background could, with assistance in gathering facts, write an article of this caliber. 

Additionally, as a special communication, it seems clear that JAMA is conceding that this is more of a position paper rather than original research. The conflict of interest here isn't of the typical variety where there is some financial benefit to be gained. Instead, it's of the very common variety where his legacy and reputation stands to benefit from publication. That's true for every academic. Of course, if you think he didn't write it the perhaps you think he doesn't deserve the reputational benefits of the article. But to suggest he should disclaim a conflict of interest in a law that everyone knows he pushed for because he wants it to succeed seems to be holding the President to a higher publication standard than we hold ourselves to. We all want our work to succeed!

I'm going to go out in a limb and make a generalization. I think a certain type of academic, generally an early career one, will look at this article and say "they wouldn't have published that if I had written it." That's likely true. We see many instances of senior people in our respective fields getting away with the kind of normative, rather than positivist, writing which the President submitted for publication. This is perhaps best used as evidence of a lack of equity in academia. This isn't new, however, and it isn't isolated to the President. It's merely another piece of evidence in support of the idea that academia ain't fair. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 21:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came here to say this. Using the acronym inadvertently eliminates the horror that one should feel when hearing and talking about the topic. I hate how we do this in many areas of discourse and think that it contributes to a general desensitization we have to the awful things that go on around us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 12:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would hit up /r/legaladvice as a start. I came across a post recently which talked about indigent parents and how some states have laws requiring their children provide for them if at all possible. Before evicting her, you want to make sure you aren't actually setting yourself up for a legal issue.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump To Call For Return Of Child Labor At GOP Convention </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 03:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 23:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this approach wholeheartedly. When you succeed in getting him fired, be sure to visit /r/prorevenge to give us a breakdown on how you did it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 23:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It bothers me that you're viewing this as an issue of fashion or clothes rather than what it truly is: a lack of respect for you. Discarding all of your clothes when you're out of town reveals that she knew you wouldn't agree to such a move when you were in town. Turning this around on you is doubly shitty because it reveals her guilty mind. 

Her lack of respect for you is only going to get worse over time. I wish you would take some time to truly examine your relationship in its entirety to see if this incident is merely another in a pattern of dismissive behavior. Is she always criticizing you? Pointing out things you do wrong or which she wants you to do different? Think carefully! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 18:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a fine explanation of fiat currency, but i believe the question was about fiat currency so I'm not giving it an upvote. Posting this comment in case I'm wrong so I can come back and do the right thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 18:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yikes...sounds like your Aunt should be grateful that you all came up with 8 happy memories. I commend you for trying to suck it up and help out your Aunt in this difficult time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 11:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that we aren't encouraged to be mean spirited here, but I'm just going to outright call you a boob. Your lack of respect for your job and your assistant is hurting your career. As well it should! This lesson should be as painful as possible so that you remember to keep your work life separate from your home life. 

Keep your work life separate from your home life!
Keep your work life separate from your home life!
Keep your work life separate from your home life!
Keep your work life separate from your home life!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 10:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm always tempted to tell people in this situation to find something your boyfriend is insecure about and tease him about it whenever he brings up whatever he is teasing you about. 

He makes a comment about your weight? "Oh, honey...that's not nice. You wouldn't want me teasing you about that bald spot opening up on your head, would you? Better get some Rogaine, amirite?!? Lulz!!" 

I'm paraphrasing, of course...one laughs rather than lulzing. Still, the point remains he will understand why you don't just roll with it when you get him in a similar spot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 10:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say you've been avoiding him for a decade? What about before then? Do you have any happy memories of him as a child? What did you think were his best qualities as a child and early teen? Dismiss the last bunch of years with something glib like "like most teenage cousins, we spent less time together as we got older." Then move into the happy memories. "But when we were children, I remember x, y, and z." Match up the recent pictures with old stories and don't worry that the time frames don't match. 

You don't have to make him out to be a saint...just grab whatever positive things you can say and ignore the rest. If you're going to make the album, which it sounds like you are, then you're doing it for your aunt and not for your cousin. When you feel like you're being dishonest or stretching the truth, remember how much your aunt will appreciate it. Best wishes!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 10:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was always taught to look for ways to extend the conversation based on what the other person said. People usually don't reveal everything at once. For the party example you provide, for instance, you could have asked her how she was enjoying the party. You could have complimented her on something or thanked her for the invitation. You could have asked her about what it takes to plan a party like the one she had - "this must have been a lot of work!" 

Basically, the first step to good conversation is listening to the other person. Once you hear what they have to say, you can find something that interests you the most about what they said and use it to continue the conversation. 

Another thing you can do to make people feel more at ease in your presence is to reveal things about yourself. Given that you have been bullied, you clearly want to be careful about what you reveal. I keep some basic bits of information handy that I can reveal without feeling too exposed (I'm a private person). If they're talking about music, share what your favorite band is. If someone is talking about having a hard time with school work, commiserate with them by sharing an anecdote about your school work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 10:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Postpone the wedding? No...cancel the wedding! The only reason the OP is even considering staying with this ass is because of escalation of commitment. They've been together for a long time and she's clinging to the good times, thinking that just a bit more effort will turn her asshole fianc around. 

Tell me: if a friend told you that her fianc was acting this way, OP, what would your response be? You'd tell them to kick him to the curb and you'd be right! Treat yourself at least as well as you treat your friends and get rid of him!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 06:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus...that sure sounds like some ammo for helping move on. I know from experience that having someone walk out on you is just awful. You've said elsewhere, and you're absolutely spot on in this, that the person who leaves has the benefit of already having accepted their decision while the one being left doesn't. 

Your comments today also reveal no small amount of self-loathing (a strong word, perhaps, but I'm sticking with it). That is really something you need to work with understanding and moving past. I can't imagine what you could have possibly done to deserve that abuse. Self-reflection is one thing, self-flagellation is another.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 06:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your ability to admit that tells me that you're going to get through this alright, sir. 

With that said, I think you've gotten some good advice here. The most important thing is to find ways to meet other people within your comfort zone. A shared hobby, for example, can provide an excellent opportunity for conversation without all the stress of having to come up with what to say. As an introvert who recently moved somewhere new and had to rebuild a social network (albeit a small one), I know it doesn't have to be as excruciating as it seems at first glance. 

More important than the how, however, is the when. Don't go rushing into anything. Work on yourself first because you're worth the time and effort. Time spent grieving, truly grieving, a loss is much more productive than time spent trying to ignore the loss. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 02:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel bad that you've gotten no responses to this post, but I can understand why. In my mind, it isn't clear whether you're being asked to prepare an actual literature review (which is a formal thing) or simply review some papers to see how these methods are applied. I can't imagine why they'd want you to write a formal literature review nor could I figure out why they'd want such a thing. That's because you'll likely find piles of articles (depending on your area) which use correlation and/or regression methods. They're goal in asking you to do this is to ensure that you will be able to understand the papers that you're being asked to read.

Can you provide some more specific detail as to what you've been asked? What is the broad field (don't be too specific, just humanities/STEM/business etc.)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 01:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To what extent do you think that the erosion of the brain from the inside out plays a part in how well (relatively speaking) the man's brain has been able to adapt to the disorder? The outer parts of the brain seem to be the parts that remained intact. To a non-neuroscientist like me, these parts of the brain seem to have more surface area compared to the interiors parts of the brain. Did that make a difference here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 01:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found it. Consider yourself forgiven! :-D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 00:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matching shirts and ties?!!  Why can't I get through this damn thread without tears? T__T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
