<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9680</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 04:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better get out the paint scraper, those Bernie stickers will be coming off very soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 04:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised it isn't free!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 04:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ted Cruz is so unbelievably pathetic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 15:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you have any stairs you refinished with this project? I will be refinishing my floors and have a set of stairs I will have to do. Curious how you may have done the stairs. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another genius Bernie supporter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 20:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 18:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 00:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, this looks like absolute garbage  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 01:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen wind up toys play the drums with more energy than that drummer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 16:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And somehow all his leg hair fell out from the ride too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 00:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classy girl  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 05:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I have another Three Musketeers? They're rather small.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 21:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just went through this process as a first time homebuyer. Homes have gone extremely quick since we began looking last fall. My fianc and I had an offer accepted the beginning of this month which happened to be the first one we made an offer on. We had to move really quickly though. The home was listed on a Tuesday, we toured it on a Thursday and our offer was accepted Saturday with two competing offers. No open house even too place, just private showings. We did go just above asking price and fortunately got the house. We were looking in Kenmore, Town of Tonawanda and Amherst, we ended up in the Town of Tonawanda not far from North Buffalo. We're really happy with the area. The lower taxes compared to Kenmore will be really nice too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 15:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you did an incredible job on these floors. Nice work! I just bought a house and the floors are in need of being redone. I will definitely be referencing your post once I start my project! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 21:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay away from the chicken!! Bad chicken! Mess you up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 13:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to hear! The build up to the event seemed like it might be difficult to get in and out with a number of streets closed. Hoping for a big win as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 04:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it. Didn't want to deal with the idiots tonight downtown. Can't wait to see the footage later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 21:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! People on Imgur usually are the worst.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First wood working project attempt, coffee table for my new house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 21:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 02:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horror....horror  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 15:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reilly you just screwed yourself!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 11:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey anybody got change for a hundred?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 03:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, this guy is a genius. What the hell was I thinking when I had mine taken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 03:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are those wheels worth more than the entire vehicle?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 03:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great pick up, pretty jealous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 03:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's your wine? Get out!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 03:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ring dings are better than anything you're gonna get at a bakery  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 01:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might be the best post yet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 05:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be the poster boy for Bernie's campaign  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 04:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wonder why these people stay in the US if it's so terrible. If they think it's so much better elsewhere, they're welcome to leave.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 04:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just had a '99 patch added to my Sabres jersey, it looks great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 04:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't Jon Voight teach him anything?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 20:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do think season 7 is the beginning of the show making a slight decline. There are still some great episodes in 8 and 9 too, but the writing just got more ridiculous after Larry left the show.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 14:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see the engagement story line not being the most interesting part of his season, but there are so many hysterical episodes. The Hot Tub, The Wink, The Gum, The Doll, The Shower Head, The Calzone, some of my favorite episodes were in this season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 14:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the year in Buffalo I wear a sweatshirt under a jersey. When it gets a bit warmer I'll wear a t-shirt, but I prefer a long sleeve shirt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 04:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're snaps. Listen, maybe we should, uh, go out some time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 04:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's gotta hurt!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 04:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that sounds interesting sir.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 04:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually the line my butcher uses when we're chewing the fat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 15:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! I got 10% off with my BCBS card. Not much of a savings on two patches though at $5 a patch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 05:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently had some patches added to a couple jerseys through the Sabres store and was impressed by the turn around time. They had them back to me in like 5-6 days  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 04:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Is there something wrong with Loni Anderson?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 03:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The editing to put this together is pretty unreal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 13:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's awesome! The whole month of March has been 20% off all Sabres apparel excluding Eichel. I would recommend the store near Transit, much larger than the Town of Tonawanda location.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 05:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great choice. Thought about getting an O'Reilly too but didn't pull the trigger. I just got a Mogilny through the Dave and Adams sale recently so I held back from making another purchase.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 00:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved the Avalanche alternates from the 90's and the red Sabres alternates from the earlier 2000's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 14:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There wasn't any exterior damage to the car, so I wasn't sure how that may have happened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overshot the spot a little </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 06:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 06:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right on. I have mostly Sabres jerseys but have some classics of other teams I will wear other times too. I've worn quite a few to Wegmans when shopping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 04:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are in NYC again and looking for a Seinfeld landmark to go to, I would recommend the West Way Diner. Jerry and Larry used to frequent there. The food is good and reasonably priced and I've never seen a very long wait. It's also not too far from Time Square whereas Toms is a bit of a hike to the upper west side. 

I definitely got a pic in front of Toms during my last trip though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 04:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Difficult to pick one...would love a BU or Team USA juniors Eichel jersey. An Avalanche alternate Forsberg would be great. Mostly old Sabres jerseys beyond that like a goat Drury, LaFontaine, or some of the less popular Sabres from over years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 05:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found a $50 off coupon when I zoomed in on a Slap Shot t shirt, but it had already been used.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 11:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such an awesome gift. What kind of work do you do?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 03:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a little concerned about the neck, it looks pretty huge but there aren't any really good pictures to tell from the listing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legit? Avs Drury </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 00:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 04:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather make my own suit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 02:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know what the price is going to be for a customized jersey?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 02:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First one looks good. I got a similar Peca jersey a few months ago for $30-$35, you could end up getting this for a steal if it stays low.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 02:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a medium red alt Miller jersey but hadn't planned on moving it. Still wish I would have gotten a Drury. I do see them pop up on eBay occasionally. Buffalo craigslist wouldn't hurt either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 02:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just cleared out my two fakes myself, didn't want them bringing down the collection. I did go the route of reselling them though, didn't go for much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I didn't take your Chuckle, man! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 23:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 04:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big Yerry is making a big mistake Yerry  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 04:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jerry! Hello! Jerry! Somebody answer that damn phone!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 03:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen that one but it sounds hilarious. Did you see the clip recently where they accidentally cut back to Rob Ray at the wrong time during a game and he had a hot dog halfway down his throat? 

EDIT: HOT DOG PIC http://i.imgur.com/eeb5Ytt.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Still the best video on YouTube </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 00:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 23:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone got it! The foul I found was mostly the atrocious stitching job on the guys otherwise blank jersey. Looks like a child did the work for a class project.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 11:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There definitely was. When I was coming back to my seat during a Rangers goal I thought it was a Sabres goal from the amount of cheering.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
