<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7184</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry that you've decided to leave.  I feel like you should keep at least a little bit for yourself in case you decide to come back.  B/c I thought I was gone forever and yet I came back almost 8 years later xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  I got a couple of 3 leaf clovers :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I upvote b/c he's so witty and charming and knowledgeable ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But seriously, all the things you mentioned is annoying af.  Loud chewing/slurping can you please stfu!!  Omgggggg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welll...I am just going to sit here...cutting these onions at my desk.  Yep....onions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not entirely sure at 10 I'd be able to form a cognitive thought process if I was in this situation.  Interesting experiment, though, this game.  I wonder if the kidnappers were ever caught. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was dying to know just which kevin had passed away at this point.

Sooo umm.  Little did you know....

OP, please update! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once you go Ben, you end up in a wheelchair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only tell you what we did, and what worked for us.  We did a modified CIO.  At 8pm, I give BabySpawn a bath, wash him and let him play a little.  I'd dress him in PJs and give him a bottle with the lights all out in his room, just the hallway light on so I could see.  After that, he'd be in that "drowsy but awake" mode.  I'd sing Twinkle Twinkle Little Star to him while I burped him, kissed him, then laid him in his crib, turned on a white noise machine, and said goodnight.  The first couple nights we waited 5 min before going in and reassuring him, patting his back, etc but not picking him back up.  Then we waited 10 minutes for a couple nights, repeat.  Then we waited 15 minutes.  That was only one night, b/c after about 2 weeks, he didn't even make it until 15 min, he'd fall asleep and mostly sleep through the night (except a week or two when he only wanted a nighttime bottle, which we'd just give him and he'd fall asleep very quickly after this.  I guess maybe it was during growth spurts, but now that he's getting table food, he grew out of it on his own.)

Now, at almost 15 months he doesn't get the right-before-bed-bottle anymore.  So when I put him down he kind of lays there talking to himself or playing with his stuffed animals and falls asleep on his own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  He eats what we eat for dinner.  Luckily he hasn't refused anything, but I can definitely see what his favourites are.  I will not cook a completely separate meal for BabySpawn.  But, for example, if down the line he doesn't like breaded chicken, but the rest of us do, I will make a couple pieces plain for him and breaded for the rest of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Love and hugs*

There's nothing wrong with needing that to help you get through life!!  And hey, you're about to drop 4!!  That's AWESOME!  You can do itttttt!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *All* addiction is sad.  Heroin, alcohol, video games, eating, whatever.  It's one thing when it's only affecting the person using, but when family is involved, it's that much more heartbreaking.  I am so sorry for you, OP.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand.  Before and during pregnancy I said I wanted 3 kids.  I guess I didn't realize how hard having a baby actually is.  BabySpawn is a pretty awesome, laid back baby, but he still needed things at all hours of the night/day in the beginning and oh gods I was not prepared for the amount of no sleep I'd be getting.  I even had a very decent support system, but, I'd lament, where were they at 3am?  Minutes and hours and days dragged on.  I dreamed about running away and disappearing.  (I wish to gods I'd known about Reddit back then; might have saved myself some tears, I think, b/c even though I wanted to talk about these feelings, I just couldn't form the words.)  I was a definite "no" to having more kids then.

But now, over a year later, we've gotten into a "groove" of sorts and I know things will still be harder at times, I feel like I could entertain the thought of having possibly one other Spawn-Kid.  I also know how I felt after BabySpawn, so I will be able to talk to my doctors and let them know about it before it gets "too hard" to talk to people.

My point is that, you might think you want one now, and that thought may not change.  That's fine.  But, in time, you might also rethink it.  That's also fine.  Whatever choice you make, it will be what's best for you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great idea, too, seeing an nutritionist.  You *can* eat that little, but it has to be the right proportions.  I kind of do something like OP does and I have a lot of success, but I also saw a doctor, had bloodwork, etc, before and now during. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trade you the soda bread for your corned beef :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would wait until he's better before you try any kind of schedule setting.

Are you bottle or breast feeding?  Are you willing to sleep train?  Are you for or against some kind of cry it out (CIO)?  These are questions you're going to need to answer before looking for a solution.  Different things work for different people in different amounts of time, but no matter what you decide, the key is **constancy**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I would get a second opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't understand this.  It's "not normal" to be careful and get things checked out that are worrying you?  Let's just *say* there's nothing wrong.  If it makes you feel better to go and get everything looked at, literally what's the harm in that?  Ffs, he sounds like an asshat.  Sorry you're dealing with this :(  *Internet Hugs* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would someone who bought a duped item be responsible?  How can you know you are (possibly) buying a duped item? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the meantime, make sure you provide proof of shipping to get your credits back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked how the novels tie into the expansions themselves.  I understand your feeling completely :)  Probably the Culling of Stratholme was my fav "read in the book then got to play it" experience.  But I really enjoyed that Lich King storyline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to throw in here that Christie Golden is a great author in general.  She's one of my favs.  Check out her other novels, too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are Alliance US, I will run things with you, carry you through my lower keys.  Add me - GoldenStar#1424 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's rude/wrong if you make it clear that you're asking for a carry.  You could also try to find a carry group yourself.  Those are usually 4 people looking for a specific + instance to run you through, mostly to farm AP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the game!!

You will want to check out /r/wownoob to get yourself into the game :)  Pretty much every class is viable end-game.  And it's far easier to level if you instance grind.  (That is, queue for instances and run through those over and over with 4 other random people.)

You should decide what you want your role to be.  Tank, heals, dps.  Then go from there.  Check out www.icy-veins.com, too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is kind of a way you can kill 2-3 bosses single target, then 2-3 AOE bosses, so you only have to change a few times.  Also if you have a lock, you can hearth out and change then be summoned back relatively quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried to update you drivers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if it's OP that's not quite right.  After all, why didn't her parents seem to know who she's talking about?  Plus, idk, something just was odd about OP only seeing work friends but nobody from her past.  Maybe OP is the robot?  She doesn't remember meeting her boyfriend b/c she doesn't have those memories programmed....omg what if she's an AI experiment?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We use the [Graco 4ever All-In-One](https://www.amazon.com/Graco-4ever-All-Convertible-Matrix/dp/B00Y2863GQ/) and so far, it's great :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm, that actually settles my mind a bit.  The carseat in my car was expensive, and my husband was hesitant to spend so much for 1 for his car b/c he rarely has BabySpawn in there.  He talked about a cheap carseat and I was like OMG NO IT WONT BE SAFE...I guess I might have been wrong :x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though I am not there yet (but will be this summer) I would imagine that having her in her own room might help a bit.  Once we moved BabySpawn to his own room, everyone slept 1,000% better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> !RemindMe 5 Hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have a great time!

(Also, you are into Wheel of Time and I don't think you commented on the D D thread!  Go check it out!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you need any dps to help you out, add me:  GoldenStar#1424

I'm 897, and I don't mind if you are slow/new/undergeared lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome.  Happy to see some positive experiences instead of negative :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A while back in 2012.  I can't remember back that far, either =/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relax and get all the rest you can :)  Feel better soon!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol better safe than sorry.  You never know.  xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, no I didn't actually do this :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously the one I mentioned above and the ones you mentioned are part of the Meta Achievement ;)

Kidding aside, I enforce this rule on myself.  I can't play unless I complete 'Insert Chore Here' b/c I know I won't ever do said chore if I log in.  I'm done for the day.  Rarely will I walk away bored.  It's been a long road but I know that I have to take care of my house/family somewhat before I zone out for the rest of the night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except, if she's enjoying playing why should she have to give it up?  Just don't play with him and go your own ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Achievement Unlocked!

Get Husband to do his chores before raid time.

0/10 Chores Remain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU...It's My Fault! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our area was hit with a snowstorm.  (As I'm sure you may have heard.)  It started as snow, but changed to ice, so everything has a good coating.  So, the neighbour's tree branch snapped and fell on our deck.  Husband starts ranting about how he should have just cut all the branches hanging over our property down (though the offending branch wasn't over our property; it's just how it snapped and the wind blew), how the house is "endangered" and how he's SO MAD ABOUT THE DAMAGE.  (Thankfully there's none.  Maybe a scratch or two on the deck that we almost never use.  Oh, no! /s)  Also the neighbour came over and apologized, offered to help us move the branches off our deck if we needed it, etc.  Literally not a big deal.

Then, he decides he wants to drive me to work b/c it's so icy, which I do appreciate b/c even though the streets are mostly clear, I haven't had my license for very long and I am a bit uncomfortable.

SO THIS MEANS NOW that he has to clean off both cars and shovel the whole walkway and driveway.  For some reason.  So that makes me even later.  And apparently my trying to help is just getting in the way.  Welp, I will 100% never offer to help you again, even if you were dying.  Okay...In the meantime, a small branch falls from one of our trees onto our roof.  WELL NOW SHIT - it's all my fault b/c I didn't want to cut the tree down and now the roof is "destroyed" and "leaking" - I very highly doubt this is the case, b/c last summer we cut down all the big branches.  e_e  BUT IT'S MY FAULT FOR WANTING TO KEEP THE TREE THERE B/C I DIDN'T WANT SPEND ANOTHER $800.00 on a perfectly healthy tree! YES!

Proceeds to drive me (  BabySpawn, lest we forget) to work, cursing the whole way.  Demanding to know how I will remove the branch from the roof, b/c since this is MY FAULT I will be the one to take care of it.  (Okay, I'm not scared,  I will climb up there tonight if it's SO important.)  Meanwhile he's driving and not cleaning off the windshield, tailgating, trying to do 50 - um, the roads are clear but they are very slippy and wet and other drivers are going slow.  We almost rear-ended a truck and there was NO reason for it.

But yeah, I'm endangering BabySpawn but not cutting down that tree.  You know, not the person literally freaking out for almost no reason and driving like a douche bag.  And tonight I'm quite sure he's going to ask for a blow job.  Nah, bro.  I'm mad enough to bite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :o

I'd play Neopets Go!!  I'm pretty sure most of the older, now-adult Neo players may be interested, and it could help attract a newer crowd, too.  I'm guessing b/c there hasn't been anything like this developed, JumpStart doesn't care to expand on Neopets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :o

If you're still doing this, please draw [Stolen_Dreamer](http://www.neopets.com/petlookup.phtml?pet=Stolen_Dreamer).  Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GL with getting it back.

I lost my main in the pw debacle but I was able to get it back in about a month, though a lot of that lost time was my fault.  Just be patient, KIND, and provide as much information as you can.  Chances are if you are innocent of any wrongdoing you will get it back :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I would not have guessed that was her at all.  Also I always pronounced her name "Puh-sell-ah" which is apparently very wrong xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am pretty much you, except I quit for WoW.

I think at this point Neopets would need a mobile app at the very least to tie into the website.  It needs more site events, too, where you'd use said mobile app as well as the website itself to complete objectives.

I do not think it will ever be the same again, but we can dream, can't we :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats!

Also that first item kind of looks good lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I came here to say was that sometimes when you order from Amazon and it comes from overseas, you do not get a tracking number.  They give you a very broad range of when it can be delivered, too, but I haven't had an issue with delivery itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BabySpawn is still a bit of a ways off for this, but I imagine that I will help him, as my parents helped me in my time.  If my kid wants some ideas on how to get started, we could brainstorm together.  If he wants help with the layouts of the poster board, I will show him how to plan it out on a bit of scrap, then have him go on the final product.  He will type his own paper, but I will proofread it, then show him where he needs to correct it, and why it isn't correct grammatically.  I don't want to leave him completely on his own, especially when he's young, but I don't want to do the whole thing for him, either.  I also image the older he gets, the less he will need/want my help, and that's okay, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then why, when I delete my comments, do I not see a [deleted] there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beast Mastery Hunter.

I play too much WoW.  *Runs and hides* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I always thought.  It literally made no sense to me "for the farmers" - I always thought, get up when you need to, why does the time matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh me, too.  I used to do this when I lived at home but now, I fantasize about someone doing it for me that much :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I change our bedsheets every month (unless for some reason they get gross), and BabySpawn's every 2 weeks unless he pees through his diaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -Why does it sometimes say "3 comments" but there's only 1, or sometimes none?

-What's the difference between [removed] and [deleted]? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ipsy.  You get some expensive makeup for incredibly cheap.  It's good for me b/c I don't want to spend a lot, but I like to look pretty sometimes :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pay my bills.  I'm not exciting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey if you're US, send me a message.  I will run the things with you, or start a new toon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should check out /r/wownoob for most things =)

Also look at icy-veins.com for your talents, gearing, and rotation.

If you want a leveling buddy and you're US, feel free to PM me or answer here.  I love making newbie toons.

PS - Shaman master class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize how faulty that logic is, right?

Okay, you messed up.  Stop doing the bad thing.  You may have escaped notice.  Worry about it when/if you get banned after that, but just don't continue doing it.  Ignorance isn't an excuse, but if you stop now, you might avoid future issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope so; I quite enjoyed his plotline and I would love to see where it goes from here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for helping to build my army! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% all star cast here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So then a "World of Warcraft" theme is possible?  I'm going to suggest this once I'm an Elf again, so I won't if it's not lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All games.  Literally ALL the games.  B/c 1 day BabySpawn will be a teenager and he will not need me to be around 24/7 (bittersweet!) and I will need to know some cool games to occupy my time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no!  I hope Toddler is feeling better today.  I added you (if that's your numbers, lol) so hopefully see you on soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given 101 Cheese Slices to User 'hollywoodshowbox'. Click the button below to continue.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, thanks a ton! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Crypt of Chance Scratchcard to User 'andromedric'. Click the button below to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Blue Conch Shell to User 'b02l23p88'. Click the button below to continue.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Warf to User 'panikingdisco'. Click the button below to continue.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Long Headed Collectable Scarab to User 'timeforpetz'. Click the button below to continue.

This thing is going to give me nightmares. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.  I don't want to think about the whys of this xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Crypt of Chance Scratchcard to User 'vulpix45'. Click the button below to continue.

A little something to help you get your map pieces! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Circlet of the Deep, Bangles of the Deep, Hairpin of the Deep, Necklace of the Deep,   Earrings of the Deep to User 'spazedout601'. Click the button below to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  Yes it is!!  All those puppets are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Zytch Scratching Post to User 'mysterykitty390'. Click the button below to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have given Crypt of Chance Scratchcard to User 'ladyluck_xx'. Click the button below to continue.

x2

Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noooo Penny Arcade is the BEST. I have a print of one of the WoW comics.  And my brother bought me the PhotoShop Hero t-shirt.  I swear nobody cool lives in NJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well first things first, see if he's on board and what he is willing to run.  Then we can just all join up someplace in a chat room and talk about it.  Or maybe make another post.  Yeah, let's do that...I can make an update post if he's down.  We can figure out what day, how often, etc.  I don't mind organizing that, I just def do not want to run the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that def sounds like a game I can never buy b/c RIP my already mediocre social life lololol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should take a peak at Legion.  It's just....everything.  It's the best xpac so far.  Lol, everyone either loves or hates the Pandas.  I really liked them and I just thought the zones were gorgeous af. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, seriously, 10/10 would be interested.  I'm very familiar with 2nd ed, and fluent w/ 3.5 - anything else I have no books/knowledge of but I'm not afraid to learn if someone teaches me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm both excited and afraid of the day my BabySpawn should decide he wants to play xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just going to leave my B-Tag here if you want to add me.  I love the WoWz.:

GoldenStar#1424 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't played this since grade school, but I do miss it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Roll20 has a really good text chat feature, so you wouldn't *have* to be on voice/Skype. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We could use Roll20 for the game, and Skype for the voice.  I've done that in the past and it worked out well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be surprised at how much you remember.  It's all D20, baby ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I played Diablo III the most, though I haven't played it much lately.  Still a great game, though. WoW has become quite a bit like it in many regards, esp with the way gear is handed out in some ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Persona 5 like the Sims?  I've never heard of that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I would play this game for 90% of my day, based on Aari_G's comment :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm completely in awe of this...

I was in a guild once where, long story short this hunter was always on, talked about how he was excited to be going on the first date w/ this girl he really liked.  Logged off that night and was gone for 2 weeks.  We laughed and said they ran away together.  Turns out he actually got into a severe car accident and almost died :/  We didn't kick him.  He was our hero after that.

I'm glad you dodged a bullet here, though!  I hope you found a nicer guild, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if you're willing to talk about xmogs with us :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg AND you like Sailor Moon?  Please join us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, we're all grills here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dungeons and Dragons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a comment on someone's post and it actually got some attention so I wanted to make a thing.  I don't have any mama friends in my area that play video games and Dungeons   Dragons.  I KNOW YOU ARE OUT THERE.  But for now, all us should assemble.  Who's interested? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you know, since he gets time to make it in the evenings, and I get to chase the baby

That's so not fair.  You also deserve you time.  This is prob my #1 pet peeve omgggg but I'm just going to leave it at that.

I think it's great that you have a plan for this weekend.  Hopefully he will be receptive and open to listening to you.  As far as meal prep/diet - personally I hate it, but it is so helpful in losing weight that I suffer for an hour every Sunday to get lunches ready for me and my husband lol.

I lost 30 lbs in about 4.5 months through diet alone.  (I don't have time to go to the gym currently, though with BabySpawn now getting older, I'm going to see about fitting it into my schedule.)  If you're interested in hearing what I did, please send me a message.  If not, that's okay too.  I am sending you good vibes and support hugs.  You got this, mama :D :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can your husband/SO take the kiddos off your hands for a few hours during the morning/night to give you a break?  A friend?  Neighbour? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.)  Accept the fact that after you have the baby, holding your pee will be next to impossible.  You can work on this, but it's still going to happen.

2.)  You can (and should) making noises around your sleeping baby.  I was afraid I'd breathe too loudly and wake him up.  That never happened xD  I was afraid to turn the TV up when BabySpawn was upstairs sleeping.  Behind a closed door.  You can turn the TV up w/in hearing range.  You won't wake your baby up :P

3.)  Get out and walk around when you are able.  Helped me feel better, helped shake off some depression.

4.)  Don't feel guilty about leaving your baby.  You *NEED* time away.  It will make you a better person, I promise you this.  Try to keep up with 1 or 2 hobbies that you enjoy.  It will help you keep your sanity.

5.)  Your whole view on life will shift in a way that I can't explain.  You will know what I mean one day out of the blue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> J - June bugs, Juniper, Jalapenos

K - Katniss, Kale, Kiwi

N - Nettles, Nectarines

U - Urn plants, Unicorn plant

Some of these I got from [this site](https://www.gardeningknowhow.com/special/children/alphabet-garden-plants.htm) so check it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't have a good answer for this one.  Well, I do have a good one but it's NSFW at all.  I mean, I can post that if nobody will be mad.  It involves a body orifice.  I guess I'll leave it at that.

**Gifting:**  Wistlists

**Seeking:**  [My Wishlist](http://items.jellyneo.net/mywishes/stealing_heaven), Nerkmids, Magic Ghost Marshmallows, Random Silliness, Active Neofriends

**User Name:**  Stealing_Heaven

PS - As always, I will be gifting after work today :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I don't see anything wrong with posting here b/c it's not associated with Neopets at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
