<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9825</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 09:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I do. He...

1. Thinks that illegal immigrants should have a right to stay if they've been working hard and following the law, and that deporting them is a ludicrous idea

2. Thinks that we should support the rebels in Syria, but not directly involve ourselves

3. Thinks that we should cooperate with both European and Middle Eastern countries to defeat ISIS

4. Thinks that the US should stay a firm ally of Israel

5. Seems unclear on Obamacare as the Republican rhetoric is firmly towards repealing it, but wants to expand Medicare and Medicaid

6. Believes that man-made climate change is a threat and supports renewable energy, although not aggressively

7. Seems to err on the side of drug treatment rather than punishment, predictable rhetoric about bringing police and communities together

But I suppose you're one of those people who will point to his stance on abortion and say that one decision out of decades in government makes him a right wing radical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 09:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kasich was like, the *most* moderate guy this election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 07:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did I say people? The UNITED STATES is a UNION of STATES, and 57% of the Electoral VOTES voted for Trump.

And I didn't vote for Trump. Asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 04:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. That would be a bit of a reach for this election but not impossible. Trump swung many former blue states by mid-10 points. His largest was a 19 point swing. A stretch, but by no means impossible for this election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 02:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Hillary was a joke of a candidate. If she lost to Trump I don't see how California within 8 is so far out of the realm of possibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 02:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [57% of the nation voted for Trump](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ec/ElectoralCollege2016.svg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe Biden said he may run for President in 2020? Could he win the nomination? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 02:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 02:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was born in 1942... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 01:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Voter turnout wasn't low. It was about average (mid 50%) since the last 10 elections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 01:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  20 years ago isn't that far away.

20 years is an eternity in politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 00:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 00:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think their religion will have much of an impact. It'll be some minor trivia in the history books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 22:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Davos is *obviously* Azor Ahai. Azor Ahai was able to fight off the Long Night. The Moon is the symbol of night. Therefore, Davos beats Moonknight 10/10 onionstomp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Crumb - House of the Rising Sun [Eclecticism] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 20:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's about time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 20:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Republicans from sure win states like NY and California often failed to go out to vote, and Democrats from sure win states like Texas had the same phenomenon.

Adding to that, the [Senate election in California didn't even have a Republican running](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_Senate_election_in_California,_2016). Would a Republican on the ballot have motivated 2.5 million more Republicans to vote in California? Who knows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 20:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  54% of voters did not vote for the Republican presidential candidate.
 It is obvious that the nation did not want a Republican President.

By that same logic more than half the nation didn't want a Democratic President. We have the system we have, and the nation through that system voted overwhelmingly for Donald Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 20:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it is obvious that the Republicans won under the current system

So the system that matters? Great I'm glad you agree with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 20:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention that a lot more Republicans in California would have gone out to vote [if there had been a Republican in the Senate election](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_Senate_election_in_California,_2016). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were too tricky for your own good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bush campaigned on a platform of non-interventionism and education reform. It is likely that he gets most of his plans done (tax cuts, NCLB). Likely 1-term, losing to Gore, who according to rumors would have run again had it not been for 9/11.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MIKE LOU AND OG ^on ^the ^island MIKE LOU AND OG ^pretty ^island </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. The GOP controls every area of government. It is obvious that the nation wants this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 05:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Court not being full is not destructive. There have been vacancies for far longer periods of time than this. Try again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We just elected a man who's main platform involved building a wall and deporting every illegal alien.

This will go nowhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 03:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOOK WHAT YOU DID, YOU LITTLE JERK! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine saying that 75 years ago lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morally? I would object. Legally? I wouldn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some things are too important to be left up to the states, like the Civil Rights Act.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all. We need a federal government. However, I believe their power should be greatly reduced. If they *CHOOSE*, however, to only meet once a year, I'm not going to object. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Hillary intentionally try to win without "straight white men" to make a statement, and could it have cost her the election? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will be her legacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The GOP was able to ride that wave all the way to 2016, in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton ran on a "New Democrat" platform in 1992, but after Hillarycare failed in 1994 (right before the midterms) the GOP was successfully able to brand him and Hillary as "tax and spend" liberals and basically made the midterms "a referendum on big government". Basically the American people didn't want what the Clintons were pushing and Gingrich was able to capitalize on that heavily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Hillary Clinton is probably the worst candidate to ever run as a major party nominee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Congress only wants to meet 1 day a year I have no problem with it. I'd prefer if Congress (and the Federal Government in general) did less. If people have a problem with their reps only working 1 day a year then they'll vote them out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But you can't approve a nominee unless you vote. The Senate failed to do it's job.

Yeah. So they do not approve. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They definitely should in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah if the Senate doesn't want it they can block it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You forgot Italy"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE OTHER ITALY!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but you and I both know that if Garland didn't get even get a vote, no one else would either.

Again, the Senate is totally within their right to not hold a vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama can withdraw Garland and nominate someone else whenever he wants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so let's *say* it doesn't mean yes or no. They are still allowed to do that. They are under no obligation to hold a vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the Senate isn't under any constitutional obligation to hold hearings or vote on a nominee

OK great we're done here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not voting means no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vox? Really? What, was Buzzfeed not turning anything up?

http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2015/01/05/the_myth_of_democrats_20-million-vote_majority_125145.html

This was included in your link but I doubt you read it.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_Senate_elections,_2014

That article is a farce. The GOP received ~4,000,000 more votes in 2014. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please explain why not voting when the outcome would be a definite no is different from not voting at all.

I'll save you the effort and just tell you. They aren't. The Senate is under no obligation to hold a vote. They are not a rubber-stamp. They are Constitutionally SUPPOSED to do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can disagree all you want. It doesn't make you right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They must vote to approve. ANYTHING ELSE means they do not approve. If they approved, they would vote. Please show me where it is said in the Constitution that a vote must be held.

I'll wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For *THE SENATE*, not voting does equal no. It is in the Constitution that they must have a majority vote YES.

For *PEOPLE VOTING IN ELECTIONS*, that is not the case. If 1 person voted in Alaska, that guy would decide where the EC votes go. They are in no way equivalent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is in no way the same and you know it. Please form an actual argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the 2014 midterms. You know, what the current Senate is based off of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The job of the Senate is to "advice and consent" to a nominee. It is not to rubber-stamp the President's nominee. Checks and balances and all that, as I'm sure you know. 

Obama's job is to nominate. He did that. The GOP in no way blocked his ability to do that. If you disagree with that statement please show me how I am wrong.

The Senate's job is to approve of a nominee. They are under no obligation to hold a vote. If you disagree with that statement, please point out where in the Constitution it says that they MUST hold a vote for any and all nominees, because I'd love to see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brexit "Something this important shouldn't be decided by the popular vote! People are too stupid to realize what this all means!" Trump Loses Popular Vote but Wins EC "How can we allow this injustice to stand?! We must abolish the EC and use only the popular vote going forward!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 07:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you pass out during the pregame but still manage to make it to the party. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 03:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> States Where a 3rd Party Candidate Received 5% of the Vote in the 2016 Election [OC] [1526x1195] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 02:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does experience really matter in regards to the Presidency? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 23:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is common to talk about how "experienced" or "qualified" a candidate is during election season. For example, this year, Hillary was commonly called "one of the most experienced and qualified candidates", and a common criticism of Trump was that he had no experience in government. But looking back over at least the last century, experience before taking office has seemed to have no bearing on the quality of a Presidency nor the ability to do the job.

FDR is commonly considered to be one of the greatest presidents of all time, being elected 4 times in landslides and seeing our nation through the Great Depression and WWII. However, his only governmental experience prior to this was 2 years in the New York Senate and 4 years as Governor of New York.

Lincoln was our greatest president. He ended slavery and won the Civil War. He served 1 term in the House over *10 years* before he was elected and spent 8 years in the Illinois House before that.

Eisenhower had no governmental experience whatsoever before he was elected. Despite this, he is commonly cited by both parties as one of the greatest presidents of the 20th century.

Ford spent 24 years in the House, 8 of which were as the Minority Leader, and spent 8 months as VP, but he is generally regarded as a very lackluster and ineffective President.

There are more examples, but I'll stop there. So, does experience really play that big of a role in how well the President is able to do his job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Like Ike (1952) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Ted Kennedy have beaten Ronald Reagan in 1980? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 1980 Senator Ted Kennedy ran a brutal campaign against incumbent Jimmy Carter, who was as historic levels of unpopularity. Despite Carter leading through most of the primary, Kennedy was able to win several key states, and refused to concede until the penultimate day of the DNC. To this day it remains the last time an incumbent president has faced a serious primary challenge, with Carter winning only 36 states and 51% of the popular vote.

Could Kennedy have beaten Ronald Reagan, who at the time was considered so extreme that John Anderson won 6.6% of the vote as a "moderate alternative" to Reagan? Or was the Democrat brand tainted by Carter so much that Reagan could have beaten any Democrat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I hear California wants to secede from the Union. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 18:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dow ends near record highs following election of Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dow Jones up 200 Points in First Day of Post-Election Trading </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who will be the next leader of the Democratic Party? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 16:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something interesting I heard watching the results come in last night is that there is no consensus on who the next leader of the Democratic Party will be. Obama and Biden are on their way out. Hillary is irrelevant after last night. Harry Reid is retiring. Bernie Sanders is an Independent. Who will step up to lead the party after Trump takes office? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is next for the Democratic Party? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if Virginia, North Carolina, Arkansas, and Tennessee did not secede after the Battle of Fort Sumter, and the Confederacy was only made up of the original 7 states? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 21:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if the four states that joined the Confederacy after its formation had remained in the Union? How much faster would the Civil War have ended? How would the history of these states and the US in general change after the War? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why has the fact that a former president could be back in the White House not been brought up more in regards to Hillary's campaign? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When my friend tells me his SO of 2 months wants them to get a shared Facebook account. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 05:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Steve Bartman Incident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 06:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did the Republican Revolution not extend to the 1996 election? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 23:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 1931 film "Frankenstein" begins with a warning to the audience about how scary the film is. Was this just a marketing gimmick, or was the film actually considered frightening enough to warrant a warning compared to other contemporary horror films? (X-Post r/AskHistorians) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 19:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 1931 film "Frankenstein" begins with a warning to the audience about how scary the film is. Was this just a marketing gimmick, or was the film actually considered frightening enough to warrant a warning compared to other contemporary horror films? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 18:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the time *Frankenstein* was released in November 1931, there had been 3 other silent film adaptations of the Frankenstein novel. There had also been several other horror films released by Universal, including *The Phantom of the Opera* and *Dracula*. Was *Frankenstein* considered so much more shocking that a warning was necessary to prepare the audience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did the Reform Party die off? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 1992 Ross Perot ran as an Independent and won 18.9% of the vote, an unprecedented amount of support for a 3rd party candidate. The only 3rd party candidates to achieve a higher level of support were Fillmore in 1856 and Roosevelt in 1912, and both had previously served as President under different parties so they had at least some "street cred" in the election. After creating the official Reform Party he ran again in 1996, winning 8.4% of the vote despite not even appearing in the debates like his previous run. 

Based on these performances, it is clear that a significant portion of the American electorate aligned themselves with Perot's political views and those of the Reform Party. So how did the Reform Party go from such a strong performance in 1996 to winning only 0.4% in the 2000 election, a mere 4 years later? Was the Party too focused on Perot himself that nobody else could successfully represent them? Was Perot's success in 1992 a one time thing, with his 1996 voters merely holdover support from his earlier run? Or did people just realize that in a FPTP system 3rd parties have almost no chance and Reform Party voters moved on to the main 2 parties? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did Ralph Nader win such a high percentage of the vote in 2000? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2000, Green Party candidate Ralph Nader famously won 2.74% of the popular vote. While that seems like almost nothing, since 1928 only 3 Third Party candidates have won higher percentage totals than that: George Wallace in 1968 (13.5%), John B. Anderson in 1980 (6.6%), and Ross Perot in both 1992 and 1996 (18.9% and 8.4%). And since 2000, Third Parties have come nowhere close to Nader's numbers. The highest total seen since then was Gary Johnson in 2012 with 0.99%, still 1% of the vote. So how was Ralph Nader able to win such an abnormally high percentage of the vote for a Third Party candidate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Halloweentown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 22:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ASoIaF] I'm a Prince of the Summer Isles. Today several Westerosi arrived in my court clamoring about ice demons from the far north. Should I be worried? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 22:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So today I was sitting in court when some of my advisors bring me several Westerosi knights from the North. They started telling me about these ice demons that can raise the dead and are primed to invade and destroy the entire continent and they're trying to get as far south as they can. Should I be worried about this? My people conduct a fair bit of trade with Westeros, and I don't want to see that interrupted. The knights also said these demons can bring bitter cold and storms. Will my people and I be safe this far south? I just want to be prepared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [The Truman Show] I was just offered a job on The Truman Show. Should I take it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. So I've had a few minor acting gigs so far, and after one of them a producer pretty high up in the TS said he really liked me and offered me a chance to audition for the show. I obviously said yes and everyone there seemed to really like me. I even got a chance to audition in front of Christof himself. I finally heard back from them today and they said they wanted me on the show! They offered me a part as one of Truman's co-workers, which is way more than I expected. I didn't think I'd be talking to Truman every day. So obviously I'm excited and want to do it, but I don't want to make any hasty decisions, because this could effect the rest of my life. They haven't gotten back to me with an exact contract yet, but I have a few questions. Will I need to live in the Dome 24/7? Will I need to do any actual insurance work, or just pretend? Am I guaranteed housing on the island indefinitely? Will my friends and family be able to visit me on the island? What do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The end scene of Lost's Season 3 Finale, Through the Looking Glass [Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 01:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Amanda Show: Bush v. Gore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 01:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would a Trump win in November represent a complete rejection of the current Democratic Party by the nation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's no secret that Hillary Clinton is the favorite to win in November. Donald Trump, though, still has a not-insignificant chance of winning, with betting sites and political pundits putting his chances between 1/5 to 1/3. Trump only became a "politician" about a year ago, and is despised by a large portion of the electorate. Clinton has arguably been preparing for this election for decades. Taking this all into account, would Hillary Clinton, arguably the most famous woman politician in the world, losing the Presidential election to Donald Trump of all people signal a complete failure of the Democratic Party nationally?

When the Democrats took both the Senate and the House in 2006 and Barack Obama won the Presidency in 2008, people predicted a period of complete Democratic domination, famously mentioned in James Carville's 2009 book, *40 More Years: How the Democrats Will Rule the Next Generation*. A year and a half later the Republicans made the largest gains in the House since 1938, and today they hold the Senate, House, and the majority of State Legislatures and Governorships. The "Democratic Domination" period hasn't come to fruition, and it seems to be going in the opposite direction. Should Trump win in November, would it mean that the Democratic Party needs to abandon their current platform? Would they double down on the "New Democrat" centrist policies, or begin to cater more to the progressive wing of their party? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [E.T.] What did we learn from the tests on E.T.? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 03:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though E.T. was only tested for a short amount of time, the tests were extensive. One major discovery that was made was that his species' DNA was made up of 6 nucleotides instead of 4 like ours is. What were we able to do with that information? Were we able to discover how his species can telepathically link with others, or resurrect themselves? What applications have these discoveries had in the past 3 decades? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's next for the Muppets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 03:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Muppets are some of the most recognizable characters in entertainment. Everyone knows who Kermit the Frog, Miss Piggy, and Fozzie Bear are. But in recent years their popularity seems to have been waning. From 1999-2011, the Muppets had 2 TV films, the last of which was in 2005. Contrast that with 1976-1999 where they had 6 theatrical films and 5 TV series. That's a very noticeable decline.

After Disney bought the rights to the Muppets in 2004 they really tried to push the characters back into the spotlight, notably with the Bohemian Rhapsody music video, and the 2011 film *The Muppets* was a critical and commercial success, grossing over 160 million dollars and becoming the only one of the 8 Muppet films to win an Academy Award. This excited me, because the Muppet films were some of my favorite movies growing up, and I thought this would be the start of a new era for the Muppets under Disney leadership, much like how they took control of Marvel, and now Star Wars. But the next film, *Muppets Most Wanted*, was far more *meh* than the last film and grossed less than half of what *The Muppets* did. The new TV show also received lukewarm reviews and was cancelled after only one season, leaving me thinking the 2011 film was just a fluke.

This begs the question: do the Muppets have any place in entertainment today? Will they be a curious relic of the past, or will they evolve and become relevant again?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What characters can solo their teams? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 01:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which characters would be able to go up against every other member of their team at once and come out on top at least 6/10 times?

Examples:

Aang would be able to solo Team Avatar.

Goku (at several points in time) would be able to solo the Z-Fighters.

Batman would be able to solo the Justice League ;). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can L [Death Note] prove that Ted Cruz is the Zodiac Killer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 16:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would Bush v. Gore be as controversial if George Bush won the popular vote? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 03:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's no secret that many people think George W. Bush "stole" the 2000 election, but when asked why they thought that, people generally have two points: more people voted for Al Gore, and Florida was "decided by one vote" by the Supreme Court in *Bush v. Gore*. But these two points really don't have much to do with each other, and are separate issues. Had Bush decisively won the popular vote, would *Bush v. Gore* be as controversial? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Ronald Reagan have beaten Jimmy Carter in the 1976 election? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 01:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incumbent Gerald Ford was [just barely](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Republican_Party_presidential_primaries,_1976) able to beat back opposition from Ronald Reagan to become the Republican nominee, and was very narrowly defeated by Jimmy Carter in the [1976 election](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_presidential_election,_1976), losing by 2.1% in the popular vote and by 57 electoral votes. He was even only the second, and to date last, losing candidate to win a majority of states. Would Reagan, without the post-Watergate controversies that Ford had (pardoning Nixon, etc.), have been able to defeat Carter? If so, how would a Reagan presidency coming 4 years earlier have effected the nation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Comic/Show Spoilers] Something good that came out of the finale. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 04:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the scariest movies to watch as a group? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 07:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a group of like 8 or so 19-20 year olds, what are some movies to watch as a group that will really scare us? Lights off, middle of the night, in a small room. We've tried watching a few (Scream, Children of the Corn), but those weren't really scary because they were cheesy/humorous enough that we had fun picking them apart. What are some that can still effectively scare a group of college-aged kids? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A T-800 is loose in San Francisco. Can Rick Deckard stop it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 20:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skynet typed in the wrong date into the time machine and accidentally sent back the T-800 to 2019 San Francisco. Can the ex-Blade Runner 'retire' the T-800?

Round 1: The T-800 is searching for Sarah Connor (who doesn't exist in this timeline). Deckard must destroy it.

Round 2: The T-800 is searching for and trying to kill Rachael. Deckard must stop it before he kills her.

Round 3: The 4 Replicants (Roy, Leon, Pris, and Zhora) vs. the T-800.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [The Purge] Does the Purge follow time zones? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 17:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Purge lasts for 12 hours from 7 PM to 7 AM. But does it follow time zones? Like, if I lived right near the [border between Georgia and Alabama](http://www.nationsonline.org/maps/US-timezones.jpg), could I just drive into Alabama and be safe for an extra hour? If it doesn't follow time zones, what about the far western states? Does Hawaii's Purge just start in the middle of the day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ultron (MCU) replaces Neville Chamberlain in the Munich Agreement. Can he guarantee 'peace in our time'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 16:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ultron heads to Munich, Germany in place of British Prime Minister Nevill Chamberlain 1938 to attempt to appease Hitler. Will he be able successfully prevent WWII and create a *real* peace in our time?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I heard Netflix renewed Fuller House for a second season. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 01:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will politics in the US always get more progressive? If not, what social issues do you see people becoming more conservative towards in the future? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 00:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the past few years it seems like social issues have been getting more and more progressive. Marijuana legalization, gay marriage, they all seem to be moving to 'the left' at a rapid rate. In fact, a Gallup poll done in May 2015 showed that [about the same number of people identify themselves as socially liberal as do socially conservative](https://cmgajcjaybookman.files.wordpress.com/2015/05/5azgvxr0dumyypjuddtcqw.png).

So my question is, are there any social issues that people will become more conservative on? Or will public opinion always move toward the more progressive opinions? What do you think the future of social policy is in the United States? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MFW Fuller House was released. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 00:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would the Democrat Primary race look like now if Joe Biden had decided to run? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 01:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until he announced that he would not be entering the race in October, Biden was considered to be a major contender, at around 20% in the polls (according to RCP). He has since said that he 'regrets every day' that he didn't enter the race. So how might the race currently look had he decided to run? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would a 2nd place finish in Iowa mean for Rubio? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 18:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rubio has been surging in Iowa these past few days, and I've seen it mentioned around here that a 2nd place for him would be incredible for his campaign. But what exactly could he do with that momentum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the cause of Ben Carson's decline? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 01:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben Carson was until only about 2 months ago one of the frontrunners for the Republican nomination. He seemed to have exploded out of nowhere in September and kept a consistent 2nd place, and even surpassed Trump for a point. But then around November his numbers began to plummet, and is now in 4th place and is still falling. This is a stark contrast to the current top 3, who have either increased their support (Trump and Cruz), or have remained relatively stable (Rubio) during this same time period. What exactly caused him to lose so much support so quickly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Sanders wins both Iowa and New Hampshire, what does that mean for his campaign? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 23:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen it on here and in a few other subs that if Sanders loses Iowa his campaign is pretty much dead in the water, and I agree with that sentiment. However, if he manages to pull off a win in Iowa, and with New Hampshire all but guaranteed for him, where can he go from there. According to RCP's polls, Sanders has been slowly closing the gap between himself and Clinton in both South Carolina and Florida, but is still losing by a very wide margin. A win for him in the first 2 primary states against the 'inevitable' Clinton would certainly turn some heads. Would it be enough to sway more voters to his side and have him be seen as a viable alternative to Clinton, or would he not be able to gather the support? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve Irwin runs a Crocodile Ladder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 21:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve Irwin (in his prime) is trying to get some new footage for a special episode of *The Crocodile Hunter*, and has decided to film some of the rarest and most dangerous crocodiles he can find. In each round, he gets all of his gear, his film crew, and must subdue each opponent for at least 60 seconds while he talks about them.

Round 1: [Gustave the Crocodile](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gustave_(crocodile\))

Round 2: [Killer Croc](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Killer_Croc)

Round 3: [The Enormous Crocodile](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Enormous_Crocodile)

Round 4: [Tick Tock (2003)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dc6Gn1GCCOo)

Round 5: [Dinocroc](http://villains.wikia.com/wiki/Dinocroc)

Round 6: [Crocosaurus](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mega_Shark_Versus_Crocosaurus) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why have we not gotten any other Final Destination films? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 18:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Final Destination films were one of the most consistent franchises of the 2000s, with 5 films coming out between 2000 and 2011. While they received mostly mixed critical reception, they were huge hits at the box office, with 4/5 films making well over $100 million, and the series as a whole is still one of the highest-grossing horror franchises. With the final film (Final Destination 5, 2011) having the second highest box office gross and the best critical reception, it seems like it would make sense to make another. But as of now, there has been no sign of another sequel being made. It seems like it would be a no-brainer to me to make another one, and I would certainly like to see another. So why do you think we haven't gotten one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does 'The Blair Witch Project' still hold up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 05:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I first saw The Blair Witch Project when I was 10, and it scared the crap out of me. I thought it was real and those people really died, because it was the first found footage film that I ever saw. I saw it again a few years later in the middle of the whole found footage craze that  happened after 'Paranormal Activity', and it didn't have the same impact, but I attribute that mainly to me having known the ending already. A few of my friends and I are getting a horror movie night going where we each pick a movie, and I want to pick this one. Now that found footage is extremely commonplace, would the film still be scary to newcomers who have never seen it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The future of the the 'Evil Dead' franchise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 04:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Evil Dead series is among my favorite horror franchises. The original was, and still is, one of the scariest movies I've ever seen. The later 2 films are hilarious, and it was great to see Bruce Campbell back as Ash in the new TV series. I even loved the 2013 reboot film, which I think is criminally underrated. Prior to the announcement of *Ash vs. Evil Dead*, I remember both Rami and Campbell stating that there were plans for an Army of Darkness 2 and an Evil Dead ('13) 2, followed by a crossover that would merge the two narratives. But since then, Campbell has denied involvement in an Army of Darkness 2, and I have not heard any updates regarding the sequel to the 2013 film. With Ash vs. Evil Dead renewed for a season 2, and with no updates regarding the planned crossover, is it safe to assume that these plans have been put on hold indefinitely? Or might Ash vs. Evil Dead take the place of 'Army of Darkness 2' in the original plan?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ash Williams vs. Betelgeuse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 05:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ash Williams has accidentally summoned Betelgeuse, and now it's up to him to stop the Ghost with the Most from wreaking havoc on the mortal world. 

Round 1: Ash is once again in the cabin and needs to fight off Betelgeuse and survive the night. Can he do it, or will he be dead by dawn?

Round 2: Ash has the Necronomicon Ex-Mortis and must banish Betelgeuse from the mortal world. Is he able to?

Ash is post *Army of Darkness* but pre *Ash vs. Evil Dead*, and is armed with his chainsaw hand, mechanical hand, and booomstick. 

Betelgeuse is from directly prior to *Beetlejuice*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Speed Racer vs. Anakin Skywalker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 08:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anakin from Episode I and Speed from the Speed Racer film. Speed has the Mach Five and Anakin has his podracer.

Round 1: The track is the podrace track from Episode I.

Round 2: The track is the final racetrack in the Speed Racer film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the contemporary reaction to the 2000 election? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 00:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was born in late 1995, so I have pretty much no memory of the 2000 election, but from what I've heard there were a ton of varying opinions. Some people were outraged by the fact that Gore lost despite receiving more votes, others were mad about the *Bush v. Gore* decision, and others were indifferent because the president was chosen in the proper way (through the electoral college), and there was precedent of this type of thing happening. So what exactly was the reaction of the American people when all was said and done and Bush was officially chosen as the new president? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to RealClear Politics, Christie is now polling .2% ahead of Bush. What does this mean for the future of both of their campaigns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 02:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.realclearpolitics.com/epolls/2016/president/us/2016_republican_presidential_nomination-3823.html

Will Christie be able to widen his lead and gain a lot more support? Does this take Bush out of the race completely? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Harry Potter] Why does anyone bother locking their doors when there's an unlocking charm so easy a First Year can perform it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 21:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Alohomora' is presumably one of the easiest spells to cast, as it's in the *Standard Book of Spells* and First Years could use it successfully. So why does anyone bother locking their doors at all? There is a counter charm, but given the number of times alohomora has been used successfully, its obviously not that widespread. So why do wizards bother locking their doors when its so easy to bypass locks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heat Miser and Snow Miser vs. Storm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 02:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heat Miser and Snow Miser can use all feats from the 2 specials they've appeared in, and are willing to work together. Storm is the 616 version.

The fight takes place in the Midwestern United States in March. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bloodlusted The BFG vs. a 7 Meter Class Titan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 23:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In light of the [teaser for the new movie](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VG5MtenlP-A).

A 7 Meter Class Titan has eaten Sophie. This drives the BFG into an uncontrollable rage where he will stop at nothing to destroy the Titan. 

Fight takes place in the English Countryside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jimmy Neutron vs. The Kids Next Door </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 23:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The KND have won their war against the adults and have taken all adults on Earth (including Retroville's) captive in their Moon Base. Jimmy Neutron isn't having any of that, and has one week to come up with a plan to invade the Moon Base and get Retroville's parents back.

Combatants:

1. The Kids Next Door (Numbuhs 1-5)

2. Jimmy Neutron and Friends (from first movie)

Rounds:

1. Jimmy and Friends vs. KND

2. Jimmy and Friends have the help of the Delightful Children from Down the Lane. The KND have the help of the Yokians.

3. Same as Round 2 but Jimmy and Friends get Father and the KND get Professor Calamitous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Venom symbiote crashes in Eric Forman's basement and bonds with him. Can Red Forman manage to put his foot in Eric's ass before he destroys the town? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 00:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Velociraptor vs. Lion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 20:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A grown adult male velociraptor (Jurassic Park version) and a grown adult male African lion.

Round 1: On Isla Nublar.

Round 2: In the African savannah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 'Too Many Cooks' guy invades your favorite sitcom's intro. Do the main characters survive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 18:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This guy](https://nypdecider.files.wordpress.com/2014/11/too-many-cooks-creepy-killer.png) is plopped into the opening title sequence of your favorite live-action sitcom. He is armed with a machete. Can he kill every main character? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goku vs. The Soup Nazi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 23:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goku is *really* hungry. The only problem is, the only place with food is the Soup Nazi's restaurant. Can Goku be calm enough to buy soup without getting kicked out of the restaurant?

Rules:

1. The line is 100 people long. Goku must wait in line until his turn.

2. Goku cannot take the soup by force.

3. Goku will willingly exit the restaurant if the Soup Nazi tells him to.

4. If Goku acts out in any way in the line he will be kicked out.

5. The Soup Nazi can see everything that happens in the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Star Wars] Did Separatist holdouts join the Rebel Alliance upon the conclusion of the Clone War? If so, how did members of the Alliance feel about joining force with people they had just fought a costly war with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 21:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't imagine that the Separatists would be eager to rejoin the Republic just because they were the Empire now. Were there any internal conflicts? Did the Alliance ever make use of battle droids? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stegosaurus vs. Triceratops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 14:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Stegosaurus](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stegosaurus)

[Triceratops](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Triceratops)

Fight in a Triassic Era forest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Color Kid vs. Arm-Fall-Off-Boy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 19:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Color Kid](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Color_Kid)

[Arm-Fall-Off-Boy](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arm-Fall-Off-Boy)

Fight in a gymnasium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I watch Arrested Development or 30 Rock? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 00:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard both of these shows are really funny and I need a new show to watch. Which should I watch first? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harry Potter (Movies) vs. Captain America (MCU) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 22:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cap as of the end of *Avengers: Age of Ultron* and Harry as of the end of *Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows: Part 2*.

Round 1: In the courtyard of Hogwarts.

Round 2: In front of the Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joaquin Phoenix vs. Hurricane Joaquin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 07:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every character Joaquin Phoenix has ever played teams up. Can they stop Hurricane Joaquin from making landfall in the USA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harry Potter vs. Sabrina, the Teenage Witch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 02:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Book Harry vs. Comic Sabrina

Round 2: Movie Harry vs. Show Sabrina

BONUS: Who is the most powerful wizard they can defeat if they team up?

Both in their most recent versions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the strongest character Batman (Terry McGinnis) can defeat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 21:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terry has his Batsuit.

Round 1: DCAU Terry.

Round 2: N52 Terry.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Highfather vs. Odin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respect Odin: https://www.reddit.com/r/respectthreads/comments/3fpe4z/respect_odin_borson_earth616/

Highfather Wiki: http://dc.wikia.com/wiki/Izaya_(New_Earth)

Fight on Charon.

I know nothing about Highfather outside of the Justice League TV show so this may be a major mismatch.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Red Lotus vs. The Incredibles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Red Lotus TotM](https://www.reddit.com/r/whowouldwin/comments/3j84nz/team_of_the_month_the_red_lotus/)

Incredibles Wiki Pages

1. [Mr. Incredible](http://disney.wikia.com/wiki/Mr._Incredible)
2. [Elastigirl](http://disney.wikia.com/wiki/Helen_Parr)
3. [Dash](http://disney.wikia.com/wiki/Dash_Parr)
4. [Violet](http://disney.wikia.com/wiki/Violet_Parr)
5. [Jack-Jack](http://disney.wikia.com/wiki/Jack-Jack_Parr)

Round 1: Fight in downtown NYC.

Round 2: Fight in a dense rainforest.

Round 3: Fight at Laghima's Peak.

Bonus 1: Could the Red Lotus take down the Omnidroid v.10?

Bonus 2: Could the Incredibles capture and kill Avatar Korra? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Goku vs. Superman 'THE' fight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From all of these Goku threads today, it got me thinking about the whole endless Goku vs. Superman debate and how it's been done a million times by a million different people. But why is it *the* fight to do? There are other 'close' fights, like Batman vs. Captain America and Hawkeye vs. Green Arrow, and there are other 'Superman-like' characters like Thor and Gladiator. So what makes Goku vs. Superman so special? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drake and Josh vs. Kenan and Kel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 17:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: It is announced that both shows will be having a 1 hour reunion show on Nickelodeon. Which show gets the most viewers?

Round 2: Tag team fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sabrina Spellman vs. Marnie Piper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 18:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Each enroll in Hogwarts. Who has the best grades by the end of the year?

Round 2: Fight to the death.

Sabrina as of the end of Season 7 of "Sabrina, the Teenage Witch" and Marnie as of the end of "Return to Halloweentown". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elder Price must convert the head of ISIS to Mormonism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 02:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elder Price and Elder Cunningham are assigned to a new mission location: Syria. Can they get Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi to join The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints?

Round 1: They are alone in Syria.

Round 2: They can have the help of Elder McKinley and other Mormons in the District. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Johnny Bravo has 1 week to get Princess Jasmine to fall in love with him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 00:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The time has come for Princess Jasmine of Agrabah to find a suitor, but instead of a prince, she must marry an American, and Johnny is the only one left. Can he successfully woo Jasmine into becoming his bride?

Rules:

1. If Jasmine does not marry within the week, Agrabah will once again fall under Jafar's rule. She and her father know this. Johnny doesn't.

2. Jasmine *must* fall in love with Johnny before they are married. She cannot marry him just to save Agrabah.

3. Johnny is alone, and has no contact with his friends (Carl, Pops, Suzy, etc.). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Koala vs. A Sloth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 01:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are both 10 feet away from each other on the top of a tree in a dense forest. One must knock the other one off the tree to win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Aladdin] What was written on the lamp? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 05:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Aladdin first finds Genie's lamp, he says 'I think there's something written here. It's hard to make out'. What did it say on the lamp? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Red Lotus vs. Team Avatar (A:TLA) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 01:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Red Lotus is Zaheer (with flight), P'Li, Ghazan, and Ming Hua (all as of their last appearances).

Team Avatar is Aang, Katara, Toph, and Zuko (all as of the end of *The Rift* comics).

Round 1: Outside of the Royal Palace in Ba Sing Se.

Round 2: At the Southern Air Temple.

Round 3: All are bloodlusted. Fight [here](https://cdn.artstation.rocks/p/assets/images/images/000/350/456/large/sergey-averkin-calm-down-friend-i-just-wanna-go-home.jpg?1418322195). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daredevil vs. The Phantom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 20:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Phantom Comic Vine](http://www.comicvine.com/the-phantom/4005-7957/)

[Respect Daredevil](https://www.reddit.com/r/respectthreads/comments/2dzadn/respect_the_man_without_fear_daredevil/)

They fight on the Great Wall of China.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Danny Phantom vs. Luke Cage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 20:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EoS and 616

Fight in Red Square in Moscow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kronosaurus vs. Killer Whale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 22:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Kronosaurus](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kronosaurus)

[Killer Whale](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Killer_whale)

Round 1: 1 Kronosaurus vs. 1 Killer Whale.

Round 2: 5 Kronosauruses vs. 5 Killer Whales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Scooby-Doo] Does Scooby not know he's a dog? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 05:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You hear it every episode.

Villain: I would have gotten away with it, too if it weren't for those meddling kids, and their dumb dog!

Scooby: Dog? Where?

Does he not know he's a dog? He does act extremely human-like. He talks, eats human food, and has even been hired by people to work actual jobs. Does he think he is a human? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rugrats piloting the Reptar Robot (Rugrats in Paris: The Movie) vs. King Kong (2005) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 02:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fight takes place in a large city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Crimson Chin vs. Ultra Lord </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 05:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toothless [HtTYD] vs. Balerion [ASoIaF] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 19:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aegon the Conqueror is trying to take Berk, and only Hiccup and Toothless can stop him.

Round 1: Toothless with tail vs. Balerion. Aegon and Hiccup are not present.

Round 2: Toothless without tail vs. Balerion. Aegon and Hiccup are riding them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S2] Why did Balon... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 02:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...want to attack the North? This part always confused me. It seemed like the worst possible decision he could have made. Instead of having the allied armies of Robb and himself attacking the Lannisters, he made it a 3-way battle, and either one of the armies could have destroyed him. Why take that extra risk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jon Snow vs. Robb Stark [Game of Thrones Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 04:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TV versions (both from right before Robb was killed).

Round 1: Sword fight to the death. Jon gets Longclaw and Robb gets his sword (I don't think it had a name). Takes place outside of Winterfell.

Round 2: Robb's army is transported north of The Wall and Jon and the Night's Watch must defend it. Do they get through?

Round 3: Grey Wind vs. Ghost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the strongest character a Great White Shark could defeat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 03:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The character is placed in the middle of the ocean, hundreds of miles from any land. Below them is a fully mature, 21-foot long, female great white shark, and it's feeding time. Who can the shark defeat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PIXAR] Do non-organic life forms have a Headquarters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 03:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are shown that not only humans, but also other animals such as dogs and cats have a Headquarters. But what about other clearly sentient, but not exactly 'living' things, like Cars, toys, and robots? They all clearly have emotions, but they don't really have brains. Is a Headquarters automatically created once they become conscious? If not, what drives their emotions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Headquarters Team [Inside Out] vs. The Joker's Mind [DC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 02:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I recently saw Inside Out (fantastic movie, by the way), and it got me thinking. What would it be like inside of the Joker's Headquarters? 

Joy, Sadness, Anger, Disgust, and Fear are all placed inside of the Joker's mind. Can they somehow make him sane?

If you haven't seen the movie, there will probably be spoilers below. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Megamind vs. Syndrome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 22:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: They both take the SAT. Who scores highest?

Round 2: Megamind in his Battle Suit (that he used against Tighten) vs. Syndrome and the Omnidroid 10.

Round 3: They each get 1 year of prep. Syndrome must fight Metro Man and Megamind must fight the Incredibles. Who fares better?

Round 3a: Same as 3, but at the last second Metro Man is switched with an angry Tighten and Frozone joins to help the Incredibles.

BONUS: Metro Man vs. the Incredibles.

All fights take place in downtown LA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jar Jar Binks vs. Mia Khalifa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 06:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Jar Jar's CotY](http://www.reddit.com/r/whowouldwin/comments/310ik3/character_of_the_year_jar_jar_binks/)

[Mia Khalifa's CotW](http://www.reddit.com/r/whowouldwin/comments/3997bs/character_of_the_week_mia_khalifa/)

Both are bloodlusted.

BONUS: They do the fusion dance. Who is the strongest character Jia Khalinks can seduce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spider-Man vs. Zilla </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 02:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 616 Spider-Man and Zilla (Composite) from the 1998 movie.

The fight takes place in real-life New York. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Animal Face-Off #3] Asiatic Lion vs. Bengal Tiger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 22:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Asiatic Lion](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Asiatic_lion)

[Bengal Tiger](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bengal_tiger)

Location: Ancient Indian temple.

[Video of fight](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D_PHs-kbypo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Timmy Turner vs. Goku </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 22:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Timmy as he appears in [Maho Mushi](http://vignette3.wikia.nocookie.net/fairlyoddparents/images/8/82/ChannelChasersPt1-167.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width/200?cb=20110912225259 path-prefix=en).

Goku as he is in the 21st Martial Arts Tournament.

[Timmy's fight scene for reference](https://youtu.be/NeMKptBqVEM?t=580).

Timmy has access to the robot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the strongest character Zoom can defeat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 02:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zoom is the Tim Allen character from the movie, *Zoom*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Animal Face-Off #2] African Bush Elephant vs. White Rhinoceros </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 22:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [African Bush Elephant](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/African_bush_elephant)

[White Rhinoceros](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White_rhinoceros)

Fight takes place in Serengeti National Park.

[Link to video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cX6iEBvDd_Q). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Animal Face-Off #1] Great White Shark vs. Saltwater Crocodile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 18:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So about 10 years ago there was this show called Animal Face-Off, where 2 animals were compared and then put in fake fights to see who would win. Like *Death Battle* but with animals. I was curious what you guys thought of it.

[Great White Shark](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Great_white_shark)

[Saltwater Crocodile](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Saltwater_crocodile)

Location: Off the coast of North Australia.

[Link to fight](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-o7nLZWyinI). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
