<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6842</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-14 04:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like the tsunami was a false alarm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-14 04:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does look like a wall collapsed as well this time. The cabinet secretary just said that the pressure seems to have stayed constant after the explosion, though. Let's hope that is the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-14 03:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say it's been a hydrogen explosion again and that the containment vessel seems to have stayed in tact.

EDIT: [Link](http://english.kyodonews.jp/news/2011/03/77606.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-14 03:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say it was a hydrogen explosion at reactor 3 (like reactor 1 on saturday). The spokesperson just said  some radiation might have leaked (like saturday) but the containment vessel is still in tact. The pressure in the vessel seems to have stayed constant after the explosion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 20:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI "Baltic" refers to countries adjacent to the Baltic Sea which is in Northern Europe. Although in a narrower (and I think more widely used sense) the term Baltic states refers only to Lithuania, Latvia and Estonia. You probably mean the Balkans which refers to the Balkan Peninsula in South-Eastern Europe and includes Greece (which you can see clearly in the image). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why earthquakes and eruptions are rarely linked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 00:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-12 22:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were 479,884 people living in Lisbon in 2009, 2.8M in its metropolitan area. I don't think it changed *that* much in the last two years. The rate of change seems to have been around 2%. (Given that the rate of decline is approximately constant (it probably isn't), there would be 460K inhabitants in 2011)

[Source \(PDF\).](http://www.ine.pt/xportal/xmain?xpid=INE xpgid=ine_publicacoes PUBLICACOESpub_boui=102944410 PUBLICACOESmodo=2) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-12 16:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is being hit by the largest earthquake in a thousand years in the area, and then a giant tsunami, reported as a "nuclear accident in Japan"?

What is it then? This certainly wasn't supposed to happen, so 'accident' is a fair evaluation, I think.

By the way, the anti-nuclear energy movement has a big history in Germany. It is deeply rooted in society by now, and the words nuclear and accident in one sentence can elicit fears in people only something like an alien invasion could. The people and especially the media probably don't look for what's likely, then. They look for the worst possible outcomes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-10 20:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck.

94' 2-3 by Nilmar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-10 19:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite a nice shot, by the way. And 10 shots for Leverkusen after 35 minutes. (Villareal: 1 shot)

The commentator just said that 8 Leverkusen players on the pitch are 23 years old or younger. Impressive.

Edit: So much for that.. Rossi 41' 1-1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-04 21:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did have problems to get approval in some countries when they started in the 1980s. 

(France, IIRC , didn't allow Red Bull to be sold until they replaced taurin with arginin in 2008. France withdrew its regulation against taurin later that year.)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> De Maizire ersetzt Guttenberg, Hans-Peter Friedrich (CSU) wird Innenminister </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-02 12:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-01 16:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Edit: Er tritt auch als Abgeordneter ab.

Das schien vorhin noch unklar, aber laut CSU hat er den Rcktritt beim Bundestagsprsidenten eingereicht. Ich hab meinen Kommentar dementsprechend editiert.

An meiner Einschtzung ndert das nichts: Als Nicht-Regierungsmitglied ist er in ein paar Jahren "frischer" als jeder Andere aus der politischen Sphre, er hat die Bild-Zeitung auf seiner Seite und wird behaupten, fr seine Fehler ausreichend gebt zu haben.

Wie du schon sagst: Er hat sonst nichts gelernt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-01 15:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Das Ganze hat so lange funktioniert, warum soll er jetzt damit aufhren?

Er bereitet mit diesem Schadensbegrenzungsrcktritt quasi schon die Rckkehr vor: Jetzt geht er noch eine Weile durch die Boulevardpresse, tritt etwas in den Hintergrund, dann wird seine Frau fr eine Weile mit Kinderpornos die Presse dominieren (vllt. fngt er auch an, sich da zu engagieren) und in ein paar Jahren ist er wieder ganz vorn. ~~(Zumal er das Bundestagsmandat ja behlt.)~~

Edit: durchstreichen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-25 22:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  well until Israel got mad at being second and asked germany to shut the doors

Not really. Before 2004 there had been a law in place which made it a lot easier for people from the former Soviet Union to emigrate to Germany than for people from other places. (except for EU citizens, obviously) For January 2005 they changed that so that there were no exceptional laws for non-EU citizens in any way. Russian Jews therefore had to undergo the same processes as everyone else. 
(As a side note: It seems that, indeed, there were more Jewish immigrants from the CIS to Germany than to Israel.) 

BUT: In 2005 they changed parts of that law (retroactively) to allow more immigration from parts of the former Soviet Union to Germany, including special rules for Holocaust victims or their relatives and for families living apart. From then on Jews had to take part in language seminars/tests and some kind of social integration prognosis like other immigrants, though.

This revision came together after criticism from Jewish lobby organisations - with ties to the Israel government - by the way. 

tl;dr: Israel didn't actually ask Germany to shut its doors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-23 16:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, if you are not Russian you must also read this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-23 16:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crime and Punishment - Dostoyevsky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guttenberg verzichtet dauerhaft auf Doktortitel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-21 21:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-19 21:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The English title is "The World According to Monsanto." [You can find it on YouTube.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fvGddgHRQyg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-19 19:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the [abstract:]( http://www2.cochrane.org/reviews/en/ab001364.html)

Zinc administered within 24 hours of onset of symptoms reduces the duration and severity of the common cold in healthy people. When supplemented for at least five months, it reduces cold incidence, school absenteeism and prescription of antibiotics in children. There is potential for zinc lozenges to produce side effects. In view of this and the differences in study populations, dosages, formulations and duration of treatment, *it is difficult to make firm recommendations about the dose, formulation and duration that should be used.* [emphasis added] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-16 22:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's your arse-shavin'.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deutsche Brse buys NYSE for $9.53 billion to create largest owner of equities and derivatives markets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-15 16:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-15 16:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but the potentially boring part of driving is when you don't (have to) shift gears anyway, isn't it? At least for me it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-13 18:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and this post is on top now.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-02 21:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can try sites like [MyP2P](http://www.myp2p.eu) or [LiveTV.ru](http://www.livetv.ru) for all kinds of other streams. 

If you want to get streams reliably you might have to install some additional plugins or programs (vshare, veetle, sopcast..) at some point, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-01 21:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I can see the domain was seized. That might take a few minutes to take effect in your DNS. You shouldn't refresh the site.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-31 15:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is probably the post you are referring to.](http://www.reddit.com/r/WTF/comments/eaqnf/pardon_me_but_5000_downvotes_wtf_is_worldnews_for/c16omup) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-26 17:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a related note the time it takes you to get to the surface on the other side of the earth will be **42** minutes and 15 seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-25 20:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journal editors would know this.

When no attempt is made to publish negative (and positive) results, how should journal editors know of them? Also, when I said published I didn't necessarily mean *published in a journal* but rather *made public*.

Would a database of studies really be detrimental to the scientific process? I can certainly see that it means more work prior to starting a study as there might be more to do in evaluating what others have done before you.

We're talking about every single study which yields a negative result: publishing all this would most often not yield anything useful.

Probably not. But in some cases it might? For instance, when the financer of a study has a vested interest in positive results (pharma industry, anyone?) it might be beneficial for everyone if they had to publish their results of clinical trials even when the results were negative.

I know I am just talking about a subset of scientific studies now but publication bias *is* a problem and I don't see many other ways to get around that. Based on a service like [clinicaltrials.gov](http://www.clinicaltrials.gov) such a database could be an option, I believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-25 17:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However, if the negative result is found repeatedly and challenges a current dogma in the field, I think it would be highly beneficial to the scientific community to publish it.

Well, yes, but how would anyone know if negative results have been found repeatedly when the results didn't get published in the first place?
Or do you think informal communication between individual scientists would suffice to achieve that? I'm not sure.

I think any study, no matter how flawed, should be published because even those flaws could help broaden knowledge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-24 16:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my.. 

To begin with, no doors where shut for the oppressed. There was an immigration law in effect since 1990 that was there to make it easier for jews in the former Soviet Union who had been prosecuted in the Third Reich to return to Germany and be granted safe haven.

That law was abandoned when a whole new immigration law took effect in January 2005, introducing the same rules and requirements for potential immigrants of all ethnicities/origins/etc. A problem before this was that many Jewish communities had been overwhelmed by the sheer number of immigrants.

That's all there is to it.

Oh by the way: In July 2006 an amendment to the law came into effect relieving a part of the regulation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-24 16:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever heard of [smaller](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ostafyevo_International_Airport) [regional](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bykovo_Airport) airports?

You probably won't see as many foreigners and especially tourists there.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-24 14:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think his point is that, technically, automatic transmissions have lower degree of efficiency than manual transmission. That's simple due to their construction.

For an automatic transmission to work you need a few additional parts that simply introduce added inefficiencies (due to friction and energy requirements) and extra weight. Even though newer transmissions lessened these effects significantly, they haven't been eliminated - and probably won't be.

That said, the electronics in the automatic transmission allow optimisations in many ways. The gear changes, for instance, only happen in the optimal rpm-range thus lowering the fuel consumption.
In (some) modern cars the latter effect is bigger than the former allowing cars with automatic transmission to have greater gas mileage.

Still, in every manual car the effect of the driver's habits is far greater. These standardized tests might not be the way to go if you really want to judge what would work best for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-24 14:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is only true for drivers who know what they are doing which - let's be honest - is not a very accurate assumption in many cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-24 11:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, seen them a lot in pubs in Germany - long before the WC if I remember correctly. I believe I've read a study somewhere that these goals improve aiming significantly thus keeping the toilets cleaner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada's record-smashing mildness  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-24 01:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-23 12:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interestingly, I haven't heard much about the controversy relating to the third reich thing - and I'm living in Dresden. I don't read Bild, though. Rather, some 'conservative' fans would prefer to have kept the old name since the commercialisation of football is frowned upon around anyway.
(And the same thing happens in almost every stadium that had undergone a name change.. In Rostock (see my crest) they still have a chant just for the old stadium name - renamed in 2007!)

That said, Dynamo couldn't even pay the lease for the stadium which is owned by the city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-20 14:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [source](http://www.reddit.com/r/WTF/comments/eaqnf/pardon_me_but_5000_downvotes_wtf_is_worldnews_for/c16omup) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-11 18:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wanted to add a [citation \(PDF\).](http://www.linuxfoundation.org/docs/lf_linux_kernel_development_2010.pdf) (Look at page 13 for information.)

*Spoiler*: 18.9% of the contributions to the kernel come from volunteers. The rest (including 6.4% of the contributions where the status is unclear) comes from companies paying kernel developers.

Another interesting point:
 There are a number of developers for whom we were unable to determine a corporate affiliation; those are grouped under unknown in the table below. With few exceptions, all of the people in
this category have contributed ten or fewer changes to the kernel over the past three years, yet the large number of these developers causes their total contribution to be quite high.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-10 21:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GK2zj5ob-wI) is Hamit Altintop's goal which won this year's Pusks Award. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-09 14:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Der Begriff Regionalverkehr (aka SPNV) hngt nicht unbedingt mit der Lnge der Gesamtstrecke zusammen. Vielmehr bezieht er sich darauf, dass die jeweilige Landesverkehrsbehrde(n) (Land oder Zweckverbnde) Aufgabentrger ist/sind. Daraus resultiert i.d.R. eine wesentlich hhere Dichte der Haltebahnhfe entlang der Strecke. (siehe S-Bahn, RegionalExpress u..) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-07 13:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russell coined that phrase in 1952 when it wasn't actually in the realm of possibility: He talked about a teapot between Earth and Mars in an elliptical orbit around the sun. It's just an analogy after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-06 15:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FC Hansa Rostock, please :)  (3rd League in Germany) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-06 11:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wFyY2mK8pxk) short video might help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-15 18:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Point taken. City might not be the best choice if he wants to win cups and play in the starting team. But where should he go then? I think he is in a position in his career where so many big clubs are interested in him that he will inevitably choose one where benchwarming is a possibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-15 17:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say there's a good chance of him winning something with Wolfsburg in the near future. You should grant him more ambition than that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chrome for a Cause - Each tab you open will contribute to a charity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-15 17:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-10 23:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only heard the number 25 million/yr quoted in the German press, which corresponds to around 21 million in current rates. Palatinehill is quite right in that regard. 

(The actual number is secret, though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks cables suggest Burma is building secret nuclear sites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-09 22:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-09 14:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This book](http://www.amazon.com/Guitar-Fretboard-Workbook-Understanding-Musicians/dp/0634049011/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 s=books-intl) really helped me get a good grasp of the fretboard. It's a *workbook* which means that there are (relatively) short explanations and then you fill out the rest yourself. It provides a good, structured way to practice, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks-Sperrungen: Die Feigheit der Konzerne bedroht die Freiheit im Netz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-09 11:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-04 17:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI Baukelien is referring to [this.](http://www.reddit.com/r/WTF/comments/eaqnf/pardon_me_but_5000_downvotes_wtf_is_worldnews_for/c16omup) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-04 12:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A-Team: 1983-1987

Top Gun: 1986


...which lawn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piratenpartei Deutschland hilft Wikileaks mit eigenem Mirror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-03 16:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-03 16:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've heard that a lot recently - and I know which blogger you are talking about - but seriously: Der Spiegel is still *the* most important outlet of investigative journalism (Yes, I'm serious) in German(y). 
Certainly, the quality has decreased significantly, their online version is a parody of journalism (Which seems to be a necessity for market leadership) and even the paper version has shown (too) many examples of biased reporting. (Relieving Stefan Aust of his position as chief editor was a good step in this regard.) But do you really think FAZ, SZ and the others don't have that? *Hint: They do.*

All this does not change the fact that most consequential stories and scandals in the past years/decades would not have been made public without it. They are prone to journalistic mistakes and biases as everyone else but they also seem to be the only ones willing to take the risk to publicise potentially damaging information. (see WikiLeaks, "Spiegelaffre") I still respect them for that.

With that said, you should read "Der Spiegel" like you read anything else: Critically, scrutinizingly. The blogger you quote is always on about media literacy. There is no source whatsoever where you wouldn't profit from that somehow. "Der Spiegel" is no exception.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FAZ-Interview mit den Spiegel-Chefredakteuren zu Wikileaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-01 18:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-29 16:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Fixed URL.](http://www.oakvillechitchat.com/hivaids-awareness-candlight-ceremony/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homopathie breitet sich an deutschen Hochschulen aus - mit Untersttzung der Grnen und des rzteprsidenten </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-25 19:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-23 21:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 0 - 1 Mario Gomez 33'

That guy can't not score these days..

Edit: See? 0-2 same guy 38' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-20 12:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The site is probably referring to [this study.](http://www.ajcn.org/content/92/5/1145.abstract)
You might want to have a look at the last sentence..:

**Results**: We observed no associations between coffee, tea, or combined coffee and tea consumption and risk of either type of brain tumor when using quantiles based on country-specific distributions of intake. However, a significant inverse association was observed for glioma risk among those consuming 100 mL coffee and tea per day compared with those consuming 100 mL/d (hazard ratio: 0.66; 95% CI: 0.44, 0.97; P = 0.03). The association was slightly stronger in men (hazard ratio: 0.59; 95% CI: 0.34, 1.01) than in women (hazard ratio: 0.74; 95% CI: 0.42, 1.31), although neither was statistically significant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CERN physicists trap antimatter atoms for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-17 21:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-15 10:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right. Most toilets with this "Flachspler" (that is the shelf one)  are ones built more than 10 to 15 years ago. Nowadays public toilets almost always have the *normal* or "Tiefspler" toilets. (mostly for odor reasons, I think) For private homes this toilet certainly has the bigger market share today as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-27 14:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably sorted the page for "best" instead of "top" which you seem to expect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-26 16:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that's going to be a sausagefest.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-26 16:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google knows the word "lawsuits", though. It means "Klagen". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-21 21:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do have a point, though. Havana Club tastes *so* much better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-21 16:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but I don't think that would be important. Although most people would probably shorten the "ein" to "n" anyway. 
Also: Wei****bier bitte. [](/troll) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-21 16:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think most places offer more than one brand but they have some kind of default beer. That means when you ask for "ein Bier bitte", you'll get their default Pilsner. (Bavaria being the exception: There "Bier" is synonymous with Hefeweizen, I think.) The same applies for Schwarzbier, Weibier and so on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Loki Schmidt ist tot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-21 14:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-21 12:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Auslnder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-13 19:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link \(PDF\)](http://www.fes.de/cgi-bin/gbv.cgi?id=07504 ty=pdf) zur Studie. Die Fragen (und Antworten) zum Rechtsextremismus sind auf Seite 73 aufgelistet.

Die Frage zur Diktatur war brigens "*Im nationalen Interesse ist unter bestimmten Umstnden eine Diktatur die bessere Staatsform*". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-30 16:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the HFCS that is being metabolised in the liver but the fructose it contains - similar to sucrose.

About the leptin, look at [this](http://www.ajcn.org/cgi/content/full/87/5/1194) study for example. There doesn't seem to be a difference between sucrose an HFCS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-16 18:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that's the pronunciation I meant. The analogy to "koontz" threw me off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-16 18:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [] is just phonetic transcription. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-16 18:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be spelled "Kuhntz". "Kuntz" would need an open (short) u sound [] like in "book".

(granted that you wouldn't pronounce "Koontz" like that) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-15 11:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People in the UK might have. In continental Europe? Not so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-14 21:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marin!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-14 21:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yellow would've been enough, though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-14 21:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almeida 1:2! That's the Werder we know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
