<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4116</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 12:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.pathofexile.com/forum/view-thread/966967/page/1#p8217766 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno about out in the states, but in Ireland there's still problems with people goin around stripping houses in the middle of being built, or occasionally even finished ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except cunt, they say cunt the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's not really better. Your statement is still "I experienced an odd coincidence among a very small sample size, so this wider claim must be true". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iron Reflexes Aegis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you're right, the fact that we disagree with him shouldn't preclude him. The fact that Alex Jones believes in interdimensional vampires and that the government is turning frogs gay is what should preclude him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad recently applied for a higher position at his company. Or, well, I say applied, what I mean is that he told them he would be leaving if they didn't give him a position which had recently been vacated. But apparently they have to open the position to the public. The requirements for the position were written based on his resume, because he worked closely with the person who previous held the job and who wrote the requirement before he left, and besides that it required a working knowledge of the IT operations of all international branches of the company, which only he and the previous occupant had. He was literally the only option for the position, but he had to blackmail the company into giving it to him, and even then they took in resumes and apparently performed several interviews for a position which they had essentially already filled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy confirmation bias batman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like you would enjoy [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AHqGV5WjS4w) video, supposing you haven't already seen it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow this victory is hollow. I want my divine back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Wanna bet?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lk59imFr6yI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, probably Russian or something similar then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the vague outline you can see of the license plate on the back of that bus/van it's not in Canada, Canadian license plates are wider and shorter. Going on my very limited knowledge of license plate styles I'd say it's somewhere in the EU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spent about 30 blessings to discover that Eye of Chayula relics cannot be blessed above 16 all attributes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/jd6Uu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maps, unlike currency, have unique characteristics. There are two ways for this to work, either it can only accept white unqualitied maps (which might not actually work because of Ilvl, which currency doesn't have, but I'm not sure), or it would just be a pretty much normal tab that only allowed maps. You wouldn't be able to stack them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that has already been pointed out to me. And I corrected myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, maybe not the best example. So a shiny Anvil, divining it to take away the -movespeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes both those things are true, but they don't negate the fact that adding a Perandus coin slot to the currency tab doesn't mean leaguestones will become part of the game, because Perandus can come from Zana mod aswell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never said they did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno about that, if you're particularly wealthy you might want a shiny Ephemeral Edge for your LL RF build or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you forgetting about Zana mods? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 10:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you explain how it confirms leaguestones?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Reddit karma

2. Might be a streamer or youtuber looking for exposure

3. Showing off

4. Maybe he's just a nice guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're talking about HoWA right? The build that can easily face tank shaper beam? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is it better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You trolling me? You said "pretty much no attacks". And you've named the one and only elemental attack skill that doesn't have a colour associated with it's main damage type. Even wild strike has a different animations for each element. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's tied to both. When you think of ice/cold you don't think of green, that's for certain. But ice and lightning couldn't both be blue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The SSF Softcore players weren't really pushing for it. Like Norse was in first for SSF Softcore for a while, and that was while leveling a second char and not really pushing for xp much at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [For the uninitiated.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yry5NQ4_pfY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhhhhh, what? Name an elemental attack that doesn't have a color tied to it's element. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
