<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4342</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nothing is impossible: Trump donation server defaced </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 20:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nothing is impossible: Trump donation server defaced </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 20:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Refresh button for Play Store updates is now in testing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 20:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Too spectacular to handle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [For those just interested in the wallpapers](https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B76gtuzZR_ZjOW8tNHd2WF9idUE/view)

Resolution for each wallpaper is 2048 x 2048.

[Preview I created](http://i.imgur.com/pKZ28m5.jpg)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Galaxy Tab S3 firmware now online, grab the wallpapers here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sources: TAG Heuer to launch a new connected watch in mid-March </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than the Feb. 26 MWC announcement, I don't think there has been any info leaked with regards to its availability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Galaxy Tab S3 manual leaks, showing Android Nougat, Grace UX, and Note-like ambition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. After listening to the last CrackBerry podcast, it got me very interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ZTE is shutting down its failed Hawkeye phone Kickstarter campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Can Light, Plus Glass, Equal The Internet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Separate US model and separate model for each major US carrier. Samsung could release only one US model compatible with all the carriers, like they did with the unlocked S7/S7 Edge, but the carriers still push for their own variants. Hopefully this goes away once CDMA is phased out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the insight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bohemia is a good one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It varies with Tecate. Sometimes it can be good and other times it's not even worth drinking. The borrachos drink it either way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The blue coral was beautiful :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do new phones ship with older versions of Android? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USB Killer now lets you fry most Lightning and USB-C devices for $55 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung teases Exynos 9 series chipset, could be the one powering the Galaxy S8 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. For most US consumers that are financing their phones through the carriers, the price increase likely won't matter, especially since the carriers regularly offer device discounts and the occasional bundle (E.g. free wireless charger, free microsd card, or Gear VR). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Galaxy S8 and Galaxy S8 Plus purported color options and pricing revealed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Galaxy S8 and Galaxy S8 Plus purported color options and pricing revealed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill would urge Texans to stop using the Chilean flag emoji for the Lone Star State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fault:

 One zippy roadster's K6A engine block left the factory without its stamp.

The fix:

 And how does Suzuki plan to resolve this minor recall that does not affect the safety or mechanical soundness of this 21-year-old kei car? Apparently, Suzuki will replace it with a new engraved cylinder block.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Suzuki Issued A Recall For One 21-Year-Old Cappuccino </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Caavo streaming box is built on gamechanging machine vision for TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Pretty disappointing that it hasn't picked up more support outside a couple of Chinese OEMs. I've been following Sense ID since it was first announced and was super excited about seeing the tech incorporated into mainstream phones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol. [My post](https://www.reddit.com/r/Android/comments/5tu3xc/lg_g6_teaser_suggests_an_end_to_bootloops_and/) for this same article was removed for supposedly breaking rule 6, which I didn't, since nothing was changed. This one is allowed to survive though even though nothing different was done?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to use Android Instant Apps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple patents screen tech capable of reading fingerprints without dedicated sensor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huawei CEO Richard Yu confirms the Huawei Watch 2 will be announced at MWC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 11:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Galaxy Tab S3 with S Pen leaks in new photo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers at MITs Microsystems Technology Laboratories have built a low-power chip specialized for automatic speech recognition. With power savings of 90 to 99 percent, it could make voice control practical for relatively simple electronic devices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LG G6 teaser suggests an end to bootloops and cracked screens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I don't use my bluetooth speaker, I usually end up using the 2015 Moto E to play music or podcasts. I place it on the shower caddy. The Moto E works fine for it and it has a water-resistant coating. Seems to be doing the job well since it has survived splashes and plenty of steam. Though I have had waterproof flagship phones, I never take them in the shower. It's more to avoid the possible damage in case I drop it in the shower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe there's any game throttling and Verizon states it includes HD video streaming. So that likely means 720p. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * $80 for unlimited data, talk and text on your smartphone with paper-free billing and AutoPay.
* $45 per line for four lines with unlimited data, talk and text on your smartphones and tablets with paper-free billing and AutoPay.

Looks like it includes HD video streaming, which is obviously better than 480p. It does state the following though:

  To ensure a quality experience for all customers, after 22 GB of data usage on a line during any billing cycle we may prioritize usage behind other customers in the event of network congestion. While we dont expect to do that very often, network management is a crucial tool that benefits all Verizon customers.

YouTube: [Not just unlimited, Verizon Unlimited](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YacWu0bi690) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looks like Verizon is bringing back unlimited data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump keeps tweeting about news he sees on TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With a group of bystanders nearby, a Mustang being loaded onto a trailer ends up crashing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You had one job... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No bees around? Here's the drone pollinator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sony's latest sensor shoots ridiculous slow-mo video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 14:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're only in for tough luck when it comes to the enthusiasts that care about the 835 more. Normal consumers make up the majority of buyers and will likely base their buying decisions on anything but the SoC. 

Also, keep in mind that HTC released the U Ultra as a flagship running the 821. Some people may not see it as a flagship, but HTC does. With no leaked launch date for the HTC 11, this could be like LG's G and V series. U Ultra gets released first and the HTC 11 comes out later in the year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Both in the VentureBeat photo and CNET Korea render, the flash and heart rate monitor module is noticeably smaller than the fingerprint sensor. Not the case in this photo. Also, in the VB photo, the opening for the camera sensor is slightly bigger. The opening in this "leak" is exactly the same as the S7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. When it comes to resale value, LG flagships always tend to dive faster than any other manufacturer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you see "temporarily out of stock" come up, wait a bit and refresh. It seems to be going in and out of stock on certain occasions. You can thank the Slickdeals folk for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [DEAL] ASUS Nexus Player + Gamepad Bundle on sale for $59 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That lone antenna line on the bottom is triggering my OCD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I see it somewhat in the third picture of the article, but it doesn't really pop out due to the angle of the shot and if it's also a bit reflective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tech bloggers and some enthusiasts that upgrade way too often. I'm the latter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully support for CDMA :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both were Black Friday deals in 2015 and were purchased without a contract. The Moto E was a VZW prepaid device. The Lumia was AT T branded, but I was able to unlock it after requesting a code. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a deal Moto had at the time I ordered. Even though I'm on Verizon, I bought the Droid version from Moto's site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't gotten around to updating my device flair, but I no longer have it. However, it was a damn good phone. Performance on it never let me down. I'm not a mobile gamer, but for everything else I threw at it, it worked as well as the pricier flagships. Also, the camera performed a lot better than what I expected. Low light photography is where it falls short, but it could still keep up with the much more expensive Z Force and some auto mode shots on it came out better than what the V20 can produce. Battery life is an obvious plus and easily beat out any phone I have owned. I'd definitely recommend it to anyone that is looking to pick one up. Great build quality and some of the Moto Mods, such as the free battery mod I received, do provide added benefits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been tempted, but I upgrade to new phones way too often and sell my previous one to offset the cost of the new phone. However, if a good deal pops up, such as a $10 Moto E or $30 Lumia 640, I will buy them to use around the house for various tasks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple inexplicably removes iCloud Activation Lock status page, which helped people avoid buying stolen iPhones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's already unlocked. Verizon phones, with the exception of prepaid devices, ship unlocked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Nathan K.](https://plus.google.com/102612254593917101378) as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He seems to have taken a break from it. [Nathan K.](https://plus.google.com/102612254593917101378) is now the one mainly doing the testing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A non-compliant type c cable has the potential of damaging any device that is connected to it. It can fry phones and destroy computers. [Here's an example](https://plus.google.com/102612254593917101378/posts/3gBj67quR5v) where Nathan K. (notable Type C tester similar to Benson) had his computer fried by a bad USB C power supply. He also had a post last year showing an HTC 10 that was damaged by a bad cable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USB-C Power Meter Helps You Spot Counterfeit Accessories Before They Fry Your Gadgets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though the display is getting larger, the dimensions of the phone are pretty much staying the same to last year's models. That area can comfortably be reached without doing hand gymnastics. However, for right-handed folk, it may result in smudges on the camera glass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 18:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't surprise me. Sony did the same thing last year with the X line. It was announced at MWC, but wasn't available to purchase until June. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump administration freezes EPA grants and contracts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HTC referred to the U Ultra as their 2017 flagship. Whether there will be another flagship phone released later in the year is a separate topic, but that doesn't take away from the fact that they launched a 2017 flagship with the Snapdragon 821. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. This reminds me of the kind of crap we were assigned to read in high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't affect the SIM card activation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daydream View discounted to $49 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 04:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they're having supply issues with only Verizon as a carrier partner, it'd probably be more of a supply mess had they expanded to other carriers. I wouldn't be surprised if Google expected this and led to them only going with Verizon. HTC just can't keep up with demand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time I've seen it that way. I've always come across it as DT2W. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah something is off. Every iPhone I've had, including my 7 Plus, hasn't shipped with the typical Android carrier bloatware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I do not want to see your house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one knows, but with shipping dates getting pushed back for those that already ordered, things aren't looking good. If they're having stock issues with just Play Store and VZW orders, I can only imagine how much more of a mess this would be had it launched with more carrier partners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure Cyborg's suit is a Transformer in disguise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not alone though. Samsung also treats the unlocked S7 and S7 Edge as second-class citizens. Both of those have lagged behind the carrier variants when it comes to updates. Heck, both weren't even allowed to partake in the Nougat beta program. Only certain carrier models had access to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They treat the unlocked G5 (RS988) like it doesn't exist. That one is still on the July security patch. Meanwhile, the carrier variants of it have gotten more security patch updates and most are already on Nougat. 

I honestly wasn't going to get the V20, but I came across a good deal and bought the unlocked US996 model expecting updates to be very delayed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Just the original gorillapod paired with a cheap tripod adapter I got from eBay a while back. I've been looking for a new setup, but I haven't gotten around to buying one yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joby GorillaPod </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! That is a great looking edit. I'm glad I ended up enabling RAW capture after noticing it was off for most of the shots I took that night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 05:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also have Snapseed installed, but I would not have thought of that. I still have a ways to go when it comes to post-processing. Haha. Definitely fun learning new techniques though. Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 05:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I owned a professional camera.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 05:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Thank you for doing this. This is exactly the image I had in mind when I first started to edit the file, but I had no clue how to go about it, especially since I'm just doing it through the Android app.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the [RAW file](https://drive.google.com/open?id=0BxV3IEbTJOKNd21BbWtrME40NTg). 

The photo came from my phone (LG V20) and my edit attempt is the image I posted. I'm still new to manual shooting and there's obviously a limit to what a phone can do. I did my editing on Lightroom for mobile. I haven't gotten around to understanding all the editing options it offers. I did most of my changes using the app's basic mode. I'm also colorblind so I usually try my best not to overdo it in post-processing, but that doesn't always work out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any way to improve this night photo? RAW linked in comments. Shot w/ LG V20 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice shot! Most of my night photos were with a 30 sec. exposure. I was using a Joby gorillapod and would place it on whatever I could. Depending on where I placed it, it wasn't always the most stable thing. I only noticed star trails starting to form if I slightly bumped the V20 at the beginning. 

You can brighten the image afterwards, but it's better to get a proper exposure while you're shooting rather than doing it in post-processing. As for extra brightness for a 15 sec exposure, all you can tweak is the ISO. However, if your main object is in the foreground and you just want the night sky for a background, you can use a light source to help you. 

[For example, this picture](http://i.imgur.com/T4myfWN.jpg). I placed the gorillapod on the back of a flimsy plastic chair in front of the tree. I had a small flashlight that could only light up a small section of the tree. I set the exposure for 25 sec. Once the V20 began shooting, I got below the tree and moved the flashlight back and forth to light paint most of the tree. Some odd looking star trails can be observed, but I think it had more to do with the phone not being on a really stable surface. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did some reading online, but most of the stuff I've learned so far has come from just playing with the app. Hopefully someone who knows far more than me can chime in.
 
If you don't have a very bright object in view, then you can bump up the exposure to get better night sky photos. In my case, the moon had already set so I didn't have to worry about it and I was in a very small town with minimal street lights. You can then tweak the ISO to get a brighter image. However, as you do this, you might start noticing more noise if you go with too high an ISO. Just so you get familiar with it, I'd start with a long exposure (say 15 sec.) and the lowest ISO. Keep the exposure the same, but increase the ISO for different shots just so you can observe how changing the ISO affects the image. You can do auto-focus, but I'd stick with controlling it manually. I stuck with an auto white balance since I'm colorblind. Thankfully, if you shoot in RAW, you can change the white balance afterwards. However, I've read that changing it manually while shooting leads to a better result rather than relying on editing the RAW file.

Check out the album I linked below showing three shots with exposure times of 10, 20, and 30 sec. I should've changed the ISO, but I kept it the same just to show how only tweaking exposure can lead to stars coming out brighter.

[Exposure from 10-30 sec. ISO kept constant](http://imgur.com/a/3sxKy) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mostly stayed with a 30 sec. exposure, but it sometimes varied between 20-30 sec. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Early morning low-light](http://imgur.com/a/0gora): I took these ones the morning after the night ones. The clouds started to come back, but I managed to catch some breaks in them and it made for some interesting shots as they were moving.

Took these photos over the weekend when I was in Mexico. All were shot in manual mode. Still learning as I go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LG V20 Night Shots (bonus in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BGR is a shit site </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Apps][Games] The Amazing Spider-Man 2 on sale for $0.99 from $6.99 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 05:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gameloft.android.ANMP.GloftASHM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This! The grayish hue the bezels have definitely put me off from the "quite black." Coming from phones that have pure black fronts, it just didn't look right to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LG G5 $349 AT T, Sprint, Verizon @ BestBuy (no contract) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 20:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The punishment is [death by snu snu](http://imgur.com/gallery/LxEj2uP) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. So why did you call *bullshit* on my original comment? Also, that wasn't me who downvoted you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 14:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The white doesn't look odd with a black front. Between the two, I prefer the titanium. I would've liked the marble more if it had more of a marbled pattern. The one I got is rather bland and looks more like a white skin. [This is more of what I was expecting](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CxvqMApVEAIrYF0.jpg), but since the marble pattern varies, it comes down to luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 14:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty common knowledge for most tech enthusiasts. Manufacturers tend to not provide any warranty support for products sold in a market they're not originally intended for.

[Amazon discusses it here](https://www.amazon.com/b?node=8160259011 pf_rd_p=2529313682 pf_rd_s=product-alert pf_rd_t=201 pf_rd_i=B01G9914OG pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER pf_rd_r=W4743XYZ1ZNVK8NCXF9R)

[This guy here found out first hand](https://www.amazon.com/review/R3I8NZI1CJXADE/ref=cm_cr_rdp_perm?ie=UTF8 ASIN=B01DCOOP5G) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 06:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All non-prepaid Verizon phones ship sim unlocked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 05:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tough truck that is hard to kill? [Hilux is always the answer](http://i.imgur.com/LpnUOsH.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 02:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Jalops always have a soft spot in their heart for Australian muscle](http://jalopnik.com/they-are-awaited-at-valhalla-the-australian-v8-falcon-1787558890) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 00:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're in the US, international models do not come with any manufacturer warranty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 19:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [When interest becomes passion...](http://i.imgur.com/dPkpqHF.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 20:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I stopped caring for his videos for a while now. If you want fancy shots, he's the go to one, but for great review content that actually goes below the surface, there are others that do a much better job. Some have already been mentioned: 

* Flossy Carter
* Michael Fisher (though I preferred him more on Pocketnow)
* Juan Carlos Bagnell (Pocketnow)
* Joshua Vergara (Android Authority)
* Max Lee
* SuperSaf TV
* Erica Griffin
* Tim Schofield
* MobileTechReview
* JimsReviewRoom

Aaron Baker was by far my favorite though. Such a shame he's no longer doing YouTube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current V20 owner here. The dual camera setup is great, but LG needs to release a software update to tweak its performance. As an example, one has to be careful when HDR is enabled. In full light, it gets the job done. However, indoors and in low light conditions, if HDR is enabled, say goodbye to your picture quality. It ends up looking over processed and quite odd. I've owned quite a few devices this year and this is the first time I've come across a situation where HDR does this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 03:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [dbrand](http://imgur.com/a/IQd0j) works fine with the [Z Play](http://imgur.com/a/fLp4O) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Play Music 50% Off Any Album (Redeem by January 28th, 2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Success! Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Yep both work well with the SW skin on the back. Keep in mind that I haven't installed the skins that go on the top and bottom section so I'm not sure if that would cause any issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Incipio cases for the V20 (Carnaby + NGP) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 15:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought these cases while Incipio was running their sale. Both work great with Skinomi's full coverage screen protector. I'll keep the info basic here since I put more notes in the imgur links below for both cases.

[Incipio Carnaby Esquire Series](http://imgur.com/a/Wvrrs): Nicest looking of the two. Incipio doesn't drop rate this case but it looks like it should provide some good protection. Fits great and all the cutouts are correct. As nice as it is, the MSRP is a bit high.

[Incipio NGP Advanced](http://imgur.com/a/mou7L): My favorite one. Slightly thinner than the Carnaby and provides better grip. Incipio drop rates this case for 5 ft. One con is that the power button cutout is a bit steep. I can still use the fingerprint sensor fine, but a more angled cutout would've been nice.

The other stuff in the pictures:

* [Skinomi TechSkin Full Coverage](http://imgur.com/a/bx3hn)
* [Slickwraps Matte Black](http://imgur.com/a/wrRQO) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 13:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I encountered the same issue with my S7 Edge back in May. Others did as well. No matter the fix I tried, whether it was the phone or messing with my router, nothing fixed it. I believe most were able to fix it, but nothing worked in my situation and I ended up getting rid of it. I blamed it on faulty hardware with the phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 13:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The carrier models have it, but the unlocked US G5 does not have Nougat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. If I spend most of the day on LTE, I get at least 4 hrs. How much I can squeeze past those 4 depends on the signal quality. On the other end, if I spend a good chunk on wifi, I can easily make it to 6 hrs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlocked phones have it, but it's called [Mobile Services Manager](http://i.imgur.com/7X3ojn8.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those that don't see it, it's called Mobile Services Manager. I disabled that sucker right away after seeing it burned through 100+ MB of data the second day I had the phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Usually" is the keyword. I usually blame the carriers for slow updates, but this year has showed me that isn't the case with LG and Samsung. Both of them have released unlocked U.S. models and both have treated those phones like second-class citizens. The unlocked G5, S7, and S7 Edge have all lagged behind in updates when compared to the carrier models. The unlocked G5 (RS988) is still on the July security patch and hasn't received Nougat yet. Meanwhile, carrier models have already been receiving the update and have gotten more consistent security patch updates. I wouldn't be surprised if the carriers are the ones pushing to get the updates out quicker and LG pretty much has to comply.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they're going to say that. The most important thing they want to sell you is Verizon's service. The phone pretty much comes second. With the exception of prepaid phones, all Verizon phones ship unlocked, whether purchased full price or on a payment plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully most decide not to show any courage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 13:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't recall the last time I've ever used the search widget. I always go straight to the browser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gotten skins from both. Quality wise, both use 3M material and are precisely cut. It mainly comes down to customization. With dbrand, you can mix and match skins to get a unique look. Going with Slickwraps, you get a skin that will be the same design for every part of the phone.

In regards to shipping times, both can be a hit or miss. My last two orders from dbrand took a week for it to leave their facility in NY. However, both of those orders occurred during sales and delays were expected. My last Slickwraps order shipped within a couple of days. They're based out of Kansas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LG isn't even trying. Marketing is pretty much non-existent and they're not even selling the V20 in Europe. Besides, LG took a long ass time to launch the phone in the U.S. They weren't even smart enough to have V20 retail units out by the time the second Note 7 recall began.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the [Incipio Esquire Series](http://imgur.com/a/hXyxE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Force has a flat screen. The Play, like the regular Moto Z, has glass that curves slightly along the edges. This is why the Force can have full screen tempered glass protectors and the other two need to have them cut short. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 03:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chris Chavez from Phandroid did [this same thing via uBreakiFix](https://www.google.com/amp/phandroid.com/2016/10/24/really-blue-google-pixel-black-front/amp/) back in October. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phones can be sold without being fully paid off. It's one of the negatives that came with the carriers moving away from the two year contract. As long as payments are still being made, the IMEI will appear clean. Once the payments stop, that's when it'll get blacklisted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do this with any carrier. I frequently buy and sell phones and have come across a lot of things. This type of scam became popular after carriers moved away from the two year contract. Payment plans don't show up in an IMEI search (I believe T-Mo does show EIP though) and the phone comes back clean. Even getting this info from some carriers is not possible. I've asked Verizon reps multiple times for various phones if they could check if a phone is still financed, but they can't say anything. As long as the original owner continues making device payments, the phone's IMEI will stay clean. However, once they stop, that's when it gets blacklisted. So a scammer can continue to make payments and stop after a few months and the buyer gets screwed. 

This happened to me with the Note 5 last year. Neither eBay nor PayPal were on my side even though I was within the six month period and provided info showing it blacklisted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 14:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> !Remind me 666 days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 04:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends. As you stated, the international version won't get warranty support. If something goes wrong within a year, then LG won't be able to help. Second, if it doesn't come with all of your carrier's bands, you're going to have subpar network performance, especially if it's missing an important LTE band. You can check out the [US carrier bands here](http://www.phonearena.com/news/Cheat-sheet-which-4G-LTE-bands-do-AT-T-Verizon-T-Mobile-and-Sprint-use-in-the-USA_id77933) and compare it to the ones the phone has. If you plan on keeping this phone for a while, then the next point likely won't matter, but an unlocked international model won't do well when it comes to the resale value. Their prices tend to drop the fastest and some buyers may be turned away from an international variant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 02:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> International version won't be CDMA compatible and it could be missing certain LTE bands used by the US GSM carriers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I didn't keep my unlocked S7 and S7 Edge devices for long. One of the perks of going unlocked is supposed to be for quicker updates, but Samsung never got the memo. I'll likely go with a carrier variant S8 in 2017. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 18:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I've never lied on one and still consistently get them. 

However, there was one survey I got twice that asked me if I was older than 25. The only options were yes or no. Seeing as how I'm 25, I was having trouble picking the best answer. Technically speaking, I am older since my birthday has passed, but no one puts 25.4 when filling out their age. I selected no and moved on. Less than a month goes by and I get the same survey. Answered yes this time and that was the last I saw of it. Like give me an option for "I am 25"! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 03:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's there for basic scratch protection. Skins are meant to provide any protection beyond that. 

As for the camera glass shattering, I don't believe it's a big issue. The people that have encountered it are very vocal about it. This is usually the case for most products. People that don't encounter issues don't feel a need to bring it up, but once something bad happens, that's when people start speaking up. For every person that reports the camera shattering, there are more out there that haven't cracked. Also, this isn't the first time it has been brought up for a device. Both the Nexus 6P and Galaxy S7 also had reports early on of the camera glass shattering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 01:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't get them to show up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always had reliability/performance issues with Samsung fingerprint sensors. With the recent Synaptics talk for the S8, hopefully 2017 brings a better fingerprint experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those having the issue, some good info to provide would be the manufacturing date. It should be listed on the box. If not, look at your serial number (not the IMEI), and the first three digits should tell you the year/month.

For example: 

* 611 = 2016 and November </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This [dbrand V20 install video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h6T322MdpJo) should do the trick. Definitely gotta have a hair dryer on hand to get the sides to properly stick along the curved back plate. To install the camera skin, I stuck it to some scotch tape, hovered over the camera section to align the cutouts, and firmly pressed down. Removing the scotch tape afterwards won't remove the camera skin since its 3M adhesive is stronger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've used skins from both of them for previous devices and they're pretty much the same. If I had to pick one, I'd say I lean more towards dbrand, especially since they offer more customization. In regards to fitment, both provide precise cutouts.

I did have one negative quality experience with Slickwraps a couple years back. After I ordered a red carbon skin from them, I found out they switched to another vinyl supplier since they couldn't get red carbon from 3M. The skin arrived and it was crap. The carbon weave looked and felt odd. Since then, I have never ordered a carbon skin from them. They've likely switched back to 3M since then (the matte black V20 skin is by 3M), but that negative experience sticks with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's very slippery. I had a few close calls with the phone before the skin arrived. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really varies with dbrand, especially if there's a sale going on. My past two orders from them have been as follows:

* **Ordered**: Nov. 8 **Shipped**: Nov. 15 **Reveived**: Nov 17
* **Ordered**: Nov. 28 **Shipped**:  Dec. 9 **Received**: Dec. 12

My prior experiences with SW have been similar to dbrand. Sometimes they ship out quickly, but other times it can take a while. I decided to take a chance with the V20 skins since SW is located in Kansas and tend to arrive quicker. I ordered my matte black skin last week and received it yesterday, which happens to be the same day my Nov. 28 order from dbrand arrived. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Minimal Protection Setup (Skinomi + Slickwraps) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently just using Skinomi's screen protector and a back skin from Slickwraps. Pictures and more detailed notes can be seen in the links below.

[Slickwraps Matte Black](http://imgur.com/a/wrRQO)

[Skinomi TechSkin Full Coverage Screen Protector](http://imgur.com/a/bx3hn)

The Slickwraps skin also comes with sections for the top and bottom of the phone, but I decided not to install those yet. I'm pleased with both products. I usually go with dbrand, but since I never expected to get the V20, I needed the skin to arrive quick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got mine new from Moto for $368 w/ tax back in October. I stacked my unidays discount with a 5% discount Moto had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 02:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Android's Holo skin! Sweet throwback </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm probably in the small group, but I honestly don't care what people do with their Note 7. I decided to return mine just to get my money back. If someone wants to keep their device, that's his or her choice. I'm not going to try and convince someone to do something they don't want to do. 

I do miss my Note 7 though :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 23:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some credit cards have a feature where they'll cover smartphone repair costs. It's sorta like a warranty/protection coverage. You may have to look into it more, but I believe it works as long as you pay your phone bill with a credit card. You don't necessarily have to purchase the phone with that same credit card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 05:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the force and absolutely loved it. I'd still be using it if I didn't sell it shortly after getting my second Note 7. Battery life between it and the Z Play is pretty big. On the Z Force, I would get between 4.5-5 hrs of SOT between charges. With the Z Play, I'm usually in the 8.5-9.5 hr range. The camera on the Z Force was a bit better, but not by much. It only slightly pulls ahead when it comes to low light performance. I never had the opportunity to hold both next to each other to compare displays, but I'd say they're even, unless you need that extra ppi for VR stuff. With regards to feel, the Z Force felt a bit odd in the hand when I first took it out the box. I got used to it, but I'd give overall feel to the Z Play. Software performance on both is great. From memory, I'd say the Force was ever so slightly faster, but it's really nothing too noticeable. I never experienced any noticeable performance issues with either device. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verizon doesn't mess around with security updates. My dad's Verizon G4 got the November security patch earlier this week. Also, I was surprised to see my $10 Verizon Moto E get the October security patch a couple days back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 21:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlocked US model (US996): October security patch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 01:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gone through a lot of phones this year and it was by far my favorite. Still miss it. At least I have [these photos of the beauty](http://imgur.com/a/2aI5o) :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sometimes connect my phone to the Samsung T3 Portable SSD. Both utilize a Type-C connection and I can easily watch movies from it or transfer content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that place! Haha. Another Tucsonan here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's likely some clause in the initial paperwork that allows them to do something like this and protects them from any legal problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 13:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the photos that were shown, the shade of gold they went with is too bright. The gold on the white model is a lot more subdued. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It started off as a Verizon employee exclusive color, but that stopped a while back. I almost ordered that color scheme from Moto's site, but after seeing some listings on Swappa and eBay, I wasn't feeling it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Skinomi techskin](http://imgur.com/a/FJvBV) for me. Still looks good and covers the entire glass. It may cause compatibility issues with some cases, but it has worked fine with the Tech21 and Incipio DualPro cases.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mophie Juice Pack - $79.99](https://www.motorola.com/us/products/moto-mods/mophie-juice-pack?utm_source=CJ utm_medium=affiliate utm_campaign=7706071 PublisherName=Skimlinks) too, but Verizon was already selling that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Incipio Vehicle Dock now for sale - $64.99 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until Google is able to maintain a stable stock of Pixels, I don't think they're going to be doing discounts anytime soon on their store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got mine yesterday and I'm in Arizona. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 14:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had both and prefer the Z Play. It's a lot more consistent than the X Pure and the photos come out looking better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in October, we heard that Samsung would be accepting returns for third-party purchases. People called them and were given a ticket number after providing all the necessary info. We were told we would get a refund by check within 10-14 business days (yeah right lol).

In regards to the exchange, at the time I called, the rep I talked to specifically stated they weren't accepting exchanges and that my only option would be a refund. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 23:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! Got mine today as well. Others on Android Central are also reporting receiving their checks today. I actually called this morning since I wanted an update after not getting that third email (169) about the check being sent out. I was caught off-guard since the rep answered the phone immediately. Nice change after the 40+ minute wait that used to happen lol. The rep stated the check was sent out on December 2. She said it would be by UPS, but that was obviously wrong. Total for my Verizon Note 7 was $958.98. I put my timeline below in case anybody is curious.

**Timeline**:

* Oct. 12 - Called to start the return process
* Oct. 17 - Received fireproof box
* Oct. 25 - Samsung gets my Note 7
* Nov. 22 - Email stating a compensation request has been submitted (167)
* Nov. 27 - Email about the compensation request being approved and is processing (168)
* Dec. 5 - Payday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To answer any questions someone may have and to also keep track of the Note 7 returns/refunds. Quite a few of us around here are still waiting for the refund checks to arrive and to put the whole mess behind us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely a noticeable jump going from the Z Force to the Z Play. The Z Force would easily last me into the second day, but I'd have to charge it a lot sooner than I do with the Z Play. I don't remember the figures off the top of my head, but I'm certain I have some Z Force battery life screenshots saved on my home computer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 20:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had all three. I first got the regular Moto Z.  I didn't even take off any of the plastic. I just used it for a couple days at home and just wasn't feeling it. Way too thin for my liking and I didn't like the camera on it. I next got the Z Force and absolutely loved it. Camera was great, performance was top notch, and battery life was awesome. I'd still be using it if I didn't get the Note 7 :( After getting the Note, I sold the Z Force since I thought I'd be sticking with the Note for a while. Big mistake. After returning my Note 7, I bought the Z Play Droid. I got it since I loved the experience on the Z Force and it was much cheaper. It pretty much matches all the pros from the Z Force. For my usage, performance has been excellent. I haven't noticed any noticeable slowdowns. The camera takes great photos (much better than the regular Moto Z) and battery life is the best. Between the Z Force and Z Play, it'd be tough for me to pick a favorite. Value for the money definitely goes to the Play, but there's still something about the Force that makes me regret selling it so quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 14:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in mind that Verizon likely had a lot to do with it since the Moto Z line all came out first on Verizon. The Moto X Pure Edition launched last year at a base price of $400. It was sold solely unlocked and without any carrier carrying it. If it was the same way with the Z line, I could see them selling at a lower price, but carriers like to include a markup and Verizon probably included some clause stating that the unlocked Moto Z and Z Play couldn't have a cheaper MSRP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 04:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta go with the band-aid phone. The Galaxy S5 looked alright from the front, but that thing went straight into a case right after I got it. The chromed plastic frame was terrible and the charging port flap was so cheap feeling. The flap was also prone to falling out and it made the phone even uglier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 04:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The home button placement still annoys me to this day. OCD triggered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
