<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wedding industry professionals what are your pet peeves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 19:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People of Flint Want You to See These Images of the Water They Were Told Was Safe to Drink </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 22:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steven Seagal gets Serbian citizenship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 18:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of far-right protesters rampage through German town, destroying ethnic restaurants and takeaways - hours after Merkel admits European migrant crisis is 'out of control' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 16:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Jersey State Lottery Law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 18:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I decided to play lottery after hearing about monster jackpot. After doing some research I found out that winner in NJ can't stay anonymous. I also found out that some states allow LLC or Trust Fund to claim the prize allowing winner to stay antonyms. Unfortunately I was not able to find specific instructions as to if and how would that work in NJ. Is anyone familiar with this matter? 

I know that chances of winning are 292 million to 1, but on an off chance that someone does win it would be a good idea if we would educate each other on how it would work in our state. 

[STATE LOTTERY LAW](http://www.state.nj.us/lottery/about/legislation/STATE%20LOTTERY%20LAW.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Howell woman faces fines for nursing baby squirrels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 15:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a gym with the pool in Northern New Jersey? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 01:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured you guys maybe able to give me honest opinion. I'm looking for a decent gym with the pool in Clifton area ... 

Edit: Did anyone try Garfield YMCA?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edison cop fired after 'lingerie episode' will get his job back, judge rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 16:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYPD to spend more than $700,000 to buy automatic weapons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 18:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AT T To End Two-Year Contracts Starting 2016 As Carriers Abandon Subsidies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 17:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Darko Milicic interview after Serbian Representation lost international game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 06:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any decent alternatives for Sony NP-FW50 batteries? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 21:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using the cage so grip is not an option. I could maybe work with a battery pack here and there, but I can't afford to power it all day with bulky battery pack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> List of NBA related players currently playing in China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 16:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FDA Approval Could Turn A Free Drug For A Rare Disease Pricey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 06:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran Sanctions Could Be Lifted As Soon As January </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 06:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any advice for selling high end used lenses/cameras and photo/video gear on ebay and craigslist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 03:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking about starting to flip used gear online. I have a lot of friends who are photographers/videographers and for the most part I have been selling to them and their colleagues, friends, etc ... In the last few month I have accumulated little more gear so I would like to find the way to expand market. Is this merchandise easy to move online? If so what should I go for, high margin or quick turnaround? How important it is to have box and instructions when selling online? As far as scammers is it safer to sell only to people in North America? Also any other advice that you think is relevant would be really appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lakewood rabbi sentenced to 10 years in prison for divorce kidnappings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 17:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MILITARY FLU419 UNIMOG LOADER/BACKHOE WITH HYDRAULIC TOOLS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 16:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fiat 126, or is it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 23:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Burr on Steve Jobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 16:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As someone how has absolutely no interest in Star Wars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 07:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newark   LaGuardia Are The Worst Airports In America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 15:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kosovo parliament hit by fresh tear-gas protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 16:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kosovo opposition uses tear gas in parliament to protest deals with Serbia, Montenegro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 15:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do they decide on national TV schedule? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 05:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More specifically why do Lakers have so many nationally televised games? Everyone knew their team will suck this year, yet it seems to me that every time I turn on the TV they are broadcasting Lakers game. For example there was so many games that would be much more interesting tonight, yet we are here watching commentators talking about football during a basketball game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When do tickets for " The Hateful Eight " go on sale? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 05:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I talked to a local theater manager and he told me rather this past Monday or Tuseday, since than I have checked every single day and there is still no information about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> " Custom " Skoda 110r </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 05:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby teaching yoga </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 02:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA for people living in NYC: You Have Until the End of December to Get Free Museum and Zoo Memberships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 00:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ansel Adams Job Opening in US Govt Pays ~$100,000 Per Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 22:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malaysia hunts owners of Boeing 747s abandoned at airport </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 18:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adults' Attack On Students At Brick Memorial Game Under Investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 15:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Passengers on the flight Frankfurt - Belgrade stopped a Jordanian who wanted to get into the cockpit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 15:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grandpa at little league soccer game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 21:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for somewhat unusual website template? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 21:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for template that would allow visitors to add/edit content. I have a large family scattered all over the world and after getting my hands on few boxes worth of old family photos I realized that more or less I have no idea who are the people in these photos. Some of them are dating back to early 20th century so people who actually know names, events, locations, etc ... are becoming harder and harder to find. Idea is to preserve family history and don't forget who we were and where are we coming from. Basically I would like to create a personal website where my family and friends can add old family photos in to specific classified galleries together with short description of events, location, names of people in images. 

I have very little experience with website development other than using a squarespace theme for my small business, so anything that would require me writing my own code is pretty much out of the question. 

If you know of any templates or have an idea how narrow down a search for something that could work for this purpose please leave a link/advice in comments. 

**EDIT** - I found what I'm looking for www.piwigo.org simple to use, looks great and there is about 140 different designs!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every Black Friday i stay home and at the end of the day I check out this site </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 04:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wayne Police: NJ Woman Posts Silly Piggies Tricks R For U On Social Media After Filing False Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 15:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This VW beetle was made out of wood by retired carpenter Momir Bojic from Bosnia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Wedding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 05:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Croatian Prime Minister falling of the armored vehicle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 20:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This farmer repeatedly asked people not to park on his land ... They didn't listen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 02:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL 8 year old Momcilo Gavric was the youngest solder in WWI. By the age of 10 he earned Albanian Commemorative Medal, was wounded once, promoted to the rank of Lance Sergeant. When he reached draft age he was jailed for two month because recruiter did not believe that he already served in WWI. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 07:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Jersey school to permit medical marijuana for students </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 00:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Jersey school to permit medical marijuana for students </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 00:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Jersey school to permit medical marijuana for students </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 00:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Knicks draft pick Michael Wright found dead of head wound and covered in garbage bags in SUV in Brooklyn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 17:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Billy Joel - We Didn't Start the Fire [ Rock n' Roll ] ... lyrics and history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 22:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most negative song that almost everyone instantly sings along? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 20:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Devil is in the detail. Josip Broz Tito showing his medal to Queen Elizabeth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 15:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Devil is in the detail. Josip Broz Tito showing his medal to Queen Elizabeth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 15:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Serena Williams chases phone thief  CCTV video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 16:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confederate flag supporter throws bomb at Mississippi Walmart after threatening store in Facebook post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 19:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I believe that Redditor in question was part of this community until recently. Maybe someone here knows how to reach out to him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 17:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found this post on /r/rage and I think that person in question will recognize him self. He deserves to know what was the reason why he stopped losing weight, so with that in mind please share this on all relevant subs. 

https://www.reddit.com/r/rage/comments/3rgz6w/overweight_guy_tries_to_lose_weight_gf_sabotages/

P.S. I hope this post is not violating any rules of this sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This [X - Post] from /r/rage needs to be seen by a fellow Redditor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 17:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has the right to know, so please share following post on all relevant subs. 

https://www.reddit.com/r/rage/comments/3rgz6w/overweight_guy_tries_to_lose_weight_gf_sabotages/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I see list of candidates for todays election in Passaic County? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 15:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fabrice Monteiro shows Senegal's pollution with garbage garments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 21:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10000 strong amateur choir from Osaka Japan sings Beethoven's - Ode To Joy - Explanation link in comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 05:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There was a massive fire in my neighborhood tonight. These are some of the guys that kept us safe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 07:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting ready to jump in the fire! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 06:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to approach TV station/local newspaper with footage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 06:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the thing. I witnessed the massive apartment building fire in my neighborhood tonight. I had my camera with me so I started filming and taking pictures. Somehow cops thought that I was with one of the fire departments ( there was 7 or 8 different fire departments responding ) and no one bothered me so I managed to get extremely close to the whole thing. There was no TV crews or reporters of any kind on the scene but I just saw local TV station talking about the fire but no footage. 

That got me wondering if I could maybe sell them some of mine footage. Since I have absolutely no experience with dealing with them I was wondering if someone could give me an advice or two. For what is worth my location is Northern New Jersey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Educational - The Story of OSHA - This film was produced and banned by OSHA. Unions found to violate the ban lost all their OSHA funding benefits - 1980 - [ X-Post /r/OldFootage ] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 16:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amateur Video - Bethlehem, Palestine - 07.23.1933 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 16:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FDR Inaugural Speech - Washington DC - March 4, 1933 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 15:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Educational - How to fly P-47 Thunderbolt - 1943 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 15:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Educational - The Story of OSHA - This film was produced and banned by OSHA. Unions found to violate the ban lost all their OSHA funding benefits - 1980 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 15:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex Baltimore cop Michael Wood gives brutally honest interview on the Joe Rogan Experience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 02:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex Baltimore cop Michael Wood gives brutally honest interview on the Joe Rogan Experience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 01:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA - Apollo 13: Houston, We've Got a Problem - April 17 1970 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 01:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Color footage of soldiers being exposed to high levels of radiation - Date/Location Unknown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 01:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Football Helmet - Inventor demonstrates helmet by having people kick him in the head with baseball bat and by running in to a brick wall head first - 1932 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 01:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to lower my Optimum bill? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 01:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically I'm looking for tips as to how to approach customer service. Currently I'm paying over $200 for TV, internet and phone and I would like to cut that as much as possible. Original contract with Optimum expired about 6 years ago and I can't change providers so I have to deal with them. Naturally they know that too so in the past it really didn't get me anywhere. Any advice is appreciated!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 sec. New York State [ 5616x3744 ] Please critique first time shooting Milky Way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 22:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mapping Migration in the United States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 13:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pulp Fiction: Cast and Crew Reunion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 05:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Launch of the USS Arizona Battleship - Brooklyn Navy Yard - June 19, 1915 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 20:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newsreel: Closing of Brooklyn Navy Yard closing after 165 years of service - Brooklyn, NY - 1966 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 20:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV Show - You Asked For It - Bela Lugosi performing magic trick - 1952 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 00:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merv Griffin Show - Rosa Parks Interview - 1983 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 00:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone recognize the player sitting on Doc's left side? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 00:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://i.imgur.com/D22wBw4.jpg) is one of my favorite pictures of Celtics and since the moment I saw it the first time I thought to my self. Damn imagine being that guy whose face is covered with Doc's arm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Le Mans disaster which killed 84 people - June 1955 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 00:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Educational - Propaganda Techniques - 1949 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 00:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buried Alive Stunt Goes Wrong - Magician Alan Alan decides to bury himself alive naked in a grave and then attempt to escape - Manchester, England - 1949 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 16:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Cyclin Sins - 1936 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 16:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ride over George Washington Bridge and trough Northern New Jersey - 1950s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 16:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Francisco Earthquake Aftermath - 1906 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 05:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Be a Sucker - 1947 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 03:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AT T Instructional Video - How to Use the Dial Phone - 1927 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 03:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Private Life of a Cat - 1947 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 01:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/OldFootage ... The name says it all, all original footage that is 30 years or older is welcomed. Anything form funny old commercials and home movies to authentic historic battle footage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 00:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Howard Hughes' Spruce Goose Flight - Amateur Footage by Leo Caloia - Long Beach Harbor, CA - November 2, 1947 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 20:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Record G force testing 47g, 632MPH to 0 in one second - John Paul Stapp father of crash test dummy - Holloman Air Force Base, New Mexico - December 12, 1954 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 20:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police Training Video - United States - 1968 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Collection of early special effects - 1900s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humorous Phases Of Funny Faces - Chalkboard Animation - 1906 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Motorcycle Parachute Jump - Los Angles, CA - 1926 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1914 British Recruits Sabre Drill - British Calvary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Funeral of Nikola Tesla with original sound recording played at his funeral - New York City 1943 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Morrison form the band The Doors talking about future of music - Late 1960s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The knife-thrower Louella Gallagher throws knives at her daughters Connie Ann, 5, and Colleena Sue, 2.5 yrs old, in Austin, Texas - 1950s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fist assassination caught on film - King Alexander Karadjordjevic of Yugoslavia - Marseilles, France - October 9, 1934 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OldFootage ... New sub dedicates to any and all footage that is 30 years or older </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First I would like to thank /r/history mod for giving me a green light to promote this sub with this self post! 

Stop by OldFootage we would love to see you there. Help us expand community and don't forget to post, comment and subscribe! If you have any ideas for the sub please share them here or send me a PM.  

P.S. If this post is braking any /r/history rules that I'm not aware of mods please take it down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/OldFootage/ Come and share any footage that is 30 years or older </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 17:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/OldFootage/ ... Sub dedicated to any and all footage that is 30 years or older </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 17:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Construction footage of Hoover Dam, 1933-1935 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 16:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to avoid parking ticket - Germany - 1959 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 16:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parking problem solving - Paris, France - 1927 [ Why is this not a standard on all vehicles? ] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 16:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newsreel: The Wonderful Uses of Asbestos - 1942 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 16:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/OldFootage ... If footage is 30 years or older it belongs to this sub. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 04:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germans Destroy Their Own Railroads - 1945 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 04:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberian coup d'tat - 1980 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 04:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blindfolded Mens Boxing - The New Sport of 1949 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 04:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Around The World In Four Minutes 1920s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 04:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Panama Canal Construction - "Through the Canal Bottom" - 1912 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newsreel: WWII Polish Refugees In Iran Fight For Freedom - 1943 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adriatic coast vacation - Home movie - Yugoslavia - 1960s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marilyn Monroe sings happy B-Day Mr. President at Madison Square Garden - New York City - May 19, 1962 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hindenburg Disaster, Hoboken, NJ - 1937 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert F Kennedy Announcing The Death Of Martin Luther King - April 4th, 1968 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newsreel - Gangsters In India - 1942 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saturday Night Live - Episode One Monologue One by George Carlin - October 11, 1975 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Last Mille Miglia 1000 mile race trough Northern Italy - 1957 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York Fire Brigade - 1893 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Titanic Before Its Last Voyage in 1912 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Francisco Earthquake - 1906 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This sub will not survive without your support. Don't forget to comment, post and subscribe! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I find casters that I need? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 06:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to replace the casters on my [Tripod Dolly](http://www.amazon.com/dp/B006TZ8R3W/ref=wl_it_dp_o_pC_nS_ttl?_encoding=UTF8 colid=3T0I55OQE8OSF coliid=I3C2PDPEV2SC8E) Basically I need 3" ball bearing caster with threaded stem. I have been looking for them for few month now and no luck. 

I would really appreciate if someone could point me to the right direction or recommend alternative. 

Casters should be as smooth as possible and easily transition from surface to surface without getting stuck. I'm will be using this for videography and I'm trying to avoid "bumps" during filming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone share some tips for filming fireworks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 21:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be using a7s and canon L glass. I'm planing to shoot 4th of July fireworks in Manhattan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about focus peeking on A7S? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 03:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just picked up A7S and [Commlite adapter](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00F3ZFQK6?psc=1 redirect=true ref_=oh_aui_detailpage_o00_s00) for Canon EF lenses. For some reason I can only use one focus mode and that is Single-shot AF. I would like to change it to DMF or MF mode so I can use constant focus peeking. When I attempt to change the setting I get following error message "Invalid With This Lens" 

For the record I tried multiple lenses. 35 2.0f IS, 16-35 II, 24-70 "old version, 70-200 2.8f IS II

I also tried to reconnect adapter to camera/lens, change battery, etc ... 

I really hope I can find the workaround because I really like the camera and I love my current glass!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.J. man urinated into slot machine, resisted cops, police say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 21:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Googled "Skinheads with confederate flags" ... was not disappointed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about A7S warranty? [Existing gear] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 23:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm tinkling of picking up A7S and I was wondering if anyone had any experience with Sony customer service. Basically what I would like to know is if I purchase new camera on Ebay from un authorized dealer for example will Sony honor manufacturers warranty. 

I know that officially no one does but, I know from personal experience that Canon will honor manufacturers warranty especially if you are CPS member.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Kevin Garnett, Paul Pierce, and Ray Allen brought the Celtics back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remove Ellen Pao from her job as Reddit CEO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 05:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NJSP fire tear gas into angry Summer Jam concert crowd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A7R Order Update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 19:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just called Sony at this number 877-865-7669 automated message is stating that all orders have been canceled and money will be refunded ... 

Edit: Just for the record I know of at least 5 different orders that were not yet canceled by Sony. I guess it is anyones guess if they will send actual emails to everyone that placed the order.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 year old girl from Serbia singing song "At Last" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 18:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yes, Despite a Lawsuit in West Virginia, It's Constitutional for Public Schools to Teach Evolution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 06:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charles   David Koch $1,000,000,000.00 Pledge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure that some of you have thought about this too. Nevertheless I wanted to point this out in simplest possible way.

 In order to offset Koch brothers political contribution for 2016 presidential elections alone, each registered voter in US would need to donate about $7 to the same candidate. 

Koch brothers "freedom of speech" is about 150,000,000.00 greater than your or mine!

That is why we need Bernie, and that is why you need to talk to anyone that would listen until their ears bleed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 51 people packed in a van - Police cam shows van carries 51 workers packed inside van in China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 01:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kidnap Victims Family Kicks Down Door, Kills Abductor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Christie spent $300,000 on food and drink over first 5 years in office, including $82,000 on concessions at Jets and Giants games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 16:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Christie spent $300,000 on food and drink over first 5 years in office, including $82,000 on concessions at Jets and Giants games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 16:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human Zoo in Brussels, Belgium white spectator interacting with young black child 1958 [400x320] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 17:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Place for Breast-Feeding Mothers at New York Area Airports </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 05:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [X Post] Russian Cirque de Solei </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 05:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here are statistics, voting records and ratings for Bernie from insidegov.com ... Really useful info! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 18:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On today's day 35 years ago we lost great leader of a small nation. Founding member of Non-Aligned Movement. To this date he had second largest state funeral with officials from 128 countries including 4 kings, 31 presidents, 6 princes, 22 prime ministers and 47 ministers of foreign affairs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 22:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honestly, I don't really care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 04:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AT T fires president over racist text, still faces $100M discrimination lawsuit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 02:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After years of searching I have finally found my one and only diploma! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 19:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear California, this is what rain looks like! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 17:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X-Post from r/videos ... Library security guard secretly record while playing piano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 17:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are you doing on MayDay! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 20:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was looking for ideas/events in NY/NJ area for MayDay celebration and naturally nothing worth mentioning is happening. We used to go out of town for massive picnics or concerts, but since this is not a national holiday in US and I don't have lot of family here that is not an option. 

Give me some ideas Reddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BRONX WOMAN MARRIED 10 TIMES NOW CHARGED WITH NOT PAYING SUBWAY FARE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 15:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harden: 'I am the MVP' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 01:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anonymous keeps its promise to Vineland N.J. Police Department and doxxes two police officers details </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 18:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Civilians Can Record Police Encounters, But When Is It Interference? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 18:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Real Reason College Tuition Costs So Much </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 03:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victim alleges rapper DMX robbed him in Newark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 00:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wieliczka Salt Mine in Poland is a 700 year old slot mine that closed in 2007. Today it houses 29 different chapels and it is about 178 miles long and 1073ft deep. Everything inside is carved out of salt including statues and chandeliers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 15:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-gay "pastor" charged with stealing $150K...blames gays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 01:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We can play Pac-Man on Google Maps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 16:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X-Post from /r/ANormalDayInRussia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 22:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> found this old picture of my uncle, he was NYC cab driver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 02:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve Nash announces retirement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 19:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Costco package question? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 03:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This just popped up on my FB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 00:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> STOP GOV. CHRISTIES BIG BREAK TO EXXON ... This petitions is about New Jersey and not political affiliation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 00:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran's Foreign Minister responds to the letter from 47 Republican Senators </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 21:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remembering Rosa Luxemburg   Clara Zetkin on International Women's Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 18:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friend of mine just posted this on FB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 15:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X-Post from /r/BlackPeopleTwitter/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 05:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My neighbor didn't want to move his car even though he was at home so snowplow can do his job ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 03:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Spanish actress lied about going to the Oscars, gets busted, her career is a lie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 18:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the easiest way of communication with deaf couple? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 18:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We were contacted by deaf couple that is interested in hiring us to photograph their wedding. So far we exchanged few emails and I talked to brides mother once. I would love to be able to talk to couple personally and get their perspective directly form them. Meeting them in person is not an option because they are located in another state and wedding would take place in brides hometown (my state)

What would be best way for us to communicate other than email? Also any advice how to communicate on the day of the wedding? Unfortunately no one in our office knows sign language. Would it be out of the question to ask one of the family members to accompany us during bridal shoot? 

I apologize if this sound like a stupid question. I have very little experience in this matter so I would like to educate my self as much as possible in order to make this process as smooth as possible. 

EDIT: Thanks everyone! This helps a lot! Just keep them coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police investigate snowball fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 17:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 players from the Celtics bench scored 60 points tonight combined. Starting 5 Celtics scored 46 points combined. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 03:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exxon Settles $9 Billion Pollution Case in New Jersey for Far Less </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 02:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about USPS insurance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 22:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First let me say I'm not a flipper, however I purchase things on Ebay/Amazon all the time and this is the first time I have problem. Seller did his part, but it looks like that post office messed things up with delivery.

I didn't receive the package even though seller send it to me, and on USPS site it does show that package was delivered. I talked to my mailman and he does not remember delivering package to me on that day. Also I talked to supervisor at the post office. She showed me some paper where my apartment number was not specified on the address. That is strange because my address is verified by Ebay and PayPal and it clearly shows my APT number...

 Basically her answer to me was that if mailman does not remember what he did with the package my shit is out of luck ...

Given that you guys are dealing with situations like this more often than most people any information/suggestion would be appreciated. 

P.S. It looks like package was insured for $100

Edit: Thanks for your help guys! I just send a message to seller asking to confirm what address did they send this item to ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Christie falls off chair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 02:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tutorial - Up and Running with Reddit ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 23:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My cousin riding a donkey in Ulcinj, Montenegro in 1972 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 22:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Citi Cut CEO Pay by 10% to $13.1M in 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 22:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is some homework for all truck drivers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 16:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drunk Russian Girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 00:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X-Post from r/anormaldayinrussia ... Winter Baptism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 17:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winter Fishing in Serbia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 17:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get well soon Mr. Bosh! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 01:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25 Years of Photoshop - Dream On </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 07:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X-Post from r/ANormalDayInRussia Russian sailors saluting war veteran 1950s (I guess) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 17:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extension cord wasn't long enough. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 17:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Live Newark: Valentines Day Land Sale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 01:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charles Mansons fiance wanted to marry him for his corpse: source </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 04:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My parents wedding was on today's date 43 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 00:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X-Post from r/videos - "Stop a Douchebag" Ep.17 - Sticker For the Lady </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 03:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP delivers on promise to award gold to Redditors who guess how much money he has in Piggy Bank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 01:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
