<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3591</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 04:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> add canned potato to main, or serve with potato also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 04:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try the mexican section of your store. In a cast iron dutch oven saute some diced onion, fresh seeded jalapeno (and/or serranno/pueblo) peppers, when onion is browning add minced/lean ground beef/turkey/chicken, add cayenne powder, cumin, s p, dried oregano, garlic powder to taste. Lower heat, add water/broth for a thickish mixture. Add refried beans (from a can). Add more water/broth as necessary, and simmer low for an hour stirring often. Don't let stuff burn on the bottom! Boom, big batch of Mexican burrito/taco filling. Package and freeze for up to 2 weeks in portion sizes. You can use this to fill an omelette, a taco, a burrito, a salad, add diced onion, rice, cheese, hot/or not sauces as needed. I left tomato out of the main and toppings deliberately as you don't like them, but they should be part of both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 04:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, what does the upper middle piece taste like? Don't be a wuss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 04:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there were some steps missed at the end. Whatevs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She won't if you don't let your meat loaf. Keep your stick on the ice. lol @ 1 American hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, chicken liver? The bottom piece looks like old meat. Could be some spices/salt that congealed together. Was it one piece at first that you broke into 5? Need banana for scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying it should not be breaded, deep fry it to cook, then into the sauce and add the mozzarella on top to melt? Serve over pasta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry mods, forgot the [Request] tag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i bought this fortune fresh udon noodle w/sauce kit to cook at work for lunch. I have microwave, toaster oven, hot/cold water, grocery store. could you give me suggestions on how to amp it up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went out for breakfast Monday at about 10am. It's hunting season here, so not many tourists or anything, the leaves have changed/dropped already. The place was full, newly expanded (rip Dairy Queen) and re-modeled, they said would I sit at the counter. Sure, why not. A couple minutes later they are calling me. It's definitely going to be either CFS w/eggs or Huevos Rancheros w/green chile. I had never had the HRGC there, so I went with that and some OJ. Perfect. Turns out they had just won best breakfast award from the local paper the day before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 02:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you could freeze a smallish piece for a while and then slice it real thin for stir fry, steak salads and cheese steaks. maybe the distributor will use his slicer to do that for you. maybe thinner for steaks and a bit thicker for stir fry/salads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 02:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see any avocado, but I trust OP: Oh, he's very popular, the sportos, the motorheads, geeks, sluts, bloods, wasteoids, dweebies, dickheads, they all adore him. They think he's a righteous dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 02:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, Montreal is in Quebec.  ffio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 06:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our urinal has a sign which says that "Illegal Dumping $100 Fine" It's an actual sign too from somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 06:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there some goofy yellow light on, in the dash, near the speedo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 06:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, is she a goer? Know what I mean? Know what I mean? Nudge, nudge! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 05:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's under 25 gallons it's not reportable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 05:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? My father bought a boat when I was young. It had a Volvo engine. I learned my lesson youngish when he didn't have any money for me to go to college. My older brother went to University and went bought a Chris-Craft. Go figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 05:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, we get reports like that. Hydro fluid under right front blade frame. WTF is hydro fluid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 05:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instrument Service and Supply, maybe? They always had jokes in their catalogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 05:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Central Wisconsin U? Not enough cheez, lol! I love those pickles though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 04:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking good, I try to get as many turkey dinners as I can each year. Usually one at work on the day, one charity dinner a week b4, one at mom's, and a couple more here and there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 03:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they offer a sandwich called "the bomb" on the menu, I think it's required that you order that. I would. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 03:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks amazing. In the video they showed the mushrooms under the meat sauce though. Great job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username doesn't check out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 02:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a grenade pin and spring? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 02:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhh, reality shows maybe. Stupid, stupid shows on television ffs. If you stop watching they will go away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 01:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look long enough beer can be found in wis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 01:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get my steaks at the grocery for about $5. The damn restaurant wants four to eight times that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 01:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://w3.siemens.com/mcms/industrial-controls/en/controls/soft/Pages/default.aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 21:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you need de-bridement? Dental Hygenist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 21:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone needs to stop watching for this to happen. Reality shows are cheaper because they don't pay the actors much. Stop watching and we'll get nice shows like Seinfeld and be much happier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 20:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I had to buy that from the Ford dealer for a snowmobile with a 4 stroke Peugeot engine 4 cyl. It was spec for the Shelby about 5 years ago. EDIT: could be a three cylinder. It's the Alpina Sherpa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 20:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> currently Medicaid, so I pay for it. And my children, grandchildren. Do you think she should be in an institution for persons with aberrent behavior?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 20:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think you are on the right track, OP, but to be truly independent you'd need about 5 million USD in the bank IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't like the stuff in HS about trying to prepare. I think we had a counselor. F the stuff, I went to the state college even though I slept through a lot of classes. When I got there, I realized what paying for an education meant and did real well. I could recommend that HS students go to community college for at least two maybe four semesters and then transfer to the big one. Work hard and do good. Also, if you have any math classes don't miss a day and do your homework every night. If you don't it will be a problem because every new lesson is based on what you learned the lesson b4. You will fall behind badly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just replaced a brand new lease modem from CenturyLink @ a new service customer because the installer installed a lease modem and the modems they sell permanent are different. Pain in my ass to diagnose the problem with the DirecTV after it didn't recognize the new modem. 1st person's life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the same at all, but my mortgage servicer is awesome. I went in with documents from my closing and my current statement that had the wrong address for over 2 years and they fixed it in 3 months. Thanks, women and guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the breakfast Grande Scramble is the best TB ever. Do you serve breakfast there? At my local steak is extra, otherwise it's bacon or sausage. Should I try the steak? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do ski instructors still get some tail, or is it all with the snowboard now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steak is kind of expensive and you might need a few tests to get it right. You could do the chicken with fancy potatoes. Get some of those baby red and yellow/yukon ones, slice to bite sized, toss w/olive oil, salt and pepper, herbs (parsley, thyme or rosemary), add a head of garlic cloves, skin removed, halved, and roast on a sheet pan in the oven turning halfway. Maybe 375f for 25 minutes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Follow with coffee and fancy Vanilla ice cream.  EDIT: NOT TOGETHER, coffee in a cup, ice cream in a bowl. Mix them on your spoon or in your mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does seem certain is that the word "brunch"that playful blend of "breakfast" and "lunch" first appeared in print in an 1895 Hunter's Weekly article. In "Brunch: A Plea," British author Guy Beringer suggested an alternative to the heavy, post-church Sunday meals in favor of lighter fare served late in the morning. ''Brunch is cheerful, sociable and inciting,'' Beringer says. ''It is talk-compelling. It puts you in a good temper, it makes you satisfied with yourself and your fellow beings, it sweeps away the worries and cobwebs of the week.'' Credit Smithsonianmag.com for the reference to Hunter's Weekly. Alton Brown used this explanation also on his show good eats, to which I couldn't find a link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 18:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should there be some vinegar in there somewhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 18:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 18:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, more of a BLEADT?  Looks great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 18:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you turned the plate with the steak on bottom, it would look like something different. As it is, looks perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 02:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Japanese friends of the family and they keep saying that we need to go there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 01:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, looks really nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 01:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if it's smoked it is going to be chewy. You can't pull it at tender and cook it to finish some other way. You have to keep smoking it. And chewy isn't that bad when it's smoked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 01:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from the Minnesota area and we had White Castle even though technically we were on the west side of the Mississippi. I can get the frozen version where I live, but microwaved bread just turns me off, and they are really expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 01:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I've had it like this, and you just eat the soft part off of the end of each leaf, is that correct? If so, I don't need any dip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I guess we're lucky. I'll watch out for issues. I have a lot of 1997 Fords that are the older style and some parts are becoming tough to get. My oldest Ford is 1986. I will say that the Ford dealer that I deal with is awesome. They always give me the part number, my cost, and if there's any question they will fax the part breakdown. I wish they had a website, but I understand it's really hard. I really like the Caterpillar website for parts, but sometimes it's impossible and I have to call the dealer. And then they are having trouble, but we figure it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Location: (Specify your country or region) USA, CO
Price range: (Minimum-Maximum in your local currency)  15-38k USD
New or used:  either
Type of vehicle: (Truck, Car, Sports Car, Sedan, Crossover, SUV, Racecar, Luxury etc.) I want some luxury, and it can't be bigger than a Chevy Colorado.
Must haves: (4x4, AWD, Fuel efficient, Navigation, Turbo, V8, V6, Trunk space etc.)  awd or 4x4.  Looking for fuel efficiency also.
Intended use: (Daily Driver, Family Car, Weekend Car, Track Toy, Project Car, Work Truck, Off roading etc.)  Daily driver 5,000 mi/yr
Vehicles you've already considered: Subaru Outback or Impreza look good.  I really like Toyota, had a Corolla '06 which was nice great mpg, got stuck 4 times.
Is this your 1st vehicle: no
Does the vehicle need to have a warranty:  Interested in the what is it Kia or Hyundai 100,000 mile warranty
Can you do Minor work on your own vehicle: (fluids, alternator, battery, water pump, brake pad etc)  Not really, I work at a shop though (parts)
Can you do Major work on your own vehicle: (engine and transmission rebuild, timing belt/chains, body work etc )  no
Additional Notes: Thanks to verdegrrl for pointing me here, should have read the wiki, sorry.  EDIT: formatting sucks, don't know how to fix it, sorry again. Currently driving a 2000 Blazer 4wd 4 door LS. Nice car, stuff is breaking though, terrible mileage, 133,000 mile on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best AWD to buy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 06:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 06:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't trick me, that's a cheesy Ritz! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 06:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> remind me 48 hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 06:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't look at the flames, I e-mailed mom and she had someone from the gas company out yesterday because there's also an outdoor NG fireplace that seemed kind of out of control also (we opened the valve and stuck a lighter in and woof!). She said that they say everything is fine. There's a regulator on the main gas meter usually, shouldn't that be fine for the whole house? EDIT: they also checked the furnace which is nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 06:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it has to do with Japanese planned obsolesence. They pull the motors and sell them to harbor freight or someone at 40,000 miles don't they? I've read that they upgrade their fire codes so you have to build a new house every 15 years or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, sometimes I can get a Ford re-man instrument cluster for a pickup. They require me to state the vin and mileage and return the old one due to US mileage faking laws. On certain Fords, if you need to buy the ignition switch you have to change the door locks also in order to keep it to one key. Or visa-versa. I wonder why they limited the odometer to 300,000 though. There are 9s in there somewhere. I've heard of similar stuff in computers, but usually those numbers are divisible by 8 or 24 or something logical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> trailer skirts. I saw some trailers with an under center "ground effects wing" to deflect air under the rear axles instead of skirts on my trip last week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 03:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a '77 Chevy K10 with 4WD full time. Basically it was one wheel drive though. Once I floored it, down to 2nd gear, pulled out to pass on the snow and ice, got sideways next to the car I was passing, pulled the t/c lever into four lock (which locks the t/c so at least one wheel in front and one in the rear are getting torque) in record time and saved it. I got behind the car and kept it cool the rest of the way and used a whole roll of toilet paper when I reached a bathroom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 03:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And ski lifts auxilliary power, big Cat loaders, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 21:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your roommate is wrong about eggs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 20:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate biscuits. I'd rather have an English muffin. I don't like cornbread much either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 12:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks really good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 11:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's probably a great suggestion. Do you think it's safe to leave it connected, or should I have them disconnect the quick coupler?
EDIT: Never mind, it will be safe with the ball valve shut off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 11:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turkey is an under-rated meat food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 02:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so.  It's in the back yard and just looks like 3/4" black pipe down to 3/8" and then there's a brass quick disconnect. Pretty sure that's how the builder set it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 22:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazingly, it's one of the things that is WAY less expensive in Hawaii vs. mainland. Smuggle a few cans back from Oahu if you go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 22:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> spiced ham only sounds weird after you eat it and look at the ingredients and there's no spices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AWESOME Huge Breakfast Burrito Casa Rivera, Oracle, AZ [I ATE] with partial cantalope for scale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 22:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 19:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at mom's last week setting up the new home. We ordered the Dyna-Glo Natural Gas 4 burner with amazon prime and it arrived in two days FedEx Ground. No conversion BS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 19:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Joetisseried ribs will change your life.

Heh, it should turn just the proper speed (or your sauce should be just the proper thickness) for it to run back and forth up and back down the ribs and never fall off. (sauce, what kind of ribs are you cooking m8?) lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NatGas grill too hot? Just got a DynaGlo DGA480SSN-D and it's hot! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 12:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, after warmup I set all 4 burners to lowest setting to do some potato in foil packs. The grill leveled out at over 425 degrees. So I turned off the right two burners and stacked the packs on the right. With only two burners the grill was still right at 400 degrees f. Seems too hot for lowest setting. Can I just use the 3/4" ball valve to throttle the behemoth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 11:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the answers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 02:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family made a cookbook. It's pretty cool, but the pages aren't numbered so it takes a while to find the recipe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 01:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a DLE?  What's a sac?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 00:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USS Montgomery had something like this fail 3 days after being commissioned.  That must be why GE is spending so much on TV commercials. That's not a robot Ricky, that's Ernie

EDIT: I guess it's something exactly like this.  http://www.geaviation.com/engines/docs/marine/case-history/lm2500-usn-lcs-case-history.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 00:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the small preview photo looks like some creepy clown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 00:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heh, that bun has so many wrinkles it looks like Mary Berry.  Looks pretty darn good overall OP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Rachel substitutes pastrami (the most sensual of all the cured meats) for the corned beef, and coleslaw for the sauerkraut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 04:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'd enjoy this dish. If I was cooking, I would have taken off the whole shell and tail, but I don't mind the way it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 04:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do the noodles soften up? Those look crispy and I don't like that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 04:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, cheesemonger I need one small slice of Gruyere for this Onion Ramen! Why isn't there any Onion Ramen? Or scallion Ramen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 04:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see that there would be any substitute. USA can pizza also! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 01:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had reservations at a swank place in Reykjavik back in early October 1986, and some US and Russians trumped me and I had to stay with some shepherd out in the range shed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 01:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> quote:  wall of stats
Well, I can tell you that they won't deliver to my neighborhood of about 250 full time year round residents. They used to bring the mail 7 miles and put it in our PO boxes.  Then 3 years ago they decided that was too hard. A$$holes too if you go there.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 03:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no rentals available in Tuscany. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 03:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll second. Get the hot ones in the can if you can't find anything else. Make a green chile sauce with chicken broth and a roux or corn starch slurry and some tomato, red bell pepper, cumin, etc (cooked carrot small dice even for sweetness and color) and freeze it up to forever. Use twice as much green chile as you think. Add some serrano/jalapeno to amp it up if you like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 03:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8 potatoes seems like a lot.  Maybe they are small.  Might be good to boil the potatoes for 6 minutes before beginning to saute.  This one calls for 6 small red potatoes pre-roasted in the oven. http://www.recipe4living.com/recipes/inspired_by_denny_s_easy_santa_fe_skillet.htm  I'd sub some jalapeno for the green pepper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what that is, but it looks expensive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks like a desert mud rally burn out contest to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, you can see it in this video. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V8HVW1l5Xcg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 18:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lunch @ work chicken salad:
Open can of chicken, drain, fluff in bowl.  Add large spoonful of dill relish, spoonful of mayo.  Serve on toast maybe w/slice of cheese if you have it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see why someone might call out m c or grilled cheese. It's funny sometimes.
However, I'm not going to upvote any post that doesn't contain the picture inline any longer. If it's an album, and I'm interested I will click again to go see the album. I might upvote on imgur.com, but not here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never octopus, but this looks really great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 23:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that looks really good.  I want to taste that fish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 23:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got to give you an upvote because your food and the dog are awesome. But really people, no more up votes if the picture isn't in your post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 18:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could add it to a pyrex pan and top it w/bread crumbs and bake it.  That would make it thicker.  I prefer mine creamy like this. I get the hormel m c in a bucket with a pound of fried kielbasa and some onion in it. stupid easy and good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 18:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like fried onion and bbq sauce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
