<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9748</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need to do in person! All my volunteering is online - I did social media for the organization and am now a contributing editor to their magazine where I interview authors. Volunteering to help with a conference is great but there are many, many ways to volunteer online instead (manage a forum, bring people together, social media, organize an online event, etc) and still connect with your writing peers and industry professionals. Good luck!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eight Steps to an Agent, a Publisher, and a Two-Book Deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome! If you join a genre based org like HWA try to volunteer. Best way to meet writers of all sorts from debut authors to veteran authors. They can really help support you. I've volunteered now for 5 years for Intl Thriller Writers (social media and as a contributing editor for their Big Thrill mag) and made amazing connections that landed me blurbs, advisors, and publicity. Also, meeting agents in person boosts you up and there is a better chance of getting a request for a full MS. Writing cons are great for this -or use a reference as a recommendation too. If you find your query is getting no response than pull it back and revise it before sending out more. I was an intern for a Lit Agency as a first reader and saw what queries got the agent's attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to know about magazine markets I would def. check out Duotrope. Many of my peers submit through this and have had good luck. You may want to start out smaller than the New Yorker to build up. https://duotrope.com/
Also, check out the Writer's Market
http://www.writersmarket.com/
Good luck!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
