<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3000</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 07:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the US, and most other first world/industrialized nations. In many places if you're poor you can't live off the land AND will die early from starvation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 14:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, did you keep out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 14:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry sir and or madam, that is against our policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 07:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like you looked right into the dark, dark, soul of Walmart and figured them out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 07:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost want to give you gold for the cleverness. Just wasn't quite clever enough though. 7/10 gold requires a 8/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 07:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but I remember at the time I did some Googling and found quite a few people were similar to me, but a lot got punished (services cancelled or a warning mainly) so it seemed hit or miss. I was in the lucky group thankfully.

Of course when cable internet was finally offered where I lived I switched to Cox and got a 60/6 (I think 6 up) line, I know the month after I switched I got a letter from Century Link saying they now offered bonded DSL in my area of up to 40 mbps and offered me a discount to go back. Even after their discount I was paying less for higher speeds with Cox.

I miss them both now since I can only get my cell tethering for high speed data where I am now. Bless T-Mobile and unlimited data/tethering.

Edit: I still wonder why they don't warn/cancel everyone. One theory I had was too many people go over the soft cap and they can't afford to do that or they'd lose a lot of customers (too many). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something I always found interesting is I had Century Link (fairly big DSL/phone provider in the US) in Wyoming which had a 250 GB soft cap (done quarterly, so if you went over 750 GB in a 3 month period) in which I used a minimum of 500 GB to sometimes over a TB a month for a year. Never got a letter or call from them, never even got throttled even (which is good since it was a 15/.812 {I think .812 I know it was just under a mb} and throttling slower would have been a pain). 

I have to tell you I expected a letter every month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 04:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Owning both I have to agree. PS4s has less going on but is so much easier to navigate AND runs smoother. I have a pretty old XBone so I dunno if newer editions or the one S improves this but XBone's GUI is so slow sometimes, and I power cycle to clear cache regularly. My PS4's, which is also a pretty old model, GUI is still fast and finding what I want is very fast.

On the other hand having more going on on the XBone does give the GUI some features the PS4 doesn't have so I guess it's a trade off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 06:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here, I kind of played it on the 360 before and my roommate has it on the PC. I said screw it and picked it up with this sell for the Xbone and wonder why I never got into it on the 360 (I can't for the life of me remember)

I mean it's no Diablo 2 which I still play from time to time and love, but it's still an amazing game all on it's own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 05:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This hit me right in the feels for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 22:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Born in '90 here and sometimes I feel my early childhood is closer to someone born in '85 or so. I DEFINITELY remember life with no internet, or computers. Then again I grew up in a small town where most families didn't get a PC before 2000-2002, and no broadband before 2005 when our cable company finally offered it. Dialup 'till then, no digital cable before 2003 or so though you could get satellite before that it was expensive and no one had it. 

I grew up on the NES untill I got my N 64 in 96, SNES /Sega only at friend's houses. So for me I remember a life pre internet, pre broadband, pre home PC. Though I guess I'm more of a fringe type in this case.

Edit to add no one I knew had a Cell phone untill 2005 (when I was 15) I didn't have one untill I was an adult. Though it wasn't too uncommon for parents to have one before '05. Mine did when I was probably about 13, many of my friends parents had them too. Only one or two of my friends had one before we turned 18 and got jobs though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 09:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy gets it. I'm happy MS made XBox don't get me wrong, but they should be happy that I (every single XBox owner) made them a success by purchasing the consoles/games/live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 09:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry late reply to you also lol.

I only have mobile hotspot (no wired where I live) so I rarely play online. I have unlimited hotspot LTE speeds (T-Mobile) but latency pre 10 PM is terrible. I'll still add you though next time I'm on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 09:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry late reply, I Iike it. I haven't run into any bugs or anything. Frames seem mostly steady with weird dips that even out fast. As for content, I dunno what it had then VS now so I can't comment there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 04:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They keep making it more of a pain to activate which annoys me.

First I had a "manage HD passes" on the front page of the mobile app.

Then I had to hit data, addons and then activate it.

Now I have to go to profilemedia settings. Technically it's as many clicks as the 2nd one but when it switched I was confused, took me 5+ minutes to find its new location. Why do they keep moving it/burying it? What was wrong with the original "manage HD passes" right on the front of the app?

I mean it seems they want to discourage one + users from activating it, which from their view I guess I can understand. They want to hold down the congestion from high data users, but they already deprioritize do they really need more discouragement than that?

Anyway I am happy with my T-Mobile One + overall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 08:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TellTale undead survival bundle includes 7 Days To Die (TellTale publishes it for console)

I bought the Undead survival bundle and got TWD s1/2/Michonne and 7 Days To Die for 18.15 the other day, great value and loving 7 Days To Die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen every season, it's just been a while lol. I agree though, amazing show.

Futurama  King Of The Hill  Family Guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 10:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed way to hard at this, take my upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 10:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To expand (I don't know much myself) it's supposed to be a user (viewer) friendly "universal" type of html web coding.

Anyone feel free to correct me and or explain better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 10:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.ampproject.org

Hope it helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 03:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember N64 games being like ~80$, PS1 new games were about 50$ but I thought that, was in large part, of the industry switching to disc based (way cheaper to make CDs/DVDs/Blu Rays than cartridges) games. PS2 (I got mine the XMas it came out, god bless my parents haha) I remember the games being 50$ USD at first but I know towards the end of the era them being like 54.99 new, maybe as high as 60.

I owned/played an NES/SNES growing up but we never got new games for them only used, and we didn't get an SNES 'till after the I had my N64 and the whole time we had our NES it was outdated by the SNES.

Anyway I never owned an OG XBox so I can't comment on it's game prices but everything I read says the cartridge days were MORE expensive than nowadays, especially when you account inflation. Those cartridges and SuperFX chips were much more pricey than discs, and on top of that less people gamed so they needed higher prices per customer. Anyway I know way to long of a post but my feelings on the current industry is:

1.
I want a 60$ game to feel like 60$ of content

2.
DLCs are fine but should be developed AFTER game release, if something is fully ready at release it should just be released with the game

3.
F* preorder bonus items/customes/etc see above

4.
DLCs should be priced right, if it's 20$ DLC it should have 20$ of content

5.
Cosmetic DLCs are fine (developed after release are fine, or at release if it is their only microtransaction and all future content patches are free - see Overwatch)

6.
Microtransactions like supply drops in full AAA priced multiplayer games are bullshit (looking at you COD)

I know this post isn't inherently about DLCs but the different "packages" and marketing of games but since others were weighing in I thought I would with my over lengthed tldr post.

Edited for typos and clarity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 07:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worked like a charm for me. The only plague that ever really gave me any trouble before this one was Necroa. I'm liking this update (expansion) though, my new favorite plague after Necroa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 23:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See I misunderstood your post, and in the context I thought you meant it it seemed like a strawman. Now I understand what you meant better from clarification on your part, and of course in the future I should probably ask for clarification before making assumptions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
