<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7913</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 00:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I think the general idea is a good prompt for a novel. Imagining what immortality would actually be like to experience is a fun challenge. Imagine how much drive they would develop to meet being the only other being on earth that might relate? And then what if the meeting ultimately is a disappointment after millennia of anticipation? Immortal A just wants a companion while B wants to eliminate their only competitor for world domination?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 00:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, I surrender. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Two", "pre-human". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Travel the continents building stone monuments inscribed with a promise to revisit each monument. Given infinite time once the 2nd person stumbled across 1 monument, they could stay in the nearby area guaranteeing eventual contact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 03:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mainly wondering because I've made a couple PvP dedicated 150's and the traffic doesn't seem that wow. And I've barely done any NG+ at all because I was trying to stay lower to practice PvP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 09:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pure sorcery actually sounds like a fun challenge for PvP. What cast speed do you consider soft cap? Do you use the fastest staff (witch tree is it?) or staff of wisdom? Tell me about your pure caster PvP build basically lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Updated Advice for SM/Level for PvP (Both Arena   Summons) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 08:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For increasing the chance of decent matches: does level really matter? Does SM tier really matter? Or is there a similar chance of finding good # and quality of matches at all levels/tiers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 10:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any builds you would recommend for starting out? I usually do a greatsword/longsword fashion souls thing w/ no resin or buffs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 10:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was trying to read up here on matchmaking but obviously I'm very late to ds2 lol and most posts are 2 years old... is it worth capping my SM at 150 to improve PvP? Or is that outdated? I've been looking for PvP at 150 and it feels pretty sparse... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New to PvP - Important Stats? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 09:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any general tips on key stats for PvP? Like a good minimum poise to build for? How much agility etc. Does armor make enough of a difference to be worth crunching numbers over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 04:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So full circle for HT effects, but only edges for the actual skill damage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 04:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you got to 85 with no augments? wow, was your paragon high? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 04:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand the big utility on Unity but I'm surprised you don't use CoE! It seems like a big boost to drop, esp. since it's well suited to Jade's nuke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 04:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if I have 20% poison on bracers or Amu I need to select that element on SH? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 22:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the rune selected on Soul Harvest matter since the set gives all runes?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 22:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What level do you aim for as minimum for augments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 22:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zero Arachyr huh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 06:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for all the responses! I think I would prefer LoN Locust but looks like chicken for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 11:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got back on WD. Last season I just cubed In-Geom and set skills for speed on standard HT. Idk what my clear times were though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are you using for TX speed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 11:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you use and what is your average clear time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 23:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most EM6 builds I've seen don't use ground stomp - can someone explain? New to Barb and the build </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 10:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I go back and forth, but really why not just play whatever build is the most enjoyable? How rewarding really is it to advance 5-10 GR higher if another build is viable and more satisfying to play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 10:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't this be adapted for solo play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 08:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah of the 4 FB Archon guides, any one of them better suited to a beginner wiz? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 22:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been thinking of trying out Wiz again, disliked the DMO twister gameplay of last season, but I hear Firebird Archon is fun to play and looks very easy to gear (also top solo GR build most likely). Wiz also has the bonus of being the most efficient DB farming class atm (Tal/Sage Flashfire). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 23:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried it out some at 12/13 ancients, far from optimized rolls. Still, even clearing a 70 was difficult. I didn't find procing Shi Mizu difficult, I found the dying constantly after procing it difficult lol.

I decided to GR with FoK Shadow which can easily reach mid-high 80's and is easy to gear and fun imo (actually very similar pull   nuke play to LoN). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 06:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are either of these top solo builds fun to play? I didn't care much for the DMO Twister build from last season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 05:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 04:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 11:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who prefer HC, why do you like it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Easiest   Fastest Build to Reach 80+ GR? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 03:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What build is relatively easy to gear that can crack 80 in a short time? I thought of WD Helltooth, any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 01:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understanding is: UE 6-set bonus * F R, not UE + F R. This is why no amount of ring Disc. can out perform it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 09:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not bad for speed TX farming...useless for GR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 12:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the explanation! So you let some mobs cut your health down till Shi Mizu procs and then same gameplay as LoN Fok? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 09:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you keep your health that low without getting killed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming you have a M6 or UE for farming (hopefully UE) I find fast split bounties to be best for collecting mats quickly. The downside is you won't gain many DBs while doing it. It is good for Souls though because of all the useless bounty items (TX is best of course). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it difficult to play/control or just annoying visually? I've been working on non-Shi Mizu because I assumed it would be easier to get started without it, since I haven't tried LoN before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 07:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also noticed my sheet dps fluctuates while strafing? is that why sometimes my FoK doesn't seem to do any dmg? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 07:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the help all - cleared 70 after cubing Crown and replacing some CDR with LoH. How much LoH is recommended? What GR should I expect to be able to clear once I get all ancients (11/13 now) and improve my gameplay? I'm surprised to be struggling in the 70's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 09:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I just copied the sidebar guide. What should I replace CDR w/ on gear after cubing Lori's? Btw the guide says use Valla's instead of Ballista? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New to LoN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 04:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Profile](http://us.battle.net/d3/en/profile/sun1tzu-1158/hero/64297373)

First time trying LoN while waiting around for season. Aside from having only 11/13 Ancients, anything obvious I'm doing wrong? Struggling to clear 75 due to frequent deaths, dps seems fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 22:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No DH build can come near UE for TX farming so you want to start with Multishot anyway, then you can always try another build for GR. I like the contrast between easy farming with UE and pushing with Shadow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 22:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Early in the season the best performing builds seemed to be ones using Karlei's Point and stacking area dmg, eventually people even dropped Seethe and combined Dark Heart and Aquila relying totally on Karlei's for resource. I never really enjoyed that build as much as FoK but no one thought FoK could compete - then I saw a 80GR clear with FoK and I jumped back in lol. It's hard to see how Karlei's can possibly compete now that Lord Greenstone's Fan has it's effect doubled but the high toughness may become required higher up?
Lightbeams 80 clear was the highest Shadow I found on Season board, and I've been told someone using Karlei version cleared as high as 81-82. If that means the two build were roughly tied the doubled boost for FoK should push it ahead for sure dmg-wise, but FoK relies almost totally on mobility for survival so that may become a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 11:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 11:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [My first guide attempt, critique welcome!](http://www.diablofans.com/builds/78734-2-4-1-solo-gr-shadow-fok) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2.4.1 LGF Shadow Guide anyone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 01:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Shadow enthusiast (there are dozens of us) I'm wondering if any experienced players are interested in doing an updated guide? I'm a casual of the family and job variety but I cleared a GR77 (currently #625) despite a very mediocre Fan (162/200 FoK boost) on PTR, I'm happy to do something if no one more qualified is interested?

Edit: Added a guide below, hopefully someone can do a better one soon!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 04:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking forward to playing Shadow more for 6, was initially disappointed with it but then came back to it after I saw some high clears, now it will be even more fun - although I wish they would add some kind of caltrops/trap element to round out the assassin play style. I like alternating Shadow with EU since they are so opposite. Going to play Shadow in S6? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 17:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As high as GR80 has been cleared using FoK version in Season 5, I'm not sure what the highest clear using Karlei's has been. Plus in 2.4.1 both Shadow Set and Lord Greenstone's Fan have their dmg doubled - this should put FoK Shadow ahead easily. I've cleared GR72 w/ Fan in current season w/ mediocre knife and low 800's para. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 01:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knew nothing about these 3rd party programs till the news. I understand that Bliz did some kind of scan and that anyone detected that was using during that time period was banned?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 19:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you do with the other arm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 08:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played HT through to GR70 and then lost the motivation to farm for an ancient Harvester etc. to keep pushing. It is boring for sure.

Surprised that Unity is preferred over CoE in Jade build? And is poison spirit significant improvement over cold? Thinking of doing Jade for S6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 08:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shadow set guide is not updated for 2.4.1, just the sidebar title is changed.....there are dozens of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 14:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What were ppl being banned for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 02:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starting trying out FoK S6 after I saw someone had cleared a GR 80 with it this season, the 2.4.1 buffs give that build about a 10 GR boost. The ceiling will be low-mid 90's imo (and Wudijo's). The dude that cleared the 80 was less than 1k para btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 11:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UE does seem very good for farming keys. But wiz has an advantage w/ DB: still fast movement but can wear Sage's (clear speed doesn't matter if you're not worried about keys). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 03:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bounties seem best for farming the other 3 mats for rare upgrades (about 60 each per cache) is that what you guys do for mats? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Farming Prep. for Patch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 22:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to stock up on mats for rare upgrading:

Are split bounties the best approach for farming mats for upgrades? If so I'd assume a cold UE build would be best for bounties. I've been using a Sage/Tal Wiz for DB's and I can't see how any DH build could compete on DBs... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best All-purpose Farming Build? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 01:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 22:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I right that you don't have 100% uptime on Vengeance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 22:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will this build be more effective than Karlei's w/ buff to LGF in next patch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 21:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume area damage is a lower priority, what are your stat priorities? CC/CHDCDRElemSkills? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> S6 FoK Build - GR80 on seasonal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 08:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seasonal solo - 52 Lightbeams, P981

Someone explain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 07:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty mystified by this guy using FoK at that high of a GR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 22:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [2.4.1 predictions from Wudijo on all sets](http://us.battle.net/d3/en/forum/topic/20742954758) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 16:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just found some high GR S6 clears on seasonal board: one at 80 using LGF(??) and another at 79 with more typical Karlei setup - anyone else cleared above 80? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 13:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The primary advantage of the Lightning rune is that it causes more procs on Karlei's resource generator. I understand that while in theory the piercing cold rune could also increase procs, that in practice lightning is easier to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 05:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the infographic thank you. Profile link pls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shadow - Resource Management w/ Aquila </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 02:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any general tips/advice on S6 w/ Aquila? I'm used to using Seethe w/ Dark Heart cubed.

I'm having a hard time keeping resource up - my Karlei's has only 11/15 resource, I assume that's my problem aside from more practice using Mortal Enemy effectively?

Also if anyone wants to make a S6 guide for the dozens of us interested in the build despite it's limits that'd be awesome... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 23:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprised by the S6 numbers - could you link the forum please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 12:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Random S6 question: How do you keep your resource up consistently for Aquila w/ no generator? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
