<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend runs a very popular Sentai / Power Rangers fan news site. The guy in Green follows him on facebook, and recently became a redpill retard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buffy is one of the few things besides star trek that helps me through these dark and trying political times. My mom dying was more a relief because she was no longer suffering and I was happy she didn't have to see Trump take over the white house. I wish she could have had a female president though before she passed. Buffy was this family tradition in our house and we watched it like it was going to church when it was on Tuesdays at 8pm on the WB. So many VHS tapes ... so so many. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck these angry trigger memes, the halcyon days of Rustled Jimmies are making a comeback! BUY BUY BUY!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well ... she died this last christmas eve  ... so yeah it worked out i guess. She survived the brain surgery so that was good. -**awkward shrug**- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "But she will never want any more juice ... " my mom was in the hospital for a brain surgery when I was 16 when this episode aired .... THE FEELS!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not enough love for the best death scene ever filmed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best death scene ever shot in a movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You never have seen "traditional family values" have you? Children are property and should be seen not heard and if one dies you had 7 others to make up for it and to be labor on the farm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> like supporting trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well i doubt it would be a stable relationship, I'm sure his wife's fury would be unbridled. It most likely would spur their divorce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, just in this context. Also i'm a little manicky tonight so ehhhhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - http://www.slate.com/articles/health_and_science/explainer/2013/07/california_grows_all_of_our_fruits_and_vegetables_what_would_we_eat_without.html

- http://www.latimes.com/food/dailydish/la-dd-calcook-california-its-whats-for-dinner-20140312-story.html

- https://thinkprogress.org/californias-drought-could-upend-america-s-entire-food-system-fb281425ce67#.xb9pb5853

- http://www.vox.com/a/explain-food-america

- http://www.slate.com/articles/health_and_science/explainer/2013/07/california_grows_all_of_our_fruits_and_vegetables_what_would_we_eat_without.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only a trained medical professional who is not a personal friend or family member has the right or legal standing to diagnose anyone.

I don't know you or your issues so i don't understand why you went on a rant like this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 08:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dis man is ded. Peritonitis 

GRUNT GRUNT AHHHHHH GRUNT .... thee end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 08:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its almost like they are asking for us to kill them ... not my words just theirs, the ones in their soulless eyes begging for sweet release. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 08:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha ha ha, you can't stop it, try and the transnational corporations either mock in public or kill you if you get to close to getting the spotlight on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> should have made it the guy looking at the horse. Men are more likely to fuck horses and donkeys actually. There is quite the infamous one in Washington state. MR HANDS!!!!!! [here is the documentary on it called "Zoo"](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MTakcENIUS4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so is addiction as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you got a corgi instead !!!! PICTURES NOW!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Sorry to make you cry on this but actually facts and truth makes political cultist double down on stupid](http://rationalwiki.org/wiki/Backfire_effect)

it basically means we need to let them die off before we can get past them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 06:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So where on the geopolitical doll did a dictator saying they were communist but was in fact an autocrat touch you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 06:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Family values has always been dog whistle for keeping women in their place, dicks in pussies even without permission, keeping gays vilified, and the church donations flowing for for-profit preachers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 06:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inbreeding does that to you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love inedible corn i sure want to buy dent corn from the plains states and midwest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3/5th of american edible produce is grown in california. The stuff not grown in california is only grow in southern costal states and make up beries, watermelon, and peaches. The midwest and in land farmers only grow dent corn. Dent corn is inedible but is packed with dense starch with it taking up 95% of the kernel of dent corn. This corn is the manority of what americas in the middle America produce now and it is only used or the agrochemicals industry creating perservitive and sweetener HFCS (high fructose corn syrup), corn syrup, xanthum gum, and 40 other some odd food additives for the automated food production industry which produces food which has long shelf lifes, high calorie count, but very poor nutritional value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fourth rule of robotics: if a person makes profit of 10 million or more money and their crime only effected people making under $100,000, acquit defendants  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Escorts and streetwalkers of both male and female varieties say at GOP convention cities there are anywhere from 3 to 5 times as many sex workers working the conservative convention hotels and triple the amount of people using grindr or male prostitution services than than democrats convention.

Its so well known the the Human Rights organizations put an advert in grindr app during the CPAC (conservative political action committee) confrence

http://www.advocate.com/politics/2017/2/26/human-rights-campaign-has-message-cpacs-grindr-users

Also reason magazine also put one too to find people to interview who are gay at CPAC

http://m.huffpost.com/us/entry/6792274

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, i have bipolar type 2 and dilated glassy eyed pupils are one of the symptoms of mania, besides rushed speaking and over the top energy and risk taking behavior outside the norm

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they are though. Those who support this are now agents of the establishment. They are following the government and giving glowing shit grin hand jobs to it. They are cult like in how they wear the governmental colors and its jingoism is something that 4chan was everything against. The agent of individualism and hedonism is now  dogs of the Government working as state alchemists and following all the Commands of a homunculus in chief  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no point to this though. I mean when it comes down to it it means 4chan is a tool of the establishment now. They support the government and they are now agents of it. What happen to the 4chan that was like fuck scientology and legit pedophiles? This looks like some high school level asshole shit right here and dogs of the government, those state  alchemists  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh your turn around a whataboutism of ***William Clinton*** is her-lare-e-us! Actually only one person accused him of rape . but he was sued for sexual harassment and hostile work environment. Only one woman has ever accused billy and that was supposedly 40 years ago while trump has been on record from testimony that two of his ex-wives he sexually terrorized and revenge raped them.

http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2015/07/27/ex-wife-donald-trump-made-feel-violated-during-sex.html

http://m.huffpost.com/us/entry/us_57fae930e4b0e655eab54dee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So rape is ok in your book? Hmmmm see for me its like not, so how is it knowing that raping your sister is why she committed suicide to get away from you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is on tape saying he did it and that because he is famous he can get away with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of all the white college shootings all of them are incel posters  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He went on that woman like a bitch in heat he was told no but he did it anyway because when you are famous you can do that kind of thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like someone took hallucinogens or is going hella manic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Garlic bread and tendies!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Reeeeeeeeeee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Young kids who are a minority of social rejects in the real world but someone important in their minecraft group online makes the meme popular its the old morons who then wish they were young again and then follow the youth saying it was theor idea all along. They are the ones who have nothing to really care about and rather just be selfish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 02:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American culture is consume culture its buy buy buy never repair just replace  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and none who went to his video camera will be seen  as attention seeking whores? Really?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/WOMf5XO.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still havent put away childish things, still think as a child, still talk as a child, still having the jimmies rustled like a child, until then you still just a kid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is something wrong with you still kid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your dad was a dick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was just never an american based on Fox news and Drudge Report  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4chan has never been a place of smart people, just stupid teenagers and adult man children / women children

The emotional maturity of the average 4channer is i would say 16 thinking they are mature as fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it funny that when people have died that Shia Labeouf will have this video placed in the Us Archives as art and that these people will be remembered as long as that video is there as trolls, racists, and attention seeking whores. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is you can see the direct connection between the socio economic trends of the time. Many people in the rust belt have lost all hope. They have no community but ghost towns that have been gutted by Walmarts killing small town main streets. They have lost all of their jobs because transnational corporations do not like that americans are uppity and demand like rights and stuff so they moved their factories that haven't figured out how to automate out 90% of the work force to asia.

in the 60s it was psychedelics to distract from war and racism and sexual violence.

in the 70s it was heroine because it was the kids grown up and still trying to party but not having anything to do.

in the 80s it was cocaine as jobs were plentiful and and people were being trained to fuck everyone else and take. It allowed people to work long hours and not have any sense of caring.

90s was the birth of designer drugs that have both stimulant effects and hallucinogens

2000 was the start of the prescription synthetic opiate craze

and now in the 2010s we are back at heroine as the drug of choice of the masses thanks to the fact its easier and cheaper to get than oxycotin. This has then circled back to the 90s since we are going though that culture again with 90s music, 90s themed tv shows, and such and now we have the rise of synthetic opiates which are 1000 times stronger and technically not illegal because they have not be classified.

Pot has always been there through all this time but it doesn't cause issues when its decriminalized. It's only when it's criminalized that you have a rise of cartel violence and other drugs from drug manufactures become addictions of choice. 


But the end is right now the rust belt in america feels broken, lost, and they want someone to blame. They can't blame themselves because they can't see they themselves allowed industry to control them and break their will, so they turn to drugs that make them completely sedated and blissful. Its funny because opium uptake in post world war 1 germany was also rife. I think there might be a correlation that show the rise of populism and demagogy particularly with the rampant abuse of sedatives. After demagogues take over though typically they outlaw the drugs and highly criminalize it's users but then promote using speed / amphetamines in their place to make the citizens work faster and longer with smaller pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no i'm just a guy who grew up in an age of japanese upskirt perverts, so i think people who fixate on needing to see up someone's skirt has got issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold my beer! 

**-EDIT-** 

Done! 

- https://youtu.be/IHVh_S9NGIU
- https://vid.me/sDdR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A man just hired a hitman to kill his mother .... good for him!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walking Beta Male incel nightmare incarnate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you got issues kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They ate principle Flutey !!!! And so the Principle is always gonna die running gag started  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was 13 episode midseason replacement on a then an upstart 3rd tier broadcast tv network. The show had no budget what so ever but has some really great stories that constantly get love later in the series though. Buffy made the WB and was the cornerstone till the CW / CBS switch over and buffy moving to UPN and even then UPN was kept alive longer than it should have because of that buffy migration too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buffy is one of those shows that defined modern feminism in television. Its one of those phenomena that has college classes about it at harvard.

Buffy was Joss Whedon's treatise about the issues of growing up a girl to a woman in modern america with the glitz and polish of demons, spooks, and vampires. Not only that buffy isn't a great student, she isn't popular because she is dealing with "working her way through school" and it deals with the issues of class struggle as well. 

The show touched the issues of teenage sex and the fact not all boyfriends treat you well, it dealt with issues of toxic relationships in real manner, it dealt with accurate depictions of survivor's guilt, what its like being a "beta male" with the group of friends she has particularly the one named Xander Harris. It made it ok to realize not everyone has to go to college to eventually do well in life. 

It was a show ahead of it's time and survived two major time slot changes, and two major broadcast television channel switches, from WB / CW / UPN. If you want a show that is witty, gets the struggles of young life, deals with them in adult manner but also funny ways with unique supernatural villians and long running plot lines that just make you squeal when they reveal, Buffy is your show. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It is when you're broke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellowship of the Punk: You have my sword, and my bow, and my roland 303! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 08:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> longer lasting high, more intense high. The reason why overdoses now total 17 per week in parts of Ohio, Pennsylvania, Kentucky and such. They have as many has 41 Heroin

http://time.com/4260798/drug-epidemic-america/

The blue states that voted for Trump were the hardest hit by the drug epidemic too.

- https://www.inverse.com/article/23509-trump-election-rural-america-opioid-epidemic-heroin
- https://www.theguardian.com/society/ng-interactive/2016/may/25/opioid-epidemic-overdose-deaths-map
- http://www.cnn.com/2016/09/16/health/huntington-heroin/
- http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bill-maher-donald-trump-drug-abuse_us_588308dfe4b096b4a231e6c0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Russian oil giant Rosneft could claim U.S. oil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 08:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Russian oil giant Rosneft could claim U.S. oil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 08:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Florida is and will always be COCAINE!!! Oxy a little bit but that is because snow bird doctors want to make money on the side and write scipts for it. 

The heroin in america is all in the RUST BELT now. They now mix Heroin with Fentanyl and now that that isn't strong enough they have Carfentanil which is 100x stronger than Fentanyl which is 100x stronger than heroin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 03:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reichbart is the proper news of the people's government. They are bringing the glory of the god liche to everyone. Dont you want to hear his sweet siren song of why nothing is your fault if you are male and white? Its all the jews, the blacks, and the mexicans faults you are not great like god liche Bannon and his trained pet jester the wonderous Donnie trump!! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Fox News is now the last line of defense of ethics, morality, and integrity in journalism the days truly have reached their darkest hour. Our hopes are now under boot to thugs, nationalists, and jingoists and fascist supporting white supremacists now allowed to roam the press halls of the white house, ones who even see fox news as their enemy as their goal is not truth but propaganda and fear to foment chaos and terror to those who have listen to their deathly siren song to blissful ignorant madness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Fox News is now the last line of defense of ethics, morality, and integrity in journalism the days truly have reached their darkest hour. Our hopes are now under boot to thugs, nationalists, and jingoists and fascist supporting white supremacists now allowed to roam the press halls of the white house, ones who even see fox news as their enemy as their goal is not truth but propaganda and fear to foment chaos and terror to those who have listen to their deathly siren song to blissful ignorant madness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Journalism is at it's darkest hour in the United States when it must be Fox News Radio correspondent who confronts white supremacist conspiracy theory reporting Gateway Pundit reporter who was just given press creds into White House briefing room </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Fox News is now the last line of defense of ethics, morality, and integrity in journalism the days truly have reached their darkest hour. Our hopes are now under boot to thugs, nationalists, and jingoists and fascist supporting white supremacists now allowed to roam the press halls of the white house, ones who even see fox news as their enemy as their goal is not truth but propaganda and fear to foment chaos and terror to those who have listen to their deathly siren song to blissful ignorant madness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Radio correspondent confronts Gateway Pundit reporter in White House briefing room </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Fox News is now the last line of defense of ethics, morality, and integrity in journalism the days truly have reached their darkest hour. Our hopes are now under boot to thugs, nationalists, and jingoists and fascist supporting white supremacists now allowed to roam the press halls of the white house, ones who even see fox news as their enemy as their goal is not truth but propaganda and fear to foment chaos and terror to those who have listen to their deathly siren song to blissful ignorant madness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Radio correspondent confronts Gateway Pundit reporter in White House briefing room </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Fox News is now the last line of defense of ethics, morality, and integrity in journalism the days truly have reached their darkest hour. Our hopes are now under boot to thugs, nationalists, and jingoists and fascist supporting white supremacists now allowed to roam the press halls of the white house, ones who even see fox news as their enemy as their goal is not truth but propaganda and fear to foment chaos and terror to those who have listen to their deathly siren song to blissful ignorant madness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Radio correspondent confronts Gateway Pundit reporter in White House briefing room </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW after I hear Scott Pruitt and Donald Trump want to make the EPA cancel the CAFE fuel-efficiency standards that have helped limit cancerous pollutants from diesel fuel and lower other pollutants from normal gas and require cars use less fuel to go farther. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its how he met his wife I remember hearing in stories  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  google Emoluments Clause dumbass.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  google Emoluments Clause dumbass.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  google Emoluments Clause dumbass.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  google Emoluments Clause dumbass.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 07:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> google Emoluments Clause dumbass. Congress has to give permission for any gift or formal title from a foreign country to a sitting president or elected official so to make sure that that elected official does not take bribes to help foreign countries or non-citizens of the united states for a quid pro quo exchange. Trademarks count as gifts / titles. This is the corner stone of the Emoluments Clause.

http://time.com/4579979/emoluments-clause-constitution-donald-trump/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wallace is an asshole though. Smug as all fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOOD NIGHT REDDITLAND!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/322892-china-offers-preliminary-approval-to-38-new-trump-trademarks

- http://www.businessinsider.com/ap-china-grants-preliminary-approval-to-38-new-trump-trademarks-2017-3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree it should and it should be highly regulated like they do in Australia and Germany. Where the power is in the woman's hands and the men come to the women in a safe space that provides round the clock security. But that is not what anyone wants who uses the services. They want to control their workers or if possible make them slaves who have no power. This is what happens many time after time and why human trafficking is mostly related to the human sex trafficking trade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As soon as any one openly announces their Myers Briggs profile without it being asked I know they are an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> biggest con, the game only runs at 720p on TV and on the portable screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China approves Donald Trump-branded escort services and massage parlours. That's right kids, bad suit wearing Pimp Daddy Don wants to help you by hooking you up with fine human trafficked hookers and tiny handed hand jobs. Only the most Christian things, old testament like. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pimp daddy Don ... with the bad fitting suits and everything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No congress has to give permission for any gift or formal title from a foreign country to a sitting president or elected official. Trademarks count as gifts / titles. This is the corner stone of the Emoluments Clause.

http://time.com/4579979/emoluments-clause-constitution-donald-trump/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China has granted preliminary approval to 38 new Trump-related trademarks as President Trump's family works to develop a series of branded products in the country, including hotel chains, escort services and insurance.

KEYNOTE THE ESCORT AGENCY PART

The new trademarks are considered by some to be a conflict of interest, especially as three of the trademarks were specifically made under the president's name.

The approval is preliminary and will be formally registered in 90 days, if no one objects to the trademarks.

But note, escort agency, meaning Trump is going to be a bloated rich, violent, woman abusing pimp in bad fitting suits we all know him to be out in the open now. Also knowing him he is going to be in for human trafficking and sex slaves to real actual morally corrupt billionaires

While Trump will never be one of them, a billionaire that is, at least he gets to service them now so maybe they might let him play with the cool rich kids like he always dreamed ...... nahhhhhhhhh still a loser who tries too hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China has granted preliminary approval to 38 new Trump-related trademarks as President Trump's family works to develop a series of branded products in the country, including hotel chains, escort services and insurance.

KEYNOTE THE ESCORT AGENCY PART

The new trademarks are considered by some to be a conflict of interest, especially as three of the trademarks were specifically made under the president's name.

The approval is preliminary and will be formally registered in 90 days, if no one objects to the trademarks.

But note, escort agency, meaning Trump is going to be a bloated rich, violent, woman abusing pimp in bad fitting suits we all know him to be out in the open now. Also knowing him he is going to be in for human trafficking and sex slaves to real actual morally corrupt billionaires

While Trump will never be one of them, a billionaire that is, at least he gets to service them now so maybe they might let him play with the cool rich kids like he always dreamed ...... nahhhhhhhhh still a loser who tries too hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China has granted preliminary approval to 38 new Trump-related trademarks as President Trump's family works to develop a series of branded products in the country, including hotel chains, escort services and insurance.

KEYNOTE THE ESCORT AGENCY PART

The new trademarks are considered by some to be a conflict of interest, especially as three of the trademarks were specifically made under the president's name.

The approval is preliminary and will be formally registered in 90 days, if no one objects to the trademarks.

But note, escort agency, meaning Trump is going to be a bloated rich, violent, woman abusing pimp in bad fitting suits we all know him to be out in the open now. Also knowing him he is going to be in for human trafficking and sex slaves to real actual morally corrupt billionaires

While Trump will never be one of them, a billionaire that is, at least he gets to service them now so maybe they might let him play with the cool rich kids like he always dreamed ...... nahhhhhhhhh still a loser who tries too hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only the best human trafficking and slavery from the Pimp Don. While he might never be a billionaire he will be servicing them all from Dubai to St Petersburg!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most Hated Woman in America | Official Trailer [HD] | Netflix's new true-crime biopic about the disappearance of Madalyn Murray O'Hair, founder of the "American Atheists" and pioneering firebrand in the political culture war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China approves Donald Trump-branded spas, escort services, hotels and massage parlours without US Congress permission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China approves Donald Trump-branded spas, escort services, hotels and massage parlours without US Congress permission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China approves Donald Trump-branded spas, escort services, hotels and massage parlours without US Congress permission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Donald Trump violated the emoluments clause so he could have a trademark in China for his own chain of Trump escort agency, meaning Trump is officially in for international prostitution, potentially human trafficing, and we can call him a pimp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Donald Trump violated the emoluments clause so he could have a trademark in China for his own chain of Trump escort agency, meaning Trump is officially in for international prostitution, potentially human trafficing, and we can call him a pimp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The_Donald killed the ability to tell if anything is real anymore. We are living in an alt-sarcasm world where you say it and are sarcastic but also mean it at the same time now. So /s was broken out to show i actually mean NONE Of this fucking bullshit. 

I just realized this is how all my native expat Russian friends act .... fuck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats why we are defunding planned parenthood in the  USA  , more miracle babies you can send facebook likes/prayers to! Becauese jesus would have wanted it this way, feel his power  /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to breath, being i have asthma 

https://www.numbeo.com/pollution/compare_cities.jsp?country1=United+States city1=Houston%2C+TX country2=United+States city2=Austin%2C+TX </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump violated the emoluments clause so he could have a trademark in china for his own chain of Trump escort prostitution agency and Trump handjob parlors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Donald Trump violated the emoluments clause so he could have a trademark in china for his own chain of Trump escort prostitution agency and Trump handjob parlors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Fuck, it felt like longer maybe it was the logged in custom search on google. Hmm anyway you can see you didnt get my clear. Maybe it was from your mom's side in some sort of ressive tarded gene </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and austin, you forgot that Austin makes up for a whole lot of shit in texas as well. It's one of the only places that will ever make me visit Texas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To fund border wall, Trump administration weighs cuts to Coast Guard, airport security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To fund border wall, Trump administration weighs cuts to Coast Guard, airport security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To fund border wall, Trump administration weighs cuts to Coast Guard, airport security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans introduce resolution to kill FCCs internet privacy rules 28: They want to let ISPs share your web browsing history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans introduce resolution to kill FCCs internet privacy rules 28: They want to let ISPs share your web browsing history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UPDATING  'Game Changer': Despite Official Denials Candidate Trump Met With Russian Ambassador Says Conservative News Site </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UPDATING  'Game Changer': Despite Official Denials Candidate Trump Met With Russian Ambassador Says Conservative News Site </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The proof of a literary war on Christians. Not really. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Trump supporter with a cardboard cutout of the president sits on a bench at a rainy Brea, California, Pro Trump rally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Trump supporter with a cardboard cutout of the president sits on a bench at a rainy Brea, California, Pro Trump rally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is how I expect the entire Trump Cabinet and staff to act when asked about ethics now that we know Trump transition team canceled plan for ethics training for staff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By Jeff Sessions Standard for Lying Under Oath, Jeff Sessions Lied Under Oath </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By Jeff Sessions Standard for Lying Under Oath, Jeff Sessions Lied Under Oath </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> setting up SSH instead of FTP for Wordpress plugin install / updates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i'm hosting my Wordpress page on a VPS and this is my first time setting up wordpress that wasn't a single install from an automated system. I'm reading conflicting and outdated reports on how best to do this. My system is running the latest for Wordpress, PHP7, and apache latest and MariaDB with myphpadmin as well on a Ubuntu 16.04 

I want to setup the update, theme install, plugin install so that it can just do it from the menu easily but it requires FTP or FTPS for ssl connection. Knowing a little bit i don't want to use plain text FTP to do that because its stupid. I want to use SFTP / SSH but the tutorials i find all have you installing files with projects that have been deprecated like sshphplib.

Any help here would be great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drunk Driver's Mom laughs at victims family while they are reading impact statement in court about the death of their father. Judge gets lit and will have none of that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 08:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George W. Bush paints dark picture of America under Trump: I dont like the racism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George W. Bush paints dark picture of America under Trump: I dont like the racism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George W. Bush paints dark picture of America under Trump: I dont like the racism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump casually suggests rise in anti-Semitic threats could be fake 'false flag' operation He made the comments to a meeting of state attorneys general, according to one of the officials present. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump casually suggests rise in anti-Semitic threats could be fake 'false flag' operation He made the comments to a meeting of state attorneys general, according to one of the officials present. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump just told the Pennsylvania AG that anti-Semitic threats may be false flag operations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says Obama behind leaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/GeorgeAmberson63 makes a satirical post explaining the complex steps one must jump through to contact George Soros and Hillary Clinton so one might become a paid leftist protester (Satire) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/GeorgeAmberson63 makes a satirical post explaining the complex steps one must jump through to contact George Soros and Hillary Clinton so one might become a paid leftist protester (Satire) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ant-Man wants Shooting Stars too! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Mom with close friends Judy and Larry at an Old Vic theater party in London, England in 1973 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump in 4 tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We need to destroy their power bases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we need to start war. Infowar. We need to destroy the online wealth springs of metastasizing viral propaganda come from. We need people who are willing to topple their online strongholds.

/r/conspiracy and /r/The_Donald and /r/TheRedPill  as some examples of where his flock of sycophants flow from. There are more but we need to pick them off one at a time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's the chemicals in the water that are making the men gay and liberals! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 13:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump on states rights (x-post /r/Libertarian) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 12:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Animation only trackers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 09:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump-Russia Investigation : Updated 2/24 7 PM EST/4 PM PST - 25 pages of sourced reports. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 08:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Media and IC can only succeed in taking the Trump russian traitors down if they are supported and everyone is actively making sure the Trump-Russia story gets out there. Keep pushing for the truth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 07:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> h.265 HEVC only trackers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any h.265 HEVC only trackers yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White House just blocked The New York Times, Politico, Los Angeles Times, Buzzfeed, and CNN from White House press gaggle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White House just blocked The New York Times, Politico, Los Angeles Times, Buzzfeed, and CNN from White House press gaggle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White House just blocked The New York Times, Politico, Los Angeles Times, Buzzfeed, and CNN from White House press gaggle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alt-right leader expelled from CPAC after organizer denounces left-wing fascist anti-semtic group </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relax to the soothing sounds of Mitch McConnell getting viciously chewed out by a constituent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Do the Trump Pump" By Bad History </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super Deluxe Presents - Trump is a Mess at his Press Conference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super Deluxe Presents - Trump Is A Mess At His Press Conference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad History - TRUMP (Pump Trump) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
