<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8487</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 05:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 seems like such a subjective term.  She's got crazy curves. Emphasis on crazy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 20:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was only speaking in a physical-appearance context.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 17:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd definitely be willing to help in anyway I can if it was more than an animal magnetism driving me.  She mentioned something last night about how Scientology makes some good points- it's just shit like that.  Highly opinionated, not going to be debated on- I just know I wouldn't be happy with her as a person.   It's really amazing how our biology can drive us to completely override logical thinking.  I'd like to say I'm not going to- guess we'll just have to see.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I win the war between mind and penis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 14:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A woman has taken interest in me that is clearly out of my league.  Her life is kind of a mess  (4 kids, no car, no job) and she has a strong personality.  Clearly she knows she's a 10 and I'm sure has had men drooling all over her her entire life- which is evident when we go out.   I know this woman is not a good choice, but as the title suggests, my pre-programming has a hard time leaving her alone.   She's super confident and last night told me, if we hang out today you'll be getting some p***y.   Talk some sense into me Reddit! 

UPDATE: Stayed in. Caught up on Walking Dead and rubbed one out.  
I appreciate all the feedback.  In the back of my mind I aways suspected  I wouldnt, but I needed a bit of support to reinforce that.  Left to the wimbs of my own unsupported decision making it would definitely have been more 50/50. 
Much appreciated.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 13:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brilliant advice.  Can I followup with a question? 
I'm currently new to personal finance and frugal living. I've made some giant strides and am feeling good about the direction I'm going, but still have a long way to go.  I have $1400 in savings which I add 10% of my paycheck every pay period.  Is that enough in there to stop the saving and add that money towards my new 0% interest card while I'm trying to pay down the debt?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with a decision! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 23:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I currently have $8,061.99 on a Citi card earning 9.99% interest (which I've heard is good)
I have the opportunity through my bank, USAA, to get a 0% for 18 months on balance transfers with a 3% transfer fee and turning over to 12.90% in Jan 2017.   Is that a good deal?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 04:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solid golllld </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So my option is to charge my Apple Watch at night, or allow it to track my sleep? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 04:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is sleep tracking even something Apple Watch does? 
It seems like a major oversight given that most other fitness trackers perform that function.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Norman! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 05:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 01:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that escalated quickly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 00:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but I love Pho! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird Science! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 00:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bedtime snack. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 15:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Half-Price Books nails it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 20:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I holding food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 01:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 15:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What font are all the kids using these days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Angry, sad and mostly confused. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 07:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superfluous wireless clients on my AirPort Extreme. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 03:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have extra Apple TV wireless clients. 

1 says Apple TV
Another says Apple TV (8) 

Seems they're both drawing wireless.  Can I get rid of one of them?  I only have one Apple TV and the network is secure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 15:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they lifting weights in the background? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My good friend Brian. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 03:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 15:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the Lord is a Mogwai.  We also shouldn't feed him after midnight.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 16:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking about actually getting a part time job till it's gone.  Dedicate everything I make working a few nights a week to it.  I'm wanting to save for a downpayment on a house but can't make much progress under the current debt.  
Thank you for your help with thinking it through- looks like I'll just stick with the card I have an work harder at both saving and finding other work.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 15:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know it's not like flipping off a goddamn light switch.  Some of these habits are engrained.  Way to insult the guy here to better his life.  Do you also make fun of people at the gym who are working to get in shape? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 15:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does it go up to after intro period?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 15:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My minimum payment every month is $150 currently.  I've been paying $200, which I know isn't MUCH more but it's just what I've been doing.  
I want to pay as much as I can without having to give up meals out.  Ugh it's my achilles heel.   $8-10 dollar lunches are like the death-by-1000 cuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 15:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tax refund arrived this morning....too bad $1600 in 100,000 mile car repairs (belts, plugs yada yada yada) will snuff that out right quick. 

What is 25% utilization?  Is that something I ask for at Citi Cards, or through another lender?

Thanks for the rapid response!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When do I jump ship from high interest CC to low? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 15:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have roughly $8,500 on a Citi card that's hitting me with 12.99% APR. I have worked out my budget now so that I'm never using it anymore, but I'm finding that the principal isn't dropping fast enough due to interest.  When/how/should I find some low interest card to work on paying it off? Drawbacks?  If this is common knowledge, I apologize, I'm new to being responsible. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 16:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonky Nipples </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once more unto the breach dear friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 19:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 01:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is tight in all the right places.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One finger or two? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 14:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EVERY TIME! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 20:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 21:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you by chance upside down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fat guy goodness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 20:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 15:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She looks like a Tina Fey who won't fart on you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 06:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GREAT core workout
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 06:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 years to humans on Mars?  In another of his videos he states A.I. will kill us in 5-10...make up your mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 20:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christmas sweater, 50's...motherly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walking through the Women's underwear dept at Herbergers, when one lady asked where to find the K-Cups... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 20:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 13:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GREAT sound!  Me enCANta! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 03:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she were a fish we'd throw her back because she is wormy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 17:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does my girlfriend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 01:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not dissing the poor guy- if that be the case, lord knows I hate getting up to speak in public; just noticing he's always in videos and in the crowd but rarely up on stage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder if Jony Ive is afraid of public speaking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 00:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He only makes videos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 05:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Touch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 04:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg Live Action Role Play- HUZZAH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 04:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...did you see the (I think recent) YouTube video aptly titled "Humans Need Not Apply?"  Somewhere in the last few minutes they talk about "creative fields" going to robots as well and provided audio of a computer-created piano solo.  Not saying you're wrong, but I think far less people are safe from this eventuality than we might think.  
I realize I'm a Debbie Downer.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
