<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6750</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did the right thing. You are pretty young and I assume the wife is too, get yourself some counseling. Good luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And she doesn't have a cell phone?  Or friends?  Or family?  A job?  Hard to believe no one is looking for her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you are with someone who is glad you are alive and well and not too concerned about your scars. You should mention it only because it may become distracting in an intimate moment. If this is some  you'd like to see long term, disclose. If not then do the deed and it's cool. Scars are not scarey. If you bleed or leak you might want to give a heads up so there's no surprises. Personally wouldn't care at all and neither would any of my friends tbh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When time has passed, what do you want to be remembered for?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *screaming* I would have died! Have you called your gyno to see what it fell out. Lol hey at least you don't have to make an appointment to get it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's call him crazy horse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nooo :0  the entire device fell out? How!! Did you feel anything prior? Did the coil look weird ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a tmi - but whatever. Does SO only feel in different positions?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol where can I find weed in Rome? I'm going to be there with my husband at the end of march. Is it cold ? What's your favorite untouristy thing to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
