<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8477</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 21:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As do sociopaths behavior to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 21:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's implied by your answer.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 21:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but I'm asking Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 21:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And these are qualities that you value in a candidate for presidency of the United States? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we go ahead and label Mitt Romney a sociopath? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 21:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's look at his past behavior and attitude towards this election. He consistently lies to seem appealing to whomever he's speaking to. He lies, blatantly and regularly, as though no one is noticing. He is clearly doing whatever it takes to win the election,  at any expense. He has preyed on weaker companies to earn himself a buck. He cheats the tax system for personal gain. I think this is textbook behavior for a person clearly lacking any type of moral compass or conscious at all for that matter. It's as though he is running just for him. To hell with the rest of us; he just wants to get into the White House. What say ye Reddit?

EDIT:many of you are unclear on the meaning of the word sociopath. Here you are

Sociopath: A person with a personality disorder manifesting itself in extreme antisocial attitudes and behavior and a lack of conscience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 18:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that puts that thought to rest. Thank you! That actually made sense to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 18:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got to realize that RT is just state sponsored television by the Russian government for people who speak english. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if zombies.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 15:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This just came to me while i was lurking. Could the dead/non-dead nature of zombies be explained as a physical representation of people in a quantum state?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 04:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been where you are. Not with regards to how the split occurred, but the emotional toll that it takes on you. The one piece of advice that I cant give you is to throw anything out that you got from or shared with her. I know you'd rather not. I know that those were good times. I know it all means so much to you, but the reality is that the stuff is torturing you. Constantly reminding you of her. Then you go and give her the attention she wants. She is enjoying being able to have you want her. She feels cool blowing you off and having a sense of control over you. 

Listen, get rid of it all, if you have anything from her that is, and don't give it to friends or donate it. send it to a landfill or burn it. its cathartic. If this doesn't apply to you, I wont mind if you ignore it. 

Good luck to you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A thought on the "persecution" that Christians claim to face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-02 19:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It occurred to me that Christian persecution is a real problem around the world. Christians are being persecuted by Radical Islam, Orthodox Judea and any other religion not their own. Much like Christianity did to other religions in the past. So, religions massacring other religions. Sounds about right. 

Thank you for reading my useless rant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
