<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9437</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some stunning Islamic medicine (Drink camel urine!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 11:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Stunning Islamic Science! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 10:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, today. I was speaking with my Muslim friend. He went on with all this nonsense about how Islam has always prophesied scientific theories. One of the examples he came up with really made me laugh hysterically. He said that their Prophet discovered a cure ages ago. That cure is: if a fly falls into your drink, dip it in the drink because one of its wings can cure disease. Here is the hadith in full: http://i.imgur.com/bWMAplL.jpg. He kept going with this stupidity about how scientists today discovered that this is true. And, bla bla bla. After doing my own research today, I found that it was utter nonsense and dipping a fly in a drink would actually be injurious, given the number of diseases that can be transmitted. And, even, if you accept this as true ( for the sake of his stupid argument), then any so-called antibiotics in the fly and any associated benefits they may accord would be quite inconsequential compared to the multitude of pathogens that can replicate rapidly. 

But in our conversation I honestly just couldn't reply. Because I was laughing out loud at this lunacy. Honestly, made my day. 

This is the Islamic science that Muslims keep telling us all about?! How unhygienic! It is probably not a good idea to get sick in a Muslim country. What if they give you a fly in a cup of water as a treatment, lol?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public subsidies now being used to discriminate against people of different religious beliefs: Disabled man rejected for subsidized housing because he is not Muslim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 03:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic ruling on whether children who die young will go to Paradise or Hell? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 09:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I found this question on the IslamQA website: http://islamqa.info/en/6496

I find it very pernicious to tell children that if they die while still being children, they will definitely go to heaven. A Muslim friend of mine remembers being told this by his teacher when he was a kid. He said he kept hoping that he would die as a child so he can get into paradise. 

I feel that it is quite pernicious and terribly wrong to say something like that to a child. What if they kill themselves "to get into heaven"? That would be terrible. 

There is also some discussion on whether Non-muslim children will get into heaven if they die. The answer is quite ridiculous:  "they will either be in Paradise or in Hell, depending on whether they would have obeyed Allah if they had lived (something that only Allah would know)."

Also - I realized, why is it that with most of these Islamic questions, there is always this statement that "The scholars are divided and bla bla bla". They can't seem to make up their own minds about anything, it seems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 09:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a difference between animate objects and inanimate objects.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic "ruling" on drawing animate objects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 10:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came across this link from an Islamic website: http://islamqa.info/en/39806 

In Islam, it is forbidden to depict animate objects as doing so is a mimicry of Allah's creation. 

LOL, again, religion with its preposterous narrow-minded and weird petty "rulings". Oh NO! Catastrophe! You drew a picture of a human! You will burn in hell! LOL!! 

Halfway through the passage in the link I attached, a sentence starts with "The scholars discussed...". LOL I can imagine scholars sitting on a table, discussing "the sin of drawing animate beings". Such a trivial matter causes this much concern lol? 

Why is it that especially in Islam, they have all of these so-called "rulings" on really inconsequential things. Muslims believe in Allah who created the entire universe but yet who would give a damn what you scribble on a piece of paper?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 10:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You burn in hell, lol :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 22:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is Islam wide in all the sects. In many mosques, before they start praying, the imam also reminds them of this (to line their feet up and make them touch so as to not let Satan in between) lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 21:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic Superstition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 21:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came across this photo from a Muslim facebook page: 
http://i.imgur.com/VwFW7zi.jpg

The Infographic is advising Muslims to make sure their feet touch when praying so that Satan won't enter the spaces in between them and disrupt prayer. 

Hahahah. I honestly cannot stop laughing. I can't believe there are people who believe this utter nonsense.  A mystical creature that doesn't even exist causes this much concern. The weird thing is this photo has almost 70,000 likes and 60,000 shares with tons of comments like "Thanks for the valuable advice" and "keep up the good work". 

Religion at its best. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 06:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
They are a bunch of retarded fuckwits. I am from Canada and visited Saudi Arabia for a while and those fuckers took me in their car, drove me to a mosque, and forced me to pray. Fuck them and fuck the Saudi government.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 09:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was new to me. Didn't know it was posted before. But very funny story LOL  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 09:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL I agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi Arabia: The Worlds Greatest Hypocrite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 10:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman Taken to Jail After Saying Jesus Would Pay Her Restaurant Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 10:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ray Bradbury quote meaning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 09:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did Ray Bradbury mean when he said: "We are an impossibility in an impossible universe?". I see a lot of religious people using this quote as a point for God. But did he really mean that? Or was he merely exaggerating the great odds of our existence? As far as I know, Ray Bradbury was an atheist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
