<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7891</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 16:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great way to put it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 13:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only prequel scene I really liked was the final battle between Darth Maul and Qui-Gon and Obi-Wan. The physical characterisation when they are trapped by the barriers is great - Qui-Gon sits and meditates, Obi-Wan hops from one foot to another like a worried child, Darth Maul prowls like a caged predator. Apart from that 30 second sequence though, it's all entertaining fluff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 11:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't wear a dead-man's switch when you're at the wheel of a boat, you're going to have a bad time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 02:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I don't know: picturesque, peaceful, vertiginous, bucolic, pastoral, calming, restorative, beautiful, well-framed, expertly-exposed, pleasing, balanced, tonally complex, cloudy, verdant, mountainous, dizzying, awe-inspiring, frightening, slightly disorientating, artistic, alpine, and ..... nice.

Ran out of steam a bit at the end there.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 01:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea if it's what a "good Buddhist" would do or not, but I would have done exactly that and put it out of its pain as quickly and humanely as possible, with a shovel or other heavy object. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 19:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, they really kicked your ass, didn't they?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 18:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allen Steele is amazing. If colonising space itself counts, Orbital Decay is also brilliant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question for you, Buddhit Buddies: if my "self" is an illusion and your "self" is an illusion, why should I be concerned with alleviating the suffering of your "self"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 13:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 23:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No colourblind mode? :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 21:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Have you seen "Super"? Similar moments of awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 13:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me too. I have come to realise that I have become very attached to being "the generous guy" and it manifests in ridiculous and pointless ways (like handing out hundreds of pounds worth of glow sticks for free at music festivals - what a waste!). However, I recognise this, but I don't beat myself up about it. It's a phase on my journey and it will pass, and it's a step up from being selfish. It does bother me that if I was really trying to increase happiness and reduce suffering, there's so much more that I could do with the 150 I blew last weekend than giving a couple of hundred people something to wave around for an hour or two.

Did meet loads of people I never would have talked to otherwise, and I got some cool photos! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 00:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do exactly the same thing on GetGlue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 17:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP neglected to mention that this is a still from the indie short "Batman: Dead End" (2003) by Sandy Collora, the guy who designed the Jurassic Park logo. 8 min odd movie here: http://m.youtube.com/#/watch?desktop_uri=%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DNUdG0VFFNSU v=NUdG0VFFNSU gl=GB

Well worth a watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 02:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it amazing how much difference the presentation makes? This one looks all "oh cool, an original alien suit (although it looks like whoever set up the display has seen "Aliens" but not "Alien"). 

But the other one, the one in Frankfurt - fraying and decaying - looks like a piece of art. It reminds me of Damien Hirst's dead-things-in-formaldehyde stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 01:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like it. Have an upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 17:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, The Thing (1982). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 15:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ross' score to "The Book of Eli" was by far the best thing about that film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 15:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience (and this is not aimed at the OP), most players who arrive on the server on their own and complain about no one else being a team player are the ones running around suicidally, getting killed, losing tickets, and blaming everyone else for not reviving them. I'm in the top 8% globally for playing objectives and in the top 10% for medical efficiency (yes, my K/D is terrible) and I see this all the time. There's only so much I can do if you think "team playing" means following you around, reading your mind as to what the plan is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 15:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alien (1979). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 15:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with you on the point about good writing carrying poor direction and production, and so does Joss Whedon: 

Screenwriter Joss Whedon was unhappy with the final product. When asked in 2005 how the film differed from the script he had written, Whedon responded:
"It wasn't a question of doing everything differently, although they changed the ending; it was mostly a matter of doing everything wrong. They said the lines...mostly...but they said them all wrong. And they cast it wrong. And they designed it wrong. And they scored it wrong. They did everything wrong that they could possibly do. There's actually a fascinating lesson in filmmaking, because everything that they did reflects back to the script or looks like something from the script, and people assume that, if I hated it, then theyd changed the script...but it wasnt so much that theyd changed the script; its that they just executed it in such a ghastly fashion as to render it almost unwatchable."[26]

(Talking about "Alien Resurrection" - extract from http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alien_Resurrection)

For my money, excellent performances, direction, editing and cinematography can carry a less-than-stellar script. But if they're not up to scratch, the best writing in the world won't save the film.

For truly great cinema, it all needs to come together. Writing, direction, performance, score, set design, costume, lighting, effects, cinematography, editing, post-processing, even the marketing and presentation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 03:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they were thoroughly soaked and washed, don't worry. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-28 17:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if you're like my friends and me, you collect about 500 empty ones of these from your local photo processing service, fill them with vodka jelly shots and then hand them out to everyone around you in the crowd at a music festival. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-18 16:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AWESOME to find someone else - I'm getting weary of suggesting this gem on Reddit! :-) "Ink" is one of the most visually and thematically creative movies I have ever seen and deserves much wider recognition than it gets.

I would also suggest Danny Boyle's Sunshine as an interesting exploration of rationalist/humanist/scientific/atheist/secular (delete as applicable) spiritualism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 01:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch the Director's Cut - it's still not perfect but it's amazing how much can be improved by reediting scenes to pace them properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 01:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My personal view (no quote from Giger to back it up) is that it is intentionally eyeless because when humans look at a face, we instinctively focus on the eyes; so when confronted with an eyeless face, we are forced to "look it in the teeth". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 01:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen a Director's Cut of a James Cameron film that is better than the theatrical release. It's like he needs a good editor/producer to occasionally say, "No, James, it's a better movie without that scene and I'm putting my foot down." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 13:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's not coincidence, it's painfully bloody obvious, trite and annoying, especially given that the ending of the story is extremely well known and has been for about 100 years. I don't mean that to sound uncharitable, what I mean is that when I first saw the movie (which I like a lot), that one line made me think "oh great, Spielberg talking down to us again." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 11:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's going into some serious therapy, possibly in an institution and likely for a very, very long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 00:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has nothing to do with what the author intended. If you know nothing about literary analysis, why call it stupid? Some people find this rewarding; you don't. Fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 17:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did a 10,000 word close-reading of the first 120 seconds for my degree. It's surprising how much you can write about a shot of a reflection in an eye (whose eye?) when you can talk about scopophilia, the cinematic gaze, audience identification points, the concept of individual versus omnipresent point-of-view, Freudian criticism's view on eyeball imagery and "the window to the soul" when the possessor of the eyeball may or may not be artificial and therefore without a soul, the mirroring of reflecting eyeballs in Rachel, Roy and the owl in later shots etc. etc. etc.

Writing about BR is fun and relatively easy, because there's so much packed into it that you can basically explore what you want.

So relax and enjoy it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 17:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hauer intentionally delivered the word to be ambiguous (father/fucker) and it was re-dubbed in post one way for the theatrical release and the other for the Laser Disc release/Director's Cut. So the ambiguous delivery in The Final Cut is actually the original. (Source: either commentary or featurette on TFC BluRay, I forget which). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
