<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8398</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries, I didn't take it as an attack, I know so little about opera I can't even tell who is good and who is bad so I'm not surprised if I sounded off.

I did choir for a year in college and two years as an adult, otherwise I only started voice lessons last December. My voice teacher used to sing light opera on stage so even she may not be a legit opera singer. She just gave me the aria for fun, mixed in with musical theater stuff like Don't Cry for Me Argentina. I know a lot of people here were questioning why my voice teacher gave me that song and said my voice was completely wrong for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is very normal to not be able to sing high notes when you just start learning to sing, a lot of singing comes down to support. Back when I was in high school, I was told by a (completely unqualified) friend that since I couldn't sing high it meant I was a contralto. She had voice lessons too, and told me she was also a contralto. Later I found out that I was actually a soprano with horrible technique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the reason I ask about fach is because last time when I posted myself singing O Mio Babbino Caro I was told it was completely the wrong fach for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if I suck at legato AND runs?

Edit: actually I might be good at legato. I didnt even know it was hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which department at your company has all the crazy people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to know of any tips too. I suck at harmonies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try to sing with your nose pinched until it is least distorted and then unpinch your nose and sing from the same place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, trained singers support their voices correctly - they use their diaphragms to support the sound whereas this guy is just squeezing in his throat muscles. He will damage his voice if he continues on like this.

Edit: added comma after no, whoops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What exactly is a coloratura? Are they lyric sopranos trained into singing crazy fast or are they naturally like that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering.

Edit: and coloratura mezzos* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Popular from Wicked annoys me, it has been overdone at middle schools by girls who cant sing

That one song from Hairspray that the 4 kids sing about love. The lyrics between Seaweed and Penny annoy me:

Him: living in the ghetto, black is everywhere you go, who'd have thought Id love a girl with skin as white as winter snow

Her: In my ivory tower life was just a hostess snack, but now Ive tasted chocolate and Im never going back

I hear that and I go...are they seriously singing about each other's races? Like I get it is an interracial couple but they are actually singing about each other's races? Really?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I love that song! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lea Salonga overenunciates in her version, I find the beginning part especially annoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I skip it on the soundtrack every time it comes up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disney. Disney/Broadway songs are the best practice songs. That is almost all I sing at my lessons.

Let's get down to business, to defeat, the huns!

Mr. Aladdin sir blah blah blah blah

Under da sea, under da sea, down here it's wetter

Shalalalalala by your side, don't be shy ya gotta kiss the girl

Be our guest be our guest put our service to the test

That one song Quasimodo sings in The Hunchback of Notre Dame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okie dokie, although I wish you make more than just $19! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are 100% right - I know that of my 17 book sales, 12 are sales I already knew about (my manager from my day job, family friends, etc.). It seems that there was 0 marketing behind my book from the publisher's part - my book is practically self-published except I didn't have to pay. Several people who saw the book cover says the cover is extremely off-putting, it looks crazy low budget and a stock photo would have been much better.

Trying to get my next book picked up by a lit agent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch your friend's review, how the hell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup sent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My process is similar except instead of Amazon I post it to fictionpress.com for free. What's weird is that what I think is one of my strongest works had almost no reviews, but a casual short story I wrote in college that got ripped apart in my creative writing workshop got 10,000+ views and lots of positive reviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sent in message </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will message you the link, want to stay anonymous on Reddit lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my book doesn't even have an ISBN number. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 09:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, although I bought 20 copies to give out to friends/family so overall I made less than I earned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't even self published lol ;_; it was just a small indie place, I actually had to query. It is pretty much run by one guy so there is pretty much no promotion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got my first check for the indie novella I published 6 months ago. The check came to $19 lol. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The royalties came to slightly more than a dollar a sale and I sold about 17 copies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound really young when you sing, 13 or so, although you look like a young adult.

Maybe it would clarify things if you posted a clip of yourself simply singing scales on "ah" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just google'd it - the lawsuit is an urban legend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I have a coworker who is a white guy and he took his Japanese wife's last name. Kind of weird when you expect someone Japanese and he shows up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Average in most ways but apparently I draw well. When I was a little kid I was once casually drawing a pic of a bear and the kids near me all started crowding around me and watching when to me it was just a doodle. Was an artist for my high school newspaper, and then never did anything with it after that. Now I work a desk job doing stuff with data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 09:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the first things my voice teacher corrected in my singing was how I (a soprano) kept trying to belt along to alto songs and then straining myself. So I would say it is ok to sound a little boring if the alternative is that you will damage your voice in the long run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, the low notes made me poop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's far, far more complicated than that. I used to think I didn't strain because I was not hurting myself, but my voice teacher pointed out I was definitely straining. Even though I couldn't feel it, she was watching my throat and my throat wasn't completely relaxed 100% of the time.

I had to completely unlearn how I had been hitting high notes because my support was completely wrong. I can hear from your clip that you are doing what I used to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch please take some lessons before attempting those high notes! You will permanently damage your voice, that is not the right technique at all for approaching high notes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't feel them once they are inside, unless they get completely drenched in blood. Then they feel kind of heavy and squishy and you have to hurry to change them before you leak everywhere. If you pee, you have to reach from behind and hold the string out of the way to not pee on it, or else it will get wet and then stick to your upper thigh and feel cold, and that is just nasty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Really shitty family, did therapy for it, still not okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Puppy love handholding - 13
Actual dates - 16
Sex - 18+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VELMA??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you get picked on for when you were growing up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 09:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im gonna guess tenor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If multiple agents liked your query and sample pages but turned down the manuscript, doesn't it usually mean you had a good premise and prose but that overall your storytelling abilites suck? I dunno, I have had people praise my writing in workshops and stuff but I haven't been able to get an agent so I clearly am doing something wrong (I think?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if a couple of them ask for more but then turn it down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 04:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to read lots of fanfiction as a teen, and it definitely means there is an amateur wuality to the writing. Chances are the main character is a girl with purple eyes who is extremely beautiful to the point every guy is in love with her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 09:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it works without a prologue, don't do a prologue. If it needs a prologue, then put a prologue. There's really no right answer to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 05:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pidy him

You pidy him

He/she/it pidies

We pidy

You guys pidy (Californian accent)

They pidy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably those 12 page essays they make you do in college that I started the night before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely agree with what you said. I guess no 1 out of 3 queries for me then, boo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since my story is from the 1st person POV of a little girl and she is a kid/teen for the first half and in her early twenties for the majority of the second half, it probably could pass as YA but I didn't want to put it in a box because there is a lot of social commentary as well. I guess if the word count is a huge deal then I would call it YA but I think a more appropriate label is New Adult. I know literary fiction can sometimes be as short as 40k so I was originally worried it was too long lol.

I might be able to add another 8-9k to the word count, but I don't think I could put more than that without it hurting the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, thank you for your feedback. I will definitely change up the synopsis because the length of it was making me question it as well.

As for length, I read that while most adult fiction is in the 70-80k range, literary fiction can be significantly shorter and my book is definitely more literary-leaning than commercial. I don't want to force in extra scenes/sentences that weaken the story just to meet the ideal word count, you know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh it definitely could be better, but at the same time if the plot were fast paced and fun then I could see an agent asking for more, you know what I mean? I don't know what the story is about - I only skimmed the samples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure it's a bit Hunger Games meets sorting hat, but there still is concrete writing and its own originality. What I mean is, say someone writes a generic Western novel with nothing unusual and there are already so many famous western novels.

Also the first Divergent book has very strong prose (the second and third books of the series are more clumsy). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the word count of the full manuscript is too short? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn that's more than a book a day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you can make the frame juicier by raising the stakes somehow? Arabian Nights is fun because it's got a historical fiction element to it where you can kill people and get away with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm, no one in my group is very literary, they're all heavy commercial writers. I think the closest we've got to a literary writer is a woman who is an English lit professor on the side but her writing is boring as hell and the main character is always not-so-secretly herself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My writer's group also does read-alouds (separate works from the critiques) and I tend to zone out if I don't find the story interesting, but rather than say it's not interesting I just kind of smile and nod and just don't comment lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the inside stories have to be relevant to the bigger story. For example, The Joy Luck Club is a story about a mom dying and the daughter finding out she has sisters in China. It then breaks down into smaller subplots to show you the rest of the community, where the daughters' stories reflect the main daughter's life and the mothers' stories reflect the main mother's life.

Orange Is the New Black is also stories within a story. The main story arc being Piper's and the substories fleshing out that universe.

As long as it's not a random-ass unrelated story, you know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm in a writers' critique group, dunno how to critique other people's work without hurting their feelings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I joined a local writer's guild fairly recently and have only been to 2 critiques. The writers are all either unpublished or self-published, and everyone else is over 40...except for a former classmate of mine who is there.

One day, my former classmate wasn't there. Then one of the old guys (he must be in his 50s or 60s) started talking smack about her. He said that she was really negative towards his writing, as if hers was a lot better, but that when it came time for her to be critiqued he expected something amazing since she was such a hardass on him, and he was surprised by how mediocre her writing was.

Now, that girl and I had taken creative writing classes in college and it was normal to be a hardass. In fact, she was much more gentle at critiquing than I was lol. Since I have only just joined the group I just mention the one or two things that I thought they did a good job on and if there are several things I don't like I will only point out the most obvious one and say it carefully. So far they like me lol.

What are your own thoughts on this? By the way I tried joining another critique group and this one is SO much better than the other one - everyone has at least semi-decent prose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My story had flashbacks where the aunt was telling the daughter a story about the mom as a little girl.

Wuthering Heights is a good example. Princess Bride. The Notebook. The Secret Diary of Anne Boleyn. Story of Aladdin in the story of Sharazad telling her husband stories to keep him from killing her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The prose looks decent (for commercial fiction, anyway), could be better but nothing blindingly bad. Maybe the problem is the query/story itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 00:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post your query here. Is the idea not original? Agents tend to reject stories if it has already been done before and done better.

Other rejection reasons:

-"Dear Agent" instead of the agent's name

-attachments in query are automatically marked spam

-You cc'd multiple agents on the same email </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 08:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the details, does it matter which agent I get? I was under the impression that big places like Writers' House had the best connections so I have only queried one person from each of the biggest agencies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I have a couple manuscripts that I had written, sent out, and then gave up on. Most of my manuscripts got some partial requests but no offer. I did get a novella published with an indie place, but they are so small that the book doesn't have an ISBN number and had virtually no mrketing, so I want to have an agent this time.

With my latest manuscript I sent it to just one agent in November, waited a month, and then saw he doesn't accept email queries, whoops! Then I sent it to just 3 or 4 more agents in December, got 1 full request and 2 rejections, 1 no response. Sent 3 more queries in this past week.

Yeah I changed my title, the first one was pretty stupid and probably hurt my chances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the love of god do not have them describe themselves in detail after looking into a mirror. It is way, way, WAYYYYY too overdone. It looks like "I took a Creative Writing class and this is what my professor told me to do" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well for actors they can get away with not doing a ton of research because the script is already written and there is someone else directing it. When you're the writer though, it's your own story.

I don't think there is such a thing as too much research. Alex Haley spent, what, 9 years doing the research needed to write Roots? I have a novella that takes place during the Trojan War and I did the motherload of research (I was already obsessed with the Trojan War but I turned the dial up to a 10 when writing it) - I made sure every plant and animal mentioned would have existed in that time and region, made sure it was realistic for a character to travel from one city to another in X number of days, made sure the items were made out of the exact type of materials that they would have been made up of historically during that time.

I don't think there can be too much research when you're on a topic like historical or science fiction, you gain a ton of respect from your reader when you know your stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Change the lyrics and make it a comedy. I once did this completely as a joke and had no intention on making it spread, but I took a Lady Gaga song and changed the lyrics to make it be about a game I was playing. I then posted it on the gamer forums and it blew up, I deleted it the next day because I felt embarrassed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah thank you for your input - I meant 15 queries for a single manuscript. I sent maybe 5 queries out for my manuscript in December, one agent asked for more, and then I twiddled my thumbs for a while and decided to submit a couple more this weekend just in case the first agent comes back to me with a no. It's still less than 10 queries for this manuscript and I was wondering if I should continue or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question: Why should you query more than, say, 15 agents? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're targeting agents who represent your genre and not even 1 out of 15 of them want to look at it, doesn't that mean your work sucks? Why do people advise that you should query more agents than that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Louis Sachar got his first book published in his early twenties. I am older than he was then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will guess Glasgow (I am American)

Edit: Actually I think I hear some Russian in there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asian American faking an English accent, is it anything like it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents are from China, I grew up in California, I heard this accent on some British documentaries and reality TV shows and I don't even know what region of the UK it is from.

http://vocaroo.com/i/s0qKL8g3wnOO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nick Jonas. Can't sing very well but can sing surprisingly high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice recording!

Right now I am taking voice lessons, 2 months in, and I have been recording my voice regularly and playing it back. I notice less strain already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This made me laugh aloud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brain is still so focused on my current manuscript that I keep picking at it andmaking changes. If the agent says ok it is ok to slip some small changes in like a sentence choice here and there, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A mich better thesis is why Odysseus cheated on his wife, spent 7 years with Calypso and 1 year with Circe. He could have returned to Ithaca 8 years earlier if he hadn't been cheating on his wife while she remained faithful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sitting around waiting for a lit agent to look through my manuscript, now what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 08:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 28, majored in creative writing, in a writer's group etc. 

A junior lit agent at a big agency requested my full manuscript a month ago and every day I check my email all nervous with a little panic attack. I know there is no use getting myself all worked up but I can't help it. 

I keep imagining what she is doing right now, like maybe she is so busy working with her other clients that my manuscript is just sitting somewhere unread. Or maybe she has volunteers who are reading it for her instead and I have to go through them first. Fuck it's killing me.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 06:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly, it just comes down to whether or not you think they make the story better or not. If trimming characters or chapters or subplots down makes a story tighter, then do it. If it needs the side story to guve a better sense if the world then keep it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 06:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, being a Writers' Workshops killed my love for reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 30 minute lessons first involve a capella warma ups, including doing an annoying "ehhhhhh" sound to find a stronger tone. And then I sing a "warm up" (not too high) song I have been practicing, either On My Own from Les Mis or Don't Cry for Me Argentina, and then harder stuff like (and a couple opera singers here criticized it) O Mio Babbino Caro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still sound very childish and I am an adult, is it just a weird combination of thin vocal cords + weird mouth shape? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh your voice is very pretty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 28/F 2 years of choir, 2 months (almost 3) of voice lessons. Singing with a different technique from before.

Don't Cry for Me Argentina
http://vocaroo.com/i/s1ZJy1K6opQU

And me redoing O Mio Babbino Caro: http://vocaroo.com/i/s0l8dfKhMRP6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do :( I just like looking at pics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do some in 3rd person and some in 1st, depending on how important it is to see things from their perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When female authors use gender ambiguous names, doesn't the About the Author section give away the real gender using pronouns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering how it works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can give it a straight-up name and have your publisher decide for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harry Potter fanfiction. Look for an R rated pairing, maybe Harry/Voldemort.

But on a more serious level, please don't write rape/abuse scenes for shock value. First of all, there are actual victims of rape or people who know victims of rape who would not want to see something like that. Second of all, it's kind of trashy to make that entertainment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bounced around, but people who have read my writing say I do have a distinct style that is still noticeable criss genre. Stephen King is a bouncer. Many of them are, actually. JK Rowling is an in-your-face example post Harry Potter (although definitely not as successful as Robert Whatshisface). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 06:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Join a writers critique group. Check for local ones at meetup.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 06:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who finally sucked it up and took lessons after years of singing on my own, I find that my teacher notices bad habits I have been doing for years without noticing. For example, I don't position my voice exactly where it should be resonating. Having a teacher watch you and point stuff out every time you are doing it wrong gives you a new perspective that you may not have before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So no one wants erotica. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one's slick as Gaston no one's quick as Gaston no one's goddamn sexy as Gaston!

Oh wait, in literature? Probably the villainess for Scorpia in the Alex Rider series. Forgot her name but she is beautiful, classy, smart, and so so evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you can sound really different when you are singing different genres. Especially when you do head voice for opera and chest voice for pop.

Favorite example is Kristin Chenoweth going back and forth in a single song:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jBJn4BHtqqY
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is my exact salary. I am 28, female, and rent a room off Craigslist for $850 a month (Southern California).

I shop at Grocery Outlet like the cheap bastard I am. My favorite shirts are from Kohl's and Target. Jeans are nicer, Nordstrom, but that's because a good pair of jeans will last years longer and be so much more comfortable/flattering.

Other than the fact I take private voice lessons, I live on the basics. The rest of my money I save so that one day I can buy a house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading Pavarotti's autobiography where he tells his parents he wants to be an opera singer and they tell him they will support him until he is 30, and that the only concern they have was whether he would be disappointed if he didn't make it. Compared that to how my crazy Chinese tiger parents reacted at my decision to be a Creative Writing major. Got so upset I put the book down for a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who talk about that novel they will write one day, having never written a single page </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blow whatever savings you have. Travel. Hell, get lost exploring a rainforest, what's the worst that could happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you date someone you are not physically attracted to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went on a date today with someone from over the internet and I have mixed feelings. Not attracted to the guy physically and we made so-so conversation. I don't know if I should go on another date with him or not.

What do you think? If I am not sure then I shouldn't have a second date, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask them whatthey like to do for fun, and then "do you go on your own or with friends?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My middle school science teacher did preach that and he got in trouble with the school district multiple times because of it but he was adamant.

None of us did anything, I remember just ignoring him and doodling in my notebooks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Chinese relatives do not understand why The Walking Dead is so popular. They saw a bit of the show, turned to me, and asked what was wrong with my people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair she would be the oldest even if the daughter were alive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds more like he had depression, not a game addiction on its own </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm this has never occured to me before. Maybe you are right - I thought it was a plagiarism defense "We couldn't have plagiarized, we only had the first 50 pages!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 01:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spartacus. The show picked up after episode 3, I would have quit if I didnt read reviews on imdb about how it got better. Turns out the show director had to fight the network for creative control and finally won out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know why literary agents ask for partials when they could ask for the full? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 01:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not talking about the default 5 to 10 sample pages they ask for with the query, but the formal request for partials after they have already seen your sample pages and query. To me it makes more sense for them to ask for the full so that they won't have to make another request if they like your stuff.

Anyone know why agents do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, but meh I am technically doing well on paper but overall I am not okay :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't max level yet but I believe it was something like "my shadowbolt crits for 4500" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much dps they could do on World of Warcraft. It was a guy trying to impress me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I am going to meet someone online from a dating site so I don't know if we will click or not in person, just being prepared. I think a dinner date may be too formal in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A toy robot that had a colorful screen and made robot noises as it moved. I remembered crying and running when it got turned on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys: if a woman went out on a date with you but didn't feel a connection, what is the best way for her to let you know? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could also be your hairstyle. Maybe you have a harsh hairstyle and could soften it with bangs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No but once my mom chased me out into the backyard swinging a wooden rod at my head, I kept catching it and letting go when she swung. Finally when she kept swinging it at me I caught it and wouldnt let it go so she stormed back i to the house and started chucking hardcover books in my direction.

Mainland Chinese mom, she is 63 now.

Edit: Actually when I was little I remember hitting my dad on the arm because he wouldn't stop grabbing at me when he was drunk. He got angry and said how dare I hit him and he slapped me across the face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I majored in Creative Writing. Graduated with no job lined up, moved back in with my mom who screamed at me for being a failure every day (and since she worked at home and I couldn't find a job that was pretty much once every hour I was awake. I had to sit at my desk and stare at a computer looking for jobs, not allowed to get up. If I stood up to stretch and the chair moved on the hardwood floor, my mom would hear it from the other room and demand why I got up.

Went on for 6 months, got a mental breakdown, went for a long walk in the rain, posted about this a couple times before here. Eventually my dad in China (parents are divorced) offered to pay for me to study abroad and I was so desperate to get away from my mom that I took the offer even though I had no desire to study Chinese in mainland china.

But the program was good - there are lots of job opportunities for native English teachers so first I tutored little Chinese kids, then I taught writing weekly reports to software engineers, and finally I took a job working for a mobile game company as an English localization editor. I studied/worked in China for 3 years, then moved back to the US and got a job proofreading manuals since I got some work experience. I got promoted from within the company by volunteering constantly for more work, and learned lots of programs on the job. Now I am a data visualization expert/salesforce admin for my company. I am 28 now.

Oh and I am not on speaking terms with my mom anymore. She did some fucked up stuff to me over the years that could have gotten her put in jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
