<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5171</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically, their human overlords can harvest about 1,680 per day.  The macaques' coconuts belong to us.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice.  I wonder where Orlando studied.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meaning that even the dumbest Kiwis are smarter than the brightest Australians?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Home result for "Is Conan Gay?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironic considering she'd have been happy to have crumbs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do you hate your parents? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit is dumb like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but they probably wouldn't have made a movie about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do you hate and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve Buscemi 9/11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 03:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 02:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't tell me what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah.  Quite strange. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austrian Authorities Seek Hitler Double Seen Around Birthplace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Magic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The three types of people in a bar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not above and beyond.  It's an unreasonable demand.  If your sweetheart wanted you to shoot yourself, should you go above and beyond for her?  Stop trying to frame it like it's part of your duty in a relationship, that's it's a give and take.  There are some things you shouldn't have to give, and partners should ask those things of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're completely wrong.  I'm not going to pretend to be someone I'm not or take an interest in something I'm not interested in just to answer a question she has of me.  And I wouldn't expect her to either.  I think it's ridiculous that you feel that's part of a healthy relationship.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with her not having a favorite team?  If she knows nothing about football, but I ask her a question about it, is she expected to learn?   You seem to be suggesting it's her duty to study something she has no interest in just to appease my inquiries.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we sure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you think when I ask my girlfriend her favorite team, I want her to answer with my favorite team?  That's ridiculous *and* unhealthy.

They're not asking about *their* tastes.  They're asking about *my* tastes.  And I don't care.  If it was about their tastes, they wouldn't need to ask me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally have no opinion.  I am indifferent.  Any option is equally valid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll set them down for a long talk about how I have nothing to offer in the way of fashion advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nonsensical!  I can give it thought, but that doesn't change the answer.  They look the same to me in whatever they're wearing.  I literally do not care, not out of laziness but out of the simple fact that it does not matter to me one iota.  They look the same in a red shirt as they do in a blue shirt.  

The fact that you and people like you think that apathy can't be a valid answer is ridiculous.  If I flipped it on them and demanded them to pick a favorite football team, would that not be equally ridiculous?  Should I be mad at them for not being able to tell me who would make a better starting quarterback?  If I ask them what team I should bet on, and they tell me "Whichever you think is best", should I demand they make a choice for me, one which I will be sure to hold them accountable for when the game is over?

I would hope not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're exactly like them.  So how would I get you to shut up about it and stop asking me?  You seem insistent on me having an opinion, when I seriously see no difference between a red bracelet or a blue bracelet other than the fact that yes they are different colors.  How are colors inherently better than any other colors?  Isn't it entirely dependent on what you wear it with?  And isn't that subject to change regularly?  How am I supposed to be expected to tell you which I like best when I am completely apathetic to both equally?  I like them the same, as in I don't care for either, which isn't to say that I dislike them both.  

How can you not understand that?  How do I get it through to people like you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
