<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5471</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Choke, by Chuck Palahniuk** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 01:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first book I read in my freshman year was "A Portrait of an Artist as a Young Man" by James Joyce. The ending is powerful and gave me this feeling that I, just like Stephen, was about to embark on a journey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My old university's library used to have give away these bookmarks with "The Sea off Suruga Province from Fuji Sanjurokkei" by Ando, Hiroshige. (http://www.artic.edu/aic/collections/citi/images/standard/WebLarge/WebImg_000029/79528_434478.jpg). I took about 20 of them and use them in all my books.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Certain Book Binding/Print Preferences? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 02:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am wondering if I am alone in my certain preferences when it comes to book bindings and print types. I really like when books are the white Bantam Book binding (for example https://www.google.com/search?q=bantam+book+paperback rlz=1CAACAG_enUS691US691 espv=2 biw=1366 bih=631 source=lnms tbm=isch sa=X ved=0ahUKEwi94OXHm9HOAhUDox4KHboeDMEQ_AUIBygC#tbm=isch q=bantam+book+paperback+hesse imgrc=E7PKy8KSm02BpM%3A). I also really like it when the print is larger and there are fewer words on a page. Also the Library of America hardcover editions are amazing. So, before I embarrass myself anymore... does anyone have these preferences and if so what are they?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 01:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For #3, To Have and Have Not by Ernest Hemingway takes place in Key West and Cuba and involves a lot of sailing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 01:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear Freakonomics is good. Most economics books are pretty dense and the famous ones such as Wealth of Nations by Adam Smith are outdated. Keynes and Marx are interesting in the sense that their theories still influence modern economics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 23:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pnin by Vladimir Nabokov. A very short and funny book from one of the greats that is often overlooked.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I read Nietzsche I read him out loud. I always find myself yelling by the end of the section. While I do not necessarily agree with everything he writes, I think his writing is full of power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 16:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Why I am Not a Christian and other essays on religion and related subjects, by Bertrand Russell**
and
**Demian, by Hermann Hesse** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
