<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2737</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a quick trip to half price books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 09:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 09:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems about right, Gatsby was pretty short and Frankenstein isn't too long either.

Both good choices though, Frankenstein is my personal favorite book of all time ^^. Just check the books to make sure they're not abridged, I know Count of Monte Cristo gets cut down a lot, so if you ever go for that one, remember it's around 1300 pages not 800 lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 08:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metamorphosis is amazing, and I just read The yellow wallpaper and that was good. Clive Barker books of blood are good and Stephen King's short stories are good.

I really like short stories when I read them, but I have this weird thing where I don't feel like they're real books, idk why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 08:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't quite remember what part 160 pages would be at, but I know part 2 of the book was a lot of build up and then part 3 took it home for me. But it is also later in the book when more stuff with the sand worms start happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Way to be subtle Reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 08:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 07:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell me where anywhere in my post is there a real name, a username, or a profile pic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The yellow wallpaper questions....spoilers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished this and boy was it amazing. I get that the story is about her being trapped and having a mental breakdown, and I'm wondering, was the ending left open ended for the reader to experience the mental breakdown as well leaving them unsure of what exactly happened?

To me, I think she hangs herself and it's her shadow creeping around the room. Because in the beginning of the story she talks about this being "dead paper" so I figured she's dead telling the story. 

But then I also think she just accepts the room and becomes one with it but also being free.

But then I think she's just walking around the room, but if that's the case, she can't get past the bed to circle the room, so thats why I think she's dead because her shadow can fit nicely in the corners and what not.

So...I'm confused, but it was an awesome read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> War and Peace, Anthony Briggs version, errors in the text? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering if anyone else has found errors in the text, now I'm not a smart man lol, but I've noticed little things here and there and there was one page, I don't remember which, which had several errors. I feel like this book was edited just fine for the most part, but some of it feels like they might have just kinda given up for the day. 


Page 430.

Denisov clapped him on the shoulder, and started pacing rapidly up and down the room without looking at Rostov, something he often did at times of high emotion. 'Oh weally,' [*she*] said, 'you Wostovs are such a cwazy bweed,' and Rostov could see that Denisov had tears in his eyes. 


Now that's just a small example, but Denisov being called a she took me out of the story. There's many more examples I've come along while reading, but this one is just where I'm at in the book. 



Has anyone else noticed this w/ this edition? Is there a way to let the publisher know, would they care? 


Also I find this kinda funny because I haven't actually met someone who has read War and Peace, so it makes me think maybe the editors didn't read it either. Though that's a bit of an exaggeration since it's like 1400 pages they're editing and people do make mistakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 6 darlings, watercolour, 11x17, bristol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 09:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imajica is actually the next book I'm going to read once get done with what I'm on right now (war and peace).

Me and a couple co workers are gonna get through the whole thing together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear god I wish, XD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should have that story in Cabal. I'm literally pumped for all the reading, Clive Barker is a beast in what I've read from him so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely in my list, I'm reading all the stuff leading to Scarlet Gospels.

Hellbound Heart,
Great and Secret Show,
Everville,
Scarlet Gospels.

I think that's the right order.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what's up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just printed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this in a Clive Barker book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Stephen King bookmark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The dark man, charcoal, 11x14, toned paper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 09:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about the confusion, this wasn't supposed to be another warrioress picture, this was supposed to be another fantasy themed picture, more of a seductive elven woman.

And yes, she's mostly nude, because right now I'm focusing on retraining myself in figure study. Also this picture is supposed to give into the stereotype that fantasy art is supposed to be pointy ears and boobs, the title "Too long without a woman", is a play on the fact that people believe nerdy guys draw sexy women because they can't get girlfriends. 

I posted this in fantasy because, I'm working on improving my artwork and the feedback I get from fantasy is much better than the feedback I get from art, and also because I'm trying to work on doing fantasy artwork, although it may be lite themed in this picture.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 09:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently posted a warrioress picture, was told I had my proportions off, here is another attempt at fantasy art, trying to up my drawing skills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] "Too long without a woman", charcoal,18x24, newsprint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 09:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Too long without a woman", charcoal, 18x24, newsprint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 09:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck, I couldn't do an e-reader, I know I wouldn't use it, I'd buy too many books on there, and it'd be just like the television, I'd start a show/book, lose interest and flip to the next channel. I did the same thing when I played videogames, I'd play my physical stuff but none of the digital stuff, I didn't feel it was real, plus I get tired of looking at screens. 

For me, with a real book, I guess I feel since I went out, and purchased the book, and am physically holding it, that I've mentally committed myself to reading it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not Clive Barker?

Also, came to see Murakami, was not disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Jungle by Upton Sinclair, was under the impression it was about slaughterhouses, come to find out it's socialist propaganda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 08:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm always looking for the book Come Closer by Sara Gran, but I never find it, so I just try to build my Murakami collection, or Richard Matheson. 

Also I never read the synopsis, I don't like knowing anything about the book, I just go off of, if the author is supposed to be really good, suggestions made by other ppl, things I've read on here, or lists I've seen..etc.. 

For example, idk anything about Elantris and I just started that the other day, and it's freaking amazing. I just knew Brandon Sanderson was supposed to be an amazing high fantasy writer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 08:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You read Count of Monte Cristo? I loved that book and didn't want it to end.

Now War and Peace on the other hand, I'm taking very slow, and I'm actually stopping to read other books in my little breaks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 08:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am legend by Richard Matheson, after reading it I was upset because I waited so long to read it because the movie was garbage, but the book was fantastic and I have no idea what that movie was supposed to be.

Also American Psycho, it made me cringe a lot later in the book, but I also laughed so much reading that, and I found myself truly concerned about Patrick Bateman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was told The Stand was one of Stephen King's best, I didn't really like it that much, too much politics, not enough end of the world, it makes me nervous for The Road and Swan Song </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually just went to half price books and picked up book 1 and 2 of Mistborn. But what I've read so far of Elantris is pretty awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 00:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually going to get the first Mistborn book but opted for this one instead, I thought I'd try a stand alone novel before starting a series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never read Sanderson before, or much high fantasy, picked up Elantris </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First chapter blew me away with how drawn in it made me. Pretty excited to sink my teeth into this book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to redo this here in the next couple weeks, after looking at it and some fantasy art sketches, I really need to bump up my drawing game. Also I'm going to use your advice on making it larger format, there was more to the cat I wanted to show. Unfortunately fantasy art isn't something I've done before, and I tried to do this whole thing without reference photos, and it came out pretty ok imo, but it can be better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm leaving this as a pencil sketch, I really need to pump up my drawing game, then I plan on redoing this and adding watercolor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, lol, I'm working on my drawing skills, I'll have something else up in a couple days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scantily clad women and big monsters, I figured it a staple in fantasy artwork 

Or lemme rephrase, I figure it's a classic combo, ex. Frank Franzetta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it is either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope this is ok here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
