<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6396</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How community digs can inspire the next generation of archaeologists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Digging Deeper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atacama Desert may have harbored lakes, wetlands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm really disappointed that Hallmark didn't go all out for ornaments for the 50th anniversary of Star Trek </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, we got the faux-gold plated Enterprise, but it would have been really nice to see a huge slew of ships from all the series and movies out, too. That way people who like to collect them (like my dad) have a chance to flesh out their collections if they missed a year or are unwilling to pay $100+ for an ornament. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's celebrate US archaeology's best kept secret </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did the tradition of making gingerbread houses begin? Why did the tradition become so popular around Christmas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 11:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone's got a mouth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 05:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jordan lead codices not modern forgeries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 01:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human blood, organs, and a surprising virus detected in ancient pottery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sharks in the jungle: real and imagined sea monsters of the Maya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the ancient Maya brought sharks to the jungle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the ancient Maya brought sharks to the jungle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the ancient Maya brought sharks to the jungle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the ancient Maya brought sharks to the jungle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 17th Century Variola Virus Reveals the Recent History of Smallpox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Virus found in child mummy suggests recent rise of deadly smallpox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Development of new techniques makes it possible to date Australian Aboriginal rock art </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look Into the Eyes of a Neolithic Man in This Reconstruction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's terracotta warriors to return to UK for first time in nearly a decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers find overwhelming evidence of malaria's existence 2,000 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aerial photo of the Great Pyramid of Cholula. Nearly twice as large as the Khufu pyramid in Giza. Local and state governments are threatening the structure with urban development. Built between 90 to 600 AD. Puebla, Mexico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aerial photo of the Great Pyramid of Cholula. Nearly twice as large as the Khufu pyramid in Giza. Local and state governments are threatening the structure with urban development. 90 to 600 AD. Puebla, Mexico [1024x752] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cholula pyramid and the fight for its preservation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cholula pyramid and the fight for its preservation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cholula pyramid and the fight for its preservation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cholula pyramid and the fight for its preservation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cholula pyramid and the fight for its preservation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cholula pyramid and the fight for its preservation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cholula pyramid and the fight for its preservation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Are you interested in the lost civilizations? I might have some interesting topics that are poorly researched and lack citations for you and perpetuate commonly held false assumptions on Maya history." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude comes in /r/ancientcivilizations, another history sub where people try to push pseudo-history and pseudo-archaeology, to try and [peddle his blog](https://np.reddit.com/r/AncientCivilizations/comments/5fy4t3/are_you_interested_in_the_lost_civilizations_i/). So, I take a look at it. What do I see? [A topic on the Maya](http://www.thelostcivilizations.info/2016/11/06/mayan-culture-origins-hieroglyphics-documentary/)? Let's see what he's gotten wrong.

Edit: this isn't the [first time](https://np.reddit.com/r/AncientCivilizations/comments/5bffkh/here_are_some_facts_about_the_mayan_civilization/) I've corrected this user

---
    
 the Olmecs, the oldest culture in Mesoamerica

There are several cultures that are older or contemporaneous to the Olmec. The Mokaya (Blake and Clark 1999), Capacha (Kelly 1980; Mountjoy 1994) , Matanchen (Mountjoy 1970, 2000; Mountjoy and Claassen 2005), El Opeo (Oliveros 1970, 1974), and Monte Alto cultures (Parsons and Jenson 1965; Demarest, Switsur, and Berger 1982), for example.

 Olmecs settled along the Gulf of Mexico and began building great cities of stone and brick. 

They had dirt mounds (Cyphers 1997; Diehl 981). The Red Palace has some basalt columns, but most of it is dirt.

 Though no one knows where the Olmecs came from, nor what happened to them, they lay the foundation for all the future civilizations in Mesoamerica.

They came from Archaic populations in the region (Wilkerson 1981). They are the culmination of centuries of cultural development in the region. They didn't come from anywhere else but where they already lived.

As for where they went, they continued to develop culturally and became the Epi-Olmec (Pool 2000).

They also did not lay down the foundation for all Mesoamerican civilizations. West Mexican civilizations, for example, diverge greatly from their eastern cousins. There is little to no Olmec material that has been recovered in West Mexico despite no physical barriers preventing people from moving and trading. West Mexico simply drew upon their own ancestral cultures such as Capacha and El Opeo.

 important cultural elements of the region were disseminated such as writing, mathematics, astronomy and the development of the calendar; all of which the Maya would refine.

It's somewhat debatable since the Olmec didn't write any of this. There's the Cascajal Block, but it hasn't been confirmed to be writing exactly. It could be writing, looks like writing to some, but cannot be read (Magni 2008). And it looks very different from Zapotec, Maya, or Epi-Olmec writing. The oldest Long Count date comes from Tres Zapotes, that's true, but it dates to the Late Formative long after what we would consider Olmec.

 The Plumed Serpent god  Kukulkan (also known as Gucamatz) was the most popular deity among the Maya. 

We don't refer to the feathered serpent at Teotihuacan as Quetzalcoatl or Kukulkan because we don't know what Teotihuacanos called it. How is the feather serpent the consort of the Goddess? Where has that been established?

 During this time the great urban centers rose across the land and the Maya numbered in the millions

You put this in the El Tajin section, but mention the Maya. The Maya did not inhabit El Tajin. And you need to provide a source on the population estimate if you're going to say millions.

 The very important ball game which came to be known as Poc-a-Toc was developed and more ball courts have been found in and around the city of El Tajin than anywhere else in the region. 

While El Tajin may have had its own variation of the Mesoamerican ball game, keep in mind that ball courts have been found that predate El Tajin. The Teuchitlan culture, for example, built ballcourts beginning in the Late Formative to Early Classic periods. 

 The Classic Maya Period: 250-950 CE  This is the era which saw the consolidation of power in the great cities of the Yucatec Maya such as Chichen Itza and Uxmal. 

You should make a note that both Chichen Itza and Uxmal were founded in the Late Classic (600 AD, Chichen - 850 AD - Uxmal) and survived until the early Postclassic (13th century, Chichen - 1100 AD, Uxmal)
        
 Direct cultural influences may be seen, in some sites, from the Olmecs and the Zapotecs and the cultural values of Teotihuacan and El Tajin

What are these influences? You need to establish that. Especially with the Zapotec, El Tajin, and Olmec.

 This period was the height of the Maya civilization in which they perfected mathematics, astronomy, architecture and the visual arts and also refined and perfected the calendar.

How did they perfect these things? And how did they differ from the Preclassic? Or Postclassic?

 The oldest date recorded in this era is on Stele 29 in the city of Tikal (292 CE)

El Bal (Ochoa and Lee 1983; Marcus 1976) and Takalik Abaj (Riese 1988; Stuart 2004) both have older dates and both are Maya

 The Post-Classic Period: 950-1524 CE  At this time the great cities of the Maya were abandoned.

Some were, some weren't. The Postclassic thrived, as well (Chase 1992; Chase and Chase 2006; Masson, Hare, and Peraza Lope 2006; Sabloff 2007; Jones 1998). It may not be as well known and published as the Classic period, but it is just as important if not more so since the Postclassic Maya were who the Spanish encountered

 The Toltecs, a new tribe in the region, took over the vacant urban centers and re-populated them. At this time, Tula and Chichen-Itza became dominant cities in the region.

The Toltecs were not in the Maya region. And they did not "take over" anything. The topic is still hotly debated and part of it is because there is this is a common misconception based on early archaeological work where people visited Tula before they visited Chichen. They saw some similarities between the two and concluded Tula influenced Chichen, but did so without any sort of dating. Radiocarbon dating, however, suggests sometime more complicated. The sites are contemporaneous in terms of architectural style and Chichen may actually be a little bit earlier (Kowalski and Kristan-Graham 2007). So we don't know who influenced who. It could very well have been Chichen on Tula. Both scenarios, though, are unlikely. The Epiclassic was a period of upheaval and change. People latched onto whatever they could to secure power and part of that power stemmed from art and architecture. There are so many common elements in this period that we refer to this art style,as the International style.

 the widely popular conception that the Maya were driven from their cities by the Spanish Conquest is erroneous as the cities were already vacant by the time of the Spanish invasion (in fact, the Spanish conquerors had no idea the natives they found in the region were responsible for the enormous complexes of the cities). The Quiche Maya were defeated at the Battle of Utatlan in 1524 CE and this date traditionally marks the end of the Maya Civilization.

One sentence you say the cities were abandoned, but the next you say a battle took place at Q'umarkaj (Utatlan) which is a city. I'm afraid you are following the popular misconception that there were no Maya cities occupied when there were. It took many years of fighting for the Spanish to pacify the Maya region. The last Maya city to fall was Nojpeten and it did not fall until 1697 (Jones 1998).

 to reach the paradise of Tamoanchan (`place of the misty sky) where beautiful flowers bloomed.

Tomoanchan is Aztec and Postclassic, not Maya and Classic. You are blurring the lines between peoples and time periods. They are not one in the same, but distinct from one another.

 The great religious book of the Quiche Maya, the Popol-Vuh

That was written in 1701. You have to recognize that it is not a Classic period document, though it may have earlier roots. There are elements of the Popol Vuh that can be traced back further into Classic and even Preclassic artwork. But we cannot verify that the story stayed the same (unless someone finds a long Preclassic/Classic inscription or a book), we can only identify shared iconography.

 It has long been believed that the losing team (or the captain of the losing team) would be killed at the end of the match but recent advances in deciphering the Mayan glyphs, together with archaeological evidence, suggests it may have been the winning team or the winning captain who was given the honor of a quick death and instant passage to paradise.

There's no evidence for either outcome. Either way, you should provide specific sources on this statement

 This is not quite correct, however, as glyphs at many ball courts, Chichen Itza to name only one, ***could be interpreted***

Could be interpreted to be sensational and drive up clicks. Come on, mate. You just said researchers say there is no evidence for this.

 Only three books of the Maya escaped the conflagration at Mani: The Madrid Codex, The Dresden Codex, and The Paris Codex

And the Grolier Codex

 The Haab and the Tzolkin work together, like gears interlocking in a machine

That's just how Westerners visualize this. The Maya did not depict their calendars like that at all

 As the long count calendar begins 11 August 3114 BCE, it goes into its next cycle (known as a Baktun) on 21 December 2012 CE.

December 21, 2012 marked the beginning of the 13th b'ak'tun. That means the Long Count had undergone 12 previous cycles. December wasn't the first nor will it be the last.
    
 The claim that the Maya somehow vanished, simply because their cities were found abandoned, is not only inaccurate but insulting to the over six million Maya who carry on the traditions of their ancestors.

But that is exactly what you did when you glossed over the Postclassic and colonial periods.

---

***tl;dr*** - second time this week I've raged over some Mesoamerican bad history. It feels nice

---

References in order as they appear

* Blake, Michael, and John E. Clark. "The emergence of hereditary inequality: The case of Pacific coastal Chiapas, Mexico." Pacific Latin America in Prehistory (1999): 55-73.

* Kelly, Isabel. Ceramic sequence in Colima: Capacha, an early phase. Vol. 37. University of Arizona Press, 1980.

* Mountjoy, Joseph B. "Capacha: una cultura enigmtica del Occidente de Mxico." Arqueologa Mexicana 2.9 (1994): 39-42.

* Mountjoy, Joseph B. 1970. Prehispanic Culture History and Cultural Contact on the Southern Coast of Nayarit, Mexico. Unpublished PhD dissertation, Department of Anthropology, Southern Illinois University, Carbondale.

* Mountjoy, Joseph B. 2000. Prehispanic Cultural Development along the Southern Coast of West Mexico. In Greater Mesoamerica: The Archaeology of West and Northwest Mexico, edited by Michael S. Foster and Shirley Gorenstein, pp. 81106. University of Utah Press, Salt Lake City

* Mountjoy, Joseph B., and Cheryl P. Claassen. 2005. Middle Formative Diet and Seasonality on the Central Coast of Nayarit, Mexico. In Archaeology without Limits: Papers in Honor of Clement W. Meighan, edited by Brian D. Dillon and Matthew A. Boxt, pp. 267282. Labyrinthos, Lancaster.

* Oliveros, Jos Arturo. "Nuevas exploraciones en El Opeo, Michoacn." The archaeology of west Mexico (1974): 182-201.

* Oliveros, Jos Arturo. Excavacin de dos tumbas en El Opeo, Michoacn. Diss. Tesis de Maestra. Instituto Nacional de Antropologa e Historia-Universidad Nacional Autnoma de Mxico. Mxico, 1970.

* Parsons, Lee A., and Peter S. Jenson. "Boulder Sculpture on the Pacific Coast of Guatemala." Archaeology 18.2 (1965): 132-144.

* Demarest, Arthur, Roy Switsur, and Rainer Berger. "The Dating and Cultural Associations of the" Potbellied" Sculptural Style: New Evidence from Western El Salvador." American Antiquity (1982): 557-571.

* Cyphers, Ann. "Olmec Architecture at San Lorenzo." Olmec to Aztec: Settlement patterns in the ancient gulf lowlands (1997): 98-114.

* Diehl, Richard A. "Olmec architecture: a comparison of San Lorenzo and La Venta." The Olmec and Their Neighbors, Dumbarton Oaks, Washington, DC(1981): 69-82.

* Wilkerson, S. Jeffrey K. "The northern Olmec and pre-Olmec frontier on the Gulf Coast." The Olmec and their Neighbors, Dumbarton Oaks, Washington, DC (1981): 181-194.

* Pool, Christopher A. "From Olmec to Epi-Olmec at Tres Zapotes, Veracruz, Mexico." Studies in the History of Art 58 (2000): 136-153

* Magni, Caterina. "Olmec Writing. The Cascajal Block: New Perspectives." Arts and Cultures 9 (2008): 64-81.

* Ochoa, Lorenzo; Lee, Thomas A., eds. (1983). Antropologa e historia de los mixe-zoques y mayas (in Spanish). Mexico: Universidad Nacional Autnoma de Mxico, Instituto de Investigaciones Filolgicas, Centro de Estudios Mayas. pp. 191, 194

* Marcus, Joyce (1976). "The origins of Mesoamerican writing" (PDF). Annual Review of Anthropology. Annual Reviews Inc. 5: 4954

* Riese, Berthold (1988). "Epigraphy of the southeast zone in relation to other parts of the Maya realm". In Boone, Elizabeth Hill; Willey, Gordon Randolph. The Southeast Classic Maya Zone: Papers from the Dumbarton Oaks Symposium, 6th and 7th October, 1984. Washington, D.C.: Dumbarton Oaks, Trustees for Harvard University. p. 68. 

* Stuart, David (2004). "Chapter 11: The beginnings of the Copan dynasty: A review of the hieroglyphic and historical evidence". In Bell, Ellen E.; Canuto, Marcello A.; Sharer, Robert J. Understanding Early Classic Copan. Philadelphia: University of Pennsylvania Museum of Archaeology. p. 219. 

* [Chase, Diane Z. "Postclassic Maya elites: ethnohistory and archaeology." Mesoamerican elites: An archaeological assessment (1992): 118-134.](http://www.caracol.org/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/dchase92.pdf)

* Chase, Diane Z., and Arlen F. Chase. "Framing the Maya collapse." After Collapse, The Regeneration of Complex Societies (2006): 168-187.

* Masson, Marilyn A., Timothy S. Hare, and C. Peraza Lope. "Postclassic Maya society regenerated at Mayapn." After collapse: The regeneration of complex societies (2006): 188-207.
* [Sabloff, Jeremy A. "It depends on how we look at things: new perspectives on the postclassic period in the Northern Maya lowlands." Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society 151.1 (2007): 11-26.](https://www.amphilsoc.org/sites/default/files/proceedings/151102.pdf)

* Jones, Grant D. The conquest of the last Maya kingdom. Stanford University Press, 1998.

* Kowalski, Jeff Karl, and Cynthia Kristan-Graham. Twin Tollans: Chichn Itz, Tula, and the epiclassic to early postclassic Mesoamerican world. Dumbarton Oaks, 2007. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ice Age hunters destroyed forests throughout Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Circular temple to god of wind uncovered in Mexico City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Circular temple to god of wind uncovered in Mexico City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Descubren templo dedicado a Ehcatl-Quetzalcatl en Tlatelolco </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human ancestor 'Lucy' was a tree climber, new evidence suggests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis of Iron Age ceramics suggests complex pattern of Eastern Mediterranean trade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Queen Nefertari's Dismembered Legs Have Been Found </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer turns off after playing Witcher 3 for 30+ minutes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last week I had a problem where I would turn my computer on, but it would turn off after a second or so. Then it would turn back on and turn back off. To get it to stop, I had to flip the power supply switch in the back. I followed [this topic](http://superuser.com/questions/556288/my-computer-doesnt-start-it-is-stuck-in-a-turn-on-turn-off-loop) and everything worked out well. It seem that clearing the CMOS did the trick. 

I brougt Witcher 3 on Friday and played it on Friday, Saturday, and Sunday with no problems. I tried to play it yesterday, but my computer turned off twice. I figured it was the high winds outside messing with the power (since the lights sometimes dimmed). 

Today I've been using it all day with no problem surfing the web and doing some school work. After dinner I decided to play some more Witcher 3. I got about a half hour in and everything shut off. I turned it back on and the monitor showed black and flickered several times before turning off again. I can't blame this on the wind since there is no wind today. The monitor did this before, but turning the monitor off and then on would display the login screen. 

Edit: I have two monitors. The one I use the most has an HDMI cable, the other a VGA cable. It's just outputting to the VGA monitor instead of the HDMI one for whatever reason until the login starts up. Then it switches back.

I've opened up my computer to make sure nothing is loose from when I put everything back together and everything seems fine. 

So what's going on with my computer?

Windows 7

MSI H77MA-G43 LGA 1155 Intel H77 SATA 6Gb/s USB 3.0 Micro ATX Intel Motherboard with UEFI BIOS

MSI GeForce GTX 660 DirectX 11 N660-2GD5/OC 2GB 192-Bit GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 x16 HDCP Ready SLI Support Video Card

CORSAIR CX series CX500 500W 80 PLUS BRONZE Active PFC ATX12V   EPS12V Power Supply

Intel Core i5-3350P Ivy Bridge Quad-Core 3.1GHz (3.3GHz Turbo) LGA 1155 69W BX80637i53350P Desktop Processor

Wintec Value 8GB (2 x 4GB) 240-Pin DDR3 SDRAM DDR3 1333 (PC3 10666) Desktop Memory Model 3VH13339U9-8GK

Built in fall 2013. No issues since I first built it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer turns off after playing Witcher 3 for 30+ minutes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last week I had a problem where I would turn my computer on, but it would turn off after a second or so. Then it would turn back on and turn back off. To get it to stop, I had to flip the power supply switch in the back. I followed [this topic](http://superuser.com/questions/556288/my-computer-doesnt-start-it-is-stuck-in-a-turn-on-turn-off-loop) and everything worked out well. It seem that clearing the CMOS did the trick. 

I brougt Witcher 3 on Friday and played it on Friday, Saturday, and Sunday with no problems. I tried to play it yesterday, but my computer turned off twice. I figured it was the high winds outside messing with the power (since the lights sometimes dimmed). 

Today I've been using it all day with no problem surfing the web and doing some school work. After dinner I decided to play some more Witcher 3. I got about a half hour in and everything shut off. I turned it back on and the monitor showed black and flickered several times before turning off again. I can't blame this on the wind since there is no wind today. The monitor did this before, but turning the monitor off and then on would display the login screen. 

Edit: I have two monitors. The one I use the most has an HDMI cable, the other a VGA cable. It's just outputting to the VGA monitor instead of the HDMI one for whatever reason until the login starts up. Then it switches back.

I've opened up my computer to make sure nothing is loose from when I put everything back together and everything seems fine. 

So what's going on with my computer?

Windows 7

MSI H77MA-G43 LGA 1155 Intel H77 SATA 6Gb/s USB 3.0 Micro ATX Intel Motherboard with UEFI BIOS

MSI GeForce GTX 660 DirectX 11 N660-2GD5/OC 2GB 192-Bit GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 x16 HDCP Ready SLI Support Video Card

CORSAIR CX series CX500 500W 80 PLUS BRONZE Active PFC ATX12V   EPS12V Power Supply

Intel Core i5-3350P Ivy Bridge Quad-Core 3.1GHz (3.3GHz Turbo) LGA 1155 69W BX80637i53350P Desktop Processor

Wintec Value 8GB (2 x 4GB) 240-Pin DDR3 SDRAM DDR3 1333 (PC3 10666) Desktop Memory Model 3VH13339U9-8GK

Built in fall 2013. No issues since I first built it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer turns off after playing Witcher 3 for 30+ minutes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last week I had a problem where I would turn my computer on, but it would turn off after a second or so. Then it would turn back on and turn back off. To get it to stop, I had to flip the power supply switch in the back. I followed [this topic](http://superuser.com/questions/556288/my-computer-doesnt-start-it-is-stuck-in-a-turn-on-turn-off-loop) and everything worked out well. It seem that clearing the CMOS did the trick. 

I brougt Witcher 3 on Friday and played it on Friday, Saturday, and Sunday with no problems. I tried to play it yesterday, but my computer turned off twice. I figured it was the high winds outside messing with the power (since the lights sometimes dimmed). 

Today I've been using it all day with no problem surfing the web and doing some school work. After dinner I decided to play some more Witcher 3. I got about a half hour in and everything shut off. I turned it back on and the monitor showed black and flickered several times before turning off again. I can't blame this on the wind since there is no wind today. The monitor did this before, but turning the monitor off and then on would display the login screen. 

Edit: I have two monitors. The one I use the most has an HDMI cable, the other a VGA cable. It's just outputting to the VGA monitor instead of the HDMI one for whatever reason until the login starts up. Then it switches back.

I've opened up my computer to make sure nothing is loose from when I put everything back together and everything seems fine. 

So what's going on with my computer?

Windows 7

MSI H77MA-G43 LGA 1155 Intel H77 SATA 6Gb/s USB 3.0 Micro ATX Intel Motherboard with UEFI BIOS

MSI GeForce GTX 660 DirectX 11 N660-2GD5/OC 2GB 192-Bit GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 x16 HDCP Ready SLI Support Video Card

CORSAIR CX series CX500 500W 80 PLUS BRONZE Active PFC ATX12V   EPS12V Power Supply

Intel Core i5-3350P Ivy Bridge Quad-Core 3.1GHz (3.3GHz Turbo) LGA 1155 69W BX80637i53350P Desktop Processor

Wintec Value 8GB (2 x 4GB) 240-Pin DDR3 SDRAM DDR3 1333 (PC3 10666) Desktop Memory Model 3VH13339U9-8GK

Built in fall 2013. No issues since I first built it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Dakota law enforcement to block pipeline protesters' supplies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mosaic-tiled Mexican skull at Leiden museum a fake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient mound used for defense hints at walled city in Japan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Mixtec skull declared a forgery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Mixtec skull declared a forgery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Mixtec skull declared a forgery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Mixtec skull declared a forgery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New discoveries unearthed at Terracotta Warriors site </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scans locate historic secret room in walls of Gunpowder plot house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gruesome Rituals Revealed in 9,500-Year-Old Graves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 17:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pembroke Castle study uncovers possible Henry VII birthplace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video Games and Archaeology - the SAA archaeological record, volume 16, number 5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video Games and Archaeology - the SAA archaeological record, volume 16, number 5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mystery in Louisiana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video Games and Archaeology - the SAA archaeological record, volume 16, number 5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video Games and Archaeology - the SAA archaeological record, volume 16, number 5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pre-Columbian Murals and Norse Sagas Suggest zero contact between the Viking and Aztec, but Clyde Winters would have you think otherwise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 02:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our bad history in question,

http://www.ancient-origins.net/history/pre-columbian-murals-and-norse-sagas-suggest-vikings-met-aztecs-and-outcome-was-not-pretty-021084?nopaging=1

It starts off in the deep end and just wades around the bullshit. There's no testing the waters with a toe dip here before going head first in.

 Did the Vikings visit Pre-Columbian Mexico?

In short, no. But I have a feeling you are going to concoct a fantastical tale to explain to me why they did.

 The depiction of white people on Chichen Itza murals in the Temple of the Warriors probably represent Vikings

Or, and Im throwing this out there, you dont understand the conventions of Maya art and you are going to completely misinterpret things.

 There are also three traditions of the Norse Sagas that mention that in 965 or 986 Ari Marson set sail from Ireland in an attempt to reach Greenland. The story has it that Marsons ship ran into rough seas and a storm threw him off course. Within six days he had reached Mexico instead. The Eyrbggia saga and the voyage of Ari Marson may explain how the first white people got to the Yucatan.

Wheres the evidence Winters? While stories are great there needs to be some hard proof that the story is speaking the truth. And the story doesnt even describe Yucatan, the Maya, or anywhere else in Mesoamerica. HOW DO YOU KNOW THEY WENT TO YUCATAN?! There's a lot of doubt (nothing solidly Viking has been found) on the settlement at Point Rosee and that is in Newfoundland where L'Anse aux Meadows is. And you're trying to tell me these Vikings just completely missed the US Eastern seaboard, missed the Caribbean, and arrived in Yucatan in six days?

 Some researchers claim that the tribes joined the conquistadors in defeating the Aztecs because they represented a return of the white lords. However, most researchers say that this story about white lords was a myth created during the Spanish conquest. Restall wrote that: The legend of the returning lords, originated during the Spanish-Mexica war in Corts' reworking of Moctezuma's welcome speech, had by the 1550's merged with the Corts-as-Quetzalcoatl legend that the Franciscans had started spreading in the 1530s.

And yet you are going to ignore that? Really?

 Murals in the temple depict black, white, and brown people. In some of these murals one can see whites fighting and in bondage to blacks.

No, what you are seeing are people in body paint. If you took time to make note of it, you would see that the black warriors have different color faces. And that your white prisoners have many horizontal lines. Unless these black Maya were capturing mummies, one has to consider that these markings are meant to portray something other than skin color. In fact, if we look at the [mural as a whole]( http://www.celticnz.org/images/Nazca/Pre-Inca4.jpg) (sorry, cant find a large image that isnt [blurry]( https://classconnection.s3.amazonaws.com/202/flashcards/2906202/jpg/012f06c82308b10f4e916a97447dfd9c62b5360b44-142ED35F6BD76775F52.jpg)) instead of this one small part, we see white people on a building in war costumes like the black people.  You know why, Winters? Because the black figures were the ones doing the attacking. The white figures were the ones [defending](http://www.jstor.org/stable/275525?seq=1#page_scan_tab_contents). But you wouldn't understand that if you had just looked at one part of one mural and ignored everything else.

 In Esotericism of the Popol Vuh by Raphael Girard, one reads about the Dance of the Giants. This Mayan dance appears to represent a Pre-Columbian conflict between white and black people in Mexico.

 This book is quite illuminating. In it, Girard discusses the Dance of the Black Giants. The dance of the Black Giants explains the reason why the other indigenous peoples joined the Spanish in destroying the Aztec nation. Girard's description of the Dance of the Giants is startling.

If you actually take a look at the [chapter]( http://www.theosociety.org/pasadena/popolvuh/pv-16.htm) it makes no mention that these giants have white or black skin. They are merely called the White Giant and the Black Giant. If Winters was aware of anything about Mesoamerica, he may know that white and black are both [colors associated with cardinal directions]( http://www.famsi.org/research/hopkins/DirectionalPartitions.pdf).  West was black, white was north, east is red, south is yellow, and blue/green is Center.

 The Chichen Itza mural indicates that the indigenous peoples had sided with the blacks when the whites first attempted to invade Mexico. However, it later appears that they felt the black giants were arrogant and boastful and they wanted to overthrow them  even though they originally had helped defeat the Vikings.

Or you read a book about Maya spirituality and because it ties into the Popol Vuh, a Kiche document of questionable age, you think it somehow ties in with the past. While it is all well and fine to conduct ethnographic work on people to help illuminate our understanding of the past, there is no bridge between these modern Kiche practices and pre-Columbian Maya beliefs. There are no murals or painted scenes which show these giants battling one another. And the mural at Chichen is inadequate because it depicts multiple black and white figures who are not fighting as well as villagers. 

 Although many of the Indigenous peoples sided with the blacks in their battle against the white invaders in Pre-Columbian times, by the time the Spanish arrived in Mexico the black rulers, namely the Aztecs, were mistreating the other groups of Indigenous peoples.

 The Spanish described the Aztecs as follows: The people of this land are well made, rather tall than short. They are swarthy as leopards, of good manners and gestures, for the greater part very skillful, robust, and tireless, and at the same time the most moderate men known. They are very warlike and face death with the greatest resolution.

Whoa, what? When did you establish that blacks were rulers of Mexico? Just on the basis of some Maya murals at Chichen? Chichen is not Mexico. Two different locations in Mesoamerica with two different cultures and two different heritages. On top of that leap that could cross the Grand Canyon, you provide a description which in no way describe the Aztecs as black.
 Archaeological evidence, Mayan and Spanish descriptions, and pictorial evidence from the codices indicate the Aztecs may have been black people. This would not be surprising because the Paleo-Americans Luzia and Naia were also black.

I dont know how to deconstruct such a bold faced lie without writing a whole book about it. What I can say is that within Aztec art they made a distinction of what black people looked like. Within the Codex there is a scene in which Cortes is meeting two Tlaxcalan lords [while being accompanied by a black servant]( http://christinaproenza.org/BlackConquistadors.pdf). Even in the colonial period when this was made, Aztec artists made it a point to highlight how different this servants skin was from their own.

 In summary, it would appear that the character named Gavite in the Dance of the Giants represents the Spanish. The blacks defeated by Gavite were the Aztecs, who were identified by the Maya and Spanish as black and were represented in the codices as a horrible people who mistreated the other local tribes.

 The whites who landed at Chichen Itza were Vikings. The Vikings were well-known navigators that sailed to many nations in Europe, including Great Britain. They may have been sailing in the Atlantic and were mislaid by a storm until they reached Mexico.

In summary? IN SUMMARY?! You didnt even prove that the white looking figures on the mural were Vikings. You chose an arbitrary date of the occupation of Chichen that coincided with Viking exploration of Greenland and Newfoundland and used that as your proof that somehow Vikings traveled all the way south to Yucatan. This is fucking horseshit and anyone with half a brain would recognize it as such. But I guess I should have expected this from a person who makes it their life [publish pseudo-history]( https://scholar.google.com/scholar?hl=en q=clyde+winters btnG= as_sdt=1%2C23 as_sdtp=). I'm kind of surprised there was zero mention from our favorite Afrocentrist Ivan Van Sertima. Didn't think of using the worn and disproven ["Olmec were black"](http://www.unl.edu/rhames/courses/current/vansertima.pdf) card to try and bolster up your position? What a shame, it would have just added to the ridiculousness of this article.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mystery in Louisiana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 21:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mystery in Louisiana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 21:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] Found a petroglyph of a boat near Copper Harbor, Michigan. [4160x3088] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went and found some petroglyphs up near Copper Harbor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 00:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cissbury Fort 'damaged by metal detectors' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 16:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10,000-year-old remains returned to Nevada tribe's control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 14:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10,000-year-old remains returned to Nevada tribe's control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 13:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10,000-year-old remains returned to Nevada tribe's control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 13:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Altar of Miracle-Making Viking King Discovered in Norway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkeys were a major part of ancestral Pueblo life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Molasses creates a sticky situation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steep commute gave ancient Egyptian workers osteoarthritis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 14:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the archaeological review behind the Dakota Access Pipeline went wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 12:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Standing Rock Police Attack Protesters Again: He Just Smiled and Shot Both My Kneecaps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 03:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archaeological excavation unearths evidence of turkey domestication 1,500 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to climb the social ladder in ancient Rome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victorian beard craze inspired false 'mechanical' whiskers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rice farming in India much older than thought, used as 'summer crop' by Indus civilization </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 14:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I kind of wish there was a Lego Star Trek game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 21:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After playing Lego Star Wars Episode 7, there is a lot of lost potential. Even if the game was only based on the Kelvin films, I think it would be a lot fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DNA study unravels the history of the world's most produced cereal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 01:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DNA study unravels the history of the world's most produced cereal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 01:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coraza de Tula. Ritual offering of a shirt made of shells, snails, and coral. Found in the Palacio Quemado. Toltec. 650 to 900 AD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coraza de Tula. Ritual offering of a shirt made of shells, snails, and coral. Found in the Palacio Quemado. Toltec. 650 to 900 AD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Coraza de Tula. Ritual offering of a shirt made of shells, snails, and coral. Found in the Palacio Quemado. Toltec. 650 to 900 AD [2000x3000] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australias oldest piece of indigenous jewellery has been found in the Kimberleys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexican experts say original pyramid found at Chichen Itza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 04:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Autism and human evolutionary success </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tooth wear patterns suggest Paranthropus early hominins had softer diets than expected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italian archaeologists find 'world's oldest dentures' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Danes identify Aalborg bishop's 300-year-old poo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Danes identify Aalborg bishop's 300-year-old poo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexican experts say original pyramid found at Chichen Itza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 13:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egyptian giant crocodile mummy is full of surprises </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 14:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Mural fragment from Tulum. Quintana Roo, Mexico. Maya. 1200 to 1400 AD [629x600] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 13:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Novel imaging approach reveals how ancient amulet was made </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Novel imaging approach reveals how ancient amulet was made </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For First Nations people, effects of European contact are recorded in the genome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For First Nations people, effects of European contact are recorded in the genome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regional asynchronicity in dairy production and processing in early farming communities of the northern Mediterranean </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Late ArchaicEarly Formative period microbotanical evidence for potato at Jiskairumoko in the Titicaca Basin of southern Peru </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Potato domestication in the Andes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neolithic dairy production in the Mediterranean </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel to launch expedition to find more Dead Sea Scrolls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> City dwellers in Middle Ages no worse off than village dwellers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Feathered serpent relief at Xochicalco. Morelos, Mexico, 700 AD to 900 AD [1600x1063] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] The Purron Dam, a 400m x 100m x 18m earthwork dam meant to cover the Tilapa River. Puebla, Mexico. 700 BC to 300 AD [640x432] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 02:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Built by the Huns? Ancient Stone Monuments Discovered Along Caspian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Underwater Stone Age settlement mapped out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was there "ethnic strife" in early colonial Mexico (i.e. Mexica v. Tlaxcallan, Purepecha v. Mexica, Maya v. Maya)? How did Spanish authorities quell these conflicts? How did they prevent them from happening in the first place? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 12:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am reposting a question that went unanswered [last year](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/3r9bml/was_there_ethnic_strife_in_early_colonial_mexico/).

 I started reading The War for Mexico's West by Ida Altman. In the second chapter she states that Nuo de Guzmn recruited troops from central Mexico and Michoacan for his entrada into the territory that would become New Galicia (Jalisco, Zacatecas, Nayarit). Perhaps not in Guzmn's case, but in others, did internal fighting arise between these mixed regiments of formerly hostile groups? Did the Spanish keep these groups in separate camps? What prevented these groups from turning on one another in the heat of battle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Colossal stone head of La Democracia, Escuintla, Guatemala. Monte Alto culture. 1800 BC to 400 BC? [508x800] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 00:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oldest Beer Brewed from Shipwreck's 220-Year-Old Yeast Microbes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Doggerland diet discovered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Doggerland diet discovered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Digital imagery reveals secrets of 800-year-old royal book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New evidence found of human activity 1.4 million years ago at the site of Barranco Leon in Orce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret Passageway Found at Shakespeare's Theater </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remote sensing technology improves small scale archaeology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 15:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oldest Beer Brewed from Shipwreck's 220-Year-Old Yeast Microbes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 14:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oldest Beer Brewed from Shipwreck's 220-Year-Old Yeast Microbes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 14:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oldest Beer Brewed from Shipwreck's 220-Year-Old Yeast Microbes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 14:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oldest Beer Brewed from Shipwreck's 220-Year-Old Yeast Microbes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 14:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did telemarketing arise after the implementation of automatic switchboards? Or did switchboard operators play a part in the rise of telemarketing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shackle-Bound Skeleton Found in Etruscan Burial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santorini eruption: new theory says pyroclastic flows caused devastating Bronze Age tsunamis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Maya king had a luxury pleasure palace outside the city he ruled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Maya king had a luxury pleasure palace outside the city he ruled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analizan las costumbres funerarias del Michoacn prehispnico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analizan las costumbres funerarias del Michoacn prehispnico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Handwritings  amp; symbols found at Emperor Liu He's tomb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Searching for Cuba's Pre-Columbian Roots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Searching for Cuba's Pre-Columbian Roots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3,800-Year-Old 'Tableau' of Egyptian Boats Discovered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 15:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The yacatas of Tzintzuntzan, Michoacan. Tarascan empire. ~1300 to 1530 AD. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 15:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The plaster sculpture of K'inich K'an B'alaam II, eldest son of the famous king K'inich Janaab' Pakal. Recovered from Temple 14 at the site of Palenque, Chiapas, Mexico. 684 to 702 AD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 15:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The plaster sculpture of K'inich K'an B'alaam II, eldest son of the famous king K'inich Janaab' Pakal. Recovered from Temple 14 at the site of Palenque, Chiapas, Mexico. 684 to 702 AD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 15:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] The plaster sculpture of K'inich K'an B'alaam II, eldest son of the famous king K'inich Janaab' Pakal. Recovered from Temple 14 at the site of Palenque, Chiapas, Mexico. 684 to 702 AD [1300x1322] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 15:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> El Valle de Tehuacn-Cuicatln podra convertirse en Patrimonio Mundial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 14:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> El Valle de Tehuacn-Cuicatln podra convertirse en Patrimonio Mundial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 14:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The yacatas of Tzintzuntzan, Michoacan. These are the religious temples of Tarascan empire, rivals to the Aztecs. ~1300 to 1530 AD. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 13:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The yacatas of Tzintzuntzan, Michoacan. Tarascan empire. ~1300 to 1530 AD. [2503x3256] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 13:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the symbolic meaning behind the accoutrements of the Tarascan petamuti (high priest)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 05:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm finally getting around to reading Afanador-Pujol's book on the Relacion de Michoacan. She describes what the petamuti wears, but does not explain what they may mean. Accoutrements like a white garland on the head, a lip plug, bracelets, turquoise encrusted gourd, and a white, maroon, and black robe. The petamuti carries a lance-shaped staff with diagonal stripes in a candy cane pattern. Below the arrowhead on the staff hangs feathers and shells. Sometimes the petamuti wears a pendant in the shape of tweezers, red and black sandals, and red paint on the sideburn area of the face.

For those not familiar with the Relacion, here are some images pulled from the web,

http://67.media.tumblr.com/5dc42b176540850a9998ab853ab84d63/tumblr_o5chgrMNcL1r55zbco1_500.jpg

https://encrypted-tbn1.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcQUTg4n9-6H-1ZPgPYxwVsv1wwDQTO7BZ5CRWyp6VwBTsG0A3Tx

http://arqueologiamexicana.mx/sites/default/files/styles/arq1200x600/public/imagen_1005.jpg?itok=ZnlfS39M

http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-z1rUM6ktybM/T5T3cn7mWzI/AAAAAAAAAFM/0SWDgYlCsKo/s1600/petamuti2.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6th-century tomb reveals longest sword from ancient Japan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 14:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archaeologists reveal new findings on the history of the early-Islamic caliphate palace Khirbat al-Minya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 01:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Origins of Remote Oceania settlers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 01:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient burials suggestive of blood feuds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 01:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2,500-Year-Old Burial Hints at Ancient Cannabis Use </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 21:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2,500-Year-Old Burial Hints at Ancient Cannabis Use </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 21:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Ceremonial center of El Tajin, a Classic Veracruz culture city, Mexico. 600 to 1200 AD [1200x1600] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 21:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We know that the Tarascans controlled a powerful empire in West Mexico that rivaled the Aztecs. But who were the people the Tarascans conquered to make their empire? How did their culture and traditions differ, if at all, from their conquerors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 19:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drones help write new history of Caribbean </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drones help write new history of Caribbean </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Age of 1st chief's ancient tomb reveals Pacific Islanders invented new kind of society </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Age of 1st chief's ancient tomb reveals Pacific Islanders invented new kind of society </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret Maya tombs lend rare insight into rule of mysterious 'snake kings' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 20:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Olmec colossal head, San Lorenzo Monument 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 03:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Lorenzo Colossal Head 1. Olmec. San Lorenzo, Veracruz. 900 BC [1121x1500] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 03:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Hillary's State Dept. Gave Special Attention to 'Friends of Bill' After Haiti Quake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Hillary's State Dept. Gave Special Attention to 'Friends of Bill' After Haiti Quake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists map genome of African diaspora in the Americas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists map genome of African diaspora in the Americas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Food culture after 1066 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Food culture after 1066 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Head of Polyphemos, the one-eyed, man-eating Cyclops whom Odysseus finally outwitted and blinded. Greek or Roman. Hellenistic or Imperial Period, about 150 B.C. or later </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Head of Polyphemos, the one-eyed, man-eating Cyclops whom Odysseus finally outwitted and blinded. Greek or Roman. Hellenistic or Imperial Period, about 150 B.C. or later [1238x1600] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Treasure Trove of Ancient Human Footprints Found Near Volcano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sort search results by content within the PDF? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 14:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am having the hardest time finding a solution to my searching problem in Windows 8. I have on my computer a lot of journal articles in PDF form. The file names are the author and year and leave out the title of the article to reduce the file path length. In Windows 7 I was able to search my folder of journal articles for key terms and have relevant results returned to me first. When I try to do the same in 8, it gives me a list of results in alphabetical order and I can't find the article I had in mind. How do I change the search settings to give me relevant results and not results in alphabetical order? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1,000 prehistoric individuals to be genetically mapped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 17:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1,000 prehistoric individuals to be genetically mapped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 17:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New database reveals ancestor veterans of the Hundred Years War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 17:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two-thousand-year-old burial complex found in north China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 17:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient crossword puzzle found in Smyrna </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 17:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only canoe recovered in Mexico from before European contact. Veracruz. 1200 to 1519 AD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] The only canoe recovered in Mexico from before European contact. Veracruz. 1200 to 1519 AD [620x540] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analizan la prctica de la navegacin prehispnica </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analizan la prctica de la navegacin prehispnica </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just how popular were ham banana rolls in post-war America? And why did they fall out of favor by the end of the 1970s? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 22:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.americantable.org/2013/07/retro-recipe-ham-banana-rolls-1947/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cambridge University archaeologists are uncovering a lost 'utopia' in the Cambridgeshire fens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 14:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cambridge University archaeologists are uncovering a lost 'utopia' in the Cambridgeshire fens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 14:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] An hacha (axe) from Mexico depicting a person with a mustache. May have been used as ballgame markers [1500x2313] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 20:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uncovering Mysteries on the Isle of Mull </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 16:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Japan 'more cosmopolitan' than thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 16:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Japan 'more cosmopolitan' than thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 16:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Cannabis 'Burial Shroud' Discovered in Desert Oasis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 21:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers reconstruct beautiful house in Pompeii by using 3D technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 20:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salt's secret success in ancient Chaco Canyon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 12:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salt's secret success in ancient Chaco Canyon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 19:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game-changing study suggests first Polynesians voyaged all the way from East Asia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 18:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game-changing study suggests first Polynesians voyaged all the way from East Asia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 18:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pre-Columbian Mediterranean Round Ship Discovered for the First Time by Underwater Archaeology Expedition in Bulgarias Black Sea Zone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 21:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asian Metal Found in Alaska Reveals Trade Centuries Before European Contact </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossil bee nest provides clues to environment of early hominin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 17:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tulane archaeologists make Mayan discoveries at El Achiotal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tulane archaeologists make Mayan discoveries at El Achiotal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long-lost Inca altar is found beside river in Peru </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 15:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How oral cultures memorise so much information </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 16:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fall and rise of Native North America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 16:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fall and rise of Native North America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 16:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
