<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject754</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 04:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent photos! I enjoy the break from shitty grabs and tail presses that have become the norm here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 02:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically William Pickard was the equivalent of Walter White </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 01:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/OQFNT.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 21:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom's church had a party of kids who brought in a ton of balloons and let them go. I was told to come down to the church with my air rifle and shoot them down. 

Not many people get to shoot inside a church and not get arrested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 21:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hands down my favorite game for that reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 20:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dead can come back to life!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 20:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandfather's brother was a city councilman in Los Angeles. He was arrested in California and thrown in Sing Sing in 1925 for accepting bribes.  During the trial my grandfather set off dynamite under his own bed to try and garner sympathy for my grandfather's brother. It didn't work. 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Charles_E._Downs

**TL;DR: Grandfather's brother was a dirty city councilman, my grandfather blew up his own house with dynamite** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 03:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I go to the climbing gym 2x a week, and I climb fairly hard. I'm just a tiny dude, I weigh maybe 120 on a good day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 02:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lose the kung fu grip, it's about caressing not choking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 02:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erm, yeah... totally unrelated. Why would I be interested in sexy 4 year olds anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 02:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend used to play soccer so she's quite strong. Besides her recently reconstructed shoulder, I think she might beat me in a fight to the death. It would be very close. It's interesting when we wrestle, because there isn't any clear winner strength-wise. It's certainly a weird feeling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 01:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my good golly gosh. Thank you for posting this, I didn't know you had a 2nd album out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 08:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out bike trials, and learn some simple maneuvers. Learn to trackstand reasonably well, practice pedal kicking (quickly going through 1/4 rotation of the cranks, then ratcheting back) up over rocks, ride over all sorts of rocks, roots, curbs, etc. at *slow* speeds and try and keep your balance. Once you have a good balance, it should be much easier to get your way through uphill rock gardens. 

Also, on looser/ longer technical climbs I downshift into a high torque gear (usually 2-2) before the hill, and just pedal hard and consistently. Don't downshift too far though, or you'll just spin your legs too fast and get tired. Keep your revs high (and consistant) so you don't stall out. The killer is having to change gears on a climb or losing momentum because then every bump is harder to get over because you don't have momentum to help carry you through. 

As for weight distribution, you want each tire to have approximately the same weight applied on it. Too much on the front will slip out, and too much on the rear will cause wheelies and poor steering control. So for climbing you need to shift your weight forward, get low on the bike, and scooch up on the saddle to keep that balance.

There are tons of MTB tutorial videos on youtube, so check some out!

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WkS8nzvqfPA

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 06:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asbestos has a 12-20 year incubation period before symptoms start, you might not be in the clear yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 06:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Cooper is it? Please have a seat right over here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 06:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 06:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Basically, this.](http://futanariobsession.com/content/No_Soul-epic-futa.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 04:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But not forever. Eventually the lyrics, the beat, the voices, everything will slowly drive you insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 20:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AROUND THE WORLD

AROUND THE WORLD

AROUND THE WORLD

AROUND THE WORLD

AROUND THE WORLD

AROUND THE WORLD

AROUND THE WORLD

AROUND THE WORLD

AROUND THE WORLD

AROUND THE WORLD

AROUND THE WORLD

AROUND THE WORLD

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 19:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> their breakfast

or 

breakfast there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 19:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Woah](http://i.imgur.com/po0eM.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 18:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is hemp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 18:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://pic.jpgdump.com/23936.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 07:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A new hat can truly embiggen its wearer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 05:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was probably during Moab Muni Fest. There were 300+ of us in Moab that weekend. Sorry for the twattery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 04:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better beware the iron beef curtains </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 21:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Muni is a ton of fun.](http://i.imgur.com/pDCrp.jpgz) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 23:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a myth. 

Planes aren't a sealed container, they constantly let in outside air and let out exhaust air, and of course everything is run through a HEPA filter before it gets to you little air nozzle. The air gets filtered and replaced about 15 times an hour.


Sources:

http://sciencefocus.com/qa/how-stale-recycled-air-plane  
http://abcnews.go.com/2020/Health/story?id=1213901 page=1  
http://airtravel.about.com/od/healthandcomfort/qt/swinefluflight.htm
http://www.sfgate.com/health/article/Close-quarters-not-recycled-air-to-blame-for-2840378.php </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 23:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yes!](http://24.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m5br53wRjA1rpugqso1_250.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 23:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty easy. Just ask to rent a safe deposit box, hand the bank some cash, and they'll walk you right into the vault where the boxes are. 

If anything, comparing your vagina to a bank vault is akin to comparing yourself to a hooker. Pay a rental fee and you can place your junk inside for a set amount of time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 23:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Is this good?](http://denver.cities2night.com/public/article_images/677.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 20:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this groomed shit? Show me some powder, show me some chutes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 15:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but I go to school with Max Schulze. He's crazy to say the least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 04:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is edited for time constraints unfortunately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 04:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mary Jane. The rest you'll have to figure out on your own! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 04:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, primarily trials and muni. Still sponsored by 661 too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 04:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Checking in? On a groomer? Show us the powder! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 23:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put on my 50 Shades of Grey audiobook, as read by Gilbert Gottfreid. Works every time. 

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5K1RcKJVbHA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 23:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Like this?](http://25.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m9cplizPCr1rryjzgo1_400.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitting some pillow lines on Saturday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 20:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 15:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to buy ammo, you can just bayonet anyone within a 500 meter range. It's also good if you're looking to become a pole vaulter. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 08:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Wait for it...](http://gifs.gifbin.com/032011/1299505686_jackass-3d-steve-oport-a-potty-slingshot.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 02:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've accidentally done this before. Springs and parts *everywhere*

http://i50.tinypic.com/670d3n.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 02:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i50.tinypic.com/670d3n.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 01:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've put my hand inside a blender hundreds of times. How else do you wash it when you're done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 01:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't always true unfortunately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 01:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Multi colored cats are females though.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tortoiseshell_cat) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 05:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best. Hit. Ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-28 20:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet he writes shitty code </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-28 02:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.assaultweapon.info/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-28 02:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you so quiet?

... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-28 02:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up in a completely middle-class environment. We didn't have any financial troubles, and we took vacations together as a family, but other than that we weren't really different from any other family. I'd like to think that I'm very well adjusted and my parents definitely taught me about living on my own and how to budget my own money (which they might have taken a bit too far, I'm sometimes a bit of a tightwad). 

Turns out our family has quite a bit of assets that I'm just now learning about. I'm so glad that I didn't grow up to be some rich snobby douchebag. Having a hand-me-down purple minivan as a first car and not living extravagantly while growing up really put me on the right track.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-28 00:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to buy this house. In one million $5 increments. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 07:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kink were you discussing via letter? How was the outcome of bringing up something 'taboo' to your wife? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 07:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 07:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Detroit then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 06:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QQh56geU0X8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 06:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In highschool I used to work at a little rinky dink place that ended up going out of business 6 months after I left. I left once I heard they had bounced a check to Domino's Pizza. Yeah. That kind of place. 

Everyone who worked there was a lazy high school worker, and I was the only one who wasn't perpetually drunk or high on shift. Since I did actual work, they put me on the gocarts because they required a bit of attention when running, and the course needed fixing if someone crashed into the tires lining the course. 

The great thing was that our gocart track was located in the back corner of the property, and only larger kids could ride, and our place was aimed towards smaller kids. Also, I worked alot of weekdays. This meant I had tons of free time, and I continually had to "fix the track". I would turn off the limiters of the cart (which made it go *surprisingly* fast, like 40+ mph fast), and then I would hop in and drift all over the place. Fix a tire over here, drift to the other side of the course, fix a tire, drift around some more, fix another tire or two. I got damn good at doughnuts, drifts, and drifting into gocart parking spaces. 

It was fantastic, and whenever my bosses would see me they would get excited that I was actually doing work and not sitting around with a glazed look in my eyes.

Then they decided I was too reliable to be playing around with gocarts and put me on cash register on weekends. And I heard they didn't offer any raises. And that they were bouncing checks. And that they had never once cleaned the balls in the ball pit (do you know how nasty kids are? I shudder to think of all the human ooze absorbed by those foam balls). I got the fuck out of there.

EDIT: I also got heavily hit on by some 12? year old girls. They were saying some *lewd* things. *Shudder* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 06:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Bindings:** Burton Cartels

**Boards:**   
- Primary: Atomic hatchet  
- New board (still in the mail): Atomic Alibi  
- Rock board: Salomon piece-o-shit, cost: $15  
- Splitboard: Home built off a Voile kit 

**Boots:** Salomon Solace

**Backcountry gear:**  
- Poles: Black Diamond collapsible  
- Beacon, shovel, probe: Ortovox package deal  
- Pack: Black Diamond Alias with Avalung  
- Ice Axe: Black Diamond Raven

**About me:**  
I primarily ride moguls, trees, chutes, and powder. I throughly enjoy off piste riding, and I think that the terrain park is a complete waste of time (no offense to those of you who only ride there), I'd rather ski the entire mountain rather than groomers with some pipes and ramps stuck in the middle. I can rock the moguls faster than many of my skier buddies, and I'm not afraid to do some hiking to get at that pow or to bag a mountain peak. 

**About the boards:**  
I've owned my **Atomic** board for 7 years, and it's been absolutely fantastic. It's light and nimble enough for moguls and trees, but it's stiff enough that I don't mind jamming through powder, crust, or anything in between. It is getting a little old though, so I'm upgrading in just a few days. I can't say enough about the craftsmanship and feel of Atomic boards. 

My **splitboard** is fantastic, although I don't have nearly the amount of days on it as I do on my regular board. If you're interested in the backcountry it's a great way to get into it, and if you don't want to spend a lot of coin, you can always build a splitty yourself pretty easily. The voile system makes it so that you lose very little rigidity in the board, and skinning is hands down the best self propelled way to get to the top of a mountain. Fuck snowshoes, they can go to hell and die. 

My **$15 piece-o-shit board** is probably one of my best purchases. I've had it for 3 years so for $5 a year, it's definitely earned its keep. It's not a good board by any means, but it's passable and the ability to charge hard through some sketchy trees is amazing. These last two seasons have just about killed it though, I've put more days on my rock board than my normal board... Oh well. Still worth it. It's taken on more rocks and submerged branches than you could shake a stick at. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 02:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the exact conclusion I came to when that happened. The giant CRAAACK was unnecessary I thought. What was the 2nd thing that bothered you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 02:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one thing I don't understand is that it's listed under 'comedy' in Netflix. It's almost anything but a comedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 18:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The razors are double edged, and you shave twice before you flip it around. So 4 shaves per blade. At least that's what I got out of the description.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 04:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this country, you gotta make the money first. Then when you get the money, you get the power. Then when you get the power, then you get the women.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 03:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If the medication is not inserted properly, you may have small cuts or scrapes in the urethra.  The small cuts or scrapes in the urethra also increases the risk of passing sexually transmitted infections between sexual partners.

Sounds good doc, shoot me up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 23:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blacks? Perfect! Give me the moguls, chutes, and trees all day every day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 01:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/onetruegod  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 01:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His wife is your girlfriend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 00:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to shave assholes. There's too much terrain change with too little visibility </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 19:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do this as well. Whenever the skin on my fingers gets dry I peel it off and eat it. I also bite my nails to keep them short, and I often bite the insides of my mouth. I'm not sure why I do it, but it's a way to pass the time I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 19:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well no shit, I have this too. I always kind of wondered about it but I guess it's not normal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-18 00:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 million a day? 2 million? 3? Everyone has a price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 23:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant that you could pay Scarlett to give you blowjobs. In addition to the yachts, beer, and gallons of barbecue. It's a win-win for everybody! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 23:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With an unlimited credit card, you can buy anything you want </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 01:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the speeds these tungsten rods will be falling, they won't have radio communications because of the plasma layer formed as the rod pressurizes and heats the air it runs into. Therefore guidance systems will have to be integrated into the rods and will have to come up with creative ways to position themselves. The guidance systems will have to be extremely reliable in conditions ranging from a vacuum to re-entry conditions, and this has always been a problem. Dropping a needle from space onto a 10 square meter target is not an insignificant task. 

Assuming the guidance systems work correctly, the very act of aiming a tungsten rod will be a huge challenge. Any fins or stabilizers will have to be extremely strong, and will have to work very quickly. At hypersonic speeds simple fins like we're used to on guided bombs will work poorly, if at all. That means coming up with another type of steering, maybe small rocket motors or something, but those would open a whole series of other problems. 

Next, you'd need to transport all this crap into space, hope it works, and hope that nobody shoots down your extremely expensive and extremely vulnerable megaweapon. It's not like our nuclear arsenals are just floating around out there at the mercy of any country that doesn't feel like being nuked. 


**TL;DR:**
Overall what will this get us? An astronomical (pun somewhat intended) debt for just a few inaccurate and highly vulnerable superweapons. Why not just fly a plane or launch a missile for an extremely tiny fraction of the cost? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 22:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would also cost somewhere near $225 million per bomb drop, whereas we can build a nuclear bomb for only $7 million and conventional munitions for considerably less. Unless we find a cheap way into space, it's never going to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 07:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of it this way: What skills will you know after college that will help you better other people? 

Hint: knowing about the second defenestration of Prague isn't too high on an employer's list of desired skills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 22:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't his asshole, he just posted the photo hosted at www.goatse.info. Unless you and I are thinking of different users </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 22:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wanted to enter a photography contest with a very close in shot of my nuts. It is rolling sand dunes? Perhaps a picture of somewhere overseas? Nope. It's a ballsack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 22:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I'm not too averse to spinning meat, and I like hearing the song "Right Round" put to moving images, I'd put up a 100 foot tall version of www.meatspin.com, complete with the spin counter and everything (assuming it's an LED billboard). I would leave it there for as long as it took the government to legislate against me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 15:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fully agree. By the end of a long ride, especially if it's a muddy one and your cables are all gunked up, your thumb can get sore from mashing buttons. I also found that on a bumpy trail, I would sometimes bump into the shifter with my thumb and accidentally shift. I just absolutely love that I can use either my thumb or index finger to shift with Shimano. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 07:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SRAM X9s are quite nice and I really enjoy them, but I absolutely love that Shimano has the dual release system where you can either use your thumb or trigger finger to release cable tension. The Shimano Saint rear shifter and XT Shadow rear derailleur are probably my favorites that I've had on my bike. 

I'm currently running Elixir CR brakes and they work quite well, but Shimano brakes are a breeze to bleed and they lock up great as well. Favorite brakes so far would probably go to the Avid Code 5s I had on my downhill bike, but for all mountain brakes I'd go pretty much anything Shimano Deore or above. 

Overall, they both make some high quality products, but I might give Shimano a bit of an edge over SRAM in shifting actuation and their brakes, but that's just been my experience. I keep my shifting system real clean so the dirt and grime others have talked about haven't really affected me. However, my experience with a fleet of rental bikes I've worked on, SRAM is much more tolerant of crap in the system which happens over time. 

**Final breakdown:** Shimano Saint shifters for quick actuation, SRAM x9 or X0 if you're looking for something dependable, Shimano brakes for the win, and it's a tossup between cranksets because there's just so many options for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 18:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for some fun, but don't have the time to warm each other up? 

*FOREPLAY MAN TO THE RESCUE!* With a single lewd look he can make the Sahara into Niagara falls, a rope into rebar, and can turn titties to diamond! Please contain yourselves, it's FOREPLAY MAN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 08:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/Ur92K.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 08:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Like this?](http://26.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lsrnikytPP1r4ws9wo1_250.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-27 19:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just broke out in applesauce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 09:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fantastic, keep it up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 06:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or like the wicked witch of the east's feet after she's crushed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 21:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My very christian friend is getting married in March. I think I have found my gift.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 21:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vibrating your mouth and scrubbing your orifices? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 21:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well using the smallest "if it fits it ships" box (giggity) from the USPS, it would come out to be approximately $5.35 x 2000 = **$10,700**

You could probably work out a bulk rate deal with the post office to lessen the cost, but shipping costs would still be significantly higher than the cost of the dildos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 21:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hypothetically, where would you go to buy bulk dildos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 18:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, you got 4 feet of snow? Well here's a flimsy 5 ounce plastic shovel. Good luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 09:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here in suburban Colorado 8.5% abv 40s are $2.50. That shit will get you ripped. The lower alcohol percent 40s are even cheaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 07:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as ill as you would feel after a sip of this concoction  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 04:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to work on your wood chopping technique  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I posted a link to an article about how hydraulic brakes work yesterday and people asked for more. If you have any SRAM products (or RockShox, Avid, Truvativ) you can read all their manuals   publications here: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 03:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 23:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first full suspension was a used Dawg that held up great. It was unfortunately stolen, but now I'm riding a 2011 Kona Abra Cadabra and that thing is a wonderful piece of machinery. I also had a Kona Stab downhill bike. It was pretty good, but I fractured my wrist pretty bad and decided that full on downhill riding wasn't all that fun. I much prefer all-mountain riding. 

My friend also has a Dawg and loves it to death. I haven't come across anyone with anything bad to say about them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 21:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The ultimate lube keg. Lube pump included" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 15:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just one of a great string of misleading statements </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 06:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.wowomg.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 05:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh y-y-yeah it's-s-s warm outs-s-s-ide. No need for a s-s-sweater h-here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 04:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmm... mercuric goodness... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 03:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True true. The jump I did this on was notoriously hard to land well (most people cased it because the tabletop was too long). So in my infinite wisdom I decided to skip the jump in front of it and bomb into it for the big air. Didn't end too well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever wondered about your hydraulic brakes and their design? If so, check out this great overview of hydraulic disc brakes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 02:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 02:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't go *too* fast though. I almost broke my ankles when I got up to warp speed and overshot the landing. Landing nearly flat off even a medium sized jump is no fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-15 19:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd nominate the [sten gun](http://www.war44.com/misc/images/3/Sten_MK2.jpg) and the [bren gun](http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d5/Bren1.jpg), but the one that takes the cake for me is the the Fench abomination, [the Chauchat](http://www.mitrailleuse.fr/France/Chauchat/chauchat.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-11 21:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something like that would literally knock the shit out of your ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
