<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4868</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When someone calls scientific records "your opinion" I realize I'm swordfighting with a brick wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama was never radical. But the tea party is certainly made up of fanatics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really have the time to rebut this in its entirety. What I will say is this: Calling it global warming is an old tired argument from ignorant ostriches. Has every new year been the hottest on record since we began keeping records? Yes. That doesn't mean climate change isn't real. It also doesn't mean we haven't caused it. Is using the current Blizzard an argument against "global warming"? No. But it is an argument for climate change. If you deny climate change and its cause you should go back to school because you aren't understanding the issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they were wrong, their paper is shamed for closing their eyes to suspicion.

That's where you're wrong kiddo! In Trump world, conservatives don't get punished for lying or fake news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wise words from someone described as a liberal fanatic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't believe he's wrong. He fully believes he's right. And therein lies the danger. People who are convinced they're right despite overwhelming evidence to the contrary are commonly called zealots. This is who is running our government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 06:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well crazy white people are going to be crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're right. He's gonna keep going until he vomits his heart out his throat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't. spiral out of control and end up in rehab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But would they care? It doesn't seem that congress really gives a shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well here's a quick fact. All tech experts are liberal. If they're conservative, they're not experts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or was it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who would know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like that veterans organization to which he claimed to have donated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to know just who elected President Pinocchio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need time to fabricate something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just described insurance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a bird! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why be fair? They're not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first step to autocracy. Remove checks and balances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "no one knew healthcare could be this complicated." -Trump.

They're not surprised. They knew it would be bad. That's why Trump preemptively tried to discredit the CBO. The republican playbook clearly states, "when you're wrong, lie." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They weren't wrong. States chose not to implement it. Republican operatives blocked state subsidies for the ACA. It's all a false narrative to trick the American people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not racist, he just wants white people to have more babies than brown people. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And by that, he meant he doesn't want other cultures in America. Because they still speak their own language. And cook their ethnic foods. And they choose to live in the same neighborhoods. Because we all know that having another culture is un-American. /s

Steve King should not be re-elected. But we'll see what his district does.

Steve King's district:
95.8% White
0.8% Black
1.1% Asian
2.5% Hispanic
0.2% Native American

Mind you, Souix City, IA is part of his district. What is it they say? If you can't beat them out, breed them out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and us pointing and laughing is exactly why they voted for Trump. Because we don't take them serious. And we don't take them serious because they're uneducated. And uneducated people always fall for the most vitriolic rhetoric. It's a vicious cycle that can only be fixed through education. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are now being beat up for finger guns. That is all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they're made of at least 50% of the same stuff. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, they will be checking through people's microwave ovens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, amazon created a "resistance radio" to promote it's "Man in the High Castle" show. Trump supporters were convinced it was a real thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if? Pakistan is in the hands of extremists already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the truth. Automation is taking jobs. Now there are more jobs maintaining automation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what if it's actually Conway who has been tweeting as Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not the only damage to the home. There were also padlocks on internal doors to lock up his victims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all for affirmative action among equally qualified applicants. This is is not that. This is saying, we want more brown teachers, but it's too hard for them. Let's make it easier. This is wrong on many levels. And one can argue this wouldn't be necessary if we had better teachers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Test meant to screen teachers instead weeded out minorities

Test meant to screen teachers actually worked

FTFY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOOOOOOO. There are already too many bad teachers. Diversity is not required in teaching. Highly qualified teachers are required. This is more important than diversity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see king's point, but his message is entirely xenophobic.

His argument is one of assimilation. I live in Miami, the home of orgullo nacional. Everywhere you go, it's Cuban and South American flags. But I argue, despite that It's part of a city's DNA, those enclaves. Where you can go and experience other cultures without leaving your own city. It's beneficial for the whole city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True enough. It's not that they monitor Americans' communications, they capture ALL communications. They only search them if they need evidence or intel. This is why they built the facility in Bluffdale, UT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And on that note, it's time for the media to start calling the lies, lies. I remember this time last year, Huffington post had footnotes in every article about trump citing that he was a serial liar, misogynist, racist, and bigot.  Those stopped when he won the nomination. And while those were important, they should have been in every article on every newspaper and website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And microwaves that turn into cameras, et cetera.

Really? they turn into cameras? What utter nonsense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how to do civics. Good for this guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bill is satirical, but people aren't taking it that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Underneath this layer of humor is a deep sadness because that's what they believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kellyanne Conway is the white house equivalent of a crackwhore dating a drug dealer. She's always instigating shit that she cannot back up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will oppress you with good government services. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's over, we fined Deutsche bank $650,000,000.

The russians find them $5,000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our civilization was built with somebody else's babies. We are a nation of immigrants. If this is the core issue with trump supporters, history won't look kind upon them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, that's it. No doubt Ross introduced them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was asking if you knew what a super majority was. It's 2/3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, yes he did. And he did it so that Trump could pay back Deutsche bank. And ousted Deutsche bank chairman ended up going to the bank where the fertilizer baron was majority shareholder. All very shady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he is removing non-partisan federal prosecutors to install people loyal to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to remove someone's right to vote. I want people to be educated in how our government works. And it's bicameral. What is a "super majority"? It takes 2/3 of the house and senate.  You are far more educated than 90% of voters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you can't answer those questions without google? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 08:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nor do I, but the alt-right think that's one step away from Stalin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's spam, plain and simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a cognitive disconnect. It's taken me most of my life to realize exactly what the parties stand for.

Democrat: the government should do what the people want and what's best for the people.

Republican: I can do whatever I believe the constitution says, and stop adding to it to say I can't. 

It doesn't take a PhD in political science to understand we need more political parties in this country. The republican party was co-opted in the late 1960's by those who saw an opportunity to walk back all of the progress made. The party of Lincoln was educated and moderate. The current state of the party is in shambles. It's members, who once stood for conservative values are now being led by the most right-wing people possible. And it is ignorance alone that is to blame.

Meanwhile, the democratic party which once stood for truth, justice, and the American way has been co-opted by social justice warriors who try to force equality by forcing affirmative action of every sort. They used to change hearts and minds. Now they leave them behind and fight for their causes like the most right-wing zealots.

It leaves people like me with a distaste for them both. I am a bit like Bernie in my want for social services. But I'm a full supporter of the 2nd amendment. The people have a contract with government. But it's now being run by people who despise government. People who believe we shouldn't have a contract. People who believe it's every man for himself. Despite the core of the republican party whose ideas are dying in the killing fields of politics, they fall for the rhetoric. We don't need a conservative or liberal president. We need a moderate president. And moderates in the congress. We need to center the country again. The current vision for our nation is a bleak and dark picture. It's what the loudest minority believe they want. Even though it goes against their own interests. Ignorance. When America stopped teaching civics, we lost something. How many of you can, right now without google, tell me what kind of legislature we have? Or tell me how many votes is required to pass vetoed legislation? Or tell me what the line of succession is to the fifth person? How many can tell me how old you have to be to run for president, or senate? How many justices are in the SCOTUS? For what reason the secret service was started? If you vote, you should know the answer to all of these questions. If you don't know, what are you voting for? Who are you voting for? Why are you voting for that person? Does that person have a record of doing those things you want?

"You don't need to pass an IQ test to be in the Senate" --Senator Mark Pryor

Those who founded this nation did so with the expectation that only the wisest among us would be senators.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seriously, if they were to watch one episode of trms, they'd see a ton of evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a national symbol of distress. You can see why we'd be concerned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Malik Obama birth certificate is fake. Look ate the date format. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obamabux are exclusive to the first bank of Kenya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it feels good to be right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol wut? White people are the purveyors of racism. What are Republicans even talking about? Their own racism makes them think others are racist? 

I am white too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 12:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like at one time there were server transfers. But someone forgot to turn off all the services. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That any of you are shocked about this means you're not reading news about it. I've known about the samsung TV camera vulnerability for years. I read the appropriate news. Even mainstream news covered this when the vulns broke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, now the easter bunny thinks he's a ccie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm in Miami, so 30 years from now my house will be waterfront property. And pushing them all the coast just means they'll come crawling back and some point and ask for welfare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the best scientists at NASA, it's 97%. Where is your God now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't create allies out of zealots. It's a shame we can't give them the heartland and leave them there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lookups only give you the IP address, which could then be accessed via VPN from another server. And those lookups sound like keepalives. A ping sent from server to server to prevent sockets from closing and sessions from timing out. It would require a lookup if they used a domain instead of an IP address </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This notion that someone with 10% of the information can make judgements like they have 100% is disturbing when taking a lunch order. This is dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You BELIEVE it's bullshit. I don't think you're capable of critical thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't have a measurement for what the current natural rate is because we've altered it. We know what past rates have been through scientific research. This is what makes this question invalid. We say, "we're affecting the rate of climate change." And deniers say, "well how much are we?" The scientific answer is complicated. The layman's answer is by a lot. Because the rate is the measurement, not the percentage. Deniers don't possess the mental faculties to understand the answer, because it's not a percentage. It's a complicated answer that doesn't boil down to layman digestible  format. And because the answer is so complicated, people say it's bullshit. Like trying to explain how an airplane flies to someone living in the 19th century.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Science is not bullshit, you Philistine. Just because you don't understand something doesn't make it bullshit. This is why your whole side wants to live in the early 20th century. Progress is scary to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't work like that. And because you can't grasp the concept, you deny. It's not the percentage, it's the speed. Ice ages typically run an average of ten thousand year cycles. The warming cycle this time is a matter of decades instead of millennia. Because of humans and the industrial revolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They forgot to include Wilbur Ross </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is actual evidence. That ukranian is currently being investigated by the FBI. We have the Trump aide confessing that Trump ordered the Russia policy softened. We also have photographic and phone records which prove that Trump met with Sergey Kislyak. We have phone records which prove that Manafort met with the Ukranian. We have photographic evidence which proves that Trump met with Russian Oligarch, "the fertilizer king". This is evidence, not speculation. Continue to ignore evidence you don't like. And this kind of tactic is childish at best. It's the same kind of tactic I see Tucker Carlson using to disqualify answers he doesn't like. Unless you provide me with exactly the specific qualifier I'm asking, everything you're saying is false. It's a tactic used by dummies to continue to support their beliefs when they don't hold up under scrutiny. It's not my opinion. I'm not going to waste my effort trying to change your deeply held beliefs. Mental illness. Sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. The man behind the curtain has made a career out of going bankrupt. I wouldn't trust him to make a budget if he had a degree in economics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just laid it out to you. It's not my opinion. It's what happened. You can claim that it's propaganda. You'd be wrong. And 6 months down the line when Trump is fully impeached and his administration is in federal prison, you can even claim it unfair. You'd be wrong again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such disrespect. Sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is ample mounting evidence of him being a russian puppet.

at the RNC, Paul Manafort met with a Russian national he worked with in Ukraine. There, he informed trump they wanted the Republican platform changed. The trump campaign then changed the Republican platform to be softer on Russia, specifically denying Ukraine weapons to fight Russia. The guy who changed it verified the order came directly from Trump. 

You are ignoring the evidence because you're not watching the news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What more evidence do we need of pay-for-play by Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I own seven pairs of 5.11 Stryke pants for work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am enjoying Far Recon: Ghost Cry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C'mon. you were thinking it.
The roads are terrible, someone should send bechtel to Bolivia.

I enjoy the customizability of the weapons a lot, but damn the packs are not microtransactions. They are transactions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing a game where I get to wear the same pants I wear to work every day is actually the best part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be amusing to watch the GOP implode from fighting over health care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They know they want a "clean repeal". Just to say they did it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They crammed it together in the 11 hour. Of course it's shit. But that was the point to make the "freedom" caucus bill look palatable. Even though it's worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's what they want. Because corporations are the United States of America. They alone contribute to the GDP. And we're all just cogs in their machines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the smoking gun? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given that the law is so vague as it stands, it's a license to kill.

You just have to establish that you feel threatened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, a license to kill bill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Satire. This is satire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the result of a last-minute scramble to cobble together a piece of legislation using crackpot ideas shouted by right-wing talking heads who hate America and her people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the republicans hate poor people so much they want to disallow them from spending any new-found wealth on anything other than their health care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This piece of shit was a navy seal. Regardless of what you think of him he bled for all of us. And he's due his day in court. That said, as a former navy seal, shouldn't he know the difference between Indians and Persians?

Read a news story claiming he was a navy seal. Upon further research, turns out he was in shipboard CIC. Makes my entire comment irrelevant. Retract! Retract! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I read that part, it's bizarre at best. That's such a huge concern that congress is worried about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What more proof of fascism do the people need? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reporting indicates that, prior to June 2016, the Obama Justice Department and FBI considered a criminal investigation of Trump associates, and perhaps Trump himself, based on concerns about connections to Russian financial institutions.

What reporting? Where are these reports? Who reported them?

In June, the Obama Justice Department submitted an application that apparently named Trump in addition to some of his associates.

I'm sorry, you, this reporter, and anyone who knows, won't have access to a FISA warrant application.

Not taking no for an answer, the Obama Justice Department evidently returned to the FISA court in October 2016, the critical final weeks of the presidential campaign. 

Where is the proof of this? Again, those who, know won't say. Those who say, don't know. FISA courts are top secret. Reporters won't get access to these proceedings or their processes.

And if you continue to read the article, it asks the questions of whether this took place or not.  Read the whole article before you run around citing sources which aren't facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no he did not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something stands out that people forget. Steve Bannon is a Hollywood elite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sad that this isn't far from reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps this was Russia's intent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is a master of diversion. This is how he go so far in business.  Diversion, spending other people's money, collusion, and then worming his way out of it through legal loopholes. He's a slimy shyster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trumps staff is now reviewing those decisions by the Obama administration to determine economic impacts

What are the economic impacts of depleting natural lands? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 13:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anyone willing to stand up to the oppressive speech of the vitriolic right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's just so odd that the conservative movement will try to elevate anyone who says the talking points loud or crass enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no one said sight it in using lead and then hunt with non-lead. You're looking for an argument that wasn't made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nonetheless, shooting at him and potentially hitting innocents is far worse than letting him get away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one is saying practice with copper loads. As for the hunt, sight it in at the range with non-lead ammo before you hunt. Your argument is invalid. And you should know, ammo is cheaper than meat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
