<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8089</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thoroughly understand your reflexive inclination to take offense.  None was intended; please offer my apologies to all Bostonians.

All kidding aside, without using actual IPA notation, it would be very difficult for me to distinguish between the Alabama accent I was attempting to transliterate above and the non-rhotic (r-dropping) New England accent you likely have, which is, among other things, much more nasal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  (because everybody has a list of what they buy at which of the 6 different stores in town, right?)

That's our story, and we're sticking to it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> English is my first language, but I did an exchange program in high school and I speak Spanish proficiently.

I worked for my state's department of motor vehicles for 8 years and when I first started, I spent a lot of time at the information counter, especially helping Spanish-speaking customers.

One afternoon, a woman approached the counter and, in Spanish, asked for information about the requirements to obtain a driver's license.  I gave answered her questions and briefly explained the process.  When I was done, she asked me where I was from.  I replied, "the U.S."

She exclaimed that she was a professor of Spanish at the (very well known and respected) university nearby and that she had never, in all her years of teaching, encountered a non-native speaker with pronunciation and grammar as nice as mine.  I would have been mortified by her praise if I hadn't also been so flattered by it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "An unrelenting hostility toward civil rights and racial justice has been the defining feature of Jeff Sessions professional life. At each step of his legal and political career, and across a variety of issueswhether voting, criminal justice, diversity in higher education and employment, education equality, immigration, or LGBTQ rightsSessions has stood opposite the civil rights community and the principles of
fairness and equality."

  "Sessions has consistently criticized the work of civil rights organizations and the lawyers who
work for themespecially when they appear before the Judiciary Committee as nominees for judgeships or other government positions."

  "Sessions has exhibited a reflexive assumption that civil rights experience renders one unfit for government service, often referring pejoratively to nominees with the ACLU gene or the ACLU chromosome.

 "Sessions has affirmatively stood in the way of desegregating the Southern District of Alabama and placing Alabamas first African-American judge on the Eleventh Circuit Court of Appeals."

 "Despite overwhelming evidence to the contraryincluding the detailed findings of the DOJ and federal courts across the countrySessions denies that race discrimination in voting exists."

 "From Sessions time as a federal prosecutor, two events in particular warrant further discussion: (1) Sessions selective prosecution of Black civil rights activists for legitimate voter assistance; and (2) the impact that failed prosecution has had on the political participation of racial minorities."

There's so much more...that's why I linked the whole report...but that should get you started. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very good tip!  Technically, that bitter white part lurking under the zest itself is the "pith" and you're absolutely right...it's nasty, bitter stuff that will *not* make your food taste better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahahaha!!!

We don't need your stinkin' *elite*, arrogant "sources" around these parts anymore.  We got alternative facts now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not arguing that ridiculing someone's heritage is a shitty thing to do (except to the extent that they are *proud* of their ancestors' abhorrent actions), but [this](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/P._G._T._Beauregard) is what "Beauregard" has to do with his Confederate heritage.  He was named after a famous Confederate general who was a key player in the adoption of the Confederate battle flag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, yes...absolutely I do.

But even more damning than "Jeff's" family ties is [his own extensive record of aggressively working to enforce bigotry in public policy.](http://www.naacpldf.org/files/our-work/LDF-Jefferson-Sessions-Report-in-Opposition-FINAL-1-9-2017.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, I was gonna say slightly less awful than Strom Thurmond, or George Wallace...but upon reflection, I'm not so sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Jeff-ah-sun Bow-ruh-gahd Sesh-uns *thuh Thuhrrrd*"

FTFY.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consider yourself fortunate, then?  I dunno.  It definitely wasn't an ingredient in standard-issue tuna salad in the kitchen/community where I grew up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd never seen this photo of the 2 of them and wondered where it was taken.

[According to Stanford University, this is from the staff workshop at the 1966 annual Southern Christian Leadership Conference in Frogmore, SC.](https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/cd093xt9916) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I've read makes me think the feds were the ones who did the drive-by.  The part where I'm really unsure what to believe is whether I think he survived and made it to Cuba or not.  I thought I had this post saved where some redditor laid out the whole theory, complete with links to good sources for the background claims that are the foundation of this theory...but of course, now I can't find it.

I dunno...it's probably no less crazy than the vast majority of other conspiracy theories, buuuut...it's just that when I read about it, there was this quality that was eerily reminiscent of how John Lennon insisted the FBI was conducting surveillance on him and his home, and everyone insisting at the time that he was a paranoid leftist.  Later, of course, we learned about COINTELPRO and how Nixon specifically targeted Lennon.  So...


EDIT:  Found the threads after all.  [Here is the main post from /r/todayilearned](https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/5ftvda/til_that_tupac_shakurs_godmother_was_convicted_of/) and [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/5ftvda/til_that_tupac_shakurs_godmother_was_convicted_of/danewli/) and [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/5ftvda/til_that_tupac_shakurs_godmother_was_convicted_of/danf077/) are the crazily detailed explanations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's brave in a couple of ways.

First, there is a tremendous social stigma around admitting that one cannot handle one's depression (or other mental health issues) alone.  This is especially the case when it comes to asking to be hospitalized.  For someone to be willing to say, "Fuck it, I don't care what people think or say about me. I need to go into the psychiatric unit for a minute and do whatever is necessary to not want to kill myself all the time" takes a lot of courage.

Secondly, people really internalize the shame that is directed toward them for having a mental health diagnosis.  A common response to this shame is to ignore/minimize how much the symptoms are affecting their day-to-day lives.  It is brave to acknowledge how much you are struggling and accept that as part of yourself so you can get better, rather than pretending it's not there/not that bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how this thread is 6 minutes old and the top comment is from a DC area resident.

I'll answer for the MD side: Shagga Ethiopian Restaurant in Hyattsville.  Get a meat combo and a veggie combo, and make sure you don't leave without a coffee or espresso drink made from truly excellent beans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite unexpected use for dill is in tuna salad. Fuckin' delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fresh lemon juice or lemon zest.  There are very few dishes that are not improved by one or the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's crazily far-fetched, but...

I think that given his family's well-documented long history of involvement with the Black Panthers and related surveillance of them by the FBI, that Tupac Shakur may have been targeted by the federal government (not anyone in the music industry), and that, having a reasonable expectation that such an attack would occur, he may actually have escaped the attempt on his life.

EDIT:  Found the threads that started me down the rabbit hole: [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/5ftvda/til_that_tupac_shakurs_godmother_was_convicted_of/danewli/) and [here.](https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/5ftvda/til_that_tupac_shakurs_godmother_was_convicted_of/danf077/)  They are part of [this TIL post from December 1, 2016.](https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/5ftvda/til_that_tupac_shakurs_godmother_was_convicted_of/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to say anything pork-based, really.  Pork fat is amazing when warm/hot, but disgusting and vile when cold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Did you get my cheeze whiz boy?

*Blues Brothers* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peanut butter, sweet pickle relish, and tomato sandwiches.

The first time I saw my ex-MIL eat that, I should've known better than to marry into a family which was the source of such madness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hummus, baba ghanouj, refried beans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you accept *The Meaning of Life*?

I understand why everyone loves Holy Grail so much, I mean, I do too.  But for me, it's *always* been the Meaning of Life, from the very opening scene forward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Demented and sad, but social." -- *The Breakfast Club*

"I love my dead gay son." -- *Heathers* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up in and around Washington, DC and used the metro system to commute to and from work most of my adult life.

Dear Tourists:  **Kindly stand to the fucking right on metro system escalators.**  The majority of us are rushing like bats out of hell in order not to miss our transfer trains, for which we have calculated the standard razor-thin margin of error.  We would *prefer* not to have to murder you in cold blood for staring slack-jawed at the acoustic tile ceiling, but **we will** if you continue to stand on the left side of the escalator, making us late for our 8:15 staff meeting.

Sincerely,

DC locals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The day I realized that I can get in my car and just **drive**.  Wherever I want, as far as I want, for however long I want.  And if I run out of gas, I can buy more.  And if I get a little lost, I have Google maps.  And if I don't have a signal, I'm still probably fine, since I speak both English and Spanish and am unlikely to end up somewhere that I can't get directions in one or both of those languages.

It was one of the most liberating moments of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, that's not a small thing; that's a hugely brave, enormous thing you did.

Much respect for recognizing that you needed help and asking for it.  I'm really glad to hear you're doing so much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The marquee behind them for *Adventure* starring Clark Gable and Greta Garbo is, imo, what really makes this old school cool.  This would've been sometime in 1945. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, nope to telling Mrs. W. about my fuck-up.

I just took my 'F' on the quiz like a woman; somehow, I didn't think that accidentally reading bear-librarian porn instead of the assigned story because I hadn't bothered to listen to a damn thing she was saying was going to earn me much sympathy from the very priggish Mrs. W.

I don't think I mentioned my, um, strange find to any friends or classmates...I was pretty mortified at how stupid my mistake was once I realized it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this, kids, is why the internet is a wonderful thing, and library card catalogs are torture devices.

In my senior year of high school, my English teacher assigned "The Bear," a short story by William Faulkner that (I have since learned) was published separately but also is part of his novel *Go Down, Moses*. 

By 12th grade, I had basically run out of fucks to give about high school, but I was at least attempting to pass English, since it was the only credit I needed to graduate.  I wasn't *really* paying attention in class when the homework was assigned so I caught the name of the story, but the author...not so much.

The afternoon before we were supposed to finish reading the story, I managed to make it to my neighborhood library in an effort to find a copy of the book. Knowing that I didn't have much time before the library closed, I searched by title in the fiction section.  There it was!  I copied down the call number and hurried toward the stacks.  My fingers tracing the numbers printed along the books' spines, I finally found the one that matched the note in my hand.  I grabbed the book from the shelf and made a beeline for the checkout counter.

I got home and opened the book, figuring I would skim enough to be able to pass whatever quiz came the following day.  The first thing I noticed was that this wasn't like other reading my English teacher had ever assigned, mainly in that it was clearly written during the (then) current century.  The second thing that really struck me was when I noticed that **ohmyfuckinggod this woman is very enthusiastically giving this bear a hand job**

It was at that moment I realized there was a good chance I had ended up with a different story about a bear than the one Mrs. W had intended.  Not only am I permanently traumatized by my memories of this book, but I also failed the quiz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Gaslighting is a form of manipulation that seeks to sow seeds of doubt in a targeted individual or members of a group, hoping to make targets question their own memory, perception, and sanity. Using persistent denial, misdirection, contradiction, and lying, it attempts to destabilize the target and delegitimize the target's belief.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gaslighting)

The etymology is interesting:  

 The term originates in the systematic psychological manipulation of a victim by the main character in the 1938 stage play *Gas Light*, known as *Angel Street* in the United States, and the film adaptations released in 1940 and 1944. In the story, a husband attempts to convince his wife and others that she is insane by manipulating small elements of their environment and insisting that she is mistaken, remembering things incorrectly, or delusional when she points out these changes. The original title stems from the dimming of the gas lights in the house that happened when the husband was using the gas lights in the attic while searching for hidden treasure. The wife accurately notices the dimming lights and discusses the phenomenon, but the husband insists she just imagined a change in the level of illumination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were all of these unspoken "rules" I didn't know about until I would incur his wrath for breaking them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IKR?!?!?!

Margaret Atwood is my very favorite author.  Her work has been formative in my life.  I don't do celebrity hero worship at all, but I've been dying to have a chance to pick her brain since I was 14, and I missed it by 20 minutes?!?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! *This* is a perfect example of what I'm talking about.

When perks are always the norm, they turn into an expectation.  It's *amazing* how fast people in general go from grateful to entitled under such conditions, and police officers are certainly no exception.  If anything, the power they wield makes them more susceptible to believing they are owed such favors, rather than less, compared to the public as a whole.

That officer who was bullying your coworker...if she had refused him entry and then he subsequently had to respond to a call at your gym while she was working, how do you think he would treat her as the victim of a crime after their prior interaction?  Exactly.  Me, too.  (And before someone *else* wants to lecture me about what how LEOs are professionals and would never let the provision of small favors color their response to a crime, let's be clear that if he were a professional who held himself to appropriately high standards, then he wouldn't throw his weight around in order to get benefits he's not entitled to.)

When people begin to believe there is a prevalent social norm that such favors should be provided, it's a frighteningly short hop to a world in which paying protection money becomes required in order to be able to rely on the idea that if you need help and call them, the police will come help you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK.  Then you're either missing or willfully ignoring the bigger picture here.  That's your choice.

It doesn't change the fact that everything about that type of collusion between police and DMV workers is, by definition, unethical, and in many cases, illegal.  People's failure/refusal to see it/call it what it is doesn't make it acceptable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, if you're the type of person who's OK with knowing that you utterly lack integrity in order to be able to take advantage of said perks.

I went through an ugly divorce and custody battle during my time there.  I could've really used that kind of leg up on my situation...but I didn't use it, because character is about what choices you make when no one is watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What she wanted me to *think* she meant was that since we had state troopers who worked as building security (at time and a half, mind you), that by extension, all LEOs were looking out for DMV personnel and watching our backs.

What she *really* meant was that the clerks who "took care" of cops would find that they no longer got issued tickets/safety equipment repair orders while driving, or if they did, would magically find them "taken care of." Officers world also look up info for clerks about their babies' dad's when the office of child support enforcement couldn't seem to manage to locate them.

Slimy, shady shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think *that's* bad, you'd be positively horrified at some of what goes on here.

In my state, the Dept of Corrections wasn't just asking prospective/new hires if they *had* social media accounts, they were **requiring** that applicants provide them with **passwords** to those accounts. Those who refused were not hired.

[The state legislature had to step in and pass a bill to clarify that no, your employer does not have the right to require you to divulge personal account passwords or non-publicly available social media content.](http://wtop.com/news/2012/04/md-employers-cant-have-access-to-social-media-passwords/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That settles it, then.  I can confirm that I've given birth to only one child, and he lives with me...so I feel fairly confident concluding it isn't you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I can't swear to it, but I don't think so, no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How many businesses (both private and government) take half days on Fridays?

As a state government employee over the course of 8 years -- literally **never**, unless I was charging it to my own accrued annual or personal leave.  That was simply not tolerated, period. Other employees didn't do it either, because no one would've allowed them to get away with that.


And sure, some days are short and fairly cushy and other days are long a terrible.  That's called having a job.  It's not different from anyone else's job in that way, and that's why LEOs get lots of OT -- to compensate them for those longer days.  Long days aren't a license to use work time, when you are being paid to do your *job*, to handle your personal affairs.  That's what your day off is for.  Oh, what? You didn't want to spend your day off sitting in the DMV?  **Neither did anyone else.**


And you keep going back to the fact that you have no issue with businesses handing out freebies as they see fit.  Well, it *is* a problem, but again, not my central point.  Would you care to explain exactly how using police time to do *hours* worth of personal business (it's not a "quick errand", please stop trying to minimize what's happening with word choice) is anything other than grossly unethical?

EDIT:  Yes, there *is* a "huge double standard"...*in favor of* law enforcement, which permeates virtually every aspect of living and functioning in American society.  To suggest the opposite is, frankly, ludicrous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: u/MichaelMoore92 has already provided the very best explanation above inn this thread for how and why -- from the perspective of a former police officer -- such freebies are absolutely unethical. Check out his answer first.

 I don't see how giving a cop a free coffee or sandwich is "extremely unethical".

Among other things, it creates an incentive for police officers to be more attentive to those business/individuals who have "helped" them when it comes to preventing/responding to crime--and less attentive to those who haven't given them freebies.  That's unethical because it puts other members of the public at a disadvantage in terms of the policing they receive.  It also encourages LEOs to selectively choose not to enforce the law -- like how my trainer (who told me to bump them to the front of the line) *never* got a ticket when she would get pulled over, because they all "knew" her.

But really, the point of my post wasn't the little freebies.  It was the DMV thing.  The reason that *some* police don't get regular breaks/lunches is because a LOT of them have the freedom to set their own schedules and take breaks whenever they want/aren't responding to an incident.  They find *plenty* of time to eat.  I'm not sure why you're OK with police using work time to do personal errands, but I'm absolutely not.  I can't decide to take a 2-hour lunch and charge it to my employer while I get my car detailed or see the dentist.  It's not treating anyone like a "slave" to suggest that they do personal business on personal, not work, time -- just like every other employed American.  There is no reason whatsoever that police should be permitted to get paid (using taxpayer dollars!) to handle personal business.  That's not what their salary is for, and what they are doing has a name: it's theft of time -- a crime for which my state not only dismisses, but also prosecutes, employees *other than LEOs* for engaging in that conduct.

It's a disgusting, unethical double standard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not a job for the inexperienced, my dear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an useless platitude that is so overly simplistic as to be utterly meaningless.  It makes me think you didn't understand what I said.  Here, I'll try again:

I didn't say all police officers are evil.  I said it is unethical for them to accept favors and special treatment from the general public.  They are civil servants just like the people behind the desk at the DMV.  It is the *definition* of unethical to allow police to engage in theft of time from their employers (and therefore the taxpayers) in order to do personal business.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 07:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Could be* any of those things, sure.  In practice, during the 8 years I worked there, this was seldom, if ever, the case.  How do I know?  Because officers would talk about it at the counter with little to no prompting...so I got in the habit of finding out.  The officer in question in the story above was, in fact, on duty.

 If they ARE on duty, it makes even more sense to let them skip the line if you are concerned about tax dollars considering that they'd be staying in line for hours.

I'm sorry...what?  No, that's not how it works at all.  A police officer can schedule his trip to the DMV on one of his days off (which, as a uniformed officer, he is *more* likely to be able to do than someone working Monday-Friday 9-5, since he likely has at least 1 weekday off), or if absolutely necessary, he can request time off to complete personal business.  You know...like all the rest of us do?

Under no circumstance should he be permitted to conduct personal errands on police time.  Just because he -- as a law enforcement officer -- doesn't understand that **stealing time** from one's employer is wrong doesn't mean that anyone should condone or facilitate that egregious conduct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 07:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/TheTrueFlexKavana should probably listen to you on this one...you are the good twin, after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 07:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol.  That's because I answered a question about (current) favorite words with that...it's the best synonym for "stripper" that I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not *that* sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please explain how the situation I described at the DMV is in any way ethical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that would be convenient.  But it makes far too much sense; we'll *never* adopt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We call that "e-filing" here, and yes, a large proportion of returns are filed electronically.

However, there are also still many people who submit their returns (or payments, for example, if they are on a payment plan for past due taxes) by mail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Providing free goods and services and offering "perks" that other customers don't get to police officers.  Worse, when police officers expect/believe they are entitled to special treatment.

It happens all the time...free coffee, free donuts, extra sides slipped in to their sandwich orders, cashiers at customer service and pharmacy desks ringing up their purchases when "closed" to others...on and on and on.  But what's the problem?  Police provide a valuable public service and they protect all of us, right? Why should I care if they get some perks from the grateful community?

I used to work for my state's department of motor vehicles.  When I first started there, the woman who trained me told me very clearly:  "When an officer in uniform comes in here, we have an unwritten policy that he goes to the front of the line.  It's professional courtesy.  They help us and we help them."  At first, I just nodded and took note of her instructions, but as I stood there watching the officer in uniform at the counter, getting assistance before a huge room *full* of other people who had been waiting for hours, it occurred to me...that's some unethical fucking bullshit right there.

Not only is he getting pushed ahead of everyone else who has followed the rules and waited their turns, if he's in uniform in my building at 2:20 in the afternoon, then **he's on duty and being paid a salary to do personal business at the DMV at taxpayer expense.**

It's bullshit, and as soon as I thought it through, I told my (former) trainer that unless that "unwritten policy" became a written one, she should expect me not to comply with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's called small caps.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Small_caps)

I'm not aware of this style ever being taught or encouraged in schools in the US, but it's *possible*, I suppose.  More likely, your dad could have picked it up as a habit if he was taught drafting/mechanical drawing, or, as many people (including my ex-husband) do, he may have just decided it looked cool and adopted it as his personal style.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It turns your...output...**bright** green.  Like leprechaun green.

The sort of distinctly unnatural color that would rightfully cause you to think something was very, very wrong with your insides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shouldn't laugh at your misfortune, but I totally am...only because I did the same damn thing.  I moved out here about 2 years ago.  About a year ago, I drove the hour or so to Morgantown to visit some friends.

When we left WV to come home, I had about 1/4 tank in the car...I thought about stopping for gas, but missed the turn into the Shell station on the way to I-68, so I just said, "fuck it, we'll be all right."

Of course, my calculations were a bit off and by the time we were approaching Maryland, the needle on my gas gauge was already touching the big, ominous **E**.  My (adult) son and I then proceeded to do virtually every step of your saga exactly as you describe, down to frantically arriving in Friendsville after dark and finding everything, including the lone gas station, closed.  Being from DC, I was downright *offended*.  Close?  Gas stations with self-service pumps *close*?  But WHY?!?!?  I don't wanna die here.

And then, I got to this:

 we saw the gleaming jewel of Accident down below

I am 100% certain this is the first time these words have ever been strung together in this order in the English language or any other.  Well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shhh...that's the more accurate version I learned at 16 that we don't talk with Dad about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funnily enough, I really, really am. Except for when I'm not.

There was a nursery rhyme about that which my father used to recite all the time to that effect...he swore it must have been written about me:

 There was a little girl, who had a little curl

 Right in the middle of her forehead.

 And when she was good, she was very, very good...

But when she was bad, she was *horrid*.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was about to call you out...all, "That's not your gf's mom! You yanked that from a post on /r/PenmanshipPorn 4 days ago!"

But it turns out that was [some other redditor's MIL with crazily perfect handwriting.](http://imgur.com/jtO8HJO)

([thread here](https://www.reddit.com/r/PenmanshipPorn/comments/5x235h/i_asked_my_inlaws_to_help_me_send_some_tax/))



Sorry for being kind of a douche to you in my head about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a queer woman, I want you to know that I am saving this post.

That's so the next time someone tells me that there's no such thing as erasure, or that women's sexuality isn't fetishized and commercialized for the benefit of straight men, I can simply show them the grotesque caricature that is your question (and your comments within the thread).

There is literally nothing I can add that /u/tornlace hasn't already explained perfectly clearly about why "turning a lesbian straight" isn't a thing, but I have the sense that you aren't interested in who lesbians really are; you're only interested in the idea of women being sexual with other women insofar as it is related to your own sexual gratification -- especially when it appeals to your ego and vanity, too.

TL;DR: Kindly fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a local, given the way that the majority of voters around here feel about accurate, comprehensive sex education, I'd wager that yes, a sizable majority are, at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maryland = MD

source: lifelong MD resident </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in western MD not too far from Accident!  It's a really tiny out-of-the-way kind of place, so it's pretty crazy to see it mentioned here on reddit for the 2nd time in less than 2 months...some travelers broke down there (no, they didn't have an *accident*) and posted about it in another sub.

Looks like Garrett County has hit the big time!

No, seriously.  If you'd ever been to Garrett County, you'd understand that getting noticed/mentioned *is* hitting the big time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You haven't given a lot of details, so forgive if I'm jumping to conclusions here, but if the dynamic in your household is what I'm understanding from your post and this response, it's time to start making a plan to move out, and not just because of this conflict over the job.

Your father really *should* understand that since you're 18 now, he doesn't get to have it both ways:  either he can treat you as a child and expect you to follow the rules he makes -- which means you get to be a child and not work/pay rent, OR, he accepts that you are an adult and therefore get the full set of adult rights *and* responsibilities.  However, **you should not waste your time/breath/effort attempting to teach/convince him of this**.  What's important is for *you* to understand that it's not OK for him to use manipulation or intimidation to cause you to act against your own best interest. Yes, it's going to be hard and not a little overwhelming, but you can do this.  Just think: you get to be a grown-up now.

Please know that I say this not as some pie-in-the-sky, "pull yourself up by your bootstraps" bullshit; I say this because my parents were super fucked up and I had to do the same thing at basically your age.

The fact that you got this job and are succeeding in it speaks volumes about your potential to grow and advance if you can just hold on to the position.  You're worthy of keeping this thing that has intrinsic value and is rewarding to you, never mind being productive, economically profitable, and beneficial for future career growth.

Bottom line: You're right, your father is wrong, and "I said so" is a ridiculous, bullshit reason for him to 'win' this dispute with.  All you need to do is figure out what steps you have to take so you can be independent and not have to deal with such ridiculousness.  You got this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  legally a tenant

Considering that OP hasn't indicated what jurisdiction she's in, you have absolutely no basis for such an assertion.

Never mind that OP hasn't once so much as hinted at the kind of shitty, entitled attitude you're attempting to project onto her.

But then, those facts really get in the way of your narrative about whiny, spoiled princesses, don't they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similarly, here's a LPT:

Do not consume an entire bag of black Twizzlers unless you are aware that the following morning, you will be given cause to wonder how and when your intestines were swapped with those of a leprechaun.

[Insert predictable joke about how black Twizzlers should never be consumed under *any* circumstances.]

Seriously, tho...scary shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pffft.  Fuckin' freeloaders.  And how, exactly, do you expect to pay for that asteroid???  *I'm* sure as hell not subsidizing your planetary catastrophe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There we go...it was escaping me.  Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muling *kind of* works, but it carries the additional connotation of doing the deed at another person's behest as a lackey, rather than for one's own benefit/profit.  Almost, but not quite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That actually *is* a fun fact.  Do you know what the accurate verb would be for the act of transporting illicit items between jurisdictions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LPT:  Do the exact opposite of this.

If you are my friend/acquaintance and you want me to *ever* respond to your attempts to contact me, **never leave me voice mail**.  Checking it is an irritating waste of time and I will avoid doing so if at all possible.

I only have my voice mailbox set up at all for business purposes and emergencies, and even so I still get hostile when I have to take time to call and listen to them (yeah, I know...first world problems).

Fuck voice mail.  Text me, email me, even actually *call* me.  But I will be super pissed if I see that little cassette icon appear -- *especially* if you ninja-sent it as a voice message and didn't even call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL.

*confirmation bias intensifies* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So she's quoting herself?  Sure.  That makes tons of sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Move out at 16 and flagrantly disobey them by beginning to date at age 17 (and eventually marrying) the person with the ethnicity/religious background combo that they would find most offensive.  Proceed to have a child with said detestable outsider.

Source:  Did exactly this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. [This](https://i.reddituploads.com/fdee9b9be8c245f6920414e770baad13?fit=max h=1536 w=1536 s=4b65a960b3534d02dd6fb3827fa50c5e) is Vincent Van Goat.

I'm a member of the (much smaller, not default) sub where a clever redditor posted his name and picture 10 days ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they're not air quotes, but I understand why OP would've interpreted them as [scare quotes](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scare_quotes)...because who, exactly, is being quoted as saying "thank you" on the receipt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
