<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YouTube Briefly Shuts Down Blizzard's Own YouTube Channel For Copyright Infringement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 22:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey bans reporting on corruption investigation of ex-ministers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 22:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A United Nations panel has approved a resolution that would have its General Assembly call on states to respect and protect the right to privacy in the digital age </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 19:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Growing threats from terrorism, computer hackers, diseases such as ebola and tighter border controls have helped Britains security industry grow at a rate far outstripping the wider economy over the past five years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 10:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Train passengers told to 'run, hide and tell' if terrorists launch attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 10:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vodafone sent phone data of more than 1,000 News UK staff to police who had asked for details of just one journalist, it has emerged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 10:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will One Mans Drug-Crazed Rampage Change Canadas History? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 10:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DC Comics Going After A Spanish Soccer Club With A Bat In Its Logo For Some Reason </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 10:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To Stop ISIS, Britain Is Set to Stop Free Speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 14:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Administration Preaches 'Human Dignity' While Covering Up Torture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 13:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Government's controversial "foreign fighters" legislation allowing the recall of suspected New Zealand jihadists' passports and warrantless surveillance is set to pass its first reading today as Labour holds its nose and votes for the bill it still remains sceptical about </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 13:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Asked to Censor Three Million Pirate Bay URLs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 12:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> E-cigarettes to be restricted, flavoured tobacco to be banned in Ontario </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 11:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police and security services will get new powers as the UK faces a terror threat "perhaps greater than it has ever been", the home secretary says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 11:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.K. Terrorism Law to Force Internet Providers to Give User Data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 14:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Highest-value terror detainees excluded from Senate investigation of CIA torture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 14:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mystery government spying with Regin: One of the most sophisticated pieces of malicious software ever seen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 13:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Zealand's Surveillance Laws Are Anti-People, Says Green Party leader Russel Norman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 09:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama has authorized the military in Afghanistan to continue to target Taliban fighters next year, a move that broadens the scope of the training mission that is to begin in 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 17:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. national security often trumps liberty - U.S. government censored newspapers and magazines while conducting prosecutions of the war's critics, sending more than 1,500 to prison with lengthy sentences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 17:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two British newspaper bosses claim that national security services prevented them from publishing allegations of a government pedophile ring in the 1980s on the grounds that it was intelligence that might damage national security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 12:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two British newspaper bosses claim that national security services prevented them from publishing allegations of a government pedophile ring in the 1980s on the grounds that it was intelligence that might damage national security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 12:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-CBS Reporter Sharyl Attkisson Shares New Revealing Emails From Govt Official: Shes Out of Control | Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 13:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Networks Divided On Use of Term Illegal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 13:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Obama administration has released five Guantanamo Bay prisoners after an administration task force determined they no longer posed a threat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 12:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police Arrest 19-year-old Terror Suspect at Heathrow Airport </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 12:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Police Will Be Allowed To Remove Terror Suspects From Their Homes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 02:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Police Spied on Reporters for Years, Docs Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 02:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AT T Challenges Government's Warrantless Acquisition Of Cell Site Location Data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 22:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new report shows the global cost of obesity has risen to $US2 trillion ($A2.2 trillion) annually - nearly as much as smoking or the combined impact of armed violence, war and terrorism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 18:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nick Clegg has conceded that the new counter-terror bill to be published next week will include a power to force terrorism suspects to relocate to another part of Britain, dropping previous opposition to the measure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 18:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A group of journalists has launched a legal action against Scotland Yard after discovering that the Metropolitan police has been recording their professional activities on a secret database designed to monitor so-called domestic extremists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 01:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL, J. Edgar Hoover, the first director of the FBI, made it one of his mission to spy on movie stars, politicians and prophets, including the likes of Charlie Chaplin, Marcus Garvey and Martin Luther King Jr. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 11:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Posting Pictures Of Homeland Security Trucks On Facebook, Man Fired And Called A Terrorist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 10:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI recruitment panel disrupted by FSU students - The students educated those present about the FBI use of intimidation, spying and raids to repress activism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 12:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the FBIs Suicide Note to MLK Still Matters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 12:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 25-year-old man arrested by anti-terror officers has been released without charge, police said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 11:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scotland Yard has launched an investigation into claims that a child was killed by a pedophile ring with high-level connections to the British government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 23:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter MacKays online spying Bill C-13 will enable authorities to monitor the private lives of innocent Canadians, without any real oversight. It will give telecom providers legal immunity for handing over your private information to the government without a warrant and without any oversight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 21:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal judge criticises FBI for alleged witness tampering in Oklahoma City bombing lawsuit | US news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 13:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judicial Watch sues feds for prying into the nation's newsrooms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 13:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The rhetoric of the War on Terror is akin to terrorism itself - The word terrorism has become meaningless, used by the United States government to support a perpetual war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 13:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big ISPs to Add 'Report a Terrorist' Button and Block Related Websites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 01:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll trolls' GCHQ script sock puppets manipulate muppets - Researchers also found separate puppet armies influencing articles on Reddit, CNN, Al Jazeera and the Jerusalem Post generated by simplistic means that admins appeared unable to identify </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 12:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSNI silent over spying on media: Force refuses to say if it used RIPA anti-terror laws to snoop on Northern Ireland journalists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 12:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the larger stains the FBI has ever had to endure on its not-so-spotless record was revealed in its entirety Thursday. A letter asking Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. to kill himself - signed, sealed and delivered by J. Edgar Hoover's FBI. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 12:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-terror bill trades freedom for illusion of security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 13:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: California Cities Spent $65M On Spy Gear In Past Decade With Almost No Oversight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 10:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI's "Suicide Letter" to Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., and the Dangers of Unchecked Surveillance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 10:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ACLU lawsuit says journalist was arrested for photographing police during Ferguson protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 10:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Student jailed for anti-monarchy Facebook message </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 10:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massachusetts town first to ban all tobacco products </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 10:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYC police to stop arresting people for simple pot possession, reports say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 09:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This happened: "Code Names of the Surveillance State" on Parliament </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 16:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britain Poised to Muzzle 'Extremist' Speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 15:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The latest government report detailing the numbers of "sneak and peek" warrants reveals that out of a total of over 11,000 sneak and peek requests, only 51 were used for terrorism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 15:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anatomy of a Drone Porn: Drone Boning Makes Sex Look Like Art </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 08:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Up-vote all you want, but the Internet isnt a democracy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 07:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So Far Feds Have Only Confirmed Seizing 27 "Dark Market" Sites In Operation Onymous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 07:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Night Time Eiffel Tower Photos Are a Copyright Violation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 18:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Up-vote all you want, but the Internet isnt a democracy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 14:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puxton Park: Single adults are banned - in case they are a paedophile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 10:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the government is tricking you into submission on its data spying laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 09:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US military sends one of its longest-held prisoners at Guantanamo Bay back home to Kuwait </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 13:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Destroying online freedom in the name of counter-terrorism will make the world a more dangerous place </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 12:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man who owns a smart TV says hes afraid of using it after reading its privacy policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 00:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California Just Became the First State to Defelonize Drug Use | VICE | United States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 00:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scots police to reveal use of anti-terror laws to spy journalists | Glasgow   West </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 11:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Court Says By Agreeing To AOL's Terms Of Service, You've 'Consented' To Search By Law Enforcement | Techdirt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 00:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australian Federal Police: We Could Use Metadata To Prosecute Pirates [Update] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 00:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 90-year-old, minister arrested for feeding the homeless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 10:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An obscure clause in EU copyright rules means no one can publish photos of public buildings in Belgium, like the Atomium, or Frances Eiffel tower at night without first asking permission from the rights owners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 10:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Telephone-data-sharing partnership involving 5 Virginia cities raises privacy concerns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 01:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
