<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject757</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's the best man for the job in Trump's eyes. They would fight any pick he put forward though obviously. They know they can't win the vote but they are going to literally pout and throw tantrums for the maximum time allowed by law. 

Imagine if they acted like adults and actually operated with some strategy and finesse to push their agenda and get some wins for their supporters? Imagine how suave these people could be if they were skilled at their jobs. They could negotiate deals that had winning aspects for both sides while looking like mature informed adults. 

Instead we have this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's the "top cop". Isn't going to happen without him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're calling the game a little early. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you claiming NGO-Monitor is inaccurate? 

I wasn't making a judgement call based on their Israel position, but only that it gave me a clue where it might lead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Don't believe everything you hear](http://i.imgur.com/TKy7u23.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understandable. Tofu betrayal is among the worst.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their source: "Given that Amnesty International has been barred by the Syrian authorities from entering the country and has consequently not had access to government-controlled areas since 2011, the majority of these interviews were carried out in southern Turkey. The remaining interviews were conducted by telephone or through other remote means with interviewees in Syria, or with individuals based in Lebanon, Jordan, European countries and the USA"

Who funds these guys? Nothing comes for free...

http://www.ngo-monitor.org/ngos/amnesty_international/

Firmly anti-Israel...that's a clue...let's keep digging.

Ahh, here we go, back to where we started as usual. Hi George Soros!

https://www.opensocietyfoundations.org/about/programs/us-programs/grantees/amnesty-international-usa-0
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any voting related search in this sub should prove as evidence they were doing a shit job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/offbeat?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, heck of a compilation of arrests at the bottom. 

Good list of names to keep handy and cross reference as more names pop up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the source](http://archive.is/dyLv3). Everyone else on youtube is just reading this to you while they sell ads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it that time of day for this post again? Can I just link [yesterday's](https://www.reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/5smocl/why_pizzagate_is_a_psyop_is_a_psyop/ddg9snv/) and be done with it please?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not really looking for truth and transparency from him. I'm trying to figure out if he got high, drank some whiskey and said a little more than he was supposed to in regards to something he does actually know about due to the fact that got dropped on his doorstep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High Alex Jones says "we screwed it up and released it early" in regards to Wikileaks. Could he be referring to pizzagate and the reason he scrubbed it from his website? Is this an indicator that Alex, Milo and Ben have all been sequestered by the "good guys" and something big is about to hit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without a doubt. There is some truth to the more you say it, the more true it becomes. It's the same tactic folks are using to normalize violence against those they disagree with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###It's a post for /r/bad_cop_no_donut at best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure what the conspiracy is, but the author discredits themselves immediately by leading with her profession as if it was relevant. He then cherry picks salacious points from the complaint written by her lawyer and doesn't offer any insight into what may have actually transpired.

Court complaints are intentionally biased for the plaintiff and make great source material if you want to write an article that reflects that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure I agree. They make huge ad buys that go across "all types" of media so this was likely some young technical guy that thought he was being clever at an agency than a direct order from Trump to spread propaganda across the land which I think is the level of drama I think is being displayed here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think this contributed substantially to her positive nomination? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate articles like this. He's so dramatic that he obscures his point. People need to learn some basic writing skills.

 "Things Will Get Worse Until US Stops Lying About Crimea"

What "things"? How will they get worse? This is the premise the headline promises.

  Russia seized Crimea narratives  become acknowledged to be lies

What? I didn't realize this was up for debate It's not like another country that wasn't Russia annexed Crimea.  [Here is Putin on video stating](http://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-31796226):

"I invited the leaders of our special services and the defence ministry to the Kremlin and set them the task of saving the life of the president of Ukraine, who would simply have been liquidated," he said.

"We finished about seven in the morning. When we were parting, I told all my colleagues, 'We are forced to begin the work to bring Crimea back into Russia'." 

Another video where Putin addresses it in the first question: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P0stuDpk318

 Anyone who is closed-minded to the possibility that the U.S. is lying and that Russia is telling the truth about the relationship between the two countries, would therefore be simply wasting time to read here, because the solid documentation that will be provided here will prove that thats not only a possibility; it is the fact, and those widespread false beliefs will, indeed, be disproven here.

I guess we're done "here" then since "solid documentation" is not provided "here" as he indicates. He rambles on for a good bit longer and I almost read  it all but his point is so detached from any other sources, including his own, that it's tough to follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They sound like a solid group:

"The MEK long has cultivated a roster of former U.S. and European officials to attend its events opposing Irans clerically-run government." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 04:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have wondered the same but it helps my perspective to see this posted by someone like you. It tells me that it's a topic in your propaganda stream and offers some indication of the source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. I've been discounting her and I'm embarressed to say I confused her with Sheila Jackson Lee. 

This woman is woke as fuck, always has been and she has paid the price for it. Looking back at what she has been saying for years should inspire us all. She deserves some serious recognition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect the details were life or death and there was likely a high risk highwire act to get to where we are...and he's got he hand extended and about to jump to the platform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think about any of these guys, you wouldn't expect them to fall into line if someone threatened them. Then again, if a friendly says "help us save the kids" then they all fall into line immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really hit me hard tonight how strong and deep this cross section of thought is. I want to believe it's the final cards, but honestly, if it happens, it will be the first time we've breached the wall and will finally get a glance of what's inside. 

I've been doing this for too long to pretend I can even pretend to imagine or comprehend the level of depth or complexity of connections that are likely involved in this. We're just getting started and this journey will last many years and change the course of human history in a similar magnitude as a world war.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh Ben oh Ben, where art thou oh Ben? 

Hope you're safe. 

Part of me does want to find solace in Alex Jones, Milo and Ben all closing up shop immediately after someone talked to them and I want to believe the conversation went like "we're about to bust all these kidfuckers wide open so just chill for a few weeks so we can get our shit together". 

As we all know, Trump hates to give any sort of foreshadowing to justice being applied lest the baddies get in, get away, have any sort of advantage, etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want to hold hands and rock back and forth until it gets here? 

I almost do but I don't think it will make it happen faster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's keep perspective on how many of these arrests were prostitution stings vs. human trafficking busts. LA is being under reported because it is legit. Memphis shouldn't be portrayed in quite the same light. I want more info on Haiti and I want more fucking arrests! So...yeah, patience... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comey's still right in the middle of it all; his story is far from over. His actions may be justifiable in hindsight. We never truly know the pressures applied to a man. He may redeem himself yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Podesta's emails were not propaganda. They were inconvenient truths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except the part where there was no actual "hacking of the election". 

If you want to count the release of unflattering emails from the DNC or John Podesta as "hacking", then you should fault the security posture of either party and/or the parties of those that were dumb enough to put shit like that in writing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's such a drama queen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true. In the grand scheme of things there have been civilizations in history that have learned and forgotten 5 times more than America has. People haven't yet begun to experience how crazy this ride can be. We haven't had a massive social shift since the 60s so there's a couple of generations still trying to figure out which way is up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was talking to the wife about this tonight. If he really does frogmarch Chuck Schumer and some other notable lib leaders there will be a subsection of people that will insist in the face of all evidence that they are clearly innocent and victims of Trump's fantastic witch-hunt. 

Hopefully it doesn't cause things to escalate further. I hate to see harm come to people who's only mistake was being blinded by propaganda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their source: "Given that Amnesty International has been barred by the Syrian authorities from entering the country and
has consequently not had access to government-controlled areas since 2011, the majority of these
interviews were carried out in southern Turkey. The remaining interviews were conducted by telephone or
through other remote means with interviewees in Syria, or with individuals based in Lebanon, Jordan,
European countries and the USA"

Who funds these guys? Nothing comes for free...

http://www.ngo-monitor.org/ngos/amnesty_international/

Firmly anti-Israel...that's a clue...let's keep digging.

Ahh, here we go, back to where we started as usual. Hi George Soros!

https://www.opensocietyfoundations.org/about/programs/us-programs/grantees/amnesty-international-usa-0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feels like they missed the mark. Maybe they should have held off until people were actually being banned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just like your opinion man. /r/politics might be a better forum for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't /pol... it's /r/conspiracy. We try to source the bullshit we talk about, not just try to wish it into existence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this is /r/conspiracy, so you're welcomed to do that and post it here but you'll probably want to find some additional evidence.

We know what data is available, as summarized above, but really don't have much in the way of leads beyond what you see.

People come through here every day shopping for a narrative that's going to fit their political agenda but they usually leave disappointed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. We got it all in once place now or is there something new? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what else is to be said about Trump's ties to Epstein. 

We have the stories where they were acquaintances but the travel logs haven't shown his name to be there, There is hearsay from someone that says he saw him on the plane once but didn't talk to him and someone else that says he ate in Epstein's kitchen when he went to visit. 

There's a the quote where Trump speaks nicely of Epstein and calls him out for liking his girls young. There's the rumor that Epstein was banned from Mar-a-lago for hitting on a minor.

What else you got? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  At the same time, Dennis Hastert isn't really a pedophile. They just framed him so that his connections to the people implicated in pizzagate would seem even more suspicious.

Went off the tracks here. To quote the Judge at his trial, The defendant is a serial child molester. 

Quoting Mr. Hastert, I want to apologize to the boys I mistreated when I was their coach. What I did was wrong and I regret it.

Isn't this scenario fucked up enough already? Do you really think it needs to be further convoluted?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, this weird sociological experiment continues but it does have a shelf life.

Current institutions will either break down completely due to chasing the Marxist ideals or the house of cards will collapse under the pressure for all to see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I were shocked. They are everywhere.

There will be a lot of bias that want this guy's political beliefs to be intertwined with his perversion but it just doesn't matter what anyone thinks. Only their actions and the impact on someone else matter and people willing to act come from every variation of mindset.

There's a good chance that someone you know and like is a pedo. Don't let your guard down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder if they were having hotdogs for lunch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already had you tagged bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not even an article let lone a conspiracy.

Some random sick fuck wants to associate Trump and crushing kid's testicles to make that point that he "feels that Trump cant pull us out of NAFTA, because that was enacted by Congress, and he cant put a tariff on Mexican imports by himself. But he does think Trump can legally halt immigration from any countries he wants, although he believes Trump should be sure no one talks about it in public as a Muslim ban.

There used to be art in this sort of stuff but now it's coming across like the work of a high schooler that just remembered his book report was due and slapped it together at lunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you have a Starbucks to go trash?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oversight Committee. "Jason can investigate anything he wants to. The President said so".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 12:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should he reject SS protection (not even sure that's an option) or just sit quietly in a locked room for the next 8 years because it might cost money to protect him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whichever one gives Israel the most latitude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they have already issued a retraction for the fake news report this fake news was based on. Can count on Allie to get it posted though. Fuck Trump! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a plugin to what they call the [HBSS Suite](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Host_Based_Security_System#How_HBSS_works) but it can be deployed as a standalone product. I don't run the desktop stuff. There's always Bitlocker from MS which is built into Windows or PGP though I'm not sure how it has faired under Symantec.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aware. Do you think everyone associate with the company is a pedo?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice that one of David Brock's crew could to take time off from fucking kids to write this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too "quietly" work at my job and would legally disclose it if required. 

"Advisory roles" are extremely common for former military and usually revolve around they idea that they can call up their buddies that are still in and get a meeting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can tell you with first hand experience that the NSA does not have that visibility nor would they spend the compute to figure it out for some schmuk that forgot his password.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say that as it is tested, the crypto has been validated (FIPS), trusted and successfully deployed on millions of machines that see some real world shit. 

I'm an encryption professional that linked a pretty comprehensive list and said what I personally use. It's a data point. Do whatever the fuck you want from there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea to build a small shelter for 20 people. No one wants them to sit in the cold. 

However, 20 plane tickets would be an even more reasonable solution that could be provided today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have long theorized there's more to this story but I always assumed a pedo angle. This is an interesting perspective on the story. Good find.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many options. 

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Comparison_of_disk_encryption_software

I have been running McAfee full disk for years which is the the solution most of the US Gov. uses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how long the MSM will continue to operate as a political party of their own. I can't imagine it will be long before they actually do start to fear for their safely and will regret crying wolf all the times before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try searching or paying more attention. So much astroturfing in here you aren't going to see any topic anywhere for too long. I stand by my original comment; every single day, almost the identical post, same sources.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Helps when the Dems literally are pouting and won't show up to work to do their jobs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We see the same post, same sources, every day for weeks. The conversation has been had. Bring new data for a new conversation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit...474 arrested over a weekend and they are just getting started.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a terrible article. He can't get past his snark enough to even make it intelligible. Old shit too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he needs help, I'll volunteer to go over and help take it off his hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Will companies die from this? No.
 
 
 
 Will companies lose customers from this? Doubtful.
 
 
 
 Will companies lose revenue from this? Doubtful.

If you're gitlab, I would say the points above will apply. No doubt about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's more to be known. Too many secrets around the secret leaker. 

If I had data to share that might endanger my life, I would not share it with WL at this point. Transparency is required.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologize to whom? Did someone get their feelings hurt because people were concerned about the source of data that affects the entire planet? 

We still don't know the full story of his hide and seek time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I missed the Supreme Court ruling on this EO. Not sure what religion has to do with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting and timely. Good post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crusade.

If you're watching the nature channel and you see two groups of animals fighting with each other, let's say elephants and lions, why are they fighting? Is it for survival or do you think the elephants are racist against the lions or vice versa?  Should one side win over the other? Is there a moral question? Do you think there is there evil in it? Which group has the 'right' to live the way they choose?

What will be the reality for the winner/loser regardless of what you think?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least you're consistent.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least you're consistent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comment history full of telling people how old and wise you are and how stupid and foolish they are. If only everyone could have the breadth of wisdom that you do then this world would be different...

Or perhaps not as this story has been replaying the same episode for the past 1400 centuries. If you're hung up about the shade of skin color of the people that want you dead, I think I'm going to pass on your brand of 'wisdom'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone hates a centrist in practice. They stand in the middle trying to angle for moral superiority over both sides while not accomplishing anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put your bag of bricks down. The war is with people that think Western culture is subhuman and want you dead. 

Take the thing that pisses you off the most; the backwoods American, racist, intolerant, religious fanatic that you know Russia manipulated to get Trump elected, and add a flair for creative homicide of everyone that they disagree with and might start to appreciate the mindset of the people that live only to see Jewish genocide.

This is the sort of thing that no one can tell you though. You have to look at evidence, read a little history and come to your own conclusions. When you realize this is the same story has been reoccurring the past 14 centuries, you can read ahead and see how it ends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, this post again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It [will start a war](http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/01/embassy-relocation-jerusalem-war-crime-170129072749859.html) which will give the US an excuse to finish it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read the Bible? Bannon, via Trump, is fulfilling prophecy. The wrath of God is quite present throughout; it was Jesus that was the nice guy. 

The 10th Crusade will kick off officially when the US Embassy is moved to Jerusalem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fat chance. Everyone knows what a freak Schmidt is, sex parties and all. He'll be used like the tool he is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 4 day old account posting this drivel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No participation trophies. Do the work or GTFO of the way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clear concerted effort across reddit...plus a bunch of retarded kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean the new Chief Conspiracy Theorist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a well informed mofo - respect your elders punk! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chief Conspiracy Theorist is finally a cabinet level position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said on the Deep State. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or if you're a young male from a country where jihad is a national pastime then we're going to need an extra minute to figure out how and if you're going to adjust to the laws of the land. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much - but you might want to put your seatbelt on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a couple hundred Arabic names that should never have entered America in the first place.

This dude was a Somalia refugee, lucky they didn't include 2016 I guess: http://www.businessinsider.com/who-is-osu-attacker-abdul-artan-2016-11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because those are laughable bullshit numbers you just made up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck Al Gore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's such a clear giveaway when someone thinks your mind can be changed after you've gotten a glimpse of the truth. They have no idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they didn't defame people then it would not be an issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 13:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is my point. Why are you making stupid comments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Trump fan, he would probably be down with it. It's all about keeping the positive momentum going. It's not like he's ever been anything but completely upfront about his zionist views. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President of the United States says "Do whatever you have to do within the confines of the law". End of fucking story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for posting. 

I hope they can tidy this line up a little. 

"The attack lasted for about 20 seconds, and in that short amount of time a group of teens was about to do some serious damage."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
