<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8593</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 15:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I never thought of posting over there! I'm subscribed to that sub too! Thank you for recommending! I will certainly be posting over there when I get the chance! :) And thank you for your compliments too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 15:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw, thank you so much for the compliment! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 15:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, thank you so much for your kind words and support! If money weren't a necessity I would make these and give them away for free. The sheer joy I get from creating them and seeing how much they make other people happy is enough of a reward. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 15:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're insanely priced! The Brother machine that sells for 800 here can be bought for 200 in the US. It's a ridiculous mark up! I bought this one: http://www.overstock.com/Crafts-Sewing/Brother-HE1-Embroidery-Machine-Refurbished/8261670/product.html?refccid=AY2U2FBVW7HJB5CJ6LAXU7TIWQ searchidx=2

You pay a small custom fee on purchase (around 20) so that when it gets imported you don't have to pay the 40% import tax! It runs beautifully and the only issue is that with it being an American product you need to buy a conversion adapter. I picked one up for 25 on amazon and it's been perfect. 

So even with the added import fee, the delivery cost and the price of the adapter, I ended up spending less than half of the UK price. 

Ahh it's shame you're so far from uni and have no way to transport it! The offer still stands if you get to uni and decide you want it though! I can't recommend http://www.plushaddict.co.uk/ enough for when you're on the search for fabric!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw, thank you so much for the compliments and kind words! I'm sorry to hear that your facing depression too, I really hope that you come out of the other end smiling! It's a long dark road, but there is an end! :) 

I currently donate a small amount to a rabbit rescue sanctuary and live off of the sales, so I'm hoping to be able to give to the mental health community when I'm a bit more financially stable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for your compliments!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blushing, blushing! Thank you ever so much!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! I'm actually donating small amounts of money to a rabbit rescue sanctuary at the moment and also living on the sales - so I'm not financially able to donate any to a hospital. I really hope to be able to do so when I get back on my feet though! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will! :) I'm hoping to have them ready for September/October time, for the Halloween and Christmas rush! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Sewing isn't too difficult to get into! You can teach yourself! I had no knowledge of sewing prior to all of this and just plunged myself into the deep end. 

Buy some cheap fabric (fleece is especially good!) and thread, search out a simple plush pattern online and give it a go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I wish you luck with getting through your hard times too! Crafting is a great medicine. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so, so much! 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I like how he came out. :) I really hope to make a terriermon when I have some free time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 14:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that sounds simply adorable! Is it the teacup bunny style you're wanting? I can certainly do that. If you send me a picture of the blanket and what exactly you want doing with it, where you want the fabric on the bunny - whether just as accents, or the entire thing, what colours etc etc, we can talk more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
