<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4589</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 02:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sajjs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 02:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ASD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 02:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DASAD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 00:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ASd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 00:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> adD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 00:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> asd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 23:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The government is set too look like a militarised insurance company that owns a few hospitals if the Tories win </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 23:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reforms promised today could appeal to UKIP voters. You can trace one nation toryism to Disraeli, who wanted the Tories to be "the party of the masses, not the classes". What Cameron did in 2010 was appeal to those deplorable pansy middle-class people who care about things like the environment. By doing so, he lost Redtop Tories to UKIP and this manifesto is made to win them back (note how much Islam was mentioned today) while being vauge enough to appeal to regular swing voters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 23:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canadian politics are generally more right-wing than British politics. The Liberal Party is probably more akin to New Labour--does whatever it can to get the vote, turning its back on climate change just because its electorally popular. The NDP seem to be close to the bleeding heart of Labour: big on public services, hates right-wing politics with a vengence, willing to make a principled stand. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 06:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
 Also, seriously, how many people do this?! That's a far bigger issue that drug legalisation, that's full on child abuse. 

How many people buy alcohol for children? More harmful drug, same principle. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 06:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it will increase usage and thus addiciton and thus OD cases  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 06:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Far less money spent on the police, prison and legal system

Probably cancelled out by AandE admissions, therapy and addiction seminars. There could also be regulatory disputes depending on how its implemented: is someone carrying more coke than they would need to in public

 Greatly reduced levels of crime especially organised crime

Seems to be happening anyway. There 

http://www.economist.com/news/briefing/21582041-rich-world-seeing-less-and-less-crime-even-face-high-unemployment-and-economic

 economic growth from a new industry and subsequent taxation 

The only way that this would be important enough to impact the debate would be if exise duties were placed on all drugs similar to alcohol. In that case you admit that we should discourage people from using drugs and they are bad.

 Reduction in accidental deaths due to improved drug quality and transparency of substances  

Mmh not necessarily. Colorado has seen a massive proliferation of weed because the government legitimised it and because all sorts of new users were trying it. There were then more vehicle accidents, children taking the drug and people just freaking out because they took too much. If we suddenly unleashed harder drugs on the public then we would certainly see more deaths because nobody would understand how to use them properly and they wouldn't know social conventions. 

 Drug addicts receive treatment instead of a sentence that makes finding work extremely hard making them a burden to society

Lots of needle exchange programmes, drug treatment programmes, amnesty programs. If you get caught for possession, you're not really going get a fine and a policie caution, not a jail sentence. 

 Reduction in prescription overdoses

Where did this come from? 

 The availability of drugs other than alcohol will lead to a reduction in alcohol related crime and accidents (IMO) 

And just subsitute it for another kind of crime? Acid is a different beast to weed, which is different to stims, which are different to alcohol. You use them for different purposes and the liklihood is that people will mix them with alcohol. 

 Decreases the availability of these drugs for children  

No way, edibles might even get banned in Colorado! I seriously doubt that an average 15 year old could get his hands on MDMA easily as it is right now. If it was legalised, he could just take some from daddy's cabinet. 


Some other problems: 

- Big drug companies akin to big tobacco 

Tobacco and alcohol companies make most of their money off frequent users. Drug companies would try and do the same, addiction would be in their every interest. 

- Drug tourism 

The Dutch hate us. Can you imagine people across Europe coming to your town for stag doos? You might say it brings in money but I don't think that measures with the shame that comes with being a drug haven. 

- People are stupid 

Out of the people I know, loads would get PTSD from bad trips. It's easy to die from plenty of other drugs too and it would be hard to caution them 

- Public nuisances 

I get freaked out by meth-heads and people on coke. Day time users would make things more dangerous as oppose to drunks that are mostly confined 

- Dependency 

It's absolutely awful to see people get hooked on drugs. As it is, drug use is falling so why take the risk?

- Drugs will affect the poorest the most 

You would only resort to drugs if your life was so stressful you needed to escape. Cigs are smoked by poor people and their health and income are taxed because of it. Drug legalisation would increase drug usage and thus entrench itself in certain communities. Working-class mothers would be more likely to, say smoke weed during pregnancy thus genetically altering the lives of kids. This would clearly exasperate inequality. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 05:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the Republican party exist in a strange place on the political spectrum. You get the occasional *libertarian* in parliament or in the european parliament or in eastern european countries or in australia, but the Republican party as a whole seem to think the state is evil rather than inefficient. I wouldn't call them Conservatives because they are just too ideological, I wouldn't call them nationalists because they love to intervene abroad. I wouldn't call them fascist either because they're overtly colourblind. I wouldn't call them libertarians because they thrive on power. I have no idea where they stand relative to european parties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 17:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'The Palestinians' that's pretty racist - it's the equivalent of saying 'the jews are zionists' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 17:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The UN Convention on the Rights of the Child defines a child as everyone under 18 unless, "under the law applicable to the child, majority is attained earlier" (Office of the High Commissioner for Human Rights, 1989). The UK has ratified this convention.

Take a look at article 12. Nothing in there says human beings in this arbitrary and dependent category human maturity should not be able to vote.

If we're going to lower it to when you gain responsibilities, perhaps it should be lowered to the age of 10, that's the age of criminal responsibility (8 in Scotland though).

Just because something has an arbitrary, socially constructed approximate cut-off line doesn't mean it does not exist. There is a debate about maturity to be had in the UK and the fact that it's ambiguous does not make it less valid a debate. 

 Woah, when did the UK Government policy become affiliated with the American company LinkedIn.

It's a broader observation about childhood maturity 


I have no idea what criteria you think makes someone eligible to take part in the political process, but I suggest you look into the arguments made about how the vote was won and extended. All the arguments about why propertied men, women, disabled persons sounded extremely similar to the arguments you are raising.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 14:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By that metric votes for women were gerrymandering. This is a value judgement, its not being kept in secret, its a policy held by other parties too and its just incomparable to the way in which ethnic minorities are deliberately cornered off in the US into inconsequential districts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 14:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  he'll be restrained substantially by the Blairite faction of the Labour party.

Wait, how so? Isn't it more likely he will rely on SNP votes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 14:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be the freedom of the press to not live up to its own standards of ethical behaviour and the freedom to hide corrections about blatent lies in small print nobody will read then? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 14:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No - they have the same idea about anti-corruption populism, hitting financial institutions, rebalancing society.  Ed's plans are more dramatic, but are apparently going unnoticed here while Warrens are less ambitious but get attention all over the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 14:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could argue that keeping it at 18 means the same. Gerrymandering is about manipulating borders - moving people who live in certain areas to places where their vote doesn't count. MPs don't crate their own boundaries, the boundary commission does so its impossible under our system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 13:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? I think they have the same outlook on the world: one will just exist as an armchair theorist, one will put progressive populist ideas into action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 13:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get your first point, but even now Milliband seems to have a prospectus that is very similar to what Warren has been talking about for a long time. It should be exciting to see this I think.


 I also think you need to very careful not to fool yourself into thinking that /r/politics and /r/ukpolitics are in anyway representative of the real world. They represent a infinitesimally small sample of very young, tech savvy, left leaning idealists.

Maybe my point was broader: if you compare Cameron vs Obama's approval ratings you get very similar numbers. If you compare voter turnout, you get similar number. If you compare the number of people who think their country is in decline you get similar numbers. 

Yes reddit may be a small sample of the population, but I think its politics are representative of how people think in general. Everything is always shite wherever you are (in the west) and whoever comes first in the election, the government will always win. It disturbs me that such low esteem exists right now: what will we think if we ever get the US standards?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 13:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're quite right: that is a massive structural failure of our system. In a lot of countries however, Gerrymandering is an issue and it feels much worse if boundaries can be deliberately manipulated to get a certain outcome vs a bad system failing across the board. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 11:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm not talking about Jim Murphy, but the party at large. Incidentally, Murphy does not sound like a Blairite anymore - call it disingenuous but he is running a left-of-centre campaign.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 10:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. I have a leftish bent as well, not Scottish so I can't say what I'd think of the SNP. I wonder though why people on the liberal-left tend to be the most cynical about politics. If there isn't any trust in the government, there won't be enough public confidence in the government to do positive things like nationalise the north sea oil supply or expand the NHS and  the people mostly likely to change things in a progressive direction and won't vote or get involved in the political process at all. 

Labour have decisively moved to the left as well, I'm not sure why the Greens and Scottish Nationalists are taking off now Labour is talking about things like inequality. They're moving to the left but they don't seem to be winning back any voters. Why is it that the SNP are taking off now, not during the Blair Premiership (when the two parties were legitimately very similar and westminster-centric)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 10:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  She - if magically transferred into British politics - would probably be a Tory. 

I think that's a bit disingenuous really. You sound like a disillusioned voter though; how can you depart from mainstream politics if you know what a system that *really* sold out would look like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 10:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for coming down a bit too much. I actually just [posted a thread](http://www.reddit.com/r/ukpolitics/comments/32f3ze/why_isnt_there_the_same_enthusiasm_for_ed/) or /r/ukpolitics about this. If [poke around some news sites](http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/election/2015) and learn about our election I'd be interested to see what American redditors think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 10:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither has Warren - we've essentially got a candidate that combines the best of Hillary (experience, connections, insider information) with the passion and the policies of Warren. 

Seriously we're the same kinds as the Americans that are on reddit and we have broadly the same political outlook. Over at /r/politics people dream of a country that isn't militaristic, has strict campaign financing rules, free health, no deadlock, multiple parties, a balanced press and politicians with an almost exact prospectus as Labour, yet we still manage to moan here. 

I take your point about the insider effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 09:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right but the presidential system is so integral to America that you'd have to shred up the entire constitutions. What would we teach in schools? America: the story of a country that flees a despotic parliamentary system, becomes the most powerful nation on earth and then goes back to the exact system it sought to avoid? 

How would anything even remotely close to that be achievable when Republicans scream about the constitution as soon as something as trivial as gun laws are change? 

The other thing is that the people themselves aren't going to get any smarter by changing the way capitol hill works. Australia have a similar system to what you're proposing and, well you can head over to /r/australia to see that they're suffering the equivalent of an unchecked GOP government going wild with climate legislation, patronage, spending cuts etc. North of the border, Stephen Harper is fucking over Canada in a parliamentary system too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why isn't there the same enthusiasm for Ed Miliband here as there is for Elizabeth Warren on /r/politics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 09:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, we're talking about two Harvard former professors running on an anti-corruption populist-progressive platform. Their policies are almost exactly alike: act on inequality, lower student debt, break up the banks and seriously crack down on corruption. 

[Search through /r/politics](http://www.reddit.com/r/politics/search?q=Warren restrict_sr=on sort=relevance t=all) and Warren is held up as the champion of ordinary people every single day. I've read dozens of times today that she should be running against Hillary for the presidency. 

Yet when I come to /r/ukpolitics, I see an equally ambitious politician that  is willing to talk about things most others don't (taking on Murdoch, Palestinian Statehood) with a very real chance of becoming our next Prime Minister. 

More broadly might point is that  that we have a political system American redditors dream of: Conservative party that accepts climate change and isn't ideologically obsessed, campaign spending limits and actual independent minded MPs that don't consult their donors before every single decision, multiple parties , no bullshit deadlock and legislation that actually passes, the chance to grill politicians in person etc yet nobody seems to be saying how great we have it. 


Maybe that was an incoherent ramble, but the point I'm trying to make is that we talk about politics in the most despairing terms possible when really we have it very very good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 08:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Just look around the western world at all of the other parties that can be elected to government: Greens, Socialist, Far-right, Far-left, Pirates, Monster Raving Loony, Right/Left Nationalists, People Power Populists, etc. etc

The beauty of congress is that 535-party system. A Georgia Democrat is going to be very different from a California Democrat, a Maine Republican is going to be very different from an Alabama Republican. We're living through pretty partisan times, but for the most part America has one of the least whipped, most accountable systems going. 

I don't know how having a third party would help anything anyway. It would just add confusion to the law making process and we'd see even less legislation. Similarly, if we saw Gary Johnson or Jill Stein win the presidency they wouldn't be able to set  a workable legislative agenda and they would have to act in the national interest abroad (basically carrying the same policies out as a republican/dem might). There would be nobody to defend them in congress any people wouldn't be able to rally around them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 00:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but the reason our tax rate never exceeds 50% is because after that point less revenue is generated and things like brain drain start to kick in. Look at Francois Hollande's supertax of this variety if you want to see how ineffective it can be.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 03:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Libertarian solution to climate change is to stop socializing the environment (as all government environmental protection organizations do), and to allow individuals to properly punish polluters through a justice system.

Question is how do you stake a sufficient claim to part of the environment? Nobody can own a common asset that everyone depends on. How would we divy up the sea and how who could justifiably stake a claim that, say a natural resource company has made an infraction on their stake in the sea? How about space, are we to distribute specfic parts of the near-universe to specific people? How about air - are we to make oxygen a buy able asset?


 Pollution is a violation of the NAP; it is therefore legitimate to punish polluters. Alternatively, you can change the behavior of polluters by refusing to purchase their products. Many corporations have 'gone green' due to consumer demand. Intel, Apple, Google, Starbucks, etc.

Lots of these companies greenwash. They may make their internal opperations more environmentally friendly, but still buy from third party distributors that cause actually contribute the most to climate change. As a consumer, I have no stake in knowing how anything I own has changed hands and where it has originally come from. A company could install a solar panel on its roof and change their distribution contract to an extremely environmentally unfriendly firm and still claim that they are doing a good thing for the environment. 

There are so many contradictions with consumer power; Bill Gates might be known for being a superb guy with his charitable foundation, but most people don't know that he has lots of dodgy investments in fossil fuel companies that go some way to causing the problems he talks about. 

Ultimately, the burden should not be on the consumer to check up on the bad behavior of the firm. Boycotts rarely work and it would be impossible for me to spend all my time researching whether or not a firm is ethical before deciding to buy things as basic as sugar and flour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 02:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Am I alone in thinking these policies seem mostly reasonable?

The womens' prison policy is just lunacy and the citizens income proposal is downright unworkable

 In fact, their opposition to nuclear power is one of the two main reasons I'm voting for them

Why do you oppose nuclear power? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 22:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Labour minority or Lib-Lab coalition. The SNP are frighteningly populist and their policies aren't costed or held up to much scrutiny. I think our current arrangements with Scotland are fine and I don't want it to be a money sink when places like North Wales, Lancashire and Yorkshire are in serious need of government money.

I think a lib-lab coalition is the most likely scenario. Labour could threaten the Lib Dems with a left-wing SNP coalition and the lib dems would be forced to move the government to the center. If the Lib Dems stayed with the Tories, then they'd essentially be saying that they are Tory light and they don't care about the fact that the majority of people are more left wing than right wing but get screwed over by FPTP. Also, it's probably the best way to get a government that supports civil liberties--this is one of the selling points of the Lib Dems and Ed Miliband was an opponent of ID cards at the time. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 00:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me sad to image what the news will be like when the queen dies :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "One man will not satisfy every person in the country--impossible." 

The problem is that outside of Reddit, Libertarianism is not a popular idea. Libertarianism does not transcend left-right politics, it does not combine the most popular parts of social liberalism and economic conservertism. I think this is the biggest falling point here and it's something Libertarians need to realize. Lets take the world's smallest quiz: 

"Government should not censor speech, press, media, or internet."  That sounds nice but the implication is "Government should not restrict the distribution of indecent pornography nor remove radicalizing and terror influences from circulation"

"Military service should be voluntary. There should be no draft."  Means that there should be no draft in total war 

"There should be no laws regarding sex for consenting adults." Legalize Prostitution without any regulation

"Repeal laws prohibiting adult possession and use of drugs." Legalize Meth and remove all regulations

"There should be no National ID card." Do not enforce everify, no background checks for migrant workers, no real check for terrorists entering the country

See it's nice to phrase things a certain way - thats how politics works but those things in combination only appeal to a few lets face it younger, wealthy white men without any obligations. 

On the point about the media blackout, I'm not sure what role the *state* has in stopping private companies doing what they want (which by the way is favoring sensationalist telegenic candidates). 

Ted Cruz upsets the status-quo, Bernie Sanders, Elizabeth Warren upsets the status quo and they get lots and lots of attention. Still, being generous to the blackout argument, if Paul got 1% of the coverage of the entire primary season he got hundreds of hours of coverage on our 24/7 news-media. I didn't see Romney become more libertarian because of Paul and I don't see our country getting more libertarian as a result of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 21:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly man you've got to take a step back and look at this from the perspective of the average voter and the GOP. Here we have a crusty old man that has a tendency to speak incoherent in a whiny sort of voice. His ideas are extreme, he looks to his ideology before he looks at the actual situation. The answer in absolutely to absolutely every single conceivable scenario is 'this is an issue for the private sector to think about'. If you're a pensioner relying on social security you're not going to take well to a man that wants to get rid of medicare and senior benefits. If you're a bleeding heart evangelical conservative you're not going to be happy when the guy says Israel is a war criminal. If you're a GOP donor you're not going to be happy with a man that wants to reduce capital investment. Most people look at the guy as if he's a crank who would go to the whitehouse, find out that the world is a complicated chessboard that could explode with any single move and have no idea what to do because he's blocked out every idea that uses the government instrument his entire life.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I physiologically 'feeling' depression in my body not just my mind? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 03:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had depression for 3 years now - my peak in the first two years was when I was diagnosed as 'moderately' depressed and prescribed a high dosage of sertraline. I eventually self-medicated and stopped taking them because I was secure, fulfilled and enjoying life for a long while. Since studying abroad, the depression came back and I'm now 'severely' depressed. I am on 300mg of Wellbutrine but it's gotten to the point where I have to garner the energy to even schedule another checkup with my doctor. I can't go through with therapy - last time (around December) I missed so many appointments and felt bad about it, I didn't do the exercises the therapist set and I didn't feel like it was very beneficial. 

My typical day looks like this: sleep in until the afternoon, go to class, come back a sleep a bit more, go to the library at around 6-7, procrastinate until around 11 then rush off whatever school work I have to do for tomorrow. I care deeply about my studies - I really want to do well, I love the stuff I'm learning but I pathologically procrastinate to the point where it's not even procrastination but self-sabotage. I then might go back and stay up until 2-4am, maybe smoke a joint and just waste more time on my computer. 

I think I understand depression - it's brought on by a dislocation of the self, it's bad because you have no agency or control over your life. The solution is simple: force yourself to do things you don't want to, be productive, fight back again your short-term impulses. It's no permanent solution, but it alleviates depression in the short-term. Your body tells you to take the path of least resistance - some days you can fight back but the black dog will always eventually be able to take you down after a while. I'm considering not even trying anymore and just doing everything I need to do while on vyvanse every other week. 

Anyway what I'm trying to ask is does the tiredness, the inertia, the lack of drive feel, the general fatigue feel like it's coming from the body rather than the mind for anyone else? It feels as I'm physically ill just as much as I am mentally ill. 

I don't know this post was too non-sequitur sorry I might go back and make it more logical in a bit. I normally make a shadow account for these posts but I can't be bothered.  I'm looking for any kind of insight, feel free to give advice, call me out, relate, whatever I won't be offended and honest opinions . cheers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Left my wellbutrine at college over spring break </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 07:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi it's currently 2.22 and I have to get a bus to DC for spring break at 6.30 tomorrow. I stupidly left my 300mg wellbutrine prescription at college and now I'm feeling everything from zero motivation to back pain to insomnia. 

This might be a more practical question than this sub normally gets but has anyone been through this? I'll be unable to get this for a week and last time I forgot to take pills for more than one day I fell asleep in public randomly and got shocks. It wasn't at all pleasant - I have a tonne of homework that I know needs to be done and I have motivation issues as it is! I'm 6000miles away from home, I'll be in a foreign city without any of my freinds for the next week and I'm freaking out as to how I'll be able to survive this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 21:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel exactly the same way mate. It's a group of guys that celebrate the exact tropes that shouldn't be celebrated. The pledging process means that those who care about their dignity the least rise to the top. Even with pressure to up grades to fall in line with university expectations, it's still a club for boys aren't at university to learn and have absolutely no productive interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 16:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 16:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 15:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 23:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for sharing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 23:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fine, I was wrong he was not a stock broker. Farage is now officially the authentic voice of Britain and all our problems would go away if we had more UKIP MPs. Happy now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
