<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8925</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 08:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A delusion of grandeur would be something like thinking that I am the most talented musician EVER and EVERYONE should be listening to me, or that I should be elected **president** because I know *exactly* how to fix the economy!!! It's very annoying to everyone else around me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 08:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point in my life, I find it very difficult to feel emotions in general. I find them very painful to experience and therefore don't really miss them. I've lived with this for years now, I've created coping techniques to avoid actually killing myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 08:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on them for four months, taking them every day. Mostly they made me lethargic - seroquil's an anti-psychotic given to epileptics to calm brain activity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 08:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not having any visual hallucinations now, but I did have auditory hallucinations last week. Whenever I was with my hallucinated friends, I could be seeing them any amount of time from a few minutes to a few days. The fact that they could disappear and reappear wasn't troubling to me at the time. They were incredibly vivid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 08:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually taken several psychology classes and own a few books on neuroscience. I'm well aware that it's merely a chemical imbalance in my brain. Knowing what is happening doesn't make my crazy any better.

**Edit**: This is what I mean by stigmatized, the fact that someone just assumes that I don't have an excellent grasp of my own mental health. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
