<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4368</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great. Too bad they spent $100+ dollars to do that when a Raspberry pi would have done the exact same thing for a fraction of the cost. I never understood why these things were so popular seeing as there are almost limitless ways to play these games for much cheaper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to point out that very few Fallout fans that I know had anything bad to say about New Vegas. It was a masterpiece in my eyes and probably the best out of the FPS Fallouts. Fallout 4 felt like all the fun things like fluid and intertwining speech trees, exploration and cool, unique knick knacks scattered about the map were replaced with simplistic and insulting speech choices (high speechcraft literally does nothing but net you caps), focused and trailored exploration (very little to no incentive to explore) and the fact that finding a unique item or weapon felt meaningless when killing a random legendary ghoul could get you the exact same (or better) item. It made exploration feel empty and conversations always felt like I knew where it was going to go regardless of what I said. Even the choices you made until the end felt meaningless when it felt like no matter what you did the outcome didn't feel rewardng. Like the meme says, it's not a bad game. By no means is it bad. It's great. But definitely the weakest of the Fallout series. It's very neutered version of the series meant to pull in Fps players or kids that may not have touched a Fallout game otherwise. If anyone ever asked me, "is Fallout 4 any good?" I'll says, "Yea, but I recommend playing New Vegas if you haven't. It's the best one there is." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2000 SR but my stats say otherwise. Looking for a permanent team. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been solo queueing and lfg since I got the game a couple months ago. Most players I paly with say I have good stats (13 elim avg QP/22 elim avg COMP) and normally I try to match or come close (I'll play with 10s or 11s) but I still always feel like I'm doing all the work. For example, last comp match I played I did 40,402 damage and we still just drawed. I'm tired of this :/ I've been stuck at the same damn 2000 level I left placements with (all solo queueing). I'm looking for a group of decent players who may need a fairly good player (been playing fps since doommatch on modem circa 95ish?) Who is mature and capable but lacks a group a good friends to play with. 

I main DVA and Bastion and can play a mean 76. I also play Reinhardt if I have to. I'm not great but I can get the job done. I'm always looking to improve my game and I'm hoping to find some serious players.

Edit: I'm sorry this is for Xbox one!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 12:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "How did you get in the country?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A guy orders Tony Hawk cartridges. Mate swaps them with Madden carts. Hilarity ensues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 12:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YouTube is basically the Hollywood of the Internet, if you think about it. I think what it all boils down to is that someone is salty.  Someone made a comment along the lines that it's the equivalent of the stand up comedian doing clubs for years and never getting a break and then some kid blows up on the internet. I think that's why YouTube gets a bad rap. But don't act like there's not plenty of YouTubers out there that don't get the exposure they deserve. PewDiePie basically craps out mindless, dumb content now where someone like Roach the Human has been doing it for years, makes decent content and has virtually no subscribers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the first one I watched! I mentioned it in my post! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres a fan film on youtube called Suburban Knight where this same thing happens but it takes place in the suburbs. Its neat! Not great but ok! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree! I like how Suburban Knight is scaled down and more homely... its fun! I do think it needs a lot of work though before its "there" but its for sure a nice departure. The Laughing Man was ok :/ didnt care for it too much. But I did find one called "Bats In The Clocktower" that was pretty interesting! Again... not *quite* there.... but cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you sooooo much! At first I was like.... Im almost certain Ive seen all the old serials until i realized this was done fairly recently Lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes... yes they are! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually the intro scene to Fallout 5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delet this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I'm paying attention to is Ryder's rocking cleavage. My heart must be a bluose at Saks Fifth cause she just stole it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
