<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, CD1, I'll be following you very shortly (temp drop today). Yay for period dances and pretty underwear though! And a glass of wine (or two) this weekend, woot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 15DPO. .5 degree temp drop. Mild Cramps. Looks like AF is coming... Not sure how I feel about that, on one hand I'm a bit relieved that we can move on to cycle 3 *finally*, after a 106-day anovulatory cycle and this cycle where I ovulated on CD41, but of course I wish that I was pregnant... I just feel a bit pessimistic, how long is this going to take if I ovulate only once every 5-6 months? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Temp drop of .5 degrees this morning with light cramps, looks like AF is coming :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No AF, and I couldn't bring myself to test this morning because I'm convinced that I can't be pregnant... If AF doesn't arrive though I will have to test again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got such a pretty chart after I ovulated... Too bad that AF is probably on the way :( 
Haven't had any symptoms at all indicating I could be pregnant and got 3 BFNs, the last one at 12DPO, so pretty convinced I'm out.
https://www.fertilityfriend.com/home/subject1257 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, sorry about AF.. Still nothing here on 14DPO, high temps but no symptoms or anything. Haven't retested as I'd rather be pissed at AF arriving than obsessing over a BFN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouf, sounds like we all have our difficulties... I agree about the rabbit thing haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how you feel, it's really hard to remember that we're adults and that outside of TtC we do have good things going for us in life... I'm pretty bitter these days as well and honestly not much helps. Unfollowing annoying pregnant acquaintances really helps, and getting back into things you love can help you divert your attention. *hugs* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Urgh, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, FF fixed the issue!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ruby I'm not offended at all, once every four weeks is clearly not enough when you want a baby NOW, I was just adding on even more in my case hahaha, no offense taken ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Argh, just saw yet another of my university colleague's FB announcement and maternity photoshoot... Honestly please just shoot me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I just did that! Not that it changes much, but I'd like to be able to see all 106 days in their glory -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Monday, no further explanation needed on why I'm moody. I hate my job, I hate the colleague sitting next to me, I hate TTC with a fucked up body...
I"m frickin 13DPO and still got a BFN yesterday, so really, I'm gonna be pissed to see AF arrive but holy hell can it happen already so that I can move on? /rant over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once every four weeks? I'd take that over ovulating once in 6 months :( But I agree that fertile days are way too far and few between. FML </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: I just corrected the temping time for my chart, there are only 2 empty circles now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FF gave me a lot of open circles because when I entered all my previous temps at around 4-5DPO it was 10 p.m. and I didn't see that FF assumed I was temping at 10 p.m... I was too lazy to change all the temp times, but they were all taken around 6-7 a.m. whereas FF thinks I temped between 6 a.m. and 10 p.m. Does that mean that in reality i'd have less open circles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can FF show my 106-day cycle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I transferred all my data from Glow to FF last week. My first cycle started on August 17 and finished on December 1st (106 days, pretty sure I didn't ovulate). I entered my data for the whole cycle, but FF only shows me the 48 first days of this cycle on my chart, which really sucks because my temping got better near the end of that cycle, and I wanted to see what the chart looked like, especially since I did have a few higher temps near the end of the cycle.
Is there a way to have the whole cycle show up on my chart, or there's nothing to do with a wacky 106-day cycle?
Thanks in advance ladies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap congrats!!!!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need your wisdom on my chart, getting discouraged! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's my chart: [url=https://www.fertilityfriend.com/home/subject1257/]My Ovulation Chart[/url]

We've been trying since August, temping since September but my first cycle was anovulatory and lasted 106 days, so this is the first time I have proof of ovulation with a temp shift. I even have an apparent triphasic shift!
I'm currently 13DPO and got BFNs yesterday and on 11DPO, almost no symptoms except a few moments of twinges of pain/weird sensation in my lower pelvic area, and a few minutes of nausea/dizziness... What gives? Do you girls have any advice for me please?? I'm getting desperate :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a super pretty triphasic chart but I'm convinced I'm not pregnant, so...
[url=https://www.fertilityfriend.com/home/subject1257/]My Ovulation Chart[/url] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second the obvious question about which supplement! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, not sure where you are, but I know that here (Canada), they're available *most* of the time, although it does happen from time to time that the display is empty. Doesn't help that they are super perishable! But homemade pad thai nom nom :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmmm, similar to our planned supper for tonight, tofu pad thai with loads of veggies and beans sprouts. Stir Fry and Thai meals FTW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I hate Mondays..
Spent the weekend with a 36-week pregnant friend who was freaking out about the impeding arrival of her baby...
Currently 13DPO and super disappointed.. Tested at 11 and 12DPO and got BFNs. I'm a bit pissed, my chart was super pretty, I even had a triphasic shift and all. Now I'm just waiting for stupid AF, come on already :( Hopegully my next cycle will be even shorter, I went from 106 days to 54 for this cycle, would be nice to have a "normal" length next time (hopefully with ovulation too).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also 10DPO today, no symptoms, no CM, my temp is up and FF has detected a triphasic pattern... I don't even know how long my LP is going to be, since this is the first time I've ovulated since stoping HBC 6 months ago. (Over)analysis any and all data is what we TTCers do! It may be boring to get such stable temperatures, but at least your pattern must be crystal-clear! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my, you're good for not testing. Good luck, I'm sure you'll keep us posted! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Read that book, it's super easy, quick and interesting to read plus is backed up by studies and actual science. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just clocked in a 5K over my lunch hour, woot! Never thought I'd have the energy for it, but I'm so glad I went! Running makes me feel so much better :) Plus we've been getting fairly nice and hot (ha!) weather this week: +1 Celsius with cloudy skies (pretty good for January in Quebec, Canada!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I told DH and he was like, "Okay, if that makes you feel better. But ONE article per cycle ok?" haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never even had a pretty chart with an obvious ovulation before this cycle, so just seeing a temp shift was like "woohoo!" ;) Oh the little things that will amuse us... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the BFPs from some of the girls that are super active and that have been here for a long while make me so happy! :) Also it's Friday so I'm just relieved to see the weekend!
10DPO right now, zero symptoms so far :( Somehow I feel like I should have symptoms at this point.. Got a BFN yesterday because I'm a tool and couldn't resist taking a test (not even with FMU, what was I thinking?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay, I'm so happy things went well for you! This motivates me to call my doctor soon and ask for the next steps to take. I hope things go well from thus on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Exactly this. u/chaunceythebear said it better than I could. I get sensitive about this too, but I try not to let it affect me too much. I'll try to memorize these words for next time this happens. *internet hugs to you* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG that is so awesome!!!! I'm so happy for you :)
I've got a beautiful chart this month but I know how you felt, I've got no false expectations (hey, at least I get a pretty chart to look at right?)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG CONGRATS!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! Welcome! I like the idea of treating ourselves when AF arrives. I've read here recently an idea I liked: one item for now so that A would suck less, and one item for later when there will be a baby... I think I might take that up! 
Oh and 100% agree about FF, I've just switched after 5months and wish I had done so sooner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love this 3 I will show my SO, as he loves photography so I know he'll enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankful that I finally ovulated, hoping this means my cycles will regulate. Thankful it's Thursday (the week is loooong).
Thankful that I feel a little bit less obsessed and dramatic about this TTC business, I'm feeling like it hasn't happened yet because it wasn't the time, but when it does I'll just be even happier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahaha awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> L (haha!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thankful for Ryan Gosling. Even though he only lives on the screen for me haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> E (end u/napmom ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm wow Egads, does that sound more like a boy's name or a girl's name? Hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 16:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 16:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start out by reading the helpful links on the right of this sub, they give all the basic info on charting, temping, OPKs, etc!
Also, everyone recommends reading *Taking Charge of Your Fertility*, which is super complete and will get you to understand your body's cycles.
And the most important advice, have fun and try not to go too crazy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm always afraid of sounding like an overdramatic, entitled bitch lol! But I have an excuse to call next week since I had an ultrasound last Thursday and want to discuss the results with her, so I will gently approach the subject with that :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *knooooow*... -_- And I'm an impatient person, so this process is really testing my sanity...
I saw my doctor in November and did a few basic tests, everything seemed normal, but if the next cycle is as long I will definitely call her back and demand more answers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, pretty sure I'm also really not mucusy in general, because apart from 2 days of EWCM (my first-ever), most days there is next to nothing to report, and it's been like that for 6 months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Travel is considered a stress on the body and can thus affect your ovulation date, which could be delayed by a few (or many) days. I'd say just try to keep tracking as best as you can, BD away while on vacation, and see how that goes. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9DPO today (CD50), still nothing to report. Convinced that I'm not pregnant just because I still can't quite believe my body is back to functioning normally, so I'm almost impatient for AF to arrive so that I can just... Move on to the next cycle. Will be calling my doctor soon, because 106 days and 50+days is definitely not a cycle length I approve of, and at this rate, we get one chance to conceive every 5 months which sucks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, that doesn't sound like normal pain to me... I'm glad you're taking it into your own hands and finding out what's going on. Keep us updated after your appointment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't beat yourself up, they're just lucky... Always sucks when other people have it so easy compared to us... I started trying at the same time as my best friend in August, she got pregnant 2 weeks in and is now at 23 weeks, and I've just ovulated for the first time in 6 months (at CD41)... Not the same battle. We're all just doing our best, so good luck to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 19:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, thanks for the heads-up, for sure I will try not to read into anything. I've been having tiny twinges in my uterus-area but that could be almost anything, so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 19:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'm glad we hit those ones at least, but I wish we had done more. FF gave a "good" rating for our timing, so it could be worse of course. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome!!

I know trying to start off casual sounds nice, but my cycles were so effed up after BC I'm glad I at least started temping right away, because I could actually *see* that my body wasn't getting back on track. If that's something you're open to, I recommend it, just so that you have more data as well a few months from now if things are not working. I hope for your sake that you're not here for too long!
Also, everyone here recommends Fertility Friend as an app, and I've just switched to it and second all the recommendations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG *fixed dick* hahaha almost broke out laughing in the office.... I really hope that his new and improved sperm machine gets the trick done for you guys :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish time travel was a thing!! I really hope your back gets better, in the meantime take what rest you can :)
Here's to hoping cycle 6 is the one for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, been temping since mid-August! I've had trouble with my cycles, first one was anovulatory (no temp spike) and lasted 106 days. For this cycle, I did OPKs almost every day between CD12 and CD42, got a few very pale lines but nothing that looked close to positive. Got my temp spike though, FF says I probably ovulated on CD41 (I got EWCM for 2 days, also a first!). Now I'm just hoping my temps stay high long enough for a nice, normal LP... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waiting for something to happen... 8 DPO, nothing to report. First proper 2WW in our 5 months of trying, so I need to not get my hopes up, especially since we only managed to hit O-3 and O-1 because I had no idea if/when I'd ovulate... So I guess we'll see! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 16:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa, will definitely try this next cycle when I'm trying to get a positive OPK (haven't gotten anything remotely close to positive yet)! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, so early! Congrats :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG Congrats, I remember your intro post! So happy for you!! Crazy that you got a BFP at 9DPO :)  I'm currently 8DPO, pretty sure nothing is happening but will try to hold out on testing at least until 11 DPO. I hope it sticks!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently 8DPO, my temp this morning jumped by .3 F... This is my first cycle in which I actually ovulated, so I don't know what to make of this. Anyone have wisdom for me?

P.S. It's Wednesday, we are all surviving this week. Woot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I hope #7 is the one for you!! I wish I had a 28-day cycle so that I could have a chance every month... Have a not-so-sucky AF, indulge while you can :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn people who don't mind their business! If people ask, I like the "my doctor told me to reintroduce meat to get my iron up" lie, usually medical reasons like that get less refuted or people will just accept it easier than if you try to explain. That's what I would do, and as someone else mentioned, maybe trying to eat vegetarian when out with larger groups of people who don't know you are TTC #2 can ease the questions of the curious! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 01:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip, I too find it to be a bit high for TTC, and my mom has Hashimoto's so I know I have to keep that in mind. I'll be seeing my doctor in a few weeks and will definitely mention it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 01:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't usually have any symptoms, so I'll guess we'll see! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are dotted crosshairs okay or should I be disappointed that I don't have a full line?
https://www.fertilityfriend.com/home/subject1257

It's the first time I have anything remotely resembling ovulation and temp rise, so I'm in new territory here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, thanks! I was a bit confused, it's complicated to know where to post when you have a general question + chart for support!

I just feel like so many people have symptoms, but I'm feeling nothing at all... So like, reverse symptom-spotting? Hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey!! No worries, TTC #1 or #2 or #5 is always going to be a roller-coaster, so might as well join in on the fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first AF after stopping HBC was about 11 weeks late, so yeah... Please don't hold your breath or you might not survive! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I figured that waiting was the main action involved here :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New on ChartStalkers, first crosshairs! Anxiously waiting for your input! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just posted in TFAB and was redirected here! Been participating in TFAB for a month but never got the chance to post here because there was nothing to stalk, haha.

A little backstory for everyone: Stopped HBC in August after 11 years, never had regular cycles but was in for a rude awakening. 1st cycle lasted 106 days (most probably anovulatory). Half of me was gearing up for a long, crappy cycle 2, half of me was still hopeful for something to happen.

Went to see my doctor in November, had bloodwork done and an ultrasound which revealed normal blood results (however progesterone was not tested and TSH was 3.69, so I'm keeping that in mind in case things keep being wacky) and a 3-cm kyst on my left ovary. Follow-up ultrasound last week revealed everything was normal. I finally migrated my cycle 2 data onto FF (was using Glow since August) because I finally ovulated on CD41! Currently 7DPO and I have a question:

I'm just glad I ovulated at all, but I'm also hoping things might have worked. However, I've had NO symptoms at all, but then again I never really have PMS symptoms or ovulation symptoms, so should I expect the same here? What else can I do except wait? Thanks in advance :)

Here's my chart (first time sharing it, let me know if it doesn't work): https://www.fertilityfriend.com/home/subject1257

EDITED TO ADD: I have never gotten a positive OPK and had been taking one almost every day as of CD12 this cycle, but they're not all entered on FF because I was on Glow and they were all negative anyway... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, just removed my chart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
