<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7578</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 07:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and was filled in with river sediments

More correctly, with glacial outwash deposits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 06:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Additionally:

The study also finds that Jupiter-family comets like Comet 67P/Churyumov-Gerasimenko were unlikely the source of [Earth's nitrogen](http://sci.esa.int/science-e-media/img/46/ESA_Rosetta_ROSINA_N2_info_1280.jpg). **-** [ESA](http://sci.esa.int/rosetta/55620-rosetta-makes-first-detection-of-molecular-nitrogen-at-a-comet/)

Which is consistent with their previous conclusion that Jupiter-family comets like Comet 67P/Churyumov-Gerasimenko were also unlikely to be the source of [Earth's water](http://i.space.com/images/i/000/044/303/original/rosetta-comet-water-measurements.jpg?1418404203) (which also consistent with [asteroids](http://www.whoi.edu/news-release/OriginEarthWater) and volcanic degassing as the primary source for Earth's water and nitrogen).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rosetta makes first detection of molecular nitrogen at a comet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 03:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Formation of Phobos and Deimos via Giant Impact </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 02:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study links the formation of Phobos and Deimos, the moons of Mars, to one or more giant impacts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 02:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 23:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fantastic, and thank you for the paper. Are you and your co-authors presenting anything at the 46^th [LPSC](http://www.hou.usra.edu/meetings/lpsc2015/) by chance?

EDIT: nvm, found the answer in one of your other comments: [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/2zmzlt/theoretical_study_suggests_huge_lava_tubes_could/cplcxtd) ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 23:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you kindly for the paper, I'll be certain to have a read. I'm excited to read a number of the papers that come from the LPSC2015 as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 20:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last active period of ~~vulcanism~~ volcanism on the Moon occurred ~~BILLIONS of~~ 50 to 10 million years ago, or less.

FTFY 

https://asunews.asu.edu/20141012-lunar-volcanism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 19:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calcium sulphate is known as [anhydrite](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anhydrite), it's essentially [gypsum](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gypsum) just without the water. In this image, taken at the [Garden City](https://twitter.com/elakdawalla/status/578714605452578817) site, Emily Lakdawalla has said the following:

"...absolutely no question water was involved. In this case, groundwater   burial... Mineral-rich water circulating through sedimentary rocks under high pressure; crystals formed in cracks in rocks."

I find it difficult to believe that the dark greenish / greyish host rock is sedimentary. This is essentially a stockwork of veins in what I would initially have assumed to be a brecciated basalt. However, we need to keep in mind that with this much fluid passing through the rocks we should expect to see some degree of alteration. This is why colour is never really a good idea to use as an identifier. Furthermore, the [location](http://mars.jpl.nasa.gov/msl/mission/whereistherovernow/) - Pahrump Hills, given the context, almost certainly dictates that these are, as Emily stated, sedimentary rocks.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 18:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the giant impact hypothesis is still the currently most widely accepted lunar formation theory. The Moon was once thought to be solid throughout, supposedly being too small to retain the heat from its formation. This changed with the Apollo landings, as seismicity was detected (moon quakes). The seismicity was used to discern the internal structure of the moon, much like how it is done on Earth. This lead to the understanding that the moon has a solid inner core, surrounded by a fluid outer core, followed by a region or zone partial melt, then a rocky mantle and crust. So while the moon retained a relatively warm central interior it was still thought to be...dead, per say.  Later, it was discovered that volcanic activity was actually quite recent, geologically speaking, within the past ~10 million years and certainly less than 50 million years ago. Again, none of these discoveries refutes the formation model; however, they do provide further insight into the thermodynamics of the moon. There also seems to be some confusion ITT with regards to tectonic activity and plate tectonic, two uniquely distinct mechanisms. The moon, while it lacks plate tectonics, is still tectonically active:

- [Lobate Scarps](http://svs.gsfc.nasa.gov/cgi-bin/details.cgi?aid=10631)

- [Graben](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=68LOZvQTjB0) 

And, there exists the possibility for volcanism in the distant future on the moon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 18:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steno, I appreciate your earlier work and contributions to geology but your information presented here is off base. There is a distinct difference between tectonic activity (tectonism) and plate tectonics. The moon is most certainly still tectonically active:

- [Lobate Scarps](http://svs.gsfc.nasa.gov/cgi-bin/details.cgi?aid=10631)

- [Graben](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=68LOZvQTjB0)

The only reason we understand that the internal structure of the moon (solid inner core, fluid outer core, zone of partial melt, rocky mantle, and crust) is through seismic activity. Geologically speaking, the moon has seen episodes of [relatively young volcanism](http://news.sciencemag.org/space/2014/10/recent-volcanic-eruptions-moon). Furthermore, it is speculated that there could be lunar volcanism in the distant(?) future. 

 the mantle is also too cool to support the movement of hot material up from the core.

That's not how density difference operate. See [magmatic assimilation](http://bio-geo-terms.blogspot.ca/2007/12/assimilation.html)

Note that this doesn't refute the point that there is currently no lava in the tubes, or that the moon does not have plate tectonics, it merely clears up some misleading statements regarding tectonism on the moon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 09:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The immediate advantage is reduced gravity, and therefore reduced costs for entry into space. The moon is rich in rare earths, [titanium](http://www.space.com/13247-moon-map-lunar-titanium.html) and could support mining with recent evidence of the existence of water. The big prize when excavating the moon; however, is [helium-3](http://www.extremetech.com/extreme/197784-china-is-going-to-mine-the-moon-for-helium-3-fusion-fuel). Lastly, it would make mining asteroids convenient as long as we could place them in [orbit around the moon](http://www.nasa.gov/content/what-is-nasa-s-asteroid-redirect-mission/). In essence, besides the scientific and technological advances that would be driven by lunar missions, there are a bounty of resources to take advantage of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 09:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moon is most certainly still tectonically active:

- [Lobate Scarps](http://svs.gsfc.nasa.gov/cgi-bin/details.cgi?aid=10631)

- [Graben](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=68LOZvQTjB0)

And, geologically speaking, has seen episodes of [relatively young volcanism](http://news.sciencemag.org/space/2014/10/recent-volcanic-eruptions-moon). Furthermore, it is speculated that there could be lunar volcanism in the distant(?) future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 06:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The practical value of these volcanic features has been [considered](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Colonization_of_the_Moon#Lunar_lava_tubes). I'm uncertain as to what resolution  NASAs twin Gravity Recovery and Interior Laboratory (GRAIL)  was able to achieve, but these features, if they do exist to such a size, should be detectable with a gravity survey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 04:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She / he may have taken [Iron Sky](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Py_IndUbcxc) a little too literal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Reveal Subatomic Particles at Home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 03:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 00:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The variation in colours have mine going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 00:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Purdue News](http://www.purdue.edu/newsroom/releases/2015/Q1/theoretical-study-suggests-huge-lava-tubes-could-exist-on-moon.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theoretical study suggests huge lava tubes could exist on moon, large enough to house cities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 23:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theoretical study suggests huge lava tubes could exist on moon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 23:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surprise! Canadian Double Crater Formed by 2 Separate Impact Events </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mystery dust cloud and aurora spotted on Mars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Successful Test Flights for Mars Landing Technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a P.Geo yet so I can't technically call myself a geologist in the professional sense but that is what I majored in. 

Sounds exciting. Care to give provide an 'abstract' of sorts on your results?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Curiosity data summaries of each sol's activities thru 804 (pdf) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 23:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 06:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very envious of you. The best I can do is follow along on twitter, in excitement. May I ask why you're there? 

EDIT: [image source](https://twitter.com/tanyaofmars/status/577483870607532032) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 06:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's really nothing wrong with two locations in which 'ice' would be jetting out from cryovolcanism. For simplistic argument we can classify glaciers into temperate or warm based glaciers and polar or cold based glaciers. Warm base glaciers are aptly named as the base of the glacier, where it contacts the surface / bedrock is below the melting point. Because of this, you achieve a mechanism that permits the glacier to move called basal slip. Cold based glaciers are above the melting point, and so they are frozen to the surface which doesn't permit basal sliding ([Figure I](http://www.acegeography.com/uploads/1/8/6/4/18647856/9088392_orig.png?451)). Cold based glaciers move far, far slower because of this and their movement is generally caused by internal deformation ([Figure II](http://www.coolgeography.co.uk/A-level/AQA/Year%2012/Cold%20environs/Ice%20movement/Glacier%20movement.jpg)). The angle of the slope certainly assists in movement (at least when gravity is not negligible); however, the type of glacier must be considered first. I'm not 100% certain on the P-T conditions on Ceres but I would assume it would not permit melting of water into liquid to permit basal slip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 05:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant(ish): [T203](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CAOig1KUYAEKmGu.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Large, Hidden Crater Spotted on Moons Nearside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 22:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surprise! Canadian Double Crater Formed by 2 Separate Impact Events </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 22:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bright spots on Ceres could be active ice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 22:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 18:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Study: [Swept away by a turbidity current in Mendocino submarine canyon, California](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2014GL061863/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deep-sea robot, caught in underwater avalanche, yields new scientific insights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 18:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MBARI News Release: Deep-sea robot, caught in underwater avalanche, yields new scientific insights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 18:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 09:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sutherland cautions that the reactions that would have made each of the sets of building blocks are different enough from one anotherrequiring different metal catalysts, for examplethat they likely would not have all occurred in the same location.

Anyone know what specific metals he's refereeing to?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colorful life-form catalog will help discern if we are alone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 09:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reports of a meteor over Switzerland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 03:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 19:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *cough cough

http://www.reddit.com/r/space/comments/2ybpd4/mars_four_billion_years_ago_credit_esom_kornmesser/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 04:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - [AGU response](http://sciencepolicy.agu.org/files/2013/07/AGU-letter-to-Sen-Cruz-March-2015.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earth science is not hard science, congressional Republicans declare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 04:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers study methane-rich plumes from Saturns icy moon Enceladus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 04:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 02:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we're looking for a well defined global distribution arguments can be made for the [first atomic blast](http://www.nature.com/news/first-atomic-blast-proposed-as-start-of-anthropocene-1.16739) as the beginning of the Anthropocene; however, there are [a number of competing proposals](http://www.nature.com/news/anthropocene-the-human-age-1.17085?WT.mc_id=TWT_NatureNews). I'm curious to know why the Anthropocene has been suggested as a new Epoch and not as an Age within the Holocene.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 09:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can vouch for this region. I did some mineral exploration on several properties while being based out of Pemberton. Exploring areas up around Gun Lake, between Harrison and Lillooete Lake, and along with some areas out in the Shulaps as well, the drive from Pemberton to Lillooete is just as magnificent, if not more so in its own way. Of course; however, it wouldn't be doing BC any justice to leave out the plethora of other mountain ranges, and magnificent sites to explore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 07:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...specifically plastics... which could potentially be preserved in the rock record.

Surprise: http://www.geosociety.org/gsatoday/archive/24/6/article/i1052-5173-24-6-4.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 05:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another Nature Article: [Defining the Anthropocene](https://eorder.sheridan.com/3_0/app/orders/4609/article.php#171) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 04:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The top-down generation (from the top down towards the centre) of silica within those specified dimensions is extremely difficult to generate. On Earth silicate minerals are actively broken down over time by weathering processes. As they are transported they tend to become less angular and more spherical in shape. Note that this process of weathering and erosion on Earth is promoted by active plate tectonics, water and wind. These same processes; however, are unlikely to be either active (plate tectonics or a similar mechanism) or nearly present to the same degree that they are on Earth. 

On the other hand a bottom-up model (from the centre towards the surface) readily generates the silica in the nano meter dimensions. This means that the source for the water must be at great depths, and at temperatures at which the silica can enter solution and be carried up to the surface where it precipitates out of solution. Thus the conclusion is arrived at in which there are active hydrothermal circulation paths at depth, which is eventually bringing the silica up. Such an analog on Earth may be exemplified by the [Lost City Hydrothermal Vents](http://1.bp.blogspot.com/_gLv0n3B4neg/SwuWFoZlLiI/AAAAAAAAIHc/pXlrn4EIp_w/s1600/Untitled-7.png):

Speculation has been offered that ancient versions of similar hydrothermal vents in the seas of a young Earth are the birthplace of all life, constituting the original abiogenesis. - [wiki](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lost_City_Hydrothermal_Field)     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 02:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a common misconception that Jupiter protects the Earth from bolide impacts. In reality, it sends more bolides our way than it does preventing them from impacting with the Earth:

*It definitely sends asteroids and comets our way and, in any given year, more than 90 percent of all objects crossing Earth's orbit are asteroids, so the protection Jupiter provides us from long period comets, or by eventually removing short period comets, is of lesser importance. Hence Jupiter is not the friend that it has been perceived to be.* - [Villain in Disguise: Jupiter's Role in Impacts on Earth](http://www.astrobio.net/news-exclusive/villain-in-disguise-jupiters-role-in-impacts-on-earth/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 00:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget about the other big discovery as of late with regard to Saturn's icy moon Enceladus

- [First Active Hydrothermal System Found beyond Earth ](http://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/2yt315/first_active_hydrothermal_system_found_beyond/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 22:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps rather than assigning the Anthropocene to the beginning of a new epoch it would be better assigned to an age within the Holocene? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 19:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying to wrap my head around what the pH values might imply

The water is less than 4 percent salinity, has a pH between 8.5 and 10.5...

The water is reasonably basic which suggests that there could be a good portion of alkali metals or alkaline oxides in solution. The question is what is the immediate source? Is it coming from the alteration of minerals alone, is it coming from potential components of microbial life as they break-down, is it a byproduct of microbial life...

The size of the silica particulate (nm) may help answer some of those questions, but it's important to note that Earth's silica based life are photosynthetic in their nature, something Enceladus would most likely lack all together. I'm unaware of any analogs on Earth that would be suggestively comparable (Chemosynthetic life forms, extremophiles, etc.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Explosive eruptions rocked the youthful moon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 19:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Active Hydrothermal System Found beyond Earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 17:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martian canyons may have been carved by wind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 17:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anthropocene: The human age - Momentum is building to establish a new geological epoch that recognizes humanity's impact on the planet. But there is fierce debate behind the scenes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 17:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 09:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might help, though I'm not certain it would, but the Earth itself experiences the pull of the moon. In other words, there are not only tides in the Earth's oceans, but in the rocks as well called [Earth Tides](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Earth_tide). And while Earth experiences these Earth tides upwards of 8", the pull of Jupiter on Io causes [Ionian tides](http://spaceplace.nasa.gov/io-tides/en/) upwards of 330 ft.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 02:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not actually true. Water is blue because of it's absorption properties and the scattering of white light, though absorption is by far the strongest factor.  In water, absorption is [strong in the red and weak in the blue](http://www.lisalaserusa.com/wp-content/uploads/spektrum-revolix.jpg), thus red light is absorbed quickly in the ocean leaving blue. Furthermore, impurities dissolved or suspended (ex. phytoplankton) in water may give water different colored appearances.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 19:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll share one of my comments from another thread here with you:

Let's shed some light and see if we can't gain a deeper perspective as to why it's actually quite easy to think of Mars as essentially barren, except possibly, for its ocean(s) at that time in its history (were they [purple oceans?](http://www.astrobio.net/topic/solar-system/earth/biosphere/did-earth-have-purple-oceans/)). Using Earth as an analog:

The 1^st widely accepted fossil evidence of microbial (simple) life on Earth is dated to ~[3.5](http://phys.org/news/2013-01-earliest-evidence-life-billion-years.html)Ga (Ga = billion years ago). Nearly 1.067 billion years *after* the formation of the Earth.

It took another ~1.3 billion years until the 1^st stage of the [Great Oxidation Event](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Great_Oxygenation_Event) to occur (around 2.3Ga) and it would take an additional ~1.45 billion years for oxygen to begin to accumulate into the atmosphere after all the natural sinks had filled. We have now endured a total of 3.65 billion years since the formation of the Earth and all there are, are microbes in the ocean. 

The earliest complex life, the [Ediacara biota](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ediacaran_Biota), didn't arrive until ~635 million years ago. After many more millions of years of evolution the 1^st fossil evidence of land plants didn't occur until the [mid-Ordovician](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Evolutionary_history_of_plants#Colonization_of_land), ~470Ma (Ma = Million years ago), and the 1^st macroscopic fossil evidence doesn't arrive until ~[433](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cooksonia)Ma.

Of course there are plenty of other mysteries around some points in the evolution of life on Earth... what triggered the Cambrian explosion of life? What role, if any, did [Snow Ball Earth](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Snowball_Earth) play as it came out of the Gaskiers glaciation? etc. Keep in mind that we also need to consider the evolution of the solar system and what stage it was at as well. For example, the sun [wasn't as luminous](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Faint_young_Sun_paradox) billions of years ago, what affect would that have on Mars?  

All that being said I hope the above is enough to highlight why it's not so hard to see Mars, in its earliest stages, as essentially barren noting that the terrestrial Earth was essentially rocky and barren until ~4.097 billion years after its formation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mars four billion years ago. credit: ESO/M. Kornmesser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 10:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 10:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly no. I managed to go to AMEBC's RoundUp event but didn't make PDAC this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 01:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PDAC? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 09:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or both </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 09:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the sole question NASA's MAVEN mission is looking to answer. The three commonly considered processes are:

- [Neutral Process](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0_iz5Nt0Qc8)

- [Sputtering](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EoUy4lsgRo8)

- [Plasma Processes](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ogcaSmofPo4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mars Rover Curiosity Is Suffering Short Circuits in Arm, NASA Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 21:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 09:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's shed some light and see if we can't gain a deeper perspective as to why it's actually quite easy to think of Mars as essentially barren, except possibly, for its ocean(s) at that time in its history (were they [purple oceans?](http://www.astrobio.net/topic/solar-system/earth/biosphere/did-earth-have-purple-oceans/)). Using Earth as an analog:

The 1^st widely accepted fossil evidence of microbial (simple) life on Earth is dated to ~[3.5](http://phys.org/news/2013-01-earliest-evidence-life-billion-years.html)Ga (Ga = billion years ago). Nearly 1.067 billion years *after* the formation of the Earth.

It took another ~1.3 billion years until the 1^st stage of the [Great Oxidation Event](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Great_Oxygenation_Event) to occur (around 2.3Ga) and it would take an additional ~1.45 billion years for oxygen to begin to accumulate into the atmosphere after all the natural sinks had filled. We have now endured a total of 3.65 billion years since the formation of the Earth and all there are, are microbes in the ocean. 

The earliest complex life, the [Ediacara biota](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ediacaran_Biota), didn't arrive until ~635 million years ago. After many more millions of years of evolution the 1^st fossil evidence of land plants didn't occur until the [mid-Ordovician](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Evolutionary_history_of_plants#Colonization_of_land), ~470Ma (Ma = Million years ago), and the 1^st macroscopic fossil evidence doesn't arrive until ~[433](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cooksonia)Ma.

Of course there are plenty of other mysteries around some points in the evolution of life on Earth... what triggered the Cambrian explosion of life? What role, if any, did [Snow Ball Earth](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Snowball_Earth) play as it came out of the Gaskiers glaciation? etc. Keep in mind that we also need to consider the evolution of the solar system and what stage it was at as well. For example, the sun [wasn't as luminous](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Faint_young_Sun_paradox) billions of years ago, what affect would that have on Mars?  

All that being said I hope the above is enough to highlight why it's not so hard to see Mars, in its earliest stages, as essentially barren noting that the terrestrial Earth was essentially rocky and barren until ~4.097 billion years after its formation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 09:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the sole question NASA's MAVEN mission is looking to answer. The three commonly considered processes are:

- [Neutral Process](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0_iz5Nt0Qc8)

- [Sputtering](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EoUy4lsgRo8)

- [Plasma Processes](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ogcaSmofPo4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 04:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yes, I'm well aware that it's a text book / ideal soil profile (the image I provided in my previous comment) and that not all horizons may be present, developed, and some may even repeat throughout the profile.

It is possible that this "soil" is just mainly composed of sand.

That's where my qualm comes in. "Sand, not soil' seems incorrect to say even if [this soil](http://i.imgur.com/bLjsalb.jpg) / horizon is simply primarily composed of sand. In my opinion it seems to fit the description of what a soil is:
Soil is the mixture of minerals, organic matter, gases, liquids, and myriad organisms that together support plant life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 01:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So soil, as far as I was aware, can be divided into distinct [horizons](https://classconnection.s3.amazonaws.com/11/flashcards/99011/png/soil_horizon.png), of which each horizon has its own composition... sand is [one of the components](http://www.soilsensor.com/images/soiltriangle_large.jpg) of soil. Can you clarify then what you mean by "sand, not soil'?

Edit: For clarity, I used the 'text book' soil profile image *not* to say that all soils should exhibit this structure, but merely to describe that soils have horizons (however poorly or exceptionally well defined they may be, should they even be present to begin with).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ancient ocean on Mars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 01:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 08:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an extremely difficult question to answer, and there is plenty of debate surrounding such a question. If you're interested; however, I would suggest reading [Earth as an Evolving System](http://www.lnu.edu.ua/faculty/geology/phis_geo/fourman/library-Earth/Earth%20as%20an%20Evolving%20Planetary%20System_0120883929.pdf) (pdf) that may help you explore your question further, specifically under Ch. 6 - The Atmosphere and Oceans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 08:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Panspermia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 08:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...life started 2 billion years ago...

Minor correction. Add an additional 1.5 billion years to that value for the 1^st preserved fossil evidence of life on Earth (i.e. ~3.5Ga). Life must have also had to evolve prior to the fossil evidence so you can extend the existence of life on Earth prior to 3.5Ga... but who knows how far back you can extend it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 08:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much evidence against such a claim (i.e. [evolution](http://www.lucasbrouwers.nl/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/12/Evo_large.gif)).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 05:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - [Rings Contest, Further Info   Details](http://ringmaster.cs.ucr.edu/Rings2.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What on Earth Made These Perfect Fossil Rings? Help Solve the Mystery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 04:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Animated Life: Pangea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 05:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 05:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - [Part Two](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A620t61OTc8 feature=youtu.be) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Great Debate: EXTINCTIONS (OFFICIAL) - (Part 1/2) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 05:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 04:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While doing some silt surveys we knew there was a Grizzly somewhere in the region. Thankfully, we never crossed its path. We were lucky enough; however, to see how it had re-sculpted the mountain side hunting hoary marmots (whistle-pigs) in the area. 

Our 1^st sign it had been in the area: [rear paw](http://i.imgur.com/IqjxxUu.jpg)

What a marmot hole looks like before a Grizzly visit: [Before](http://i.imgur.com/IeoPLpA.jpg)

What a marmot hole looks like after a Grizzly visit: [Redecorated](http://i.imgur.com/HEH5rWj.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vancouver Archipelago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 02:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Coastal Paleontologist down under: Introducing Eotaria crypta from the Miocene of Southern California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 07:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists identify mineral that destroys organic compounds, with implications for Mars Curiosity mission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 23:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 05:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to your brief summary I'd like to add some insightful links for anyone interested in further details. There are a number of books available that provide great information, though admittedly they may not be very 'user friendly' to most lay persons. 

The 1^st book is fairly costly: [Comets: Nature, Dynamics, Origin, and their Cosmogonical Relevance](http://www.chapters.indigo.ca/en-ca/books/product/9781402034909-item.html?s_campaign=goo-PLATest mkwid=yevPjqFu_dc pcrid=44154474422 s_campaign=goo-Shopping_Books gclid=CK2DlubR6sMCFWfJtAodxGkA_g); however, if you're really keen   interested, it can be found online (pdf).

The 2^nd book is a compilation of scientific papers, and is currently still available for free in individual paper form (pdf): [Comets II](http://www.lpi.usra.edu/books/CometsII/download.html)

The 3^rd book is provided in the same format as Comets II, and you can compile the pdfs using Google's search engine, and the provided titles: [Asteroids III](http://www.lpi.usra.edu/books/AsteroidsIII/download.html) 

As with the 2^nd   3^rd books, the 4^th and final addition is also available for free as individual pdf's that can be compiled to construct the included chapters within the book: [Meteorites and the Early Solar System II](http://www.lpi.usra.edu/books/MESSII/download.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 11:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. http://rationalwiki.org/wiki/Electric_Universe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rosetta's closest encounter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 11:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oil Eating Microbes Have Worldwide Underground Connections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 23:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 22:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wiktionary.org/wiki/gnarl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada's Gnarliest Tree, Avatar Grove, BC [OC][3456 x 4608] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 05:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jupiter glimpsed as aliens would see it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 18:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 17:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you provide a link to the already submitted and popular post please? I can't seem to find it, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Particles Found at Large Hadron Collider </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 18:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spaceplane re-entry is a European first </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 18:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Val Parghera:- A fascinating stop motion video of a large rockslide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 21:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 07:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The outcrop itself](http://i.imgur.com/jw68ktz.jpg), was on the road down to the Buckley Bay ferry terminal just south of the Trent River. I'm not overly familiar with each formation so I'm at a bit of a loss as to whether or not it was from the coal-bearing part of the section; however, I didn't notice any coal (although my short time at the outcrop was too limited to be certain of this). In the outcrop photo, the 'burrow' was located on the far side of the road (the right hand side), and I found a small fragment believed to be derived from an ammonite (though this could be incorrect) on the near side of the photo (left hand side). 

Are the Trent River Formation and the Pender Formation one and the same? Finding papers regarding the lithostratigraphy can be somewhat confusing :| Any idea as to what the current nomenclature is?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Comets Are Like Deep Fried Ice Cream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 07:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 19:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologize for the lack of scale, it was situated too high up in outcrop for me to actually reach it (I had to take the photo with my camera at arms length above my head). That being said it's ~9cm in length, and ~2cm in diameter. 

As far as I'm aware these are marine sediments (there were small ammonite fragments found very nearby), though I am having some difficulty determining which formation it is. It's a member of the Naniamo Group Sediments, consisting of alternating predominantly mudstone / shale with interfingered siltstone. Overlying these there appeared to be bedded, fine grain sandstone. From what I can gather, I would assume that I was within what is known as the [Pender Formation](http://www.uvic.ca/science/seos/assets/docs/PenderFT13.pdf) (pdf) though there appears to be some contention regarding its provenance depending on the region of study ranging from coastal plain and deltaic deposits with marine tongues, to shelf/slope deposits and even deep marine deposits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help identifying this burrow (thalassinoides?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 03:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moon Phase and Libration, from the Other Side </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 01:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 18:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, okay thank you for the explanation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 11:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologize, it appears the permissions for the page may have changed. [Google Catch View](http://webcache.googleusercontent.com/search?q=cache:nWE0minceJEJ:www.gns.cri.nz/Home/News-and-Events/Media-Releases/slippery-base-on-underside-of-tectonic-plate+ cd=1 hl=en ct=clnk gl=uk) allows reading of the page however. 

EDIT: Embargo has been lifted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 06:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During my degree I did a bit of research on the tectonics of Io - it's pretty interesting seeing as Io has the tiniest fraction of water (something quite common correlated to volcanism on Earth). In fact, Io is the most volcanically active body in the solar system, all of which, is due to tidal heating.  

What you're looking at is [one](http://www.windows2universe.org/jupiter/images/JPL_io_interior_gif_image.html) of Io's active volcanic regions known as Tvashtar Catena. This particular area has seen eruptions reaching ~ 385km in height and spreading over 700km! If that were on Earth, it would nearly cover the entire state of Alaska.    

This particular eruption:
An eruption on Tvashtar on February 26, 2007 was photographed by the New Horizons probe as it went past Jupiter en route to Pluto. The probe observed an enormous 330 kilometres (210 mi) high plume from the volcano, with an as-yet unexplained filamentary structure made clearly visible by the background light from the sun. - [wiki](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tvashtar_Paterae) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists discover slippery base on underside of tectonic plate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 06:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 06:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - **Study**: Stern, T.A., Henrys, S.H., Okaya, D.A., Louie, J., Savage, M.K., Lamb, S.H., Sato, H., Sutherland, R.,   Iwasaki, T. (accepted). A seismic reflection image for the base of a tectonic plate. Nature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists discover slippery base on underside of tectonic plate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 06:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 00:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not 100% certain; however, it seems that it would be such an unlikely scenario that it a) would not be my 1^st interpretation and b) it seems so unlikely that it might as well be impossible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every round object in the solar system under 10,000 kilometers in diameter, to scale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 19:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moon business regulation step taken by U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 19:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moroccan Meteorite May Be a 4.4-Billion-Year-Old Chunk of Dark Martian Crust </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 09:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists discover organism that hasn't evolved in more than 2 billion years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 09:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 09:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chalk is derived from coccolithophores (a marine phytoplankton) deposited in deep marine settings. Coal is derived via the process of coalification, i.e. the accumulation, and compaction of organic rich material (plant material, peat). Knowing that the two environments differ greatly, you can exclude *chalk* as a possibility. Under this pretext it's likely to be sandstone.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transient flow of water on Vesta (an asteroid) suggested by gullies and lobate deposits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 20:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transient flow of water on Vesta suggested by gullies and lobate deposits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 20:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In his latest letter, @brynjo puts the plunge in US oil rigs into perspective. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 19:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asbestos found in Nevada and Arizona: Roadblock and potential health hazard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 20:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asbestos found in Nevada and Arizona: Roadblock and potential health hazard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 19:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joint Dust Analysis Deflates Big Bang Signal: No definitive evidence for cosmic inflation is found </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 19:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 01:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It certainly is :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 01:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to be that guy but due to the mechanisms of atomic interactions (repulsion) nothing *really* ever touches anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I Touched The Moon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 19:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extreme Worlds May be Habitable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 02:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NewHorizons2015 vs. NASAVoyager 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 08:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Crab (40s) [OC] [3456 x 4608] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 19:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 19:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm not. I saw the image on twitter and thought /r/Geology would appreciate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossiliferous limestone w/ geopetal structures, stylolites, and faults/veins | Gigapan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 20:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mini helicopter could give future Mars rovers a new view </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 02:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 02:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~It'll be interesting to read the paper for the finer details, but to state that asteroids (and especially meteoroids) had magnetic fields seems to highly misleading. Firstly there's the size - meteoroids are far too small to have their own magnetic field, and as for asteroids... it's a bit more complicated. Some asteroids are considered to be the building blocks of planets - remnants that never became planets (thus they would never have become large enough to form a proto-planet and differentiate which would allow for a self sustaining dynamo - which gives rise to a magnetic field), while others are the remains of proto-planet debris. The study looked at pallasites, of which there are two theories regarding their formation. The most common theory is that they represent a region that was undergoing differentiation within a proto-planet. The mixture of olivine within a nickel-iron matrix suggests that they are derived from [the core-mantle region](http://www.philipmetzger.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/asteroid-and-meteorite-types.jpg).~~ 

~~The semantics of it all can be tricky.~~

EDIT: Read the article, and it is entirely different process of magnetic field generation. I'll certainly have to read the actual paper. Thanks for sharing OP.

   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study suggests Canadian government strategy is not enough to preserve caribou population in the boreal forest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 05:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 21:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Faster, no. Diamonds don't like racing.

Actually, typically diamonds are brought to the surface by becoming entrained in kimberlite magmas at depth. It's [well documented](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0377027306000588) that these are the fastest ascending xenolith bearing magmas (typical xenolith bearing magmas ascend upwards of 18km/h) with ascent rates upwards of 108km/h and exit velocities upwards of 720km/h. Fast, yes.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers decipher letters from Herculaneum papyri carbonized by eruption that destroyed Pompeii. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 19:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 04:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One minor critique, they left out another possible source of lunar water - [the moon](http://news.nd.edu/news/37699-water-on-the-moon-its-been-there-all-along/). As was pointed out by Green J., cometary and solar wind impingement origins are [somewhat problematic](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22016644). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research Paper: Diagenesis and clay mineral formation at Gale Crater, Mars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 03:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 18:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the sake of interest, I noticed there wasn't a link provided for SMS (Seafloor Massive Sulphide) mining and thought I would provide one: [Nautilus Minerals Ince.](http://www.nautilusminerals.com/s/Projects-Solwara.asp) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossilized fish skull shakes up the evolutionary history of jaws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 18:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 10:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did a quick calculation in another thread a while ago to show why the expected earthquake is to be so large, which is as follows:

For the sake of interest, the following calculation shows the potential magnitude of the expected mega-thrust EQ. 

The rate of convergence between the Juan de Fuca plate and the North American plate at the Cascadia subduction is ~4cm/yr or 0.04m/yr ([40mm/yr](http://i.imgur.com/EtlFS8F.jpg)). The article records the last great EQ occurrence on Jan. 26, 1700. Given the time since the last great EQ (2015 -1700 = 315yrs) and a rate of convergence of 0.04m/yr we can quickly calculate the expected slip distance from the accumulated deformation. 315yrs*0.04m/yr = 12.6m

The locked portion of the thrust fault is roughly [1000km long and 100km in width](http://i.imgur.com/JBDR3u1.jpg) so the area is 100,000km^2 or 1x10^11 m^2 . Before we can calculate the [Mw](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Moment_magnitude_scale#Definition) we need to know the [Mo](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Seismic_moment), where Mo = ()(area)(slip distance).   is the shear modulus and is 4.5x10^10 N/m^2 . 

Thus Mo = (4.5x10^10 N/m^2 )(1x10^11 m^2 )(12.6m) = 5.67x10^22 Nm

Plugging Mo into the equation for the moment magnitude scale we get the following:

Mw = (2/3)(Log_10Mo)-6.0

Mw = (2/3)(Log_10 5.67x10^22 Nm) - 6.0

Mw = 9.2

**TL; DR** - the potential magnitude of the expected mega-thrust EQ is M9.2

A good site to visit is [Canada's Live Seismogram viewer](http://www.earthquakescanada.nrcan.gc.ca/stndon/wf-fo/index-eng.php). By selecting a station of choice you can watch the seismic activity of that region as it comes in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 23:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   it does not meet the International Commission on Stratigraphy requirements

Not sure I quite follow... Which one of [the listed requirements](http://www.stratigraphy.org/index.php/ics-statutesofics) does it not meet?



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Horizons' first optical navigation images of Pluto and Charon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 19:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ocean Life Faces Mass Extinction, Broad Study Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 18:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 19:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with using coal is that it appears at different times, in different locations. Similarly, any agricultural event will be localized. In paleobiology, the best fossils are the ones that appear quickly, are well preserved, have easily recognizable morphology, have a wide range (global), and disappear suddenly. The reason for this is such that it can be used as a very precise data point for chronological analysis. Many abrupt geological events define the boundaries within geological time and while coal, etc. would certainly be considered abrupt - a better choice is the 1st atomic bomb. It, much like the K-T extinction event, leaves a global signature that is easily recognizable occurring at the same time, everywhere.        </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First atomic blast proposed as start of Anthropocene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 06:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First atomic blast proposed as start of Anthropocene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 06:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 06:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The detection of exo-planets typically depends on the presence of a star. Analyzing how that stars light dims as the planet transits its host star. Another common method is to watch for the star to wobble. If a star is wobbling it's because there is another object acting on it, ie. a planet. In the case of bodies beyond Pluto within the [Kuiper Belt / Oort Cloud](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v424/n6949/images/nature01725-f1.2.jpg) there is no star to watch for a wobble or dimming effect. We are left to watch the orbit of other bodies within our own solar system and how they interact with one another (much like [the discovery of Neptune](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pluto#Discovery)).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 18:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We have no clue what that ratio is at this point. 

That's quite an overstatement. [We certainly do have samples of subsurface terrestrial water](http://i.imgur.com/Nf37A4b.jpg) derived from olivine-bound melt inclusions and other mantle derived mineral assemblages. Certain mantle plumes, such as those that formed the Hawaiian Islands, Iceland, and Baffin Island, appear to have tapped into primitive, un-degassed, deep mantle sources. For example, sampling of Icelandic mantle-plume materials results in D range of between +60 and -140 . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 17:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a planetary scientist, I put my money on a mix from both sources. 

And what are those proportions? So far analysis of D/H^[1](http://www.esa.int/var/esa/storage/images/esa_multimedia/images/2014/12/deuterium-to-hydrogen_in_the_solar_system/15107123-1-eng-GB/Deuterium-to-hydrogen_in_the_Solar_System.jpg), ^[2](http://www.whoi.edu/news-release/OriginEarthWater) ratios shows that if there is a contribution from cometary sources - it's not detectable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 17:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asteroids, yes^[1](http://www.esa.int/var/esa/storage/images/esa_multimedia/images/2014/12/deuterium-to-hydrogen_in_the_solar_system/15107123-1-eng-GB/Deuterium-to-hydrogen_in_the_Solar_System.jpg), ^[2](http://www.whoi.edu/news-release/OriginEarthWater) - not comets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 17:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During planetary accretion asteroids were the main contribution to Earth's mass. Olivine is only present within the upper portion of the upper mantle (seen [here](http://elements.geoscienceworld.org/content/1/2/73/F3.large.jpg)), due to phase transitions (P-T constraints), and will undergo phase transitions to Ringwoodite as depth increases **(**Olivine --  wadsleyite (beta-phase) -- ringwoodite (gamma-phase) -- silicate perovskite plus magnesiowstite**)**. The geochemical composition of Earth's mantle is often normalized to what is known as [CHUR](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chondritic_uniform_reservoir) or Chondritic Uniform Reservoir, where the class of meteorite is a [carbonaceous chondrite](http://www.whoi.edu/news-release/OriginEarthWater) (likely the dominant source of Earth's water).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kwekwaxa'we (Raven) | Kwakwaka'wakw Ceremonial Mask [OC][4608 x 3456] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 07:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 20:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those interested, their associated work can be found in their paper, "[An r-Process Kilonova Associated with the Short-Hard GRB 130603B](http://arxiv.org/abs/1306.3960)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Does Gold Come From? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 18:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 07:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In order to be conclusive (definitive, or at least have very strong evidence for or against the hypothesis) the best approach would be thin section analysis with a petrographic microscope, alongside stable isotope analysis (making use of ICP-MS or TIMS for example) measuring 13C, 18O, 15N, and 34S. Morphology alone can be convincing, especially when paired with other relationships (temporal, spatial, etc.). It will be nice to see what other geobiologists think of her analysis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 07:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EOS degree majored in geology, I'd suggest you read [the paper](http://online.liebertpub.com/doi/pdf/10.1089/ast.2014.1218) in detail. There is compelling evidence that at least some of those morphological sedimentary structures are extremely improbable to create (and last), especially given their temporal, and spatial correlations if they were to be abiogenic in nature. I'm not stating that these morphological sedimentary structures are biogenic in nature; however, I wouldn't brush it off with such apparent ease as a good majority of persons appear to be doing. 

PS - As a side note, "critter tracks" are termed [ichnofacies](http://www.sepmstrata.org/CMS_Images/SeilacherControls.gif) whereas these share similarities to terrestrial microbial mats, which are entirely different from "critter tracks."   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 06:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you able to assess the likelihood of this being microbially formed? 

ap0s hasn't assessed the likelihood by any means. He(?) has not provided any counter arguments to any of the evidence provided in [Noffke's paper](http://online.liebertpub.com/doi/pdf/10.1089/ast.2014.1218). Rather, he has merely stated that he doesn't believe the evidence is compelling without giving supportive arguments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 06:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they could just as easily be erosional features.

Actually, they can't *just as easily* be erosional features. I suggest you read the paper, in detail if you haven't already, in which Noffke provides very compelling evidence, and even includes good arguments as to why they most likely are not erosional features. 

Your comparison to the Allan Hills Meteorite is fallacious (apples to oranges) due to the differences (although there may be some similarities) in scale. Textural features may share similar morpholigcal structures at the nano and microscopic scales between biogenic and abiogenic factors; however, at the macroscopic level distinct differences can be discerned as the similarities between morphological structures of biogenic and abiogenic factors become more distant from one another. This is what allows for the classification of [ichnofacies](http://www.sepmstrata.org/CMS_Images/SeilacherControls.gif) in geology / paleobiology.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 06:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The paper: [Ancient Sedimentary Structures in the 3.7 Ga Gillespie Lake Member, Mars, That Resemble Macroscopic Morphology, Spatial Associations, and Temporal
Succession in Terrestrial Microbialites](http://online.liebertpub.com/doi/pdf/10.1089/ast.2014.1218) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mars Rover Photos Potentially Show Evidence of Ancient Microbial Mats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 06:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 20:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The paper: [Ancient Sedimentary Structures in the 3.7 Ga Gillespie Lake Member, Mars, That Resemble Macroscopic Morphology, Spatial Associations, and Temporal
Succession in Terrestrial Microbialites](http://online.liebertpub.com/doi/pdf/10.1089/ast.2014.1218) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mars Rover Photos Potentially Show Evidence of Ancient Microbial Mats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 20:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 20:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mt. Rundle [from another angle](https://www.flickr.com/photos/luxlaboratories/9641092240/in/photostream/lightbox/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 07:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In her paper, [Ancient Sedimentary Structures in the 3.7 Ga Gillespie Lake Member, Mars, That Resemble Macroscopic Morphology, Spatial Associations, and Temporal
Succession in Terrestrial Microbialites](http://online.liebertpub.com/doi/pdf/10.1089/ast.2014.1218), she makes a very compelling case for her interpretation. While some morphological sedimentary structures she provides, I find, are somewhat questionable, a good portion of her evidence seems extremely difficult to explain by natural means without biological activity, especially given the temporal and spatial relationships. As she states herself, "...the similarities in morphology, but also in distribution patterns with regards to MISS on Earth would be an extraordinary coincidence." 

TL; DR - There is a good chance this is exactly what she has concluded they are, fossil mircobial mats. 

EDIT: And just because, here is a fossil microbial mat from my personal rock collection: [Microbial Mat](http://imgur.com/a/OZxyV) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 03:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm going to have to disagree with you. The *scale* of Hubble images does not permit evidence of life. On the other hand, paleobiologists and geologists use [ichnofacies](http://www.sepmstrata.org/CMS_Images/SeilacherControls.gif) (morphological sedimentary structures) to discern paleoenvironments. In essence, these are potentially 'fossils'. The added spatial and temporal correlations adds further support to the claim. 

 That's science, deal with it.

You obviously lack the qualifications in the necessary field of study (and have not read the paper), so please stop now and you'll save yourself some embarrassment. 

EDIT: Spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 02:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The key word, currently, is *if*. *If* these morphological sedimentary structures are the result of ancient microbial life *then* it proves that there *was* at some point, microbial life on a planet other than Earth. It would not; however, prove that there *is* microbial life elsewhere, but it would certainly seem to increase the probability of such a statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 02:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So no, it does not. 

No it does not what? The title of the article is, "Do Mars Rover Photos Show Potential Signs of Ancient Life?" and it does show *potential* signs of ancient life (ie. there exists the potential that these structures are the result of microbes). It does not; however, *prove* that microbial life was the direct causation to the morphological structures because we need to investigate them further with other methodologies. 

Of importance is the following statement:
...if the Martian structures arent of biological origin," Noffke says, "then the similarities in morphology, but also in distribution patterns with regards to MISS on Earth would be an extraordinary coincidence."

It's very tantalizing evidence provided by a very knowledgeable geobiologist.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 01:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Study: [Ancient Sedimentary Structures in the 3.7 Ga Gillespie Lake Member, Mars, That Resemble Macroscopic Morphology, Spatial Associations, and Temporal
Succession in Terrestrial Microbialites](http://online.liebertpub.com/doi/pdf/10.1089/ast.2014.1218) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study Shows Striking Morphological Similarities Between Martian Sedimentary Structures and Microbial Structures on Earth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 01:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do Mars Rover Photos Show Potential Signs of Ancient Life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 01:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 08:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically any planet that lies in the potentially habitable zone, is likely rocky, and is of a similar size.

Venus actually exists outside of the [habitable zone](http://www.nature.com/news/earth-is-only-just-within-the-sun-s-habitable-zone-1.14353) and can be termed a (dry) [terrestrial planet](http://www.sciencemag.org/content/340/6132/577/F2.large.jpg) as opposed to Earth-like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 07:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and resides in the Goldilocks zone.

Venus is actually outside of the habitable zone while [Earth is just within it](http://www.nature.com/news/earth-is-only-just-within-the-sun-s-habitable-zone-1.14353). Note the following figure: [here](http://www.aanda.org/images/stories/PressRelease/PRaa200708/figure.gif)

Figure 1. Illustration of the habitable zone (HZ) boundaries as obtained by the two teams. The upper part of the figure shows the HZ
of the Sun (at its present age). The red curve shows only the most extreme outer limit of the HZ. The actual outer boundary is indeed
located some where between 1.7 and 2.4 AU. The green limits show the boundaries of the photosynthetic zone as computed with
the model by von Bloh etal. The middle part of the figure shows the limits of the HZ of Gliese 581 computed with the atmospheric models from
Selsis et al. The lower part illustrates the boundaries of the photosynthetic zone computed with the geophysical models from von Bloh et al. The boundaries are shown for several possible ages (5,7,and 9Gyr-old) of the Gliese 581 planetary system. Following the latest estimation, Gliese 581 would be 7 Gyr-old. The purple bars surrounding planets Gliese 581c and d illustrate the variable distance to the star caused by the eccentricity of the orbits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Study Casts Further Doubt on the Impact Event Theory Surrounding the Younger Dryas Cold Period. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 07:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 05:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The basics of fracking (directional drilling, etc.) remain the same but the technologies are actually new. Higher pressures are being used nowadays during well stimulation than could previously be used due to limitations in technologies such as [proppants](http://image.slidesharecdn.com/measuringthesizeandshapeofproppants-120321110131-phpapp02/95/measuring-the-size-and-shape-of-frac-sand-and-other-proppants-12-728.jpg?cb=1332346747). Furthermore, well sites can be relatively close to one another with increasing numbers compared to those during the start up of the fracking boom. There are still a plethora of unknowns; however, and more research is needed to answer a lot of questions in the field with a high level of confidence.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 05:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the possibility exists for larger earthquakes to be induced than from traditional means.

Due to the difference between an EQ of Mw  4.9 and Mw  ~8.0 it is generally accepted that no matter the number of small EQs, they (light EQs) will not be able to produce a Great EQ. I'm curious to know to what extent such a statement can reach. For example, to what extent can a number of minor EQs trigger light, moderate, strong, major, or great EQs? How close does the relation between seismic moments need to be in order for one to trigger the other? 

Thanks for your time, and keep up the much needed research in this field of study.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Curiosity results from AGU: Methane is there, and it's variable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 04:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Down Dragon Alley [OC][3456x2774] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 07:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woolly Mammoth [OC][4608x3456] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 07:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 03:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Zoned Ultramafic Complex](http://petrology.oxfordjournals.org/content/50/2/289.full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jupiter Moon Europa's Giant Geysers Are Missing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 03:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 21:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's certainly not nephrite, and in order to have any confidence in calling it jadeite you're going to need a far better image to analyze than the one provided.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rosetta comet science results Press Conference (AGU 2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 10:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Horizons on Plutos doorstep Press Workshop (AGU 2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 10:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recent findings from NASA's Curiosity rover about modern and ancient Mars Press Conference (AGU 2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 10:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Horizons on Plutos doorstep Press Workshop (AGU 2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 10:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asteroid impacts may have sparked life on Earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 09:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 03:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm shutting down what has been shut down from the scientific community, because there is no evidence to support the claims of the electric universe. Your refusal to acknowledge that fact is not only absurd but delusional. 

I am trying to have a serious discussion. 

No you're not. You are attempting to force me to accept your lunacy as equivalent to scientifically credible evidence - [a logical fallacy](http://rationalwiki.org/wiki/Balance_fallacy). 

How can this model describe what is happening on Enceladus? It can't.

1st - You are equating the historical formation processes of Earth with the historical formation processes of Enceladus. It is incorrect to equate the two. 

2nd - You are playing [God of the Gaps](http://rationalwiki.org/wiki/God_of_the_gaps). Simply because you lack a complete understanding of processes regarding specific bodies in our solar system does not mean you get to fill it with w/e you *feel* like (ie. electric universe). 

You should shut up with your rude and immature behavior. 

Until you grow up and start thinking critically, logical and reasonably you are the one who is being rude and immature. Do not force me to accept your bullshit, and then cry when I retort at the sight of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 21:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just... stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 12:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you under estimate 'most people.' 

The first calculation I did was literally [distance = speed x time](http://www.bbc.co.uk/staticarchive/701b935ef4072b0f79c429a0d461a6cce437f1c2.gif). I would certainly hope most people understand that. 

The next calculation I did (which I also provided a hyperlink for people to click for clarity) was for Mo which is just multiplying three basic variables together: area (which is length x width), distance, and the [shear modulus](http://wikipremed.com/01physicscards600/156a.gif) (admittedly this variable may be a knew concept to some; however, a full understanding of it isn't really required as you'll see).

The final calculation was just as simple as the previous ones. I multiplied 2/3 by the log of Mo and then subtracted 6.0 to find Mw which is 9.2. And, again I provided a link for clarity to Mw.

It's also totally meaningless because of the number of variables.

No, the number of variables present in any set of equations have no bearing on 'meaning.'

I'm sure your calculations hold some meaning

It means that the expected EQ would measure 9.2Mw (or in non-Swahili, a M9.2 on the [Richter scale](http://i.imgur.com/kVsvEzf.jpg) which is a [logarithmic scale](http://www.sms-tsunami-warning.com/theme/tsunami/img/earthquakes/richter-scale/richter_scale_graphic_representation.gif))


    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 11:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But before there was no water, an today, there is large and vast oceans.

http://www.whoi.edu/news-release/OriginEarthWater


I believe in the electric...universe [theory]

That's extremely [unfortunate](http://rationalwiki.org/wiki/Electric_Universe) to say the least and is highly problematic to your understanding of how the world around us operates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 11:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the sake of interest, the following calculation shows the potential magnitude of the expected mega-thrust EQ. 

The rate of convergence between the Juan de Fuca plate and the North American plate at the Cascadia subduction is ~4cm/yr or 0.04m/yr ([40mm/yr](http://i.imgur.com/EtlFS8F.jpg)). The article records the last great EQ occurrence on Jan. 26, 1700. Given the time since the last great EQ (2015 -1700 = 315yrs) and a rate of convergence of 0.04m/yr we can quickly calculate the expected slip distance from the accumulated deformation. 315yrs*0.04m/yr = 12.6m

The locked portion of the thrust fault is roughly [1000km long and 100km in width](http://i.imgur.com/JBDR3u1.jpg) so the area is 100,000km^2 or 1x10^11 m^2 . Before we can calculate the [Mw](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Moment_magnitude_scale#Definition) we need to know the [Mo](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Seismic_moment), where Mo = ()(area)(slip distance).   is the shear modulus and is 4.5x10^10 N/m^2 . 

Thus Mo = (4.5x10^10 N/m^2 )(1x10^11 m^2 )(12.6m) = 5.67x10^22 Nm

Plugging Mo into the equation for the moment magnitude scale we get the following:

Mw = (2/3)(Log_10Mo)-6.0

Mw = (2/3)(Log_10 5.67x10^22 Nm) - 6.0

Mw = 9.2

**TL; DR** - the potential magnitude of the expected mega-thrust EQ is M9.2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 04:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Abundance of elements in the universe](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Abundance_of_the_chemical_elements#Abundance_of_elements_in_the_universe) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 04:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hydroxyl (OH), in geology, is generally synonymous with water. For example, when estimating water content in lunar minerals they look at the hydroxyl content, whether it be in apatite, [anorthosite](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/v6/n3/full/ngeo1735.html) or otherwise. The following isn't a perfect example given the context, but it helps to show how H2O is locked away as a hydroxyl group and a hydrogen atom: http://imgur.com/jy716Bl  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 07:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was in grade three our class was taking a trip to the local swimming pool. I can remember the day, and the general route we took. We were all singing kids songs and were all excited. I was the second last in the back of the line, and we were almost there. There was one cross-walk to go across, up the sidewalk, and we were there. Looking down for a moment I noticed my shoe was untied; however, so I stopped, and knelt down to tie my laces. I was now last in line and almost everyone had crossed the cross-walk. As quickly as I could, I finished tying my laces and stood back up. Everyone had cross the cross-walk by now and I wanted to catch up as to not be left behind. I ran towards the cross-walk, and looked to my right. I couldn't tell if there was a car coming because there was a van parked just off the side of the road but it looked clear from what I could tell. I quickly looked to my left and saw a white car. It was a fair distance away; however, and if I ran I could easily make it in time before it got to the cross-walk. 

I raised my head to gather my senses. I was on a bed of some sort, on my back. There was a rush around me, and all I could really see clearly was the glint of light on the scissors as they rushed to cut through my blood soaked clothing. I remember seeing tears in their faces and hearing crying before everything faded back to black.

In the end my skull had been cracked from ear-to-ear, and I was paralyzed from the waste down. I made a relatively quick recovery I suppose and the parallelization did not last. I can recall asking my father at a young age what it was like when you're dead. He said, "Do you remember what it was like before you were born?" And, that's what it was like for me. There was simply nothing. One instant I was there, and in the blink of an eye I was gone. 

I have had a few other close calls in my life, and only once did I ever see a tunnel. It wasn't when I was going out of consciousness; however, but rather when I came to.        </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stegosaurus gets a Hollywood makeover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 03:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 02:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so improbable that it might as well be impossible for humans to create a runaway greenhouse effect on Earth:

 What weve shown here is that a runaway greenhouse atmosphere that would sterilize the planet is actually possible for Earth, with the amount of sunlight it receives now, says Goldblatt. Fortunately, it would need 10 times more carbon dioxide in the atmosphere to trigger this than burning all of Earths fossil fuels  every bit of coal, oil and gas that exists - would give. - Colin Goldblatt

 - [Study](http://www.uvic.ca/assets2012/docs/pdfs/hidden/ngeo1892-aop.pdf)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientific riches await Philae comet lander, if it wakes up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 23:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 07:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's one I took of the Milky Way as well](https://www.flickr.com/photos/luxlaboratories/15143169535/). Didn't even use a fast lens, f3.5 (fisheye) ISO800 and 30s exposure. I made the mountains silhouette in post, as well as other minor tweaks to get the Milky Way to 'pop.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 09:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [A number of possibilities exist](http://photojournal.jpl.nasa.gov/catalog/PIA19088); however, the most likely (imo) are serpentinization^1, and methane clathrate release^2 . 

1) Serpentinization: occurs on Earth all the time, creating a group of minerals called serpentine minerals (serpentinite). When basalt - oceanic crust - (composed primarily of pyroxene, and calcic plagioclase feldspar, and minor olivine) reacts with the ocean water it alters to serpentine minerals which are hydrous (containing H2O/OH). The process is exothermic and produces methane (CH4) in the process. An interesting region on Earth in which this reaction is the key support system of life in the deep ocean is known as [Lost City](http://www.lostcity.washington.edu/science/chemistry/serpentinization.html). The general formula for the reaction is as follows:

[Olivine + water + carbonic acid  serpentine + magnetite + methane](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Serpentinite#Serpentinite_reactions)

What I find interesting is the production of magnetite, and heat from the reaction. There may be detectable magnetic anomalies in regions that are undergoing serpentinization, and there should also be anomalous heat. Not only does this have implications for future research, but the magnetite could act as a food source for bacteria, the heat provides an energy source and there is liquid water - a microbes paradise. 

2) Methane clathrates: Ancient deposits of methane could be trapped in ice [methane clathrate](http://www.giss.nasa.gov/research/features/200409_methane/crystal.jpg) within the subsurface. During warming episodes, or anything that may cause an insatiability (tectonism, etc.) the clathrates could become unstable, and vent into the local atmosphere causing periodic spikes.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 09:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is old news... [15 May 2013](http://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-22544761) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
