<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9063</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any way to increase difficulty in just cause 3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 16:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just picked it up last night and it's pretty fun, but I'm noticing it's extremely easy. I've put a few hours into it and I still haven't been able to die. Was a big fan of the last just cause where did the mini map and health go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 00:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I mean https://www.reddit.com/r/maschine/comments/2pt0p6/my_new_favorite_site_that_converts_youtube_videos/cn0cv3o I know it's possible I've seen a couple different threads on ni forums saying it's possible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 00:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/maschine/comments/2pt0p6/my_new_favorite_site_that_converts_youtube_videos/cn0cv3o this is what I mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 00:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steinberg ur22 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 23:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Microchopping is really hard to master, pulling different sounds from multiple samples and getting them to fit well in a mix can be hard. Like I said though, it's all about how it sounds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whip vs bag? What do you prefer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 19:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tried searching this question and couldn't find it, what do you prefer? I'm still trying to decide myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 18:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Internal is just what is going on in maschine, I want to sample things off YouTube and movies and shit on my computer without having to convert them to wav.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 18:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/slowcooking/comments/3o9eel/mozzarella_stuffed_meatballs/ got it from this sub, it was the highest up voted post for the whole sub  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 17:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would sample an actual guitar bass line and get a nice tone, pitch it lower probably and then add distortion and compression. just me though or a sine wave with distortion and a filter on top with compression </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to record computer output through interface into maschine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 17:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had my maschine for almost a year now and I love it. I've always thought you need a program like sound flower to record internal sounds into maschine but I've done some research and have seen a couple people in threads saying you can just use a input of your interface to record. I can't figure out of to route it in maschine though. Tried searching but unable to find and answer and I'm sure it's a simple answer too. Thanks to anyone who helps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 15:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's honestly whatever sounds good to you man. J dilla is known as one of the best samplers and half of his beats are just 4 bar loops, other artists microchop there samples. I find its easiest to find a 4 bar sample, chop it into 16 chops (for my 16 pad maschine) and then play around over my drums to see what I like. You have 16 one bar loops making it easier for timing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 15:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 13:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually just a sample in uptown  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 13:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/yAf4CPfQFlE check out this video it's how she made uptown. It wasn't even a chord progression it's just a sample  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time using my Crockpot! Made the mozzarella filled meatballs posted last month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 02:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 21:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was in the summer I think maybe the end of summer sale they usually have  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 16:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally sampling this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 01:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's kind of wierd that only Ontario smokes these and they're huge here. Some people do just put tobacco under the bowl but they call that "batch bowls". I don't really know the story about how they got so big but they do get you alot higher using less weed, which is a big reason why so many high school kids smoke them. Do get really addictive because of the nicotine and makes quitting 10 worse because you're essentially quitting weed and tobacco at the same time. The doctors in my town hate them because apparently it is waaay worse for your lungs to have weed and tobacco in your lungs at the same time as apposed to one or the other
Edit: the name for them is "poppers" or "pops"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 00:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [these](http://imgur.com/6hQBHXM) You can find them at any head shop in Ontario they were really big in the small town I come from. They make it easier because you can just stamp the weed into the bowl after you pack your tip. I smoked them for a few months and they do get you a hell of alot higher but they're terrible on your lungs and alot more addictive then just weed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 23:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome thanks for taking the time to type that out. Coconut oil is better then butter? I've heard of that before but never tried it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 22:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on where you get it but they will give you a percentage so you know how much thc there is. It won't be as strong as a dab but will taste better. They are potent without a tolerance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 21:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you? This year's been really shitty for skiing so far, I am on the east coast though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 20:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol sounds like me and my friends in grade 6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 20:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People around here smoke poppers, they rip off the tip of the cigarette and put it under there weed. We even have specific pieces you can buy in stores for pops. Some people even ripoff half a cigarette under there weed. It wasn't the tobacco </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 20:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've made edibles before, never with vaped weed before. Do you have experience specifically with vaped weed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty sweet thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone here make edibles from there vaped weed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't use my vaporizer much but I am going to start using it more soon. I only have a couple grams already vaped but I'm wondering how much I'd need for a batch of brownies? (around half a cup of butter) I was thinking around 20 grams but it's vaped so it won't be that strong. Someone with experience help me out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who rolls prerolls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Canada so there are no pre rolls here but I've always wondering who rolls them. They are always a perfect cone and they probably need to produce and Insane amount. Is there people being paid to roll joints all day or is it a machine? Help me out here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should have put a carbon filter on it! The water would never go yellow or smell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where'd you order that long whip?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 18:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro those are not cbd..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 18:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude your fine, all my bud comes in the mail as long as it's not going over borders your fine. Next time make sure you don't click signature required. Some sites have it checked off automatically  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 18:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean extract infused e juices?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 18:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could probably still find someone that would pay 150 for it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 18:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use weed like this for joints!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 17:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use 3osx if you are using FL studio  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 17:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> numark and technica turntables through a Steinberg interface into maschine mostly. Use my mk2 for alot of stuff but trying to get more analog. I rent synths from my local store quite a bit. Experimenting with the micro korg right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 17:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Following everyone back https://soundcloud.com/ustincox </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 17:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive been extremely impressed with the maschine expansions I've purchased. I have about 13 or 14 (got the 9 for 99 deal) and I have been blown away. So many sounds and kits ready to go on maschine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 15:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Il post a pic when I'm home I got a technica and numark turntables, akai mpk mini, maschine mk2, Steinberg interface, rokit 5s, audio technica headphones (not sure the model) and a shitty laptop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 22:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally just saw those! I think I've changed my mind... A little bit extra but totally worth it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 22:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I'm trying to get prepared before I start school while I still have a job! Kind of looking at it like an investment too because me and my girlfriend really enjoy cooking (she's a chef) so I don't want to cheap out!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 22:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'm kind of a freak about what I put into my body, mostly from my anxiety haha. But who wouldn't want a better tasting, healthier dab?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 21:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I'm finding that is the general consensus  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 21:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool thanks for the insight. I think the general consensus is that it's probably better without it which helps alot!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 20:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I really wish they shipped to Canada!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 20:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish they shipped to Canada!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 20:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish they shipped to Canada!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 20:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right, but I have always vacced everything for 48 hours regardless. I would never smoke unpurged oil  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 20:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only 75 bucks compared to 50. And I'm not living at the college I have my own apartment and don't start school for a couple months  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is iStir worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 19:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting my first Crockpot tonight (first year college) and I want to get a good one so I never need a new one. My options are pretty much between the cheap no name Loblaws ones that are pretty much just a basebones slow cooker or a real crock pot. There are 2 options for the crock pot one has the new iStir feature that automatically stirs it. Is this needed? I'm already spending a decent amount of money so I may as well is what I'm thinking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 18:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get all my bud in the mail never once has it not came. As long as everything stays domestic there wouldn't be any problems. I never saw this thread though so it doesn't really matter to me. Sounds like a cool idea though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 18:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still have to purge iso, atleast a heat purge  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 17:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a new hobby, I like to get high and play guitar or make beats  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 17:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't purge it at all?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 16:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear every week someone posts this or "I want to make beats where do I start"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 15:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs some purging  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 16:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toronto producer here let's work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 22:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm that's interesting. Maybe it did start happening after 2.0 because I've never used maschine before 2.0 so it could be the case  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 04:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These were just free last week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 00:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didnt see this till an hour ago... didnt read the rules either so I ended up cooking something up haha I know its late as fuck but feedback would be appreciated https://soundcloud.com/ustincox/okc-6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 23:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't open projects that you started in the standalone program in the vst, I know it sucks to hear  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 22:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a sp but you can sample vinyl in your maschine you know. Maschine is really good for live stuff tbh I don't know why you'd want a sp over that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 22:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you even try searching this sub first? This shit gets asked every week...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 03:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here in Canada there are tons of companies that do alcohol delivery for 5$ flat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 00:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you can't. Read the rules. There are daily feedback threads where you can post it and it will get buried under 300 other posts but you definitely cannot post singles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 23:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't give any details about what you want to do with it, your budget, how much experience you have etc. With the information you've given me I'd say get the mk2 it's alot faster,  more options, more screens. You can get things done alot quicker with the mk2. The mk1 things will just take longer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 23:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's ignorant haha, he said after he dropped cellar door he was done rapping forever. He's said he's going to quit multiple times and never has  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 23:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming from someone who's been following  them religiously since the start, they have blown up alot in the past 2 years  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 22:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? You can't post singles there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Geezy - What it is [Toronto street rap] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 22:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 22:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that I'm aware of, there just happened to be one for the city I moved to. You can always make your own </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 21:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 21:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 to 5 million </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 21:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for Android. Or ios when I used to have an iPhone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 20:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also have android an ios apps! A must for any music head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 01:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao I know, the hurt is real  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 00:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got mine used and it was hard as fuck to get all my software downloaded, plus I didn't even get one of the programs that came with it (kontakt I think). I have to use the guy that I bought it from's account to download the software and once I get a new computer I could see that being a problem. I did save a but of money but I kind of wish I just paid the extra and got a new one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 20:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huntsman?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 20:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a couple of those in my local ent sub too. Sketchy forsure, I never reply  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 20:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word. My soundcloud should be on my flair. I guess il just stick to uploading to soundcloud and YouTube  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Native instruments Black Friday sale! Lots of expansions and vsts 50% off for a limited time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 19:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Native Instruments Black Friday 50% sale. Lots of expansions and vsts 50% off for a limited time! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 19:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 19:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to your record store and sift through the dollar bin. I guarantee you'll find an lp that is all bell songs. Lots of them out there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it worth sending beats out yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 19:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been producing for a year now and have been progressing alot at a steady pace. I have some stuff that I am impressed and happy with but I feel like I'm not at my full potential yet. (now that I think of it I probably never will feel like I'm at my full potential haha). It takes alot of time to find the proper emails and sift through my projects and actually send them out. I work alot so I'm trying to make the most of my free time. Anyone else in the same boat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 19:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know if you work in the oil fields alot of company's test for everything including alcohol. Mostly because there are alot of alcoholics out there and they can't have people operating machinery while intoxicated  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 19:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh that's an interesting analogy. Anyone have any more info on this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Geezy - Lunatic [Toronto street rap] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 15:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 13:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will check this out when I'm off work, sounds like a dope idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 00:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol huh... I have all of those in vhs still...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 19:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Power Tools for Synthesizer Programming is the only book I've found usefull. Other than that a couple copies of sound on sound? There aren't many books that will help much. Just fuck with your laptop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 18:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mawfk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 16:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch, is it still under warranty? If it is they'll repair it but if not they will send a new one for a cheaper price </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 15:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear ya, I'm currently with that same problem looking into an mpc myself for christmas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 15:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you checked out maschine? You say you want to manipulate your samples into something completely different and that is the best part about maschine. You have endless possibilities for effects and manipulation. You should definitely check it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 15:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 05:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just use your hardware, lots of programs are like that including maschine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 04:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you start this post by saying you know there are already alot of posts like this?? This gets posted every week I guarantee if you made one search you would have found 20 threads the exact same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 01:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lady bugs we need more fuckin ladybugs! (tpb reference)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 00:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Online would be your best bet tbh wait till cyber monday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 19:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ottawa Ontario  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found while closing a pool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 18:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 16:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word!  So are mine I thought I was tripping. It's really annoying to when you want to listen to a certain song. The 36 Chambers is a really bad press too it skips at the same point on a certain song and isn't that loud  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 03:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maschine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 23:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You never watched trailer park boys??  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 23:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They never warned that they were going to commit war crimes and shoot  defensless pilots as they parachute from there jets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 23:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What your saying is true, but it is also a war crime to shoot defensless pilots as they parachute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 22:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they warn them about shooting there pilots as they defenslessly parachute from the jets?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 22:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is definitely a war crime  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 15:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My apartment has no vents. Am I at risk for carbon monoxide? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 15:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in an old building that has no vents. There are two fans that go outside I think (kitchen and bathroom), and lots of windows. The area I live in gets very cold in the winter (ottawa) and I can't really have my windows open all day. Over the weekend I never left the apartment because I wasn't feeling well and didn't have any windows open. I haven't bought a co detector because I believe the company I am leasing from should provide it (minto) as it is a law to have one in Ottawa. Since this weekend I have just always kept a window open but I won't be able to do this all winter. Not sure if this is even the right sub but someone direct me if not. 
I am a male, 19, Caucasian. Also if someone could give me any signs to watch for carbon monoxide poisoning that would be helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My apartment has no vents in it. Am I at risk for carbon monoxide? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 14:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 01:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyday, I love listening to my stuff. It makes me feel good knowing I made this myself and it still sounds awesome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BEAT TAPE] Vol 1 - subject9063 (OC) 5 beats 5 minutes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 21:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 19:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ocarina of time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 19:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure you can broadcast anything to twitch. You just need a screen recorder if not mistaken  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 18:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think they're going to stop just because they've been charged with war crimes?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 17:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would that change anything?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 05:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only about a [2] and I still had a hard time reading that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
