<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3404</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New poster for Keeping Up With The Joneses (Zach Galifianakis, Jon Hamm, Isla Fisher, Gal Gadot ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 10:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rebecca Ferguson Joins Hugh Jackman, Zac Efron, Michelle Williams, and Zendaya in Musical Biopic, The Greatest Showman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 04:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stanley Tucci returning for Transformers: The Last Knight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 04:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of the good romantic comedy movies that release between 2015 - now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 04:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted this question few weeks ago and /r/movies and I want to hear some answers from the user of this subreddit. I asked this question because My friends and I want to watch some recent romantic comedy movies before we watch Bridget Jones Baby. Yes, I watched the first two movies recently and I think the franchises is one of the better romcoms.

Can you help me find good romantic comedy movies that release between 2015 - now? Because My Friends and I are looking for those movies.

Thank you

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Poster gave me a confused boner. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just watched the Geo-Political Psychological thriller kino Captain America: Civil War (1994) and I must say it still holds up after all these years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FRESH] Colbie Calliat - Like Tomorrow Never Comes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Avengers: Age of Ultron just released, this truck parked in front of my parents house. I thought this sub would appreciate it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sebastian Stan Joins Steven Soderbergh's Logan Lucky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Funny Picture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 11:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [THROWBACK] Rihanna - Rehab featuring Justin Timberlake. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 08:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keajaiban Reza Artamevia yang Terancam Tenggelam Bersama Aa Gatot Brajamusti. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain America: Civil War Extended Gag Reel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Click Here.](https://twitter.com/FiImFeed/status/770635978956570624)

If this post violate some rules, mods can delete this post.

Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VMA Videos Become Available Online After Vevo, MTV Strike Distribution Deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 12:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aa Gatot Brajamusti Ditangkap Polisi terkait Kasus Sabu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 05:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Blind Brother Official Trailer (2016) (Adam Scott, Nick Kroll, Jenny Slate) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 16:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carly Rae Jepsen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 03:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taylor Swift Is Skipping the MTV VMAs 2016: She 'Was Never Scheduled to Attend' Says Source </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 03:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An analysis of 2016 Summer Movies Compared to the Previous years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 17:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netizen Sebut Presiden Jokowi Sebagai 'Lady Gagal' Dilaporkan ke Polda Sumut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 16:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jessica Biel, Richard Schiff, Tommy Lee Jones, Alec Baldwin, James Marsden, Milla Jovovich and Luke Tennie are joinning Rob Reiner's Shock and Awe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some of the former indonesian child singers made this music video to prevent Indonesian Children from some brainwashing children songs such as 'Lelaki Kardus'. #SaveLaguAnak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 13:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> War Dogs Almost Starred Shia LaBeouf and Jesse Eisenberg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 14:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #GingerLivesMatter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 14:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time when two females around same age got cast, someone is suggesting a lesbian scene. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 06:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Gunn: "If youre complaining about the ethnicity of Mary Jane your life is too good." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 05:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FRESH] Ingrid Michaelson - Celebrate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 04:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jack Reacher: Never Go Back (2016) poster (Tom Cruise, Cobie Smulders) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 01:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Marsden, Toby Kebbell, Lucy Punch Join Sofia Vergara in Ensemble Comedy The Female Brain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 14:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello, this is Sisiwkanamaru and I am a Disney Shill. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 03:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I showed one of the mod my credibility as a Disney shill and they gave me this flair. You can ask me anything about shilling with Disney.

These are my proof of my shilling on Reddit

* [Zootopia](https://np.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/467uio/i_just_got_back_from_the_screening_of_zootopia/)
* [Captain America: Civil War](https://np.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/4hax8w/what_was_the_best_film_you_saw_this_week_42516/d2oq7gj)
* [Star Wars: Rogue One](https://np.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/4xbelm/star_wars_rogue_one_trailer_2/d6e1imw)

Ask me Anything about this shilling with Disney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surf's Up 2: WaveMania - Teaser Trailer (John Cena, Undertaker, Triple H, Paige, and Mr. McMahon) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 03:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arrival (2016) Teaser poster (Amy Adams, Jeremy Renner, Forest Whitaker) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batal Dikukuhkan sebagai Paskibraka 2016, Gloria Natapradja Hamel Dikabarkan Stres. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 13:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Shape of Water: Guillermo del Toros Cold War Fantasy Begins Shooting With Michael Shannon, Sally Hawkins, Richard Jenkins, Doug Jones, Michael Stuhlbarg and Octavia Spencer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 00:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Birthday to our Feminazi, Jennifer Lawrence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 16:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jason Isaacs joins Dev Patel, Armie Hammer, and Nazanin Boniadi in Hotel Mumbai. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 11:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If this post reached 200 upvotes, I want the moderators of this sub to change the theme to Walt Disney Studios theme. This includes the Walt Disney Picture, Walt Disney Animation Studios, Pixar, Lucasfilm, and Marvel Studios. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 16:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best films of 2016 so far, according to Empire Magazine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> the New Rogue One: A Star Wars Story Trailer, enjoy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 04:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dave Franco, Olivia Munn, Jackie Chan to voice Lego Ninjago Movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 02:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All-Female 'Magic Mike' Spinoff Looking to Avoid 'Ghostbusters'-Type Backlash - Warners will make 'Magic Michelle,' for around $70 million, according to sources, about $80 million less than the reported $150 million that 'Ghostbusters' cost. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 16:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, this movie leads by **Alexandra Daddario, Alison Brie, Amanda Seyfried and Jennifer Conelly.**  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nathan Fillion and Martin Short to Guest Star on Modern Family. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 04:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Didn't like Suicide Squad? Try Sinister Squad (2016), a movie about a group that consists of a bunch of Criminals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 18:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of the good romantic comedy movies that release between 2015 - now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 18:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently I watched Trainwreck with Amy Schummer and I really enjoyed it. I have not paid much attention to this genre recently. 

Can you help me find good romantic comedy movies that release between 2015 - now? Because me and my friends are looking for those movies.

Thank you

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am watching the movie for the awesome dialogues so I can quote it when I want and it sounds cool. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 13:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If I start to hate superhero movies for editing, or any movie, then am I watching the movie for editing?
 
 I am watching for the plot and awesome dialogues so I can quote it when I want and sound cool...

[Context](https://np.reddit.com/r/DC_Cinematic/comments/4w9ny3/is_it_just_me_or_are_critics_more_harsh_towards/d656r4x) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Direction got a new competitor, One Erection. One of them will get a role in a Christopher Nolan Movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 12:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joel Edgerton eyeing a role in Red Sparrow opposite Jennifer Lawrence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 11:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forget 3D at the movies, 4DX is the next big thing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 07:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harry Styles prepared to get minfucked by our lord, Christopher Nolan and His Crews. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 06:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hellen Mirren in Fast 8 with Vin Diesel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 15:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shailene Woodley to star in film about craziest OkCupid date ever, No Baggage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 14:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We got the new essay. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 02:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As a savvy veteran who has reported the industry for years John Campea, it is really THAT much of a stretch to see a certain amount of BIAS going on in favor of Disney and/or Marvel over the past couple of years? Seriously....bias exists in every OTHER industry including those who report the news and those who critique....whether it be politics, finance, or sports. You can't deny this - it can sometimes last for six months or six days and the favored players (or companies or teams) can shift dramatically like that - we've seen it with Donald Trump, Bernie Sanders, Tim Tebow, Lebron James, Tesla, Apple, etc......at any given time, there will often be a bandwagon of support towards one particular team or group, how is the entertainment industry immune to that then?? :) Rewind back just four years ago and there was a ton of goodwill towards Chris Nolan from The Dark Knight and Inception that spilled over into the release of The Dark Knight Rises....how it was covered, how it was reviewed, etc. This is not a new phenomenon and at this particular time - probably for the past couple of years - there has been an increasingly obvious bias TOWARDS Disney/Marvel properties online and even from the trades. And it pervades so many of the reviews I have read and/or watched, "oh here we go again with Zack Snyder....you know he still produced this one?" "I don't know....we DID hear about all of those re-shoots." "Wow it looks like they're trying to copy 'Guardians of the Galaxy with all of these music cues." NEWSFLASH: Guardians of the Galaxy was NOT the first film to use retro pop tunes in its marketing and/or to play ironically throughout the movie just as an example. ;) Bias exists and even though it can shift from one player to the other (see the coverage that Trump was receiving six months ago vs. now for an example), you can't deny it. ;) Regardless is it absurd for any fanboys to believe that shutting down Rotten Tomatoes is a solution?? Yes of course....but crazy fanboys exist for every property: it was Marvel fanboys who drove Joss Whedon off of Twitter last summer. Is the most obvious solution for Warners/DC to make a certain type of film that will play better with critics? Probably....but that doesn't mean there isn't a bias nor that it should be ignored either.

 To further elaborate, bias can take many forms but it's usually a shift towards the perceived "winner" at that particular time....it helped Donald Trump get the Republican nomination with hundreds of millions in free TV time, it helped Finding Dory get a 90% plus Rotten Tomatoes score even though I don't know one person who didn't think the film was "ok" - sorry the two most obvious RECENT examples are Disney and Trump, but I am not equating the two at all.

 [A Comment From A Savvy Film Professional \(not me\)](https://np.reddit.com/r/DC_Cinematic/comments/4w1c19/on_critics/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sony shills just paid Rotten Tomatoes to give Ghostbusters good reviews and BvS bad reviews. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 16:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suicide Squad's costume designer Kate Hawley breaks the Skwad's attire down, piece by piece. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 13:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a Disney and Marvel Shill and I just watched Suicide Squad. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 10:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gave this movie 3 out of 10 because kids will have puberty faster if they watched this movie with Margot Robbie, Jared Leto, and the Edginess of this movie.

[uj]

I watched Suicide Squad and you can ask me anything about this movie

[/uj] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not a movie but Leonardo DiCaprio to Host Hillary Clinton Fundraiser. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 16:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pokmon Sun and Moon Is Getting Vibrating Peripheral Bracelet, Z-Ring from Takara Tomy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 11:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ***Experience the Z-Ring for Real on Your Own Arm!***
 
 Tomy International will be releasing a Z-Ring item for sale, timed to match up with the launch of Pokmon Sun and Pokmon Moon. 
 
 When a player uses a Z-Move in Pokmon Sun and Pokmon Moon, his or her real-life Z-Ring will light up, vibrate, and play sounds to go along with the video and sounds in the game. With this new experience, players will feel the force of these overwhelming Z-Moves with even more realism! Please look forward to more details about the Z-Ring to come from Tomy International.

 [Official Site](http://www.pokemon-sunmoon.com/en-us/z-moves/)

[How the Z-Ring works in-game (left) and the physical model](http://i.imgur.com/mdnbzxa.jpg)

[Info from Kotaku and Takara Tomy](http://imgur.com/a/eJk74)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aubrey Plaza and Elizabeth Olsen join Ingrid Goes West, a dark comedy about a young woman who becomes obsessed with a social media star </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 06:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SS] Suicide Squad: exclusive new look at Joker and Enchantress from EMPIRE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 17:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Dano will make his directorial debut, Wildlife, with a script he co-wrote with Zoe Kazan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 07:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wacraft and BvS are underrated gems. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 04:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FRESH VIDEO] JoJo - Fuck Apologies feat. Wiz Khalifa. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 16:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does any critic justify that Marvel's fantasy cape flick, Thor: The Dark World is better than DC's German Expressionism Arthurian Thriller kino, Batman v Superman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 12:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kate McKinnon, Jason Bateman, T.J. Miller, and Olivia Munn in Office Christmas Party (December 9, 2016). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 14:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DC and Warner just converted this Marvel Shill (Our Prophet Stuckmann) into their Shill in two videos and this video is the evidence. B R A V O S N Y D E R. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 06:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Trek Beyond is ripping of one of the Marvel's Space Opera, Les Gardiens de la Cosmos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 04:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's not forget the hunk Brendan Fraser used to be... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 14:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Trek Beyond - Chris Stuckmann Movie Review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 14:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Cast of DC's Legends of Tomorrow are hunting Pokmon currently after they hunted Vandal Savage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 02:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They hunt Pokmon right now after they hunted Vandal Savage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 02:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Marvel Cinematic Universe succeeding and What Other Lessons Should Other Would-be Franchises Take from It. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Movie Critics are not Movie Critics if they think that Ghostbusters (2016) is a good movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 10:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not a movie but the feud between Taylor Swift and Kim Karadashian is the best gladiator match of all time in our history. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 12:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to talk about this feud that is better and more convincing than German Expressionism, Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice and Geo-political psychological thriller, Captain America: Civil War.

Also, not a poplular opinion but this feud is better than the feud between /r/movies and the newest Ghostbusters . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the most legendary Pokestops in my town. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 04:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/fuck2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 06:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fred Savage (The Wonder Years   The Grinder) is Hooked on Pokmon Go </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 13:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone want to join this Pokemon GO meetup? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 10:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ghostbusters (2016) IMAX Poster. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 03:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our prophet, Christ Stuckmann said Ghostbusters (2016) is an okay movie and better than Ghostbusters II. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 10:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scarlett Johansson Names Black Widow Her Favorite Role </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 02:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW a movie put an unnecessary romantic subplot that pander to female audiences. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 05:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am glad that someone mentioned this foreign underrated gem. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 05:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Heyday of the Insensitive Bastards poster (James Franco, Natalie Portman, Kate Mara, Kristen Wiig, Jimmy Kimmel, Amber Tamblyn, Rico Rodriguez, Abigail Spencer, and more) (Trailer inside) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 16:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain America: Civil War hits Digital HD September 2 and 3D Blu-ray, Blu-ray, DVD, VOD and Digital SD September 13 for NA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 15:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [THROWBACK] Nelly - Tilt Ya Head Back (featuring Christina Aguilera) (Britney Spears demo version snippet in comment) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 14:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This comment hit two circlejerks in one post, 1994 is the most awesome year for movies and Avatar does not have a cultural impact. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 23:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The LEGO Batman Movie is a 90-minute Easter egg, according to Lord and Miller </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 23:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Film Academy did not invite any /r/movies subscribers to Make Major Push in Diversity. How do /r/movies represent their kinos so underrated gems like Moon (1994) can be nominated for Oscar???? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 23:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We should apologize to Zack Snyder because we were wrong about him. BvS is bad is bad because the editing not because his direction and vision. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 16:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Customize Your Converse Kicks With 'Suicide Squad' Illustrations on NIKEiD. Choose from Harley Quinn, The Joker and Deadshot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 09:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bridget Joness Baby Trailer #2 (Rene Zellweger, Colin Firth, and Patrick Dempsey) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 17:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tyrese Gibson Returns for Transformers: The Last Knight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 06:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE think that Rotten Tomatoes is a SJW propaganda? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 23:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A New Image of Colin Trevorrow's The Book Of Henry (Jacob Tremblay, Jaeden Lieberher, Maddie Ziegler, and Naomi Watts) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 17:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> we are going to get shitty rehashed, unoriginal comedies or action sequels that don't need any brain power to understand if people cannot appreciate my Kino </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 10:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hope Paul Feig's Ghostbusters tanks so Hollywood stops catering to the SJWs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 17:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> United Kingdom will join Spiderman: Homecoming if they vote to leave Europe Union after the Referendum on June, 2016. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 05:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Both Sony and Paramount Jockey to Develop Agatha Christie Films, Sony is courting Alicia Vikander and Paramount is eyeing Emma Stone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 13:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If this post is reached 252 upvotes, Sony and Marvel will let me join Spiderman: Homecoming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 06:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jason Statham's Rick Ford will be back in Spy 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 12:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marvel Doctor Strange and Guardians of the Galaxy volume 2 are confirmed to be risky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 17:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Legend of Tarzan - "Conquer" Final Video (Alexander Skarsgrd, Samuel L. Jackson, Margot Robbie, Djimon Hounsou, and Christoph Waltz) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 16:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vera Farmiga will face Liam Neeson in new thriller The Commuter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hollywood does not want China to be successful and these analysis explain the reasons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 17:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Critics is one of the reason that movie industry is lack of innovations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 08:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NA] Finding Dory got A and Central Intelligence got A- on Cinemascore. How these scores going to be affect their domestic opening weekend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 06:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We cannot let kids, children, toddler, and poop machine destroy our experience when we are watching our nostalgia Kino. It is a serious business. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 17:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FPI visited Kompas Gramedia group and discussed the "angel berita' of Satpol PP raid few days ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 04:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piss off /r/moviescirclejerk in one sentence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 17:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't have to be your opinion, but it has to be something that would get a whole bunch of people riled up. Stolen from [here](https://np.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/4odzhw/piss_off_rmovies_in_one_sentence/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman v Superman is considered as Christian Drama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 04:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the cast and characters of Storks (Andy Samberg, Kelsey Grammer, Keegan-Michael Key, Jordan Peele, Ty Burrell, Jennifer Aniston, and Katie Crown.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 23:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/movies moderator are a bunch of racists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 19:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They keep censoring the news about Donald Glover joinning Spiderman: Homecoming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Capekinos are light-geek culture and Warcraft is actual geek culture. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 11:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rotten Tomatoes is fun-cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 09:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elizabeth Banks May Join Cate Blanchett and Sandra Bullock in the Oceans Eleven Spinoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 05:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An open letter to Duncan Jones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 23:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE think that Critics hate our Kino, Warcraft for no reason? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 18:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and also, DAE think that critics just an elitist butthurt SJW who supports their agenda like new Ghostbusters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raffi Ahmad dan Syahrini Jadi Pengisi Suara Film "Finding Dory" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 15:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [THROWBACK] Nelly Furtado - Explode (One of the most underrated songs from her) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 08:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zack Snyder looks Jacked (Getting Ready For Justice League) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 16:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prophet Stuckmannn reviewed our Game Kino, Warcraft. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 11:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that CIA's other name is Bill Wilson. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 14:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cate Blanchett Is Circling The All-Female Oceans Eleven Film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 05:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This pleb does not understand an absolute kinograph. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 16:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monique Ganderton (Stunt double for charlize Theron   Nicole Kidman) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 09:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NA] May 2016 Box Office Highlights: 'Captain America'   'Jungle Book' Topped the Month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 04:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I do not want to give my money to the millionaires. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 18:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Akankah Jadi Blunder?] Kampanye Pertamina di FB Malah Bangkitkan Kecintaan pada Shell? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 16:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SJW just ruined our day. This billboard should be a campaign for Jennifer Lawrence to stop doing X-Men Kino. Because this is X-Men not X-Women. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 12:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most underrated Heroes of /r/movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 17:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is something missing in this comment. I think it is a common sense. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 08:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [THROWBACK] Vanessa Hudgens - Come Back To Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 06:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> B R A V O S I N G E R. I think he will made a history with the most boring superhero kino ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 16:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cobie Smulders and Scarlett Johansson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 15:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS] Zack Snyder's live reaction on Captain America: Civil War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 17:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ----------- Please upvote to the left to increase Warcraft's Rotten Tomatoes score. One Upvote equal to one percent increase in Warcraft's Rotten Tomatoes score </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 15:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently, [this movie is on 19%](http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/warcraft/), so your upvote or upsnap is really meaningful to this movie. This movie are really gritty Shrek.

Thank you

**EDIT 1, Monday May 30, 2016, 14:08 GMT:** 

The movie is now on 33%. It is higher than Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice, please upvote this thread to increase the Rotten Tomatoes score.

**EDIT 2, Monday May 30, 2016, 15:24 GMT:** 

The movie is now on 44%. It is higher than The Angry Birds Movie, please upvote this thread to increase the Rotten Tomatoes score.

**EDIT 3, Monday May 30, 2016, 16:24 GMT:** 

The movie is now on 58%. It is higher than Man of Steel, please upvote this thread to increase the Rotten Tomatoes score.

**EDIT 4, Tuesday May 31, 2016, 1:48GMT:** 

The movie is now on 123% and we only need 100% to reach our goal. It is higher than any movies, please upvote this thread to increase the Rotten Tomatoes score. Any excess point on this movie will be used as additional increase in Rotten Tomatoes score for the upcoming sequel.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ghostbusters (2016) just got a valuable shill. He is on the Sony's payroll to support this movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 05:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Uj] I want to post this MovieBob's opinion about new Ghostbusters on /r/movies but I am afraid of the reaction. [/uj] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 18:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3D Sucks   Expensive. P.S. B R A V O N O L A N </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 16:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Gorgeous Captain America: Civil War Concept Art </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 14:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NA] Friday Box Office Estimates: X-Men Apocalypse $26.4m; Alice TTLG $9.7m; The Angry Birds $5m </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 18:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American critics like to think they are the center of the world and European critics are more sophisticated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 13:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

 [American critics like to think they are the centre of the world. Batman V Superman showed the power bad reviews can have. American critics feel the need to give bad reviews so they can exercise their power.](https://np.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/4l4ktw/the_difference_in_opinions_on_the_warcraft_movie/d3ka26r)

 [European critics are more sophisticated. They don't care if they have an effect on the movie. They just want to write the truth. **I'm talking shit just in case you haven't noticed**.](https://np.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/4l4ktw/the_difference_in_opinions_on_the_warcraft_movie/d3ka26r) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [THROWBACK] NLT - That Girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 04:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why everyone is pissed that Duncan Jones or David Bowie's son made a bad adaptation of a video game? I think he already made a good one in 1994. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 17:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I watched Battlecraft (1994). AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 11:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie may starred by unknown but it was the best video games movie of all time. David Bowie's son directed this masterpiece and Moon (1994) 

**12  out of 10**


[uj]

I watched Warcraft (2016) you can ask me anything about the movie. I never played any World of Warcraft franchises.

[/uj] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Legends of Tarzan new Poster (Alexander Skarsgrd, Samuel L. Jackson, Margot Robbie, Djimon Hounsou and Christoph Waltz. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 05:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank god, somebody just brought this foreign underrated gem back on the /r/movies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 15:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet is so helpful these days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 11:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fruit Ninja is also being made into a movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 11:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defending "That" Scene In Batman V Superman - John Campea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 07:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ICYMI: Happy Endings cast reunion at Vulture Festival </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 04:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elizabeth Olsen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 06:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, it's called Team Cap for a reason </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 05:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scre4m and Fant4stic are some of the best horror movies I've seen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 17:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just re-watched both of them within the past week. Just the way they made the movies with the camera angles and the filters they use, especially in Fant4stic later when they got their power. It feels like a body horror from David Cronenberg.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Avengers vs X-Men Supercut Trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 15:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [THROWBACK] Ashley Tisdale - He Said She Said </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 12:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woody Harrelson joins Matt Damon, Julianne Moore, Josh Brolin, and Oscar Isaac in George Clooneys Suburbicon, a script by Joel and Ethan Coen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 17:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Jennifer Lawrence hate post (May 18, 2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 15:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I watched X-Mehhh: Holocaust. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 11:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the movie and I thought it was mehh. They have Mr. Tumnus, Jennifer "Feminazi" Lawrence, and Michael Assbender.

[uj]

I watched the X-men: Apocalypse and it was enjoyable. The third act kinda repetitive but I like the new Nightcrawler, Jean Grey, and Cyclops. There are some characters that kinda underused but McAvoy and Fassbender gave a great performance.

I would give this between 7.0-7.5 out of 10

[This is the Ending.](https://www.instagram.com/p/BFUlWqNKolq/)

 [Spoilers](#s "They are going yeast mode, I mean beast mode in their training against Sentinel dummy")

AMA

[/uj] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Captain America: Civil War Spoilers) Winter Soldier's trigger words inspired by this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 04:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why reviews are useless... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 16:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can do this All Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 07:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Light Between Oceans - Official Trailer (Michael Fassbender, Alicia Vikander, and Rachel Weisz) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 13:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This topic is like the tagline of the movie. LIVE. DIE. REPEAT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 01:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain America: Civil War in Edo by Brian Judkins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 01:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TL;DW: Avengers and Chelsea Handler are racists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 14:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS] Finally, I can see this exact moment at the movie theatre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 04:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I watched Angry Bird the Movie, I can confirmed that this movie has the political thriller influence. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 18:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guys proved that his [theory is right](https://np.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/42zmcq/anyone_else_noticed_any_political_undertones_in/). AMA

[uj]

I watched the movie, you can ask me the question.

[/uj] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dinner Party: Captain America   Friends with Chelsea Handler is Available on Netflix featuring Chadwick Boseman, Chris Evans, Sebastian Stan, Emily VanCamp, and Frank Grillo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 09:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People just too stupid to understand the Martha scene and I am embarrassed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 16:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Petition to Stop Disney from paying critics so Batman v Superman and X-Men: Apocalypse can get good reviews. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 02:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sebastian Stan discusses the close relationship between Cap and Buckyincluding the risqu slashficand how the Marvel Cinematic Universe stacks up against DC. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 18:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sebastian Stan on Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice, I Enjoyed it. I think visually it was insane. I thought Ben Affleck was an incredible Batman. I thought that fight sequence he had against all the guys, that was sick. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 18:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emma Thompson attacks young actors who 'cant act' and only get cast due to social media following </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 13:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
