<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3080</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain a few things to me please? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 18:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. What is Trump's policy on health care?  
2. What is Trump's policy on the economy?  
3. What is Trump's policy on the middle east?  
4. What is Trump's policy on education?  
5. What is Trump's policy on technology?  
6. What is Trump's foreign policy?

So far all I've seen are little 140 character limited tweets from him. 

Do any of you even know what his policies are?

We have great policies. The best policies. Are policies are so good they'll amaze you.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Funny golf stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the video of the pros shanking their shots reminded me of something that happened when I was playing golf as a teen. I played golf up until I was 16 and then quit when I went to university. I just started playing again this year (I'm 32), so this happened quite a while ago but it is something I will never forget.  

I was playing a tournament in Ireland at my local course. We used to have a tournament every Thursday during the summer for youths. I must have been 14 or 15 at the time and I was paired with Fergus, a fella I knew from school and who I would golf with quite a bit.  

Fergus was known for getting the yips every now and again, and despite this he would still put up a very decent score. I think he was playing off of 12 or 14 at the time.  

We were on the second hole, a par 5 dogleg left. I hooked my ball into the woods, and he hit his perfectly straight. By some miracle my ball hit a tree and went flying forward and ended up further forward than his drive, but still in the woods.  

Anyways, I'm standing by my ball trying to figure out how the hell I'm going to get out of the woods with my next shot. Unbeknownst to me Fergus takes out his 3 wood and shanks it like you wouldn't believe. He still catches it pretty solid. I don't see any of this, as I'm still trying to figure out a way to get out of the woods.  

Suddenly my legs are taken out from under me and I'm laying face up with this killer pain in my right leg. Then I hear a shout of "four", which is bloody hilarious. 

I can't stop laughing and as I get up Fergus is running over to me with these huge "OH CRAP!" eyes on him. He drops his club half way and people behind us are wondering wtf he is doing. 

I can't even stand properly when I get up and I check under my clothes to see how bad the mark is and my leg is black where he it. Instantly black.

I wasn't able to play the rest of the tournament and Fergus didn't want me to go back because everyone would know what he did and he was worried he'd get in trouble.

It was absolutely hilarious. I felt so bad for Fergus, and I'll never forget his face when he was running towards me with those eyes.

Do you lads have any funny stories from the course?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lalo Dagach on Twitter: "We now live in a world where criticism of Muslim homophobia is islamophobia." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 04:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PGA Coverage is St. Jude over? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 00:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Day four only started an hour ago due to the weather but they stopped the coverage at the scheduled time of 6 anyway. Is there anywhere to watch this? 

**EDIT** PGA Tour Live listened to my complaint and put on some extended coverage.

Fuck yes!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-gay pastor arrested on 70 counts of child pornography. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 04:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens: "Is it moral to believe that our sins, yours and mine, can be forgiven by the punishment of another person? Is it ethical to believe that?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 01:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens: "Is it moral to believe that our sins, yours and mine, can be forgiven by the punishment of another person? Is it ethical to believe that?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 01:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens: "Is it moral to believe that our sins, yours and mine, can be forgiven by the punishment of another person? Is it ethical to believe that?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 01:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I reached this year's goal by breaking 80 today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 17:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory scorecard: http://i.imgur.com/XvaNuIH.jpg

I had no idea I had beaten 80 until I got into my car and did the math while the car cooled down. I had checked the score on my front 9 at the half way point and was pleased enough but did not want to get my hopes up as I've scored 39 on the front 9 a few times and blown up on the back 9 before.

A few take aways: my irons were poor today, in a way. The distance was perfect but I pulled a lot of them left. I did not give myself enough chances for birdie. Some of this was down to how I lined up for the shot.

My chipping saved me today. I hit the pin twice with my chips and mostly left the ball within three feet or so.

My putting wasn't the best so lots of room for improvement there. Scoring 79 when 30 shots are putts is brutal enough. 

I really am absolutely delighted with my chipping today. I've been practicing it for the last two weeks and it has really payed off. 

With such a low GIR I probably didn't deserve to break 80 but as I said I owe it all to how I chipped today.

Hopefully I can get another round or two in the 70s this year. Need to continue to focus on irons, chipping and now need to put a lot more focus on putting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Donald is a gentlesir "I know some of you may think l'm tough and harsh but actually I'm a very compassionate person (with a very high IQ) with strong common sense" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 03:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is a gentlesir "I know some of you may think l'm tough and harsh but actually I'm a very compassionate person (with a very high IQ) with strong common sense" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 02:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What goes through your mind when you're swinging? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 18:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I count to make sure my rhythm is correct so I do some beat counting which I was taught by my pro in my last lesson, and I also ensure I keep my head down. That's literally all I am thinking about. I just trust my swing and let it do its thing. I find if I overthink things I'll catch it thin or heavy.

However, I still end up catching the ball heavy every so often when I am tired. 

Clearing my mind and just focusing on rhythm and keeping my head down has really improved my game. Is there anything else I should be focusing on or thinking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Married golfers (and lads/ladies with significant others) with wives/husbands who do not golf, how often do you go to the range and go golfing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 22:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fitness: Where Your Swing Hurts - Golf Digest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 04:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Back in the office after our yearly golfing trip to Myrtlce Beach. I don't want to be here anymore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 17:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are the media allowed to do this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 15:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Ireland on voting days there's a total media blackout because the media are not allowed to influence voters, by law.

Why the hell is this not the case in the USA? This is disgusting.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fantasy of the Deathbed Conversion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 01:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fantasy of the Deathbed Conversion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 01:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fantasy of the Deathbed Conversion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 01:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Myrtle Beach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 02:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Myrtle Beach day three. I really have to come back here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 19:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grande Dunes Myrtle Beach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 19:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 50 of the 150 balls I ordered from LostGolfBalls that went missing have showed up just in time for my 4 day golfing trip to Myrtle Beach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 01:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had a lesson on Friday and it was brilliant. If you're considering lessons please do it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 02:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lesson was with one of the pros at the course I'm a member of. He's listed as a top 50 PGA professional instructor in the states. I saw him giving lessons to others at the range and I really liked how he interacted with people so figured it was worth a shot. 

Prior to the lesson every so often I'd hit a shot thin. I wanted to find the cause of this. 

After the first three shots I hit, all of them good, he was able to say he thought it was my tempo and that I was lifting my head a bit. 

He brought me out to the 150 marker on the 18th and asked me to hit 5 balls to him on the green with the club of my choice (my 7 iron). Two were good and three went a bit right into the trap. He said the good ones traveled around 135 in the air and ran up to 145 or 150.

We went back to the range and he recorded me. He completely analyzed my swing and liked what he saw for the most part. Good posture, not moving my head or lifting my feet on the back swing. He noticed me lifting my body slightly before impact and it was because I wasn't keeping my head down. 

He also counted the time I started swinging to impact and it varied quite largely.

He taught me about tempo and got me counting 123, 123 (I start lifting here) 123 I'm at the top of my swing, and then I swing and strike.

I think I'm explaining the tempo badly I need to do it visually but I digress.

I saw results instantly. We worked on this for an hour and almost every shot was perfect. When it wasn't i was lifting my head again, but tempo remained good. Not surprised by that as I play the bodhran (Irish drum). I used to have issues every so often with my 4 iron, so he looked at me hitting that and got me to put the club in the middle where I hit the other irons and I hit it brilliantly.

I played a round the next day and was hitting a 9 iron 145 (about 135 in the air), up two clubs from before the lesson. I still scored the usual mid 80s because my putting and chipping is shit, but I had 10 birdie chances thanks to improved driving and irons.

This was a fantastic experience. If you're thinking of going for a lesson please do it. I will be going back for chipping and putting lessons which will hopefully help me break 80. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warming up for my round as the sun comes up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 11:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fecks sake. Not again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 19:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A great collection of photos of Irish golf courses from Kevin Markham </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 17:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much would you expect to pay for lessons with a PGA professional? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 23:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm taking lessons with a lad who is supposedly very good. It's $150 per hour. Just wondering what others are paying for a similar service. I have no idea if this is considered cheap or expensive, as the lessons I had back in Ireland were free -part of membership. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Golfklbburinn Brautarholti golf course in Iceland. Absolutely stunning. Have any of you played here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 20:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any of you ordered from LostGolfBalls before? Looks like my order made a detour via Canada and then went missing (I'm in North Carolina). This was my first time using them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 18:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jesus lads, the Clare GAA page is like something from the 90s. It reminds me of the old Angelfire websites yonks ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 16:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rory McIlroy donates 666k Irish Open prize to charity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 04:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had the course to myself tonight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 02:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Rory McIlroy fan got the perfect response when he shouted 'get in the hole' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 16:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My view for the next hour or so </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 18:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My wife is gone until Tuesday and my new toys just arrived. Happy Friday folks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 19:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/YfOoK

I got the SLDR woods last year, and just purchased the irons, a 60 degree wedge and the putter. 

Also got the bag and the trolley. My old bag was tiny and used to annoy me greatly.

I picked up a range finder as my club only has 150 yard markers and I'm used to having 100s.

I'm off for a lesson and a round of golf. Have a great weekend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shannon man in court for posting publicly available images from Facebook to a porn site. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 21:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need wet gear suggestions as I left mine in Europe and it's going to be raining this weekend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 16:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The weather man says we'll get an inch of rain Friday followed by rain for most of Saturday. My round is at 11.10am on Saturday morning and as stated, my wet gear is back home in Ireland.

I'm probably going to give an umbrella a skip as we're using a cart for the round, but I need pants, some sort of top, multiple towels, a few extra gloves would be handy as well.

Anything else I'm missing? What essential wet gear items do you carry?

I'm kinda short so I'm hoping I can find something by Zero Restriction that fits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the last good book that you read? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 03:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it common for courses in the states to be without 100 yard markers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 03:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of times I played a 9 iron instead of an 8 today was a bit annoying. First time playing without having 100 yard markers. 

I suppose I will have to invest in a range finder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any golf courses in the area that allow you to pay yearly for membership? Lots of courses require you to pay a life time membership up front. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 17:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any golf courses in the area that allow you to pay yearly for membership?  

Lots of courses require you to pay a life time membership up front, which isn't ideal if you're only going to be in the Triangle area for a few years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It appears as though I don't like modern books (books based close to the present day) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 00:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried lots of modern books but failed to get interested in them. The most recent is Ian McEwan's Saturday.

I just don't like stories set with technology, phones, and so on. 

One of the last books I loved that I finished was Germinal by Emile Zola - a book set in the 1800s about a mining community in France. 

Am I alone here? Anyone else find themselves not liking books based in the current period?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The local paper posted a photo from a recent charity walk (Darkness into Light) but didn't notice that one kid.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 23:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The local paper posted a photo from a recent charity walk (Darkness into Light) but didn't notice that one kid.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 23:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We've had some visitors the last three nights. They've done some digging but didn't cause any damage. Hoping this does the trick. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 01:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things have clicked lately and I've nobody to talk to about it so I figure this is the place to talk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 06:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played golf as a teen. There was lots of pressure on me as my grandfather was a scratch golfer and helped build the course I played at in Ireland. I got down to a 7 handicap but once I started college at 16 I stopped playing. 

I'm 32 now, living in the states and bought a set of clubs last year. I went to the range four or five times last year and I've been about twenty times in the past couple of months. I've went a lot this year.

My game has never been as good as it is now and I feel I owe it to putting in the time with my irons at the range. There's a par 3 course I play that has also helped immensely. 

My grandfather was always an irons guy, never used woods and focused on his short game. Times have changed since then and I love my driver, but I feel the time on the par 3 course has really helped me. 

I played a regular course last weekend and shot a 78, probably my best ever round. I played nine holes today and was 2 over but was rained away - it's thunderstorrm season in North Carolina.

Everything is just clicking lately, and while I love it I can't help but wonder how much better I would be if I never stopped playing. I'm not even a member at any course as I just moved here, but I should really settle on a course soon. 

I don't really have a point to this. I just wanted to talk to some folks who play. This is such a great sport and I'm still relatively young, in the sense that I hopefully have another 30 or 40 years left to play. 

I haven't felt like this since I was a kid. I have golf fever and I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joda-Time: How to show TimeZone on a Time object? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 15:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LocalTime is a time representation without a TimeZone.

Is there any other time object that will show the TimeZone?

I tried using DateTime but that obviously includes the date, and if you only use a pattern of "HHmmss" the date defaults to 1970.

**EDIT: Resolved** This gets me what I need: 

    DateTime dt = DateTimeFormat.forPattern("HHmmss").parseDateTime("114937");
    System.out.println(dt.toString(ISODateTimeFormat.time().withZone(DateTimeZone.UTC)));
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This has got to be Hillary's most outrageous tweet yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 13:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @HillaryClinton mi espaol no es muy bueno </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oompa loompa doompety doo. The Donald will be the ruler of you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 14:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oompa loompa doompety doo. The Donald will be the ruler of you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 13:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 May Book Discussion: For the Sake of Argument: Essays and Minority Reports. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 21:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 May Book Discussion: For the Sake of Argument: Essays and Minority Reports. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 21:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original thread with the schedule for 2016 is here:

https://www.reddit.com/r/ChristopherHitchens_/comments/3yycrr/2016_book_club_schedule/

This month we are focusing on a nice collection of essays which cover a wide range of topics. The picture on the front of this book was taken on his wedding night in their apartment. I actually consider it a dashing photo of him. 

The book itself is very good. Some of the topics are somewhat dated by now but still worth reading about. Their importance hasn't waned with time. Enjoy!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The NFL draft is on today, you can watch rooms full of white guys in suits negotiate prices to trade young black men and nobody see's anything weird about it... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 02:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another reason to stay childfree. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 22:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On hour 28 of this migraine. Never had one this long before. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 02:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else sick of this exaggeration culture on reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 19:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see this shit on every front page thread on this fucking site.  

"I died".  
"I laughed so hard my dogs had to see if I was OK".  

Or the opposite:   
"tears are running down my face after watching that"

It's not just on reddit, I see it in most online outlets and communities, but its probably more prevalent on here. 

If you reply with "so edgy" you're part of the fucking problem too.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TWC "promotion" has ended. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 14:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As per the following: https://www.reddit.com/r/triangle/comments/4frbbp/check_your_time_warner_cable_bill_for_home_wifi/d2bkfuq

Looks like mine jumped from 70-something to 90-something.

**Before**  
11/24-12/23 Extreme Internet 39.99  
11/24-12/23 Ultimate 300 Upgrade 30.00  
11/24-12/23 Internet Modem Lease 5.99

**After**  
03/24-04/23 Extreme Internet 49.99  
03/24-04/23 Ultimate 300 Upgrade 30.00  
03/24-04/23 Internet Modem Lease 10.00  

Apparently my "promotion" ended, "but we're still including you in another promotion because the real price should be 119.99."

I just have internet. What a crock of shit. I don't see 119.99 ANYWHERE on their site for my zipcode. The advertised price is 64.99.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We finally moved to IntelliJ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 19:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we finally moved to IntelliJ this week. Well, three members of my group did. I was able to convince management to get a few licenses so we can do a proof of concept. I got us set up on Monday, and it's only Wednesday and I can safely say that I don't think I could ever go back to eclipse.

IntelliJ is far from perfect, there are some annoyances but it does everything eclipse does.... just does them better. I had heard that before and it's only now that I appreciate it.

The only thing annoying me at the moment is hot deployment to tomcat is failing but that seems to be a resource issue more than anything else - it runs out of memory when attempting to do it. I'm forced to use a crappy Lennovo T440 as my work machine.

Thanks to those of you that took the time to convince me to make the jump. This has made my work day so much more exciting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IntelliJ has issues stopping Pivotal tcServer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 21:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I press stop, it never seems to send the signal to the tcServer and it just doesn't shut down.

Has anyone else had this issue? Up to now I've been killing the java process but this is becoming painful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I finally got a board! I moved the wine fridge after taking this picture. I could do with getting a mat as well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 18:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graham Linehan on living in fear: 'I had brought the woman I love to a place where she wasn't safe' - Independent.ie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 14:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Java Annotated Configuration Question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 16:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi folks,

For those of you that use annotated configurations for your java beans, do you have an ApplicationConfiguration class that sets up all of the beans for you, or do you just stick @Component in the class declaration and deal with it that way?

For example:

    @Configuration
    @ComponentScan(basePackages={"test.package"})
    @PropertySource("classpath:/config/resources/env-settings-${server.env}.properties")
    public class ApplicationConfiguration {
    /** The timeout. */
    @Value("${defaultTimeOutMillis}") 
    int timeout;

    @Bean(name="testFactory")
    public TestFactory testFactory() {
		return new TestFactory(timeout);
    }

Or do you just stick @Component on the TestFactory class and then @Autowire it?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homeland Security want me to keep my greencard in this piece of paper to prevent wireless communication with it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 12:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Bernie ever suggested taxing churches as a way to raise $71 billion per year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 13:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Hitchens Day everyone! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens live tv compilation best bits no1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 04:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens live tv compilation best bits no1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 03:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colleges and universities spend 1.5m in public funds annually on chaplains </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 04:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The essence of the independent mind lies not in what it thinks, but how it thinks." - Christopher Hitchens [1366x768] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 01:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are you up to on this fine weekend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 21:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Importance of Immutability in Java </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 00:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a saying or expression that really pisses you off? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 00:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 April Book Discussion: Blood, Class, and Nostalgia: Anglo-American Ironies. Reissued 2004, with a new introduction, as Blood, Class and Empire: The Enduring Anglo-American Relationship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 16:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are you working on this week? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 02:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The week ahead is an odd enough one for me. I'm dev on call so chances are I won't get much project work done. I have to complete a Domain Model by Wednesday, and review it with our clients. I only started it on Friday due to delayed analysis from our architects, so there's a bit of pressure there. 

I couldn't sleep last night, woke up at 2am, and spent five hours playing around with how I want the application I'm working on to be structured. I'm delighted I did this, because I realised a few things that I wasn't aware of. We're a week or two behind - I should be coding already but I'm not yet.

Last week I opened the required tickets for certificates and all of that jazz that goes with creating a new internal web service. I'm hoping that stuff gets complete soon so I'm not held up when coding actually happens.

I have a proof of concept application created, and I wrote the code to communicate with the back-end last week but can't test it due to the certificate issue... so I'm fairly far ahead of things as it stands. Once I can test that to make sure it's working it's just a matter of handling a request properly. I should be done with development in a week or two which leaves some time for JUnit and Sonar fun.

Sorry for the ramble. :) So what have you got going on this week? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 April Book Discussion: Blood, Class, and Nostalgia: Anglo-American Ironies. Reissued 2004, with a new introduction, as Blood, Class and Empire: The Enduring Anglo-American Relationship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 19:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original thread with the schedule for 2016 is here:

https://www.reddit.com/r/ChristopherHitchens_/comments/3yycrr/2016_book_club_schedule/

We're getting near the end of this journey! This month we're focusing on a nice analysis of the anglo-american tradition   history, what some might call America's obsession with Britain (see The Churchill Cult). Please don't skip the introduction of this piece, as it is great piece of writing in its own right. 

Happy reading! This is a brilliantly evocative collection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crash on 540 between Apex and Morrisville impacting 4 lanes of traffic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 14:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avoid 540 if you can this morning. I counted 10 ambulances and 2 fire trucks. They were using a crane over the overpass, apparently a truck crashed and fell onto the road below. I saw news cameras at the scene but can't find much about it online.

**EDIT** Stories starting to appear now: http://abc11.com/news/truck-falls-below-triangle-expressway-bridge/1270176/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well lets give it a go - what are you working on this week? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 23:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a few things going on. I need to figure out where a threading issue came from (one I fixed by using joda-time). I also need to document the changes I implemented last week, and state why they are beneficial. I @Autowired everything, and got rid of static everywhere. Almost all variables, objects, and methods were static. However the developer who wrote the old code sees no issues with using static like this so I have to get him on board with the changes. I don't think he's too happy with me at the moment so we'll see how the conversation goes. 

He also had a 1400 line void method which changed the state of things - impossible to test. I made this return something so we can actually test it, but I need to see if I can refactor it. It's filled with business logic so I have to understand that first.

I need to fix some sonar findings and also get started on a new application that is due by the end of the month. That is going to be tough going and will take priority over the other work I am doing.

So lots of coding, refactoring, documentation and meetings this week. Hectic, but fun. :)

So what do you have going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I started Germinal by Emile Zola today. I can barely put the book down! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 01:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been threatening to read this book for ages, but something always seemed to get in the way. It's a fascinating read so far (I'm around 90 pages in). The only other thing I read by Zola was his letters and essays during The Dreyfus Affair (most notably [for me anyway] his polemic "A Plea for the Jews", which I consider one of the best essays ever penned) so I guess I don't have a frame of reference for his fiction, but this is outstanding. I'm kind of raging I left it so long to finally read this.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any interest in a weekly thread about what you're working on this week? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just trying to get some activity on the sub that might be of interest to others, especially new developers. If we had a thread about what people are working on this week (without breaching NDAs of course) it might help new developers see what a typical work week is like for us.

I'm working on a framework migration right now for a large JAX-WS webservice, and trying to fix some threading issues. The following issue with Spring screwed me over, but I found a workaround thankfully. https://jira.spring.io/browse/SPR-9786

Currently getting rid of all static objects and replacing them with @Autowired beans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Autowired Bean initialized at start up, but null inside a web request? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 11:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a JAX-WS service which has one Autowired bean like so:
    
    @HandlerChain(file = "handler-chain.xml")
    @WebService(portName = "MyService", serviceName = "MyService", targetNamespace ="http://www.example.com/wsdl", wsdlLocation = "WEB-INF/wsdl/MyService.wsdl", endpointInterface = "example.MyService")
    @BindingType("http://schemas.xmlsoap.org/wsdl/soap/http")
    @Service
    public class MyService extends SpringBeanAutowiringSupport implements MyService, ApplicationContextAware {
	
	/** The log. */
	private static Log log = LogFactory.getLog(AccountFeaturesService.class);
	
	/** The context. */
	@Resource
	WebServiceContext context;
	
	@Autowired 
	Controller201607 controller;

The above controller is autowired fine as the server starts up (and also when I run a JUnit test on it).

However, once a web method comes in and this service is invoked the reference to the object is null.

Is there any way to avoid this without making it static? I'm also trying to avoid calling getBean() inside the web request.

**EDIT** It looks like there is a spring Jira open for this, but it remains unresolved. https://jira.spring.io/browse/SPR-9786 

I tried the workaround using processInjectionBasedOnCurrentContext(this) in a @PostConstruct but it did not work for me. However, doing a null check in the web method then calling it worked.

**RESOLVED!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ultimate Mombie demands preferential treatment in hospital after drunk teens treated ahead of sick baby on St Patrick's Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 22:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since becoming a developer I've always had problems switching off if I haven't solved a problem I have been working on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 12:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here I am at 7am on a Saturday reading up on something I need to figure out because I can't sleep well when issues like this plague me.

I am not viewing this as working because it's something I need to know to be a better developer so I'm furthering my career. I'm up early researching it as my wife sleeps. As soon as she's up I'll continue with life's obligations.

Surely I'm not the only one who has issues switching off and leaving work at work?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did Sanders lose NC? Because only ~35% of NC voters participated in the presidential election this Tuesday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 16:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL of Pedro Albizu Campos, a Puerto Rican who met deValera and assisted with Ireland's Struggle for Independence. He became a consultant in the drafting of our Constitution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 14:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Paddy, not Patty, ye goat! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 19:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to stare death in the eye how great writers confronted their mortality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 16:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The real harm Hillary Clinton inflicted on Bosnia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 16:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I live in Apex, NC. I haven't seen one flier or advertisement for Bernie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 13:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What gives? We are ten minutes from Raleigh - where Bernie is speaking this morning. Hardly anyone even knows about his rally this morning. The triangle area I'm in is full of relocates from New England. This should be an easy area for him to win but its like we have been forgotten about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the cringiest thing you've ever done? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 14:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After threatening to do this for years, I finally made the jump today. I'm very excited! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 01:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miesha Tate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 16:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feck off cup! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 00:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans are just Europeans on a different rock. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 00:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where's the live update thread? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 00:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The (American) pint of Harp. It's like a glorified glass. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 23:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any expats out there that have returned home or are thinking of doing so? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 20:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've given myself until 2020 to decide but at this point it's almost a certainty that I will be moving back. The industry I work in wasn't impacted by the recession (software development) and I only moved away to get some experience outside of ireland. 

Just wondering if anyone on here returned or are thinking of doing so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 1997 Sun Microsystems document "Java Code Conventions" states: "Avoid lines longer than 80 characters, since theyre not handled well by many terminals and tools". Do any of you abide by this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 15:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: http://www.oracle.com/technetwork/java/codeconventions-150003.pdf

We abide by it in the company I work in, but if I'm honest it makes some parts of the code terribly difficult to read. We all have 24 inch monitors now so limiting a line to 80 characters is painful. If statements look terrible, to give one example.

Is your java shop strict about this character line limit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> java.lang.AbstractMethodError when calling java.sql.Connection.setClientInfo(Properties) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 18:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     Properties props = new Properties();			
    props.setProperty("ClientUser", "TestUser");
    props.setProperty("ClientWorkstation", "TestWorkstation");
    props.setProperty("ClientAccountingInformation", "Test");
    props.setProperty("ClientApplicationInformation", "Test");

    try
    {
    sqlSession.getConnection().setClientInfo(props);
    }


The above code fails with java.lang.AbstractMethodError. I'm not sure if this is some sort of library conflict in my classpath, or what the issue might be. java.sql.Connection is Abstract, as is the method I'm calling, but I can't extend java.sql.Connection in order to write my own setClientInfo().

Google reveals other people having the same issue but no resolutions provided.

One of the caveats here is that I cannot set the client info on the bean when it's initialized because I need to set it when a request is made (it's going to be different every time), so setting the info on the bean in my applicationContext.xml isn't an option for me.

Have any of you seen this before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're a salaried employee you're working today for free. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 15:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders on Bank Bailouts (4) (S   L Crisis) [3/13/1991] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 17:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders: National Health Care System (1) [2/20/1991] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 17:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> O'Malley Park, Limerick. Where people cement broken glass on top of walls and sheds to prevent people from getting into their gardens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 15:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The life of an oppossissionist is meant to be difficult" -- Christopher Hitchens. Keep your heads held high folks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 05:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After being screwed by FF, and then by FG, the Irish electorate have decided to vote overwhelmingly for both of them again. Stockholm syndrome? It's enough to make a cat laugh. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 23:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Survivor - The Atlantic. I compel all of you to read the diaries of Victor Klemperer if you have not done so already. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 23:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the worst? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 02:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Americans who won't vote for a socialist Jew are more than likely the very same Americans who celebrate the birthday of a socialist Jew every Christmas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 02:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salman Rushdie: Iranian state media renew fatwa on Satanic Verses author with $600,000 bounty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 14:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salman Rushdie: Iranian state media renew fatwa on Satanic Verses author with $600,000 bounty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 14:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moonshine Ageing Update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 21:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part One was here: https://www.reddit.com/r/firewater/comments/43l92e/moonshine_ageing_part_one/

Here's how it looks after 19 days: http://i.imgur.com/fkZawi1.jpg

It tastes delicious as well. It's really picking up vanilla from the wood and has softened quite a bit. The alcohol content is still very high at the moment, but has definitely lessened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moonshine Ageing Update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 21:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part One was here: https://www.reddit.com/r/whiskey/comments/43l83p/moonshine_ageing_part_one/

Here's how it looks after 19 days: http://i.imgur.com/fkZawi1.jpg

It tastes delicious as well. It's really picking up vanilla from the wood and has softened quite a bit. The alcohol content is still very high at the moment, but has definitely lessened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 18:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something something brown bread, something something pumpernickel, pumpernickel bread. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 01:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You will literally die when you see this monkey rape a goat on the top of the Cliffs of Moher. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 00:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Clinton literally bit my face and raped me while Hillary recorded it. 1 updoot = 1 prayer. 1 share = 10 Hanukkahs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 00:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US government declares people unsafe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 00:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who let the herp, about this derp? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 00:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton kicked my dog. I can has updoots? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 23:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JAX-RPC (java.util.Calendar) vs JAX-WS (javax.xml.datatype.XMLGregorianCalendar) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 16:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our old code used JAX-RPC, and as a result dateTime was represented as so: 

Timestamp2016-02-17T16:01:16.000**Z**/Timestamp

Our new code using JAX-WS represents the same dateTime as follows: 

Timestamp2016-02-17T11:01:16.000**-05:00**/Timestamp

According to the XMLSchema-2, both represent the same timestamp, just different objects and thus a different representation. https://www.w3.org/TR/xmlschema-2/#dateTime-timezones

We're being instructed to change the JAX-WS object to output using the 'Z' timezone offset, but I'm not entirely convinced that's the right approach.

I would rather go with what JAX-WS is suggesting, and inform our customers about the change in representation which is in line with the XMLSchema standards.

How have you folks handled this change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a worthwhile charity to donate to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 04:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could break one law without punishment which law would you break, and how would you break it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 01:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could add a new feature to reddit, what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 19:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You found out you have 24 hours to live - what would you like your tombstone to say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 20:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats your favourite snack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 03:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats your happiest childhood memory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 00:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prizing Doris Lessing - The Nobel committee finally gets it right </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 17:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the spec of your work machine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 03:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is a Lenovo t440, 8gb of ram and an i5. Lately it's almost impossible to do my job and I'm battling with the company to give me a better model. They seem to give top-end MacBook Pros to company execs who do nothing but use PowerPoint... And developers who need web sphere, tomcat, RAD and Eclipse are stuck using old bricks with no battery life. I actually have a "new" laptop considering what others are using. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't Americans celebrate Pancake Tuesday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 15:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moment Japanese rugby fan met his sporting hero Shane Williams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 14:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People with their dream job, what do you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 14:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans of reddit, who, in your opinion, was the finest American to have ever lived? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 19:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone help me out here? Why are people saying it was close? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 05:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton has over 400 delegates, almost 25% of the required delegates needed.

Bernie only has 1.2% of the delegates he needs.

How is that close? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Did Christopher Hitchens Study in University? Interview on Writing (1993) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 00:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A reminder to join us at the book club over at /r/ChristopherHitchens_ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 23:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens: The Lost Interview (2008) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 23:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 February Book Discussion: Imperial Spoils: The Curious Case of the Elgin Marbles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 23:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 February Book Discussion: Imperial Spoils: The Curious Case of the Elgin Marbles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 23:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original thread with the schedule for 2016 is here:
https://www.reddit.com/r/ChristopherHitchens_/comments/3yycrr/2016_book_club_schedule/

We had some good discussion last month - thank you for participating! 

This month we are reading Imperial Spoils: The Curious Case of the Elgin Marbles, reissued and updated 2008 as The Parthenon Marbles: The Case for Reunification. 

In 1801, Lord Elgin, then ambassador to the Turkish government, had chunks of the Parthenon sawn off and shipped to England, where they were subsequently seized by Parliament and sold to the British Museum to help pay off Elgins debts.

Christopher makes a very solid case for their return. 

Happy Reading folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moonshine Ageing, Part One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 23:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted over Christmas that I managed to secure a case of moonshine (13 jars actually), and that I planned on ageing some of it in a barrel.

Well thankfully I got everything together and started the process today.

I'll update /r/firewater again when it's ready to bottle and consume.

In the meantime here's some photos: http://imgur.com/a/f7dNg

The 5 litre barrel (1.32 gallons) took 6.5 jars of moonshine.

If you have any questions or tips, I'm all ears!

Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moonshine Ageing, Part One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 23:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted over Christmas that I managed to secure a case of moonshine (13 jars actually), and that I planned on ageing some of it in a barrel.

Well thankfully I got everything together and started the process today.

I'll update /r/whiskey again when it's ready to bottle and consume.

In the meantime here's some photos: http://imgur.com/a/f7dNg

The 5 litre barrel (1.32 gallons) took 6.5 jars of moonshine.

If you have any questions or tips, I'm all ears!

Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Meaning of Life with Gay Byrne - Fionnula Flanagan - October 3, 2010 - Video Dailymotion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 17:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ideas for the sub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 20:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi folks,

I don't want this sub to be seen as mine, in any way. It's ours. I'd like it to be community driven. I'm on reddit every day, but work 60 hour weeks so don't always have the time I wish I had. I also run the book club over at /r/ChristopherHitchens_ (the _ is intentional as the actual mod is MIA) and take takes a bit of my time too. So don't rely on me for anything - do whatever you like. I trust you all.

I'd like to open this up for ideas for the sub. As suggested by /u/iHaveAgency [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/atheism/comments/438w56/i_started_rpastorarrested_a_couple_of_weeks_ago/czhfr1s) we should add colour coded post flair, and implement some method to stop reposting of old stories (stopping duplicate URLs for instance).

Please reply with anything you'd like to see on here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I started /r/PastorArrested a couple of weeks ago, as a joke made by a member on here (more inside) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 15:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started /r/PastorArrested as a joke after a discussion with a member on here a few weeks ago.

When I first searched for pastor arrested cases, I was shocked (not sure why I found it surprising honestly) to find just how many Pastors throughout the USA have been arrested - even just in the last six months.

I set up Google alerts (recommend by another member here) to alert me of new news stories of pastors being arrested. I get alerts almost daily, some times more than once per day too. I actually can't even keep up, and I've not posted a lot of stories as I've been too busy with work and real life crap.

The awful thing about this, is that none of the major news agencies are covering the arrests. It appears to not be covered at the national level at all - it's just covered by a local news station that quite often even gets the case details wrong.

Check out /r/PastorArrested for yourself, and if you have any ideas for the sub or how we can/should get the word out please let me know.

**EDIT** If you want to help out and be a mod, etc, let me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austin pastor arrested for sexual abuse of youth member </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 14:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pastor arrested for allegedly stealing $21,000 from church to pa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 14:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men jailed for IS promotion outside Topshop in Oxford Street </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 14:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL about Snake wine an Asian alcoholic beverage produced by infusing whole snakes in rice wine or grain alcohol. The snakes, preferably venomous ones, are not usually preserved for their meat but to have their "essence" and snake venom dissolved in the liquor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 03:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl kissing Sphinx </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 03:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When she say she on Tinder to meet friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 03:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite part of being an adult? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 03:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be honest, it's being childfree. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans of reddit, what's a cultural norm that might be considered odd or strange by a foreigner? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 00:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patriots Fans Go OFF On Kicker Steven Gostkowski On Twitter Postgame For Missing Extra Point </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 20:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to make a decent cup of tea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 06:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens updates Orwell's tea essay. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 06:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patriot fans lose mind after redditor posts TIL stat about Grok not missing a PAT since 2006; Grok goes on to miss a PAT in tonight's game and everyone gets violent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 01:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patriot fans lose mind after redditor posts TIL stat about Grok not missing a PAT since 2006; Grok goes on to miss a PAT in tonight's game and everyone gets violent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 01:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A local man made a turd in his yard for his daughter! Her reaction is priceless! What a dad! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 00:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's a picture of me updooting into snow. Please give me that sweet sweet karma. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 23:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unexpected interior. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 21:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lads the banner in here is fucking classic. Great work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 21:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exploiting a 15 year old kid for sweet sweet karma. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 20:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria and the Struggle Against Takfiri Totalitarianism -- this is what a plagiarist looks like. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 19:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australia laying the smack down. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 07:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've never seen a man this brave in all my life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 02:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were going to be stranded on an island for years with one book, which book would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 02:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun owners of Reddit - what guns do you own? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 01:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite meal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 00:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your favourite thing to do as a kid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 20:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What book are you currently reading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 19:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mostly naked girl on a lake. This will be on the front page very soon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 17:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tian Tian woke up this morning to a lot of snow, and he was pretty excited about it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 16:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tian Tian woke up this morning to a lot of snow, and he was pretty excited about it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 16:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-pastor accused of rape arrested </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 16:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police arrest pastor who raped his 14-year-old step-daughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 16:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Rainbow City youth pastor arrested for producing pornography </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 16:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now this is a fashion trend I can get behind [NSFW] (/r/pics +2800) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 03:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suzi Jamil showing Sam Harris like you've never seen him before. (Majiid Nawaz retweeted this too) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 02:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Up Voted Because Arse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 01:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lisa Hannigan - Home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 23:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lisa Hannigan - Home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 23:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm not even sure what to say..... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 23:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a non-essential thing you cannot live without? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 23:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People born in the year 2000 can buy guns in some states in the USA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 23:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 21:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL when Queen wanted to release Bohemian Rhapsody in 1975, various executives suggested to them that, at 5 minutes and 55 seconds, it was too long and would never be a hit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 05:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world is a darker place without Christopher; but we must carry the torch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 04:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see calls for his voice, his opinion on current events, everywhere I look. As I peruse reddit, twitter, The New York Times, et al.

We must stop this form of lamenting. It's downright lazy. It's intellectual suicide. It's saying we can't think for ourselves. That is against everything Christopher taught us.

Be the voice you miss. He said the life of an oppossissionist was not meant to be easy. Within our reach is a seemingly endless stream of incidents, events, for lack of a better word "things" to be opposed to.

So oppose them. Write. Find your voice. He said the grave will provide plenty of time for silence and he is silent now, but it doesn't have to be that way. 

It's time for us to carry his torch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OK, I'll admit it. Hitchens was fucking right. Dammit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 04:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a bit of a shit post, albeit extremely light hearted. 

Growing up in Ireland, I started drinking alcohol at an incredibly young age. I was twelve the first time I was drunk, but I had consumed alcohol a few years prior to this. Twelve is around the time I started drinking regularly. One thing I could never handle at this age, or through my teens was whiskey. Two things would happen to me; violent tendencies and stupefaction. After touching the stuff once I realised it wasn't for me, and stayed the fuck away.

I was visiting Rory, a friend of mine, in the cold of winter one year when I was around twenty-five and we were talking about whiskey and how I couldn't drink the stuff. Rory sat me down and showed me the ropes, so to speak. I learned how to respect it, drink it properly, and hydrate afterwards to avoid hangovers. We did a whiskey tasting with several different kinds of whiskies and I learned the differences, and discovered what I liked.

This started a long and happy whiskey fuelled road. I have an incredible whiskey collection today, the most expensive bottle being costing 5,000. It's a very expensive (and fun) habit. 

However, and this is where Hitchens comes in... Being an avid Hitchens fan I'm well aware he was a lover of Johnny Walker Black and Perrier. Now, I dislike Johnny Walker Black, it's a fairly low-grade whiskey and Hitchens admits he only drank it because one can be guaranteed to find it in almost every bar on the planet. If he stuck to high grade whiskey he would be disappointed when he found himself in a situation where it wasn't available.

This weekend I decided to add Perrier to some low-grade whiskey I was drinking. It wasn't Johnny Walker Black, but it was as good (or as bad) as it, and holy fucking shit. It was a fantastic experience.

I wouldn't add Perrier to expensive whiskey, (and Hitchens would agree there), but when adding it to the low-grade stuff it really makes a fantastic drink.

Congratulations Hitch, you were right, and I have no idea why I ever doubted you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What have I done?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 02:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daughter files $9 million civil lawsuit against Eugene insurance-agent dad who allegedly sexually abused her | Local | Eugene, Oregon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 01:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Moriarty tells a story Part 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 01:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Moriarty tells a story Part 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 00:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Moriarty tells a story Part 1 (the other parts are in the side bar of the video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 17:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We had snow this morning! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 16:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone else toast their bread on one side as a child? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 16:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's snowing in Apex? Is it snowing anywhere else in the Triangle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 15:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could change one thing about reddit, what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 15:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Is there any group out there that handles immigrant integration into the west, specifically Europe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 03:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marrero pastor arrested for rape of juvenile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 15:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
