<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8651</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> upyost if u liek the royals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 22:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dae Lorde lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody else get their preorder pack again last night? (PS4) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 19:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is this phenomenon called? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 21:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to google it, can't find it. It's when two people can do something to benefit both parties but they still won't do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not even a player and I'm hype </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 04:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I registered ~7500 reference points on my face scan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 00:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the setup I used: http://i.imgur.com/TfoyGhx.jpg

Set yourself up as the third point of a triangle between the two lamps. 

I looked at my face on the screen, and backed away/came forward until my skin tone looked accurate. I filled up the green square from my hairline to my chin, and looked left to right, and I looked to the left and right at 80 angles, NOT 30. For some reason that helped me, it did lose my face, but I'd rather the scan get stopped in the middle than lose the scanning of the last parts of my face. Then, I tweaked my face in the face sculpting options. The scan looked great, only problem was that my skin tone didn't match up with the 2K skin body. It was still good enough to use, however.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things I am over: "refreshers" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 22:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FYI: You can tweet people on the Social Media section of MyPlayer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 09:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the fuck is up with illegal screens this year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 21:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are illegal screens the new "kick ball" plague that happen nearly every single game? Wiggins just did it on 3 consecutive possessions, kind of annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, voice control lasted about 2 hours before I had to turn it off. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 02:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently "excessive timeouts" is a thing now, so if you call a timeout you forfeit a free throw.

Anyways, D-Wade nailed a fader in my myPlayer's face to tie with a second left. I say out loud, "h*ooooo*w?" Boom, technical foul for excessive timeouts. 

If only we could turn off certain commands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we compile a list of all the mentors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 02:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is all I know so far

Rockets - Harden

Thunder - Durant

Clippers - Redick

Timberwolves - Thaddeus Young, Corey Brewer

Suns - Markieff Morris

Hawks - Al Horford

Raptors - Terrence Ross

Kings - Demarcus Cousins

Bucks - Kendall Marshall, Brandon Knight

Pelicans - Eric Gordon

Magic - Channing Frye

Knicks - JR Smith

Hornets - Al Jefferson

Jazz - Trey Burke

Pistons - Andre Drummond

Spurs - Danny Green

Nuggets - Ty Lawson

Wizards - Bradley Beal

Mavericks - Brandan Wright </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This soundtrack is easily the worst 2K soundtrack to date. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 23:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does not go well together at all, and even if it did, it sure as hell would not get me pumped to play virtual basketball.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some of NBA2K15's worst (best?) face scans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 16:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A collection of face scans from the first hour of the NBA 2K15's release </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 08:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio State Psychology Class </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 23:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giancarlo Stanton on getting hit in the mouth with a fastball: "pfftbthplbubhjhtttthhth" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 09:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wearing seatbelts is so EPIC!!! :3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 04:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AND THEYRE OFF FOR THE KARMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 22:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW] JUSTIN VERLANDER NUDE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 04:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justin Verlander leaks Justin Upton's nudes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 03:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "So I found my new Halloween costume" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 19:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I think Jesus Montero should be banned for life" - Pete Rose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 03:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Murray </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 22:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Murray </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clayton Kershaw came on me and cured my ALS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 06:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 00:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SHAMELESS PLUG: Join us at /r/classicbaseball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 00:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello fellow baseball lovers! If you're intrigued by baseball or would like to reminisce on old times, come to /r/ClassicBaseball. We have a growing community, fantastic mod team, and a great new look thanks to /u/Gtt1229. 

Our moderators, as well as members of the community, do our best to add new stuff every day, making it a bit of a "museum". We've got everything from the early days to the 90's. Come enjoy the history of baseball with us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matt Shoemaker's wife is not happy about her husband losing his no hitter! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 07:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1989 FBI letter addressing N.W.A.'s "Straight Outta Compton" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 22:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After a 10 year study, Columbia University confirms good pitchers are good </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 21:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we please stop the Altuve height jokes? You all sound like little kids. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 19:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AND JOSE ALTUVE LOOKS LIKE ONE LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jon Lester gives Pat Neshek a blowjob while wearing a suit in exchange for his jersey number. What a fucking classy guy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 00:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schilling: The Holy Spirit led me to Trout. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 00:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schilling: Miguel Cabrera led me to a gas chamber. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 21:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cespedes to A's: "Wow you guys have a really low payroll" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 00:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IAMA le SENIOR MODERATOR of /r/gaming :3 ask me anything!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 20:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey did you guys know this chick slept with some semi-important people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 20:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/Braves had a meetup! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 19:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh FUCK, the Royals announced postseason tickets just like any other team in the running for the playoffs!!!! What the FUCK were they thinking???? DAE ROYALS FUCKED EVEN THOUGH I LOVE THEM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 20:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wow, the prices for the A's playoffs games are so affordable if you've already paid the hundreds of dollars for season tickets! What an amazing organization. Please give me upvotes btw </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 07:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rob Manfred? More like Rob Bitchfred. LOL DAE FUCK COMMISSIONERS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 01:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE, FUCK THE DH? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 01:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, did you guys know the Mariners had a good year once? Upvotes to the left </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 21:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comcast banded with Ferguson cops to kill my father, Robin Williams, by stabbing him with the beak of a jackdaw. Please give me karma in my time of need. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 19:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, did you guys know the A's have a small payroll? Upvotes to the left </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 22:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For every upvote, the mods here at /r/baseballcirclejerk will help feed a starving Royals fan who has endured far worse than any member of a genocide. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 09:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I haven't given a shit about the Royals all year, but hey they're in first place pls give karma!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 16:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros mascot TROLLS ADRIAN BELTRE!!!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 00:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tigers head to the 19th inning. Fucking Cabrera trying to be better than Trout at everything. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 01:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having a camera angle problem... Help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 00:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got the PS4 remaster, and about 2 hours into the game I noticed the camera angle keeps falling down... Like it keeps making me go to the ground with my vision. Can't figure out why. Tried restarting encounter, the game, even the console... Nothing. Any help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE BASEBALL IS TEH BEST SPORT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 18:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KissCam Update: My mother wants me to come up out of the basement and clean her living room instead of playing Dota 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 00:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got on the Kiss Cam, AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 16:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BTW I'm dating this 10/10 now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE HATE HAWK HARRELSON? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 18:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upvote if you came. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 17:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HUNTER PENCE RAPED MY DOG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 20:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andrew McCutchen: "I really didn't know what to think about the whole situation, but the support from these neckbeards on Reddit really helped me cope with the situation." We did it Reddit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 16:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look at this fucking asshole. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 04:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our signs worked! We did it Reddit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 04:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ----- Number </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 23:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tigers acquire David Price, send gas chamber considerations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 22:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear /r/baseball mods: Disable thumbnails. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 20:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With all these twitter links it makes the sub look unappealing. It would look better without thumbnails.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BREAKING: BILLY BEANE TELLS CESPEDES "GET YOUR .303 OBP OUT OF HERE YOU PIECE OF SHIT" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 20:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally fulfilled a childhood dream yesterday! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 06:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JP Arencibia, batting .152, has 7 RBI's tonight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 05:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some players that most people forget played on a certain team? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 03:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, the one year Teixieira was on the Angels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NO C******* ALERT - Bartolo Colon has gone 6 minutes without eating one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 20:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK he just ate another Cinnabon. We were so close.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Reddit Day at Globe Life Park! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 01:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rockies Giveaway Day Featuring Misspelled Tulowitzki Jerseys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 02:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a friend's dad got a ball signed by angel hernandez... what he wrote was priceless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 17:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dallas Keuchel tosses a ball with a message to a heckler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 10:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> many machado gives cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 20:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a place where I can watch all the gag reels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 10:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And also, where the hell are they from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Colorado Rockies are currently not doing well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 21:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we should boycott because we're losing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Major League Baseball, please stop it with the Dogs' Nights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 04:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Major League Baseball: please stop it with the Dogs' Nights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 04:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a baseball fan, have been since I was a pup. I watched the Rangers at the veterinarian, ate Jim Thome's Classy Meat Mix, and I played bat dog on my little league team because, well, I'm a fucking dog. I broke my grandma's Tiffany lamp in 1996 when the Rangers won the division because I was jumping around foaming at the mouth like a rabid dog. I've never caught a foul ball, because I don't have hands, but I bring my paw glove to Globe Life Park every time I go, although I usually end up sitting on it because I fucking hate it when my owner puts that shit on my paws, fuck you, you don't own me. I don't live and die by the Rangers' record like I used to when I was younger, but I still watch the games and yelp and lick my chops and rock a mean rally cap. Like I said, I'm a fan. I am also a dog.
In the last couple years, I've seen more and more "Bark at the Park Nights" crop up at parks around the country, and Globe Life Park is no exception. When I first heard about it, I thought, "Cool, I'm a dog! Does that mean I get to go out on the field? Eat the players? Run the bases and score some treats?" Well no, as it turns out, it means I get a collar. I'm not kidding. Globe Life is far from the only place that's doing this. The Royals' "Dogs' Night Out" features "mini-groomings" and an Instagram competition for best selfie. I couldnt make this up.
And I can't even begin to explain how offensive all that is. Is this really what the front office thinks of dogs? Is this really how shallow you think our fandom runs, that we would swoon over some groomings and dog jerseys instead of a chance to get involved with the game? I already have to put up with the other dogs barking their fucking asses off every inning break; I already have to settle for bat dog if I want to set foot on a diamond; now I can't even be a legitimate fan anymore? Let me tell you something: Dog collar fans aren't real fans. They're not coming back after DNOs. Because they're not interested in baseball. So unless you're planning to adorn all your attendees with collars and jerseys every night, you may as well not even bother, because you're pushing the rest of us away.
My plea to MLB is a simple one, and one that I think is shared by all dog baseball fans: Please just stop. You're getting in the way of the game.
EDIT: Well, 4 hours later, I have gotten a ton of responses, comments, and PMs. Some have been supportive, some constructively critical, and some mean-spirited. I just wanted to say thank you for taking the time to read my rant and share your thoughts, whatever they may be. And to the kind stranger who gilded this post, thank you very much, m'Trout!
EDIT 2: So, a solution has been put forward that I think will appease almost everyone. MLB team ad people, if you're reading, ditch the collars and make "Dogs' Night Out" about AW SHIT DID YOU JUST SEE THAT FUCKING SQUIRREL GODDAMNIT FUCKING LOOK OH MY GOD THERES A FUCKING SQUIRREL ON THE FIELD HOLY SHIT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In this moment, I am euphoric. Not because of any phony Girls Night, but because I am enlightened by my own vagina. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 01:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just FUCKING hate when ballparks try to get people to come to the game. FUCK THEM BY THE WAY I'M FEMALE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 22:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You could say the Yankees TV crew takes German Heritage Day seriously. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 00:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @Suns twitter account accidentally starts beef </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 23:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Suns, tweeted "@Suns: Hey @dallasmavs, Has anyone pitched Summer League back up big men to @mcuban on #SharkTank? Could use a few for 4th Q."

The Mavs tweeted in response: "@DallasMavs: .@Suns great idea. Why didn't we think of that? #fail"

And then Mark Cuban chimes in with "@mcuban: @Suns @dallasmavs rule #1 of social media.  Never insult another team and it's players when you are down 22 points #MFFL"

The Suns replied, "@Suns: @mcuban We weren't. We were saying we could use the back up bigs. We're down three centers/forwards."

As of now, the Suns have deleted both tweets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> During FOX broadcast, "Derek Jeter" mentioned 666 times. "Tony Gwynn" mentioned -4 times. DAE FOX SUCKS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 20:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even if you hate the Jeter, you gotta admit, you gotta euphorically tip your fedora to him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 21:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Jeter League Jeters defeat the Not Jeters by a final score of Jeter to Jeter. Jeter named Most Valuable Jeter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 05:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MFW TROUT TRIPLED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 02:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DEREK JETER 2TART2 THE ALL 2TAR GAME WITH A CLA22Y 2HORT2TOP PLAY, A DOUBLE, AND A RUN. WHAT CLASS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 02:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOAT CHALMERS : "I'm coming home" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 00:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE 2-TIME GOAT NBA CHAMP MARIO CHALMERS "I'M COMING HOME" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 23:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE 2-TIME SINGLE HANDED NBA CHAMPION MARIO CHALMERS "I'M COMING HOME" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 23:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MARIO "GOAT" CHALMERS: "I'M COMING HOME" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 23:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MARIO CHALMERS "I'M COMING HOME" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 23:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm visiting Cleveland in a few weeks, wanna catch a game. any help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 21:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw the ticket prices are downright outrageous. Is there any cheaper prices than 20 in the outfield or is that what I'm gonna have to settle with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody else told Jackson Ellis "I must be sitting" to him saying he was gonna win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 08:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, that shit was intense. I pushed the shit out of him while yelling at him. These cutscenes need to get under control lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Rangers' starters ERA over last 11 games: 10.25 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 03:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna kill myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if Lebron signs with the Bucks instead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 21:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a parent filed a bullying report on a Texas high school football coach for beating his son's team 91-0 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 03:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> check em </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 02:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Onion] Lebron James leaning towards joining Al-Qaeda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 21:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Lebron James didn't exist, who would be the massive star everyone talks about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 04:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, you might say Durant, but he's not as flashy as Lebron and is definitely more conservative. Who would be the one everyone bandwagons on and ESPN talks about at least 15% of the day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The prophecy has spoken </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 11:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Cuban: "What I can tell you is that we made this purely a business meeting. No tours. No banners. Strictly basketball and business." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 08:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: TWITTER PROOF https://twitter.com/caplan_nba/status/484571145606164480

Got this from Mark's cyber dust app (snapchat with text). I would've screenshotted for proof but that would've gotten me deleted, or at least Mark said he'd delete screenshotters. Just take my word for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The trend continues in Dallas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 03:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anon has a draw thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 01:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Texas Rangers lead the AL in shutouts (12 games) and the MLB in giving up 8 runs in a single game (16 games) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 04:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was Malvo listening to on the tape recorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 21:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't figure it out, if it was something that happened offscreen or happened in a prior episode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Machado is derived from the Latin word "macha", literally meaning Hitler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 03:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I go 0 to 10 real quick, real fucking quick nigga </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 21:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel kind of bad about thinking this... Does anyone else agree? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 19:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upvote if you agree. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 18:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rangers have the most shutouts in the league (10), and the 24th best ERA (4.22) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 23:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rangers just won a game 1-0, with their starting pitcher touting a hefty 9.82 ERA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 05:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senior Quote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 04:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senior Quote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 04:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After 1 month of baseball, Chase Utley leads in batting average, Giancarlo Stanton leads in RBI, Ryan Braun leads in Puppies Murdered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 23:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAE Ryan Braun is an asshole? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elvis Andrus with the fantastic swing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 07:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a city in Texas renamed itself to "DISH, Texas" in order to receive free Dish Satellite service for 10 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 00:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just an observation on Kevin Kouzmanoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 05:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy filled in for Beltre after Beltre's injury, and has started his career with a 10 game hitting streak (only 5 people have ever done this) and 9 RBI's. Makes me wonder what will transpire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MFW watching babies get excited makes me feel constipated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 00:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MFW I'm at a Defecation Identification competition and I'm asked "what kind of dung is this" for the championship round </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 23:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl thinks she's funny for tweeting a threat to American Airlines, promptly gets a response </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 19:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mavs just shot 94% (16-17) against the Jazz in the first quarter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 03:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is now the franchise record for best shooting percentage in a quarter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I hate Hall of Fame mode on myplayer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 21:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clippers beat the T'Wolves pretty bad tonight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 06:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kevin Love on the Nets' recent turnaround: "They're in the East." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 03:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This was probably the most frustrating, crock of shit game I've ever played on 2K. For some reason, this guy had the exact same team as me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 05:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The newest edition in the Hunger Games series </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 23:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I am the only one that sees an invisible rabid dog while trying to start the wave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 07:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tyler the Creator's mugshot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 03:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryan's contribution to Oscar's welcome back party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 07:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my mother asks why there's lube and a Disney DVD case on the nightstand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 08:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When someone asks me where my Rolex is while I'm playing bongo drums. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 18:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wilt Chamberlain in his prime, or Lebron James in his prime? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 01:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reds close to signing Homer Bailey for 6yr/$100mm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 01:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FUCK JAY LENO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 23:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT A PEICE OF SHIT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In MURICA, we drive spaceships. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 22:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I really wonder what goes on in people's heads when they make these 4-panel pictures. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 20:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This woman must be listening to underground rap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 06:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlanta's response on Twitter to Kevin Durant's clutch shot. Truly not fair. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 05:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlanta isn't happy with the outcome tonight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-28 04:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The day /r/HHH died </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 00:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody else taking advantage of this MyTeam discount for gold boosters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 22:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit I turned 8,000 VC into 5 new gold players in just a few minutes. This discount makes it perfect to where you actually make VC off buying a pack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Predicted Derozan scoring 40 6 months in advance. Unfortunately it was against the Mavs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 03:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @BBALLFAN510 with the awkward sexual innuendo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 03:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kept the Christmas lights on Muntz and Cletus's houses. I thought it was fitting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 00:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody else think Domination on MyTeam next-gen is full of shit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 03:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wondering if it's just me. Players can't complete easy passes, the other team becomes the '96 Bulls. It's infuriating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The chilling conclusion to the pizza gif. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 02:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He should probably take this as a sign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 20:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hakeem Olajuwon's website. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 01:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's better, 2 premium characters or a building with a character? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 21:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to decide what to do now that I just hit 150 donuts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a banana fan, my favorite moment from 2013. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 20:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't let it stay outside in the cold. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 04:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Real Recognis Real </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 02:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the funniest thing you've seen happen in the stands of an NBA game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 01:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's time we sit down and talk about the Eastern Conference. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 05:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [2K14] Best booster to buy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 04:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saved up 11,000 VC and want to know what would be a good first investment for MyTeam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do y'all consider the top 20 albums/mixtapes of 2013? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 04:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curious what y'all think. I feel like this is probably a thread that was already made, and if so can I get a link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL today is Mariano Rivera and Vin Scully's birthday, making November 29th [le]terally the classiest day of the year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-30 01:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elvis's tweet about Ian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 08:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enes Kanter shoots a jumper over the backboard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 04:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to make a good 8-10 minute mix of various rap songs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 03:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to assemble a rap song montage in Garageband, and I need a few pointers on making it not sound like it was assembled by copy/paste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SERIOUS] What, in your opinion, is the best thing to happen in the 21st century? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 01:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romo nails a ref in the head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 22:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Ortiz wears helmet after Game 6 to avoid assassination attempt by Miguel Cabrera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 04:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Hadfield upvotes to the left </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 19:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl is so brave that she cuts the hair of a person who thinks Justin Bieber is gay. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 04:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Josh Hamilton tips his helmet to a "baseball town" chanting crowd after flying out in the ninth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-30 00:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's not a better time for a selfie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 05:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rangers and Angels are both wearing red jerseys today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 18:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's annoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rangers commit 4 errors in one inning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 02:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First one since 1984.

Implosion complete.

EDIT: Oh and not to mention the fact they were all in a row </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody know what the hell kind of spider this is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 20:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the XBOX 360 version of GTA V, the word "playstation" is blurred out in the song ADHD by Kendrick Lamar, the only word blurred out on any radio station </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 06:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just thought it was kinda funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody else think Michael's son is Jonah Hill? [GTA V] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 22:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leonys Martin laser arm [GIF] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 02:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red Sox present Rivera with the 42 pitching placard, blowjob, and steak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 08:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yu Darvish loses 1-0 for fourth time this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 22:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fucking motherfucker fucking shit i'm fucking tired of this fucking shit i'm fucking pissed fuck this fucking team right now fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For each upvote, $1 will be sent to the Neckbeards Against Pitcher Wins Foundation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 23:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jose Fernandez causes brawl after taking too long to order at the concession stands at Marlins Park, oh wait, who would be there to complain? LOLOLOLOLOL TROUT RULEZ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 03:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just waking up in the mornin gotta thank Trout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 03:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From /r/hockey, who is your favorite goalie in the NHL? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 22:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman OWNS Louisiana State Trooper. Can confirm, was hat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 19:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeff Malone - Best buzzer beater ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 02:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charles Barkley behind the back pass </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 01:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ball Movement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 21:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE FUNNI NAME </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 18:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Jordan threading the needle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 22:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allen Iverson threading the needle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 22:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BREAKING: Obama goes to war with Syria, proving even Obama thinks war is a reliable stat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 20:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Hadfield + Baseball = Karma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 19:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rondo Recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 19:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did he lie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 01:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Throwing a sharp bat at a player? You're fucking stupid for this one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 04:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fukn intaleront funDIEs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 01:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE BALLS R TESTICLES </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 06:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since 2010, 17 pitchers have torn their UCL, and 4 have returned. None did it under 11 months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 06:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IMPORTANT POST REGARDING /r/baseballcirclejerk, PLEASE UPVOTE FOR VISIBILITY, I GET NO KARMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 05:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
