<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4680</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abra is DEAD serious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 00:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 21:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might be the only one, but I kinda love that idea. Felix was quite great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 21:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! You are my favorite! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 16:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Line 162 in Book 13. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 16:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, really? Where? I'd love to see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was reading the Odyssey when I found this line: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 01:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Those mortals? If any man, so lost in his strength,
And prowess, pays you no respect - just pay him back.
The power is always yours.
Do what you like. Whatever warms your heart." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 00:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a mac user, I don't now what I was expecting... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 00:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... There was a flashlight... In Fallout 3...?

Are you kidding me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 19:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually did that the other day. Yep. Lots of Martinis and Poker, basically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 19:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PLOT TWIST:
Turns out the players end up destroying the main city, and were the destroyers the whole time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 00:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's all an illusion."
This is stupid without an explanation, so here it is: only the simplest creatures see the world the way it really is. Our view is so tainted, by whatever we think. Our opinions, our thoughts, form the reality we live in. And everyone lives in a different reality. Understanding of this, and a clear mind... leads to that power. Complete control, and understanding. Knowing that... you're wrong, and you're right in the very way you observe the world around you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 18:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well done, sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 18:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ordered them online from Barns and Noble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 18:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ordered them from Barns and Noble. Hope that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 18:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems legit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 04:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about that... Only realized after I had already posted... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 04:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did my hole you build a wall~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure if these are welcome here, but this is what I received for my cake day, after a 007 themed surprised party. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 02:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 04:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will join your firm! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 02:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, link fixer bot. Anyone that is not familiar with such a glorious subreddit can now go there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 02:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...
Don't make me show r/murica this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 03:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you caught I was only joking. I really hope it's not a race... I'm still in Kanto, actually. Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 02:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BLASPHEMY!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 17:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Game. This remains my favorite game of all time. Screw them haters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 02:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever seen Fullmetal Alchemist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 17:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! That's really cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 17:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. I'll keep this in mind. By the way, I'd love to hear a bit about the class you made if you don't mind... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 17:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! This lays things out very nicely! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 02:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I've thought about this, and know that I'll probably have to go through things quite a few times. Thanks for pointing me in the direction of some good classes to "steal" stuff from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd like help with the most daunting D D task I have ever undertaken. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 02:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have noticed the lack of a good Alchemist class in 4e. True, there is the artificer, but that's not quite what I was thinking, and yes, there is the alchemy mechanic, but it's kinda terrible and not at all what I'd like it to be, so I'm making an Alchemist class! I have school and a lot of homework so I don't expect to have it DONE anytime soon, but I hope to get the heroic tier within 2 weeks to a month. If you would like to make any suggestions, please do! 

TL;DR: I'm making a 4e alchemist class! Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 05:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game: Crystal. Starter : Chickorita, my favorite pokemon. I don't really have any special plans yet, but that's subject to change. I still have to beat firered... I'm coming on this train let, and plan on using september to my advantage as much as possible. I'll be a little behind the entire time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 04:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably mentioned here a lot already, but angel beats. Durarara is pretty great as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 23:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had Red Scales in mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 21:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I tried to play dubstep, and kirby music, but my players always bickered over which songs, so we stopped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 20:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. Good to know. I'm considering an Assassin character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 15:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. That's a really cool roleplaying idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 15:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is the Assassin class? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 15:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the feeling. I have a character I'm trilled about, but can't play because I'm always DMing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 15:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 15:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He convinces them to be dead with his sword" That. Is one of the greatest sentences I have ever heard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 15:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm playing a Teifling as well! I never get sick of roleplaying as them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/DnD, what are you currently playing as? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 23:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Players, what is your current character?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 22:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you hear the one about the circus fire? It was in-tents! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reagan Theory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 20:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Reagan was an actor, is it possible he was simply hired by someone else who was actually running the country in that time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 15:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fedora's are cool. Nuf said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 01:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like... Splosion man, but more splendid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 21:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, I thought everyone loved Slaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CDI Link </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 15:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 01:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you provide the lyrics please?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men, you have work to do! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 03:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 02:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super Smash Bros. End of story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL An American named Dolan is a candidate to become the pope. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 16:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 01:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dubstep... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-10 16:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two stories for this. They're kinda long, so sorry about that. 

1. So, my dad organizes concerts for a living in SLC. One day, a couple of my friends and I were going to a concert. For driving purposes, we decided to just spend the night out at Saltair, which is where the concert was. A LOT of people have died there in its history, be it from drug overdose, the three fires, or the several times it flooded. I got curious, always one interested in the paranormal, and headed into a room where I knew a rockstar had overdosed once. I pulled out a voice recorder, and did my first impulse: starting singing. The next day was an Angels and Airwaves concert, and so I started singing that. By the time I reached one of the last lines of the song, I felt something strange: a hand reaching up and touching my face. Like, I honestly through my friend was there messing with me, but I looked and no one was there. I would love to say I stuck around like the manly man I wish I was, but I left. Quickly. When I listened to the voice recording the next day, there were drums playing along with the melody of the song. Still have no idea why any of that happened. But if it was a ghost, I am proud to say I rocked out with a dead rock star.

2. At my school, we use laptops. A lot. All of the students are required to have one. Also, they give everyone an email under our school website, which has quite a nice "firewall" as I will call it. This firewall prevents anything from getting in or out. You can't email anyone outside the gmail community, and the outside community can't contact that email. Ever. But over the last couple days, strange emails have been arriving from weird adresses. They are always under a name that occurs exactly twice in the united states. They always say something like "hello honey" or "good morning darling" or something of the sort. I tried to email one back, and it said the adress didn't exist. Now, I know what you're thinking: "idiot kid got a virus from a spam-bot. Well, no. I personally checked anyone's laptop I could get my hands on for viruses. None. AND I asked the tech people at our school. These emails heading straight into our inboxes shouldn't be possible. The emails at first were adressed to people with the same first letter of their name as you, than to everyone with at least three letters, and than to you and you alone. If Reddit knows what's going on here, I'd love your help, by the way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-10 16:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indie Game. If you're a gamer, or even if you're not, this is truly a great movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 04:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That toy car by the place where you find Raul. Shudder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 04:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm a mormon going to a school in which everyone kinda hates the church. It's nice to hear someone say something nice about my believes for once, even if just vaguely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 01:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, how do you think Scrubs portrayed life as a doctor? Do you think it's accurate, or has nothing to do with it? Also, what is Janitors real name?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 16:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scrubs. Have an upvote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 16:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My father promotes concerts for a living. We've met a lot of great people in bands, and a lot of terrible people. People you would expect to suck (my example is Kesha) are actually great to talk to, and some people you'd expect to be cool (the black keys) are total assholes. Seriously, if you listen to the black keys... You have no idea how much of an asshole the guy you're listening to is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 16:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully not... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 16:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very interesting point. Kind of an objectivism thing, and I can understand that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 16:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, exactly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When my friends ask how much karma I have... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, what? Oooooh... I meant to say help. No clue what the hell happened there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am officially interested. I'm no pro, but I've done voice acting and writing before. If you'd like my life, I would love to give it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
