<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject723</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw.  You are too clever for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an immature and ungrateful thing to post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are also for building up the existing Body-see prophecy vs tongues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope-maybe you could try your sister.  I just did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Gifts of the Spirit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are essentially super-powers that we use to help the Church and glorify God!

Discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You looking for one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bible says they worship demons-or stone and wood-so yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your mom need a date?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That wasn't directed to you-it was directed at the Secular Humanist who wasn't bothering to actually read what I said but was arguing with what he thought I said.  Mispost-my apologies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump supporters are growers, not showers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dump day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to read again, friend-for comprehension this time.  My point is that long-term dating WITHOUT SEX (not without marriage) is practically impossible.  The context is as stated in the OP's original post.  This is not to apply to non-Christian couples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you looking for an argument? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you!  This OP had sex within 2 months of starting dating.  My experience is that staying abstinent is PRACTICALLY impossible for the long term-especially when there is zero reason to not just get married.  Paul was abstinate-but he didn't date.  Scripture has something to say about it if it will be heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus does it for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  Go eat some right now.  Bacon is delicious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are not more compassionate than God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Secrecy is really more important than justice, compassion, holiness, accountability, the name of the Church, and the souls of children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good post, OP!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I advise you always take the easy route.  That way you ensure a life of mediocrity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I left the part after this years convention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Narcan-duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah!  What a clown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loneliness.  Get into a small church and be very honest with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both of those books are AWESOME!  I've read them both a bunch of times.  2 other pieces of advice
1.  Read with others-your gifts are not meant just for you, but for your church!  So, read with your brothers and sisters and invest in each other.
2.  Teach-teaching what you've learned is the culmination of learning it!  You will retain so much more AND others will be blessed too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look-you obviously aren't going to take my advice.  That's okay.  But I stand by every word I said.  
I'm sitting here watching my 6 year old play Wii boxing and my 1 year old eat blueberry pancakes for dinner.  I've been exactly where you are and I'm not so old that I've forgotten what it's like.  
Marriage is NOT for the faint of heart-but don't let anyone despise your youth either.  These long-term engagements are a terrible idea.  Do you think you are getting "more spiritual" by practicing abstinence?  If you are going to be abstinent then you should not be dating.  YOU know and I know that before long you'll be cuddling, then touching, then the "abstinence" you've been practicing is all done and you both feel ashamed, she develops an eating disorder.., whatever.  If you love her marry her, if you don't then don't be a weak bastard and keep having sex with her because you are selfish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough.  Good luck with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had to have gone to Med school from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been married 14 years, have 3 kids with 1 on the way, am a homeowner with a great paying job and we are active members of our church, where I teach in a small group.  
You wise-sounding advice is in direct contradiction to the Apostle Paul in 1 Corin 7.  Also, what age was Mary when God thought her old enough to be married?  You are simply parroting social constructs, reinforcing modern thoughts on sexuality, and promulgating the excuse most young couples use to cohabitation, establish "sexual compatibility" by being promiscuous, and generally avoid growing up until they are in their 30s.
Sex is wonderful!  It's meant to be enjoyed while you are young!  Trust God in that He will make the marriage if much is made of Him in the marriage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still lost the popular vote... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it does not.  Marriage is a commitment universally entered into by people who have ZERO idea what a commitment it will end up being.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A long engagement/ dating relationship once you've had sex is, in a word, impossible.  It is also NOT a commitment-you can break it off any time.   1 Corinthians 7:9 is aimed directly at you!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's way simpler than you imagine.  THe hurdles you mention are ones you cling to because you use them to protect you from committing to a course of action.  "Not in a good place" is code for not having any money.  I'll tell you a secret-it's way more fun being poor every day with some you love, going to bed and making love, taking showers together in your tiny apartments bathroom, rejoicing over making the rent, deciding which used furniture to buy off of Craigslist than masturbating and semi-repenting in your parents basement.

Given your timidity, let me predict how this will go:
-you will date for awhile, fall in and out of bed with one another, resent each other, grow distant, break up and move on 
-you will have a tepid relationship with God over this period because you refuse to obey, but you are too scared to really turn your back and walk in "real" sin-in a word, you resign yourself to being lukewarm 

My advice is to commit-to be a man, to trust in God, to move forward into an adventure together.  

Just some advice from a total stranger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!  That's the best:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His teaching is solid.  I don't enjoy his writing style, but he's the real deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's a Christian, you are friends, you are obviously attracted to her-what at you scared of?  Commitment?  Life isn't for the weak or timid.  Guess what-marriage is a challenge for EVERYONE.
In love: don't be a coward.  Man up, propose, have a SHORT engagement, get hitched and get going.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's straight from the Bible, by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get married-then screw your brains out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great!  I hope God blesses it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yikes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember John the Baptist-you'd hate to have your head on a platter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of Ephesians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone here has triple digit IQs-so no one here voted for Trump.  Satire and scathing mockery only... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is the cause of the chaos!  The best way he could rid his administration of chaos is to jump in front of a train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternative fact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, were you posting facts or alternative facts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From 7 years ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our explanation: he's retarded-sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do listen to Pence-then I listen to Trump directly contradict him 2 days later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 05:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going to cast his Trump vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 05:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet you clearly can manage it.  Your name is Hispanic, are you sure we shouldn't deport you?  That's what the Donald would do... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 04:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you need him.  Good God your life must be sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 03:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need a daddy?  Trump is a terrible choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's the embodiment of the term "pompous ass". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not a "European Interest",  but a Christian, conservative, American, middle-class male.  Trumps administration is a clown show because Trump is a pompous, self-possessed ass.  His personality disorders are going to make a stable, sane policy-driven executive branch impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 01:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well-we can agree we think the other wrong.  Have a nice night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am seeing the entire story that the verse is a part of.

Are not two sparrows sold for a penny? And not one of them will fall to the ground apart from your Father. But even the hairs of your head are all numbered. Fear not, therefore; you are of more value than many sparrows.
Matthew 10:29-31 ESV

The principle in both of these texts is the same.  God knows everything that will happen, has a purpose and a plan for you personally and specifically, and you are invincible and have nothing to fear because you will accomplish His plan for you.  That was what God was telling Paul on the way to Rome.  The Jewish plot could not succeed because Gods plan was different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be misapplying it if I said that no Christian would die until they gave their testimony in Rome.  I am saying that Christians won't die until they have completed Gods purpose for their life.  That is the EXACT application of that verse.  You are the one who has pulled it from the context to stand by itself.  Read it in the story-realize it applies to all Christians, and  be encouraged..., or don't.
You response says more about you than it does about the verse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your response says more about you than the verse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God has no purpose for you?  That's kind of embarrassing to admit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure it does.  Just engage some linear thinking.  You can do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live 5 minutes from this church.  It is NOT in a high crime area at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should move on but he's too insecure because he lost the popular vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump sucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got the same amount of class as your "glorious leader". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep.  This former Republican agrees with you 100%.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if you use logic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean?  The point is that God holds your destiny-He has a plan-you won't be killed until He has decided you've finished the task He has for you.  Until then, you are invincible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The brilliance of this article is unmatched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is just a coarse buffoon.  He has zero class and zero tact.  I'm a white conservative but not a whiner, so any group can have whatever caucus they want and it won't hurt my feelings at all.  Stop trying to be the most persecuted and man up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sucks.  That's why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Princes word is worth nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does anyone even listen to Pence?  Trump comes back two days later and tweets the opposite then says "Mike and I haven't discussed it".
This clown party is a joke of an administration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corrupt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion you should approach God the way Jesus taught His followers to pray the Lords Prayer.  Doing it by rote or along the guidelines, as a meditation-it doesn't matter.  Frequently my prayers have just been me saying nothing, but waiting attentively and expectantly.  It's not the prayer that has the power, but the One being prayed to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can be born into a christan environment-but you must be born again to be a Christian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romans 13:4-an "avenger who carries out God's wrath on evil doers".  Gods wrath certainly includes inflicting death.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot actually happening in the words "LET THERE BE LIGHT".  Think about the properties of light, the rules it follows and the mysteries it poses.  Approaching the creation text with pride is always a mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You too have final testimony to give. And you are immortal until you give it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take courage, for as you have testified to the facts about me in Jerusalem, so you must testify also in Rome (Acts 23:11). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 05:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it.  There's not a lot of crime on Briarwood's campus is there?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love these sorts of posts.  Small, well thought out, human-scaled, very intentional use of color and materials.  I'm a big FLW usonia and Sarah Susanna fan.  I love the wallpaper in this space too.  The only thing I'd change is having the kitchen sink at the window to be able to look out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piper on the design of Gods Grace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 11:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Sweet Designs of God  devotional by John Piper
http://www.desiringgod.org/articles/the-sweet-designs-of-god </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for him.  I'm a Church at Brook Hills guy and David Platt was my pastor for years.  He is focused and humble.  A very good leader for the IMB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 10:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if they are already studying with the Jehovas Witness.  The book is heavy, but I've found topic searches to be brief and concise.  If you treat it like a reference tool and not like a novel it is, I think, invaluable for a new believer.  I do take your point, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've stopped listening.  The podcast has gone somewhat schizophrenic in my opinion.  Payne would do well to take some pointers from David Ridgen at SOMEONE KNOWS SOMETHING from CBC radio.  He knows how to take all the crazy threads and bring them back into one narrative.  
The actual timeline in this podcast is still in flux and it feels like we just keep coming back to the same questions without getting any answers.  And it's like there's no awareness that the podcast is even stuck in this loop. 
Sorry to be a downer, but I'm out.  There's a lot of true crime to listen to out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just not to scale for a normal human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very hectic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys are perfectly harmless, never poisoned anyone...we get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Derp  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rasmussen, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're talking about Trump, right?  I keep hoping he has a stroke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this thing snowballs and takes down this entire terrible administration.  What a pack of liars and frauds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right.  About 2 generations before Christ Rome was essentially a dictatorship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pick up Wayne Grudems Systematic Theology.  It is very readable and well-organized.  It is a big book, but don't be intimidated.
Rest assured-your Holiness is not dependent on you processing power. As Christians we are striving toward dependence, toward humility, toward meekness, toward child-likeness, toward becoming less.  Just beware that knowledge can puff up, and it  an be very subtle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Signposts with Russell Moore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How old are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 04:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most Jehovahs Witnesses are wonderful, kind, sincere people.  They are usually generous and warm and very friendly.  However, they are a false church because they do teach salvation by works, not by trusting in the work if Jesus Christ alone.  Their Gospel cannot save.
If I were you I would avoid studying with them.  I would find a small, Protestant church that believes in expository preaching and study the Bible with them.  Trust that the Holy Spirit will make any time you spend reading Gods Word worth it.  I would also recommend Wayne Grudem's Systematic Theology as a reference for all the questions you will have.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As literally as Jesus did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a church family? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you wanting someone to tell you not to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 3 ( soon to be 4).  Memory verses are essential.  We do read the stories in the Bible from the Jesus Story Book Bible, but will also read from a couple other Children's Bibles with pictures.  The point there is to paint the big themes, present Jesus, explain who He is and why He came.  
Then we select verses that are important for kids to know. Gen  1:1, John 3:16, Eph 6:1, etc.  We try to use the FighterVerses app, Seeds of Praise Songs (on RightNowMedia if you have a Roku), memorizing the books of the Bible.  We actually have a dry-erase board close to our dinner table and at the end of dinner just go through the verse a couple of times.  Kids brains are amazing.
I have friends who are musical who have family praise night-they pick some praise songs and everyone goes at it with their own instruments.  I can sing-so Zi will usually just pick a fun praise song and start singing it to the 1 year old, clap her hands with her, and the 2 and 6 year old don't want to be left out so they join in without any promoting.
I would encourage you that NO ONE has it all together.  It's very important that you are unified with your spouse on what you are going to do.  Do it once a week or 5 times a week-it doesn't matter so much.   What matters is that they see that Christ has a special place in your heart.  I would always say prayers with them every night.  I would model repentance to them in your interactions with them and with your spouse.  I would pray that God would grant them the gift of repentance and faith.  It's His to give!

Just a lot of random advice from a complete stranger! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus the King was a great study through Matthew.  He takes the Word very seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of the ASHES TRILOGY by Ilsa Bick.  Anyone read that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
