<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9822</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 17:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally not a dumb question. For me, my weight fluctuates pretty seriously due to water. It's important to measure your weight loss in averages, not just by the weekly drop you see in the scale. See this article for a good summary: http://greatist.com/health/understanding-scale-bloat-and-weight-loss

 I know it's difficult to wrap your mind around. For example, I weighed myself on 1/10 and weighed 251.7, weighed myself on 1/15 and weighed 252.2. Weighed myself this morning and it was back down to 247.5...water weight is weird. Just continue counting your calories and doing you...the weight will come off. Maybe try other measurements like the article says. I've found my best scale is the mirror truthfully.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 03:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAMMIT I really needed to see this post and read the comments. Recently started eating as strict as I've ever been, cut out alcohol and soda, working my ass off in the gym, the works. Saw a 3.4 pound drop two weeks ago and this past week gained two...even though my routine never changed. Thanks for reminding me to just keep pushing through even though my body is being difficult!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 17:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I have a Fitbit Aria which logs the average so I will keep a watch on that. Thanks for calming me a little hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weight Flux - M/22/250 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 15:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey r/fitness! I posted this question into r/loseit but got semi-choppy answers so I figured I would throw it out here to see what you all thought.

After losing about 85 pounds I figured it was time to kick it into high gear to lose the rest of the weight I want to lose, about another 50-60 pounds. I started with a new gym after leaving Planet Fitness and found me a personal trainer. I hit cardio by myself M,W,F for about 40 minutes and do strength/weight training with my trainer T,R for about an hour. Last week I lost about 3 pounds so I was obviously pretty pumped. I've started drinking significantly more water to ward off loose skin/stay hydrated. Additionally, my diet is super strict which I have NEVER swayed from since starting the gym flow back in mid-December. I usually eat at a 1,200-1,300 deficit, filled with meats and lots of veggies. So all is well on that front. 

Got curious yesterday and weighed myself...+1.6 pounds. I thought whatever I'll be fine. The more I went throughout my day the most pissed I got. I've been working my ass off and gained weight, wtf. Weighed myself again today and was still at around +2.0 pounds. 

The good folks over in r/loseit mentioned that it's most likely water weight causing this...either from muscle repair (my legs have been extremely sore since training on Tuesday) and that this was normal. But dammit, I'm looking to see results here! If it really is my muscles retaining water, should that start to decrease after I do my cardio today?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 00:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually bought a foam roller the other day and haven't used it...going to start tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 00:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm drinking a fairly large amount of water to ward off any loose skin that may happen during my weight loss but I will bump it up more after reading about all of this. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 20:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg funchords a loseit celeb on my post hahaha. Thanks for the insight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weight Fluctuation - M/250/22 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 15:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey gang,

So here's the sitch. I'm six foot even and 22 years old. I weigh myself normally every Sunday morning, right before breakfast, butt naked. I have a Fitbit Aria which I am generally pleased with. Last Sunday I weighed in at 250.7, my newest low. Throughout the week I eat at a strict...very, very strict 1,200 - 1,300 deficit, making sure all my macros are in check (protein high/carbs between 20-30g). I also hit the gym hard - M,W,F pure cardio on the elliptical (burnin about 500 calories) and T,R doing weight/resistance training with my personal trainer. So everything seems fine and dandy.

Got curious this morning and weighed myself. I actually gained a pound and a half this week instead of losing wtf. I was so pissed and have incessantly been thinking about it. My guess is water weight but I'm not 100% sure HELP PLS. So depressed over it because I was really hoping to be in the 40's this week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 22:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "great start to a life journey"

What a great way to start off your discussion. So many diets fail because people lose sight of the life long goal to a healthy lifestyle, they only look for a short-term fix. Kudos to you for having the right mentality!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 19:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Count me in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 19:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I started my weight loss journey I was so depressed and filled with self-loathing I couldn't even look at any mirrors. I would lay in bed and cry for most of the morning, cry getting dressed and then put on a smile as I walked out the door. It was the hardest years of my life. However, the best day of my life was when I decided "fuck this, I'm better than this and dammit I can beat it." Once I started losing weight and working out, the depression became a faint little memory in the back of my mind. 

Always remind yourself that you're worth it. YOU are in control of your body and YOU have the power to change yourself for the better. You got this!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 19:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all have to start somewhere! Focus on the diet definitely. Find out your TDEE, eat below that, get your macros in check and start seeing results. As someone else said, MFP will be your best friend! Once you're comfortable working in exercise, go for it. Keep up the great work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 18:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't ever feel stupid posting about how much you've lost. Five pounds is five pounds closer to your goal dammit. Keep up the good work and before you know it you'll be at your goal! Get that diet under control, get back into the gym and kick ass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 18:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stick with it. Get your diet down pat, add in some exercise and watch the pounds slip away on the scales. You got this, no biggie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 17:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every Sunday morning, hop out of bed, go to the bathroom, do my business, strip naked and weigh myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
