<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9341</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still haven't justified putting someone through a lifetime of suffering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't decide, it's for the parents to decide. I just think it should be legally okay to do, rather than forcing parents or society to care for a severely disabled child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not eugenics. Eugenics is aiming to improve the quality of the human race. If these people are so disabled that they wouldn't be reproducing anyway, then killing them wouldn't be changing anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend's cousin is similarly disabled, he has no self awareness and just drools most of the time. It has taken a terrible toll on her aunt. I fully agree with your position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ['We are out of the food chain!'](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-wRrRWay3lE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it likely isn't, so the humane thing to do would be to end their life before they have to suffer. I've justified it, it's for the greater good of the child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still haven't justified putting someone through a lifetime of pain, when you could prevent it before they are even aware of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And also give me access to a market of 500 million people where I made the 10 in the first place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yes, pain and suffering.](http://4.bp.blogspot.com/--OcJbuCgv8c/VNpqOFpSrQI/AAAAAAAAAJs/Cba4BMPy4l0/s1600/www.dermamin.com.jpg) I'm sure he does enjoy living and I am not advocating for killing him. This was just one example, there are many conditions which pretty much guarantee a lifetime of pain, how can you justify putting someone through it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not advocating killing adult or child disabled people who are self aware. It is a mercy killing more than anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [What has the EU ever done for us?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p-fRo5-p9hE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'lol' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you on that last sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you. I think that comparing this way of thinking to Hitler is a poor argument. This is completely different. A baby which has just been born has no self-awareness and will not even know that it is going to be killed. As long as it is done humanely then I think it is often for the greater good. A severely disabled child is a drain on society and the family it is born in to. I also find it morally reprehensible to sentence some children to a lifetime of suffering (those born with [epidermolysis bullosa](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Epidermolysis_bullosa), for example). We put injured animals out of their suffering, but we won't do it to our own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> through an announcer's table. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, very bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 10:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not been posted here before though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only sensible comment inn this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't believe it hadn't been posted here before when I searched for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'I'm just here so I won't get fined.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, yet we have nobody to represent us! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To not be spoken for from the opposite side

So what is your side? The Tories? The Tories don't give a flying shit about you, or the majority of the British public. I would rather have someone slightly further away influencing our policies (influencing, not controlling) and keep all the benefits of EU membership. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, they behave like children and they should be treated like children. Imagine a family of 2 parents and 3 children. If a vote is held to decide what will be had for meals, then sweets and chocolate would win every time. This is because the children lack the knowledge about how their decision will affect them in the long-term. Good parents would listen to their requests for these bad foods, but ultimately prevent them from damaging themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they believe the EU is bad for its constituent nations

Please explain how so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but more they want to be sure they made the right choice

I have come to the same conclusion. When they realise that immigration will hardly change, they pretend that they voted for something else, such as 'taking back control'. All they will accomplish is to hand power to the ruthless Conservatives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! We dunt listen to experts here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hate to be a nit-picker (I don't really, I love it) but health and safety legislation only applies at work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just remember that not all of us wanted this. We have been torn away from the EU against our will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just Scotland, there are many Englanders who hate what the Leave voters have done to our country. The whole vote was a shambles. Sensible countries require a super majority to pass major changes like this. The reality here is that there was no percentage requirement, but the politicians have screwed us for personal gain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would upvote more, but for the struggle of logging in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you rearrange the letters in 'Karrimor' it spells 'a K mirror', which is a description of the logo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savage! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 22:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Trying to find players near your skill...'

There aren't any that even come close, that's why I can't find any matches! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Reminded me of this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CgCjTTYnPKU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The majority of the UK think that every day is a tragedy in Brussels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called an interrobang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck are people just stood there filming Help them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Reminds me of this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VugtWhufJhI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope I win.

I always quote this and nobody ever knows what I'm on about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I've just witnessed the birth of the next Facebook or Apple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still, compared to other energy sources which can currently supply our energy needs, it is the better of the evils. Global warming may not be an immediate concern, but it is no less serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The technology used in Chernobyl is over 45 years old, it was an inherently unsafe design and no reactors are constructed like that any more.  
Fukushima was a freak accident under extreme circumstances and nobody actually died during the disaster. 600 deaths were attributed to it, but this is small compare to the 12,000 deaths PER YEAR from mining coal for energy.  
 [Deaths per TWh of various energy sources.](https://emanuelemilitello.files.wordpress.com/2014/05/deaths-per-terrawatt.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 10:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ROGUE ONE SPOILER ALERT!

In Rogue One at the end when they are on the beach waiting for the fireball to hit them, they should have fried to a crisp well before the fireball hit them, radiation travels at the speed of light! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I found the same one in a sex toy shop in Stuttgart airport.](http://i.imgur.com/IbX9tl3.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 09:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy the mercury poisoning! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
