<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8423</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 01:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superbly prime might be a bit faster, but going goes FTL while also teleporting around with IT.  Goku is too damn wiley for anyone but flash BL Flash to speedblitz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 01:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine it would be like breaking the sound barrier in that his shadow would trail behind him a fair distance.  But the answer is always yes.  Flash once ran fast enough to catch up to himself.  Of course he can out run his shadow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 17:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets give this another shot.

Elves and dwarves have changed appearance and attitude throughout history.  The two mythologies where you'll find elves are the closely related Nordic and Celtic mythologies.  /u/itsallfolklore already talked about the Prose Edda and their "elves."  However, the dark elves seem closer to dwarves, as they live underground and were able to craft new hair for Sif after Loki cut it off, both of these are main themes in for Tolkien's dwarves.

But for elves and dwarves in celtic literature.  In celtic myths, elves are seen as more mischievous if not out-right malevolent.  Old medicine books like Balt's Leechbook and Wio Faerstice list elves as the cause for such maladies as elfshot, a pain caused my elves shooting you with arrows.  Later we can see the myth of elves have stayed mostly the same in Romeo and Juliet, during Marcutio's speech about Queen Mab, how she may give women pleasure nightly pleasure or warts.  Here we see fairies and elves used interchangeably.  Even as late as 1884, when Princess Nobody was published and The Shoemaker was translated, elves were both described as, and drawn as little fairy people.

Scandinavian elves are much more similar to celtic elves than Tolkien's elves, though they would fall between the two.  While some elves were small like celtic elves, as in The Elf of the Rose, but they could also be the size of a human when luring men into their elven dances.

Dwarves are much less interesting.  Tolkien's dwarves are closer to the myths of gnomes, which Paracelsus used interchangably with pygmys, called them earth elementals who live underground and are only about a foot tall.  Later, closer to Tolkien's life, gnomes were described as small people who live underground and protect riches in Among the Gnomes: An Occult Tale of Adventure in the Untersberg.

Tolkien elves, dwarves, and humans are a christian allegory.  The Silmarillion is a bible of sorts.  Dwarves as a sort of Ishmael - an interference with God's (Illuvatar's) providence brought about by impatience, who would throughout history be at variance with the Elves.  Abraham and his sons compare with Fanwe.  Faenor is not Joseph, but instead is cast from Eden.  Earendil has something in common with Enoch and Elijah, in that he, as mortal, achieved passage to the blessed realm.  The devil was imprisoned for 1000 years and allowed free again, exactly the same as Melkor.  There are several differences that I wont go into, but the parallels are many.  

Tolkien grabbed bits and pieces of several myths, kept some characteristics, and added heavy christian framing.  While he didn't invent them entirely, he did put a new spin on elves and dwarves that has lasted into current pop culture.

I did not forget about orcs, I just have no idea where they came from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 13:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Short answer: Yes

Slightly less short answer: the general description of elves and dwarves were not made up, they both shared similarities with exist legends, in broad strokes.  Aconnection with the forests, aloofness, indifference to men for elves; a life lived underground, greed, selfishness, distrust of men, dwarves are more a composite of dwarfs and the friendlier parts of gnomes (goblins got the unfriendly parts). Where Tolkien's vision for these fantasy races starts is in the more fine details that do exist as current fantasy tropes.  Even the names, elves and dwarves, was sent back by his editor with elves changed to elfs and dwarves to dwarfs because that was the current day plural of the almost entirely different mythical creature.

Long answer: Go get a bachelors in philology with a minor in history.  Possibly a masters as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 07:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All we really have to go on is the name; the three blasphemies.  This makes me think it is a reverse of the holy trinity, the father, the son, and the Holy Spirit.  This ties in well with them returning if one is alive, they are most likely one being inhabiting three bodies like their namesake implies.  (High master rating). But three bodies to a mind does not a religious mockery make.  This would lead me to believe that the three bodies are not the same and do not share the same powers. We would have a Christ-like figure, most likely resembling what this thing once was, a disembodied spirit (high stranger/mover), and some form that allows fire and brimstone to rain down (high blaster).

If I had to guess, I would say three shard connecting to one person and absolutely ripped his mind apart, much like the rank 15 parahumans crazyribbon gave us examples of.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 23:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People used to argue over which was the worst expansion.  WoD killed the argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 07:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But her power is focused n projectiles.  If youre Skitter, you want to know you're about to get pelted with rubber bullets and tear gas.  If you're Lung, you want to know you're about to get pelted with a Davy Crocket nuclear warhead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 19:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicago tap is pulled from Lake Michigan, one of the cleaner lakes you'll find (mostly because there's so much fucking water they're hard pressed to dirty it up to a significant degree) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 14:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without them, Gandalf would have not vanquished Durin's Bane, fell, and be sent back as Gandalf the White.  While the song of the Valar sounded like chaos and discord when Melkor sang his own tune, Eru's words are " no song can be that is not of my own design" or something.  The point is, everyone has a part and the War of the Ring would have been lost many times over without Merry and Pippin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 14:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie supports Palestine independence!? Bernie hates the Je- oh wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 13:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True but, like Tom, the power offered by the ring is a trifle to him at that point.  This and his magic resistance would let SSG Goku resist the ring.  Also IT it into mount Doom as its shown he can jump universes and dimensions with it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 03:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, the only one who can resist the ring out of this bunch is current Goku due to his God status. The ring is magical.  Cap, superman, and pre-God Goku all have desires.  The only way to resist the ring is to have dreams that the ring can not twist (like Sam seeing himself as a Garden dictator forcing everyone to turn the world into a well kept garden while he rode around on a horse, muscles and shirtless) or the power offered by the ring is a trifle ( hi-dol, merry-ole). 

Cap fails hard.  His will will work against him as it drives him to better himself.  Similarly, while supes is powerful, the ring offers him magic power, and he is a very tragic character who has lost a lot and doesn't want to lose more.

Goku is the embodiment of increasing power but he has shown a very high resistance to magic since going supercyan that he just didn't have before.  This will let SSG Goku resist the ring.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 06:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gives me respect for the people who go toward that instead of away.  Even Armsmaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 18:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what they call homeopathic medicine that works?  Medicine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 06:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it were a decently competent man with a gun I could see Geralt possibly winning 3/10.  But you chose to put him against one of the best Cowboys in fiction.  With dead eye, Marston would put six bullets in Geralt in a second.  Even without dead eye, Marston is just too fast on the draw and his weapon is just too effective in this match up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 06:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a vagina penis tail.  We all know what it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 06:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to wonder how all of Bonesaw's implants effect psychic powers.  We know, from magneto, that metal can protect against psychic attacks.  Would the steel reinforcements implanted throughout jack's Bonesaw's, Shatterbird, and Burnscar's bodies help them resist the telepathic assault?  At least long enough to deal with the telepath. Hard to mind rape when the silicon on your precious electric chair has gone full allu Akbar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 06:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really.  Wolverine is fast, but Siberian gets to ignore every bit of wind/resistance which greatly increases her speed.  It took Armsmaster using his precog software to dodge her hits, and he was barely dodging them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 06:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say no, though I couldn't explain what's going on in the scene you mention either.  We see Robin's suit defaced with several of the Joker's calling cards.  This is an old bat who kills.  I don't know who or what this joker is( money still on Jason Todd), but he is already the Joker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 06:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An idea.  Combining this thought process with the fact that men are more likely to have genetic abnormalities.  My psychology professor said something that has stuck with me.  For every disorder like depression, and GAD, it is theorized there is a disorder that works in the opposite; making someone perpetually happy and ambitious or contented and out going.  These would go almost entirely unreported as there would be no reason for someone to seek out a professional.  

With this in mind, what if men are more likely to be successful because we're more likely to get good and bad genetic diseases? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 14:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slow down there.  Cruz is a cucknadian but Obama was born in Hawaii, his mother was a natural born, and his father was a LEGAL immigrant.  I see no problem with his natural statues.  I see more problems with Hillary's natural born status as the fifth circle of hell is not US territory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 07:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly agree here.  A rock and sling was pretty lethal in the hands of someone who can use it, and I'd bed Green Arrow could use the fuck out of it; probably several kill shots in the first minute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 18:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people are saying how the pipe weed is just tobacco, etc.  but you have to realize that Gandalf wouldn't smoke pipe weed if it was marijuana.  Marijuana is a depressant.  Gandalf is in the body of a frail old man, his mind is his weapon and he keeps it sharp.  Gandalf would hate pipe weed if it slowed his mind and sapped his will.  However, a stimulant like tobacco is exactly the kind of thing someone like Gandalf would smoke often for its affects ( and for the social aspect).  We also see him drink very little and never get drunk throughout the books.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 14:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, Always Sunny reference.  The implication is sexual.  "Powers get me on a super team -- being team mates with Starfire gets me kinky alien sex" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 14:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I know Aragorn could not master the ring but I have followed Aragorn for several hundred pages at this point.  Sauron knew of Aragorn's lineage but has no idea how powerful he was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 04:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hal Jordon as Parallax.  Guy Gardener when he had the green and red rings.  Bloodlusted Flash.  Bloodlusted Plastic Man.  I'd have to research to find more above S-tier.

Edit.  I mentioned two lanterns and somehow forgot Kyle with the white ring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 04:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's just... So many things are intertwined you usually have to elaborate on stuff to even explain other stuff.  Usually you just explain until you end up at "because an Ainur made it that way"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 04:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Gardener is a mean, unlucky son of a bitch.  The ring judged him and Hal as equally worthy but went to Hal because he was closer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 04:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly correct.  However, he was slain and the ring was taken, the disappearing thing is movie only.  As for his physical body, he did have one at the time of the War of the Ring, but it was sickly and frail.  Sauron himself tortured Gollum.  As far as turning invisible, the ring pulls the wearer into the shadow realm if the user can not resist the pull.  If they can, they exist in both realms like the ring wraiths.  This is why anyone who wore the ring traveled west; they were no longer wholly of this realm as a piece of them had forever faded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 18:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it doesn't not have to be a prostitute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 14:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damian Wayne absolutely loves being Robin.  A lot of it could just be brainwashing from Ras and Talia, but he loves beating people to a bloody pulp.  Also any guy on a super team with Starfire.  Because of the implication. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 14:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That and they share the same lord, the Ainur Manwe.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 06:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First part, restating a point she agrees with from the Drudge Report is perfectly fine.  Second, you're using the red herring argument fallacy.  I now can't defend the Trumpkin' viewpoint without you inadvertently being pro pedo.  It's funny because you're literally doing the kind of smearing she was talking about that the Clintons perfected.

I think you're in the wrong sub, here you go buddy.  /r/hillaryclinton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 23:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The blessing of Manwe and Yavanna can be taken from Aragorn seeming to be supernaturally commanding, even to strangers who don't know who he is.  Aragorn is also able to use magical properties in plants only kings can, which directly tied into Yavanna.  These feats are in the book trilogy.  

Aragorn's lineage is detailed at length in the silmarillion.  Melion is the great grandmother of Elrond and Elros.  Elrond chose to be elf and Elros chose to be human and became king of the numenoreans of which Aragorn is the rightful heir.  

Tolkien wrote later in his notes the times Eru interviewed in the world, one of which was tripping Gollum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 15:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To add to this, the ring also enhanced his already significant ability to influence and command people.  As for the right amount of power to put in the ring, Sauron was originally a maiar of Aule, the craftsmen, and a power maiar at that.  Despite having no direct hand in making the elven rings, the elven craftsmen still used Sauron's methods and this is what gave Sauron power over the elven rings.

And as for Sauron's ignorance of Aragorn and mistake thinking no one could he destroy the ring, he was completely justified.  Aragorn is the rightful king (which garners a blessing from Manwe and Yavanna) of the line of Elros the half elven, mix of man and elf with the boon of both and hardly a drawback of neither, descendent from the maiar Melion, one of the strongest Maiar we see.  No one but Eru himself knew how powerful a wildcard like Aragorn truly was.  And Sauron was right about no one being able to destroy it, it took direct intervention from Eru to trip Gollum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 14:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like clockblocker can tag anyone with his striker ability with any part of his body, so can saitama.  His power is to win, like ptv but makes his path the path to victory in a show of huge reality manipulation.  He can get punched and thrown around but his power is always in affect. On anything that comes into contact with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 07:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DOOM makes quick work of this disappointing trap and even quicker work if whoever set it.  They will soon feel the wrath of Dr. DOOM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 15:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jack would steer around S-class threats but not fighting them head on.  His shard is The Communicator rather than receiver, he's the closest thing to a telepath in worm as his shard can "talk" to other shard and figure out what they're doing.  For contessa, her shard would tell her and, inadvertently, Jack the path for beating Jack.  Jack would know the path and avoid it.  So Contessa's power would say 102 steps to kill Jack... Recalculating, 135 steps to kill Jack... Recalculating, 177 steps to kill Jack... And so on.  As for taking on eidolon or Alexandria, the communicator shard implies going both ways.  We're moving into speculation here, but it's implied that jack's shard will talk to other shard and say "this human and I are a fountain of knowledge unparalleled, you should not kill me as it detracts from our goal" and the other shard agrees, directing the cape to go nonlethal or even purposefully lose.  When a shard goes against its host, bad things happen (see Leet)

tl;dr Jack is a blaster 3, thinker 12 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 07:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry but you're all boned.  Like Nilbog or Behemoth, the S9 are S-ranked.  When they show up, so do the entire protectorate.  They killed Hero and scarred Alexandria.  They're arguable at their strongest with two of the top five heaviest hitting capes, one of the best tinkers in the world, two capes that can do city-wide mass killings, and a cape who has managed to live 20 years as leader of the nine, Jack.  Most normal capes don't make it to thirty and he's pushing 43; he's a fucking boogeyman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 07:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Major Worm Spoiler.

WoG states that jack, in a one on one fight, will be able to beat any cape but contessa.  And his and contessa's thinker powers cancel out, as thinker powers are to do, but jack keeps his blaster power so majority goes to him.  The only reason Jack lost is because the dragon's teeth, unpowered humans, got involved and made blind spots.  Before he got tagged by Gray Boy, Jack was just not going down despite the constant attacks by half a dozen A and S ranked capes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 22:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I know, yes.  Wog might say setting different.  Shame every endbringer has a counter to her.  Leviathan now has radioactive water, smurf can dodge and redirect, and bahemoth would... Like it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 18:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only Miss Militia can use her guns, no one else.  As far as the upper limits, it's said she was able to form warheads so something like the massive Davy Crockett which could weight up to 71 lb and was massive to boot (usually mounted on jeeps or on stands) would be one of the biggest.  But really, the specialty of her power was the surprising amount of versatility she had more so than the raw power she could put out.  For squishy parahumans, she could make a riot shotgun that shot rubber bullets that exploded into pepper gas when they hit.  For more resilient parahumans like hookwolf  or Lung, missiles, explosive rounds, and even a plethora of grenades could be pulled out in seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 22:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would actually give him a striker infinity. The whole point is that he wins with one punch.  So his power is to win but he can only beat you if he punches you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 17:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To take a qoute from worm, this puts him in the "too scary to live" category.  Thor treats bullets like bug bites, but how would he fair against a heart attack?  Bruce banner/hulk can take a bullet and spit it out, but how would a brain aneurysm work out?  Too much power in a rogue element.  We don't k ow the Death Note's power ceiling but what if it's above sky father tier?  What if only death herself is immune?  Frank writes silver surfer, Thanos, and Loki in his death note over coffee before going out for the night.  They die.  Frank is now the most wanted man in the multiverse and is dead within seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 17:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pythagoras was pretty good.  Whipping around the screen via right triangles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 15:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard to say, it could be a few things.  A bit about Elrond, he was the great grandson of a Maiar of no small power, he wore one of the elven rings of power, and he has a spell hiding his entire realm from those he didn't want to find it (much like his great grandmother). The glowing things could be the marking of his divine heritage like other children of holy beings (Jesus).  The glowing things could be the a visual component of the spell hiding Rivendale.  Lastly it could be a poor interpretation of what a ring of power is.  Take your pick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 15:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their souls pass into the halls of Mandos with the souls of men.  Men pass on but elves must wait until the world ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 14:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, but I couldn't think of a humorous way an old southern gentlemen would say "for most women, breast growth is not caused by their mammary glands expressing milk but by a natural growth in the breasts.  For a small minority of women, lactation can start significantly before or after birth.  This can cause problems as newborn's diets should consist of incredibly fatty colostrum and the mother's body not following the usually schedule can result in  digestion problems from drinking milk immediately post partem or simply having nothing to eat as the woman is not expressing." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 08:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/deadbedrooms

It's 90% Pity posts or humbebrags, but 10% is some pretty solid advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 08:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you see, the hormones in women's bodies get all uppity.  You got the boobie milk making hormones, the loosely goosey hormones, the expanding hormones, and the feel good hormones.  ( prolactin, progesterone, estrogen, dopamine). Now on top of making their uterus induce hysteria and there moods swinging like an old tire swing it's doing some good stuff too.  The trifecta, boobies, booty, and hips, are growing and they'll stay growed.  The milk won't come in until after the belly goes, so this growth is all natural.  And they lady parts are preparing.  They have all that blood flowing down there,  engorging this, swelling that, making it all warm, and sensitive.  And those hormones, they make her want to be close.  Very close.  As close as a man and a woman can get.  And with a belly like that--I hope you ain't a religious texen because there ain't no cow girls or missionaries to be had here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 17:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly this.  While other bosses like expensive cars, nice suits, and fancy meals, the Joker only takes the amount he needs for the next heist.  Other than that he has one ratty suit, and probably eats nothing but ramen and bananas.  He never looks healthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 17:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if he changes while erect would it just stay hard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 04:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're most likely not a public figure who bases his persona around family values and the bible.  Not defending the rat but I can see how an innocent man would be flustered in his position.  That said, he totally stuck his dirty rat penis into all five of those women.  Classic sleazy stereotype of having a woman in each city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 17:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and people tha aren't Goku and sometimes piccolo are relavent for a while.  Also some pedophelia humor but just look past that.  The dubbed version is on Hulu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 06:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over coming vastly powerful enemies is sort of Link's thing.  I mean, the big bad always has the world's embodiment of power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 17:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rumor has it she's one of the few celebrities who lurk/post on 4chan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 17:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not really painful, is really inconvenient, especially if it happens when you're in the middle of something.  It's also a bit of a dash to plug the bleeding nostril before blood gets on you/the floor.  I don't get them often, a handful a year at most, but I'm mostly just annoyed, like, you fucking nose stop fucking bleeding there's no reason to bleed... Still bleeding?  Of-fucking-course you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biden has stated multiple times he was no intention of running and is retiring after his stint as VPOTUS.  The poor guy lost his son, he seems so much different after Biden Jr. died.  Less fun perverted grandpa and more sad grandpa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 05:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey now, every generation has entitled assholes.  Our generation just has slight more that can grandstand their totalitarian beliefs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 16:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, love, cunt, tree, music.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 16:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary will make a great president.  Just not a great president for 99.9% of people out there.  Her donators would love her presidency: wars, trade deals, you name it, they'd benefit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 13:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing happened in my store.  Turns out Cap 2 can't be the slow stockers and the pluggers and 3rd's speed comes at the cost of inaccuracy.  I always tell my associates to do it right and speed will come with practice so I always knew it wasn't us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 13:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back during my IMS days we had one unloader make a chair in his pallet and sit down on it when he got tired.  He didn't do that more than once.  Had another associated make a bed in the steel and try to nap during his 15.  We found him a couple hours later and he was fired pretty quickly.  When the demographic you try to hire for is young guys then you tend to get weird ones.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 07:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm lucky one of my ASMs will take his dress shirt off and throw the fuck out of a truck.  And any supports who come back to GM know its my room while the truck is unloading.  Now if only we could have more than 5 people a night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 18:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no, we've already covered ad hominem and that's a terrible use of the Post hoc ergo propter hoc fallacy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 17:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red Herring Fallacy.  Any other logical fallacies you want to cover? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 17:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, almost every line on your post is an logical fallacy. Definitional retreat, appeal to ignorance, red herring.  There's more but you get the gist.  Most importantly you removed Hillary from the argument and relegated it to simply "a democratic or republican can want to remove WMDs from rogue states" which is the red herring and not really what he asked.  No one is arguing against that point.  Please answer his questions because, as the one making the claim, burden of  proof lies on you.  If you don't know how to answer it that stop parroting talking points you don't understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 17:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump needs ~66% of the remaining delegates.  There's some pretty big winner-take-all states still (looking at you, California) but there is still a pretty good chance moving forward that the convention will be contested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Doom vs The Justice League </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 05:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A dimensional portal opens up connected my marvel and DC Earths during one of DC Earth's more peaceful times.  As a result, the JLA is helping no the Marvel world clean up all of their villains.  Doom has a year to study, spy, and prep for the JLA come knocking on his door.  He can get limited access to the DC Earth and potentially make allies and gather resources but has to lay low for obvious reasons.

Round 1: original Justice League members, Aquaman, Batman, the Flash, Green Lantern, the Martian Manhunter, Superman, and Wonder Woman.  They come at Doom one after the other.

Round 1.2: The whole team comes at him at once.

Round 1.3: replace MM with Cyborg.

Round 2: The Justice League from Young Justice is on the other end of the dimensional rift. Superman, Batman; Wonder Woman,Flash, Green Lantern (Hal Jordan), Aquaman, Martian Manhunter, Green Arrow, Hawkman, Hawkwoman, Zatara, Captain Atom, Black Canary, Green Lantern (John Stewart), Captain Marvel, Red Tornado, Doctor Fate, Atom, Plastic Man, Icon, Red Arrow, Blue Beetle II, Black Lightning, Green Lantern (Guy Gardner) all turn toward Latveria.  Each comes one after the other.

Round2.2: all at once

Round 3: The Justice League unlimited, with all its might, turns toward Latveria.  How long can Doom hold out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 17:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the black cracked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 13:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So your choice is between a giant douche or a turd sandwich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 07:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She might, depending on source of the aura.  Nitrogen gas doesn't absorb IR radiation but it can make a good heat sink or just plain snuff out fires by cutting off oxygen.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A way out there theory on Parian's powers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 06:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been thinking over Parian's power and how WoG states it will be useful against Behemoth.  I'll state and support two points for my theory.

Parian is a bud off of Behemoth.

Parian's power is Nitrokenises, or the control of nitrogen while in gaseous form.

First, what nitrogen is and can do.  Nitrogen is the most abundant gas in the atmosphere, roughly 70%.  As far as weight goes, it is a fairly light gas but can exert a lot of force when put under pressure.  Pressurized nitrogen gas is used in powerful air powered guns and fire extinguishers.  Lightening can not form without nitrogen.  ATP energy making cells in the body need nitrogen (personal theory on how Behemoth cooks people from the inside out, uses all their ATP at once.)

As for Parian's current use of her power and how it could really be the manipulation of gaseous nitrogen, this is easy to explain as well.  Filling her dolls with her telekinesis as she does is actually her pushed no more and more nitrogen into the container until she is able to manipulate the whole of the container filled with the gas.  The leaking she feels whenever the doll is punctured is nitrogen literally leaking back into the atmosphere.  The fine manipulation Parian manages of small needles, threads, etc, is her extremely fine control of the nitrogen gas blowing the light object where she will it.  This explains the breakdown of control for heavier objects, she has to use more force to push with the nitrogen in the air and the result is unstable.  Parian is also extremely limited by the Manton Effect or else she could just stop your brain from getting any energy and kill you with a though.  Or Behemoth you from the inside out.

So since WoG states Parian got her powers during a behemoth attack, and behemoth is very predictable, it's safe to assume he was using his control of all energy forms during the fight.  While we don't know if endbringers can bud or not, the potential to counter while being similar to behemoth with nitrokinesis is high enough to assume, in my opinion.

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 03:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's the males that can actually afford a lawyer that get custody half the time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 19:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, a few reasons, none of them very good on their own but add up to outweigh the other option imo.  Business owners have money to make any legal battles long and costly, since they have everything to lose they'll fight tooth and nail.  As much as I hate to spout "Job creator" arresting and closing the businesses you want to instead hire legal employees seems like throwing the baby out with the bath water.  And closing all of the places where illegals do illegal work won't get rid of the illegals immigrants, just drive them to do illegal work.  Essentially you would be treating a symptoms and ignoring the underlying issue.  

And the wall isn't just Wall: Exxxtreme with Extra Length and Width, it has motion sensors, lights, extends into the ground, and other bells and whistles.  It's a tool as well as a deterrent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 17:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is a good thing and no it's not like the Berlin Wall.

It's not that people don't want to do the work illegal immigrants do, it's that illegal immigrants drive the wage of the jobs down to McDonalds levels.  Adjusted for inflation for the pay in the 80s, a farm hand and a meat packer, the two jobs heaviest in use of illegal labor, should make around 15 and 21 dollars an hour, respectively.  There isn't much unskilled labor that pays near that, especially ones high school kids can do, farm hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 17:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> implying any comment painting Trump in a bad light doesn't get bot up votes.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 17:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I did that during some of my high school sexcapades.  I was a loser, naturally, and hung out with the randumb crowd.  Well this girl I was dating and I were about to go at it when I said the same line, deep vaguely raspy Patrick voice and all.  Well she decided to reply in her best impression of sandy cheeks and wouldn't you know it we ended up role playing Patrick teaching sandy how to give a blowjob.  Talk about post orgasm shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 06:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anduril was reforged from a masterwork sword by one of the most power elves of all time, Elrond.  From a strictly mechanical standpoint, it was reforged as a +1 bastard sword of courage.  It produced an aura against fear.  It also had some requirements, mainly to be the rightful king to wield it.  Since they normally go hand in hand, Anduril's sheath was magic in its own right.  It was made specifically for Anduril and made sure the blade would never tarnish or be broken, even in defeat, ever again.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 06:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fyi this is a copy pasta about some nerd sperging over katana stats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 23:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more like magic is subtle than enchantment.  Gandalf made a lightning bolt hit a group of goblins with a lightning bolt but it was during a storm.  Sam made himself look like a large imposing hero but accidentally when saving Frodo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 23:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She also gave magical items to each of the walkers still present.  Aragorn got a magic scabbard, legolas a magic bow, Frodo a magic vial, Sam a magic seed, and they all got magic cloaks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 17:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any source on that claim?  Legit curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 07:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey buddy, I think your pallet is leaning into the steel a little bit.  And that one is leaning into the one next to it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 07:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone but cap 2 and maintenance refuses to Make bales.  Of course, this is a hold over from when only IMS and maintenance made bales.  Also I don't fuck around with getting people coached.  If I can get a produce associate coached for taking our break pack cart, I could get someone coached for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 06:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a breakdown of what my horribly understaffed cap team two does.  We usually have 5 people a day counting supervisors.

Set up truck.  This involves pulling my the freight away from the doors and toward the back of our tiny 3 bay back room.  Usually half of the steel can't be pulled because of old freight just there.  Also apparel has their dozen or so full roll bars back there as well.  

So the truck is set up and I get to throw for the fourth time this week because my coworkers who showed up are all inexperienced, morbidly obese, 65 year old women, or have one leg.  So I can't supervise now.  The line moves so slowly I have time to fill it, jump out of the truck and stack on a few skids at the front and separate the fright on either side of the line before jumping back in and throwing some more.  As the day goes on it becomes apparent that we have no room.  We backload into yesterday's trailer which takes time.  We finish with hopefully no meal violations.

After lunch management keeps us from pulling until 9.  They put two people on it and one usually leaves at 10.  I had to cut 7 hours last week.  I came in and worked for one hour.  Anyway, the freight takes way too long.  Management has us checking off every single thing over 50$ on the truck since we had over 2% shrink this inventory.  So I usually sweep and close the truck around 1am.  Every associate but two leaves at 11 every night so I might leave by 12 to if one of them is there.

This turned a lot more rant-y than I wanted it too. Sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 07:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must have had a bad experience with trump supporters.  Over at /r/the_donald I've only seen memes and genuinely nice people who support trump and will gladly tell you why without cramming his rhetoric down your throat (unless in meme form) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 16:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right but sadly the word discrimination has become so emotionally charged that when people hear it their expectations are set.  By changing the term to something new, positive discrimination, then the pre-build notions of the term are suppressed or circumvented entirely.

Yes it's fucking stupid but so are most people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 11:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to myth busters, my fire extinguisher now doubles as an emergency drink cooler.  Able to take a beer down to enjoyable drinking temperatures in just a few minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 01:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always assumed it was a heavily communist place, which would tie into your theory well.  All the kids, save prince Tuesday and Daniel's sister, are exactly the same age.  There are specific places and rituals around getting food that never costs any money.  Only one spouse works in any relationship.  

Instead of a free community what if it was a small community part of a larger whole like The Giver?  Perhaps Prince Tuesday is the only teen because the rest were drafted.  

Also what is wrong with Baker Acre? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 14:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soldier of fortune.  If you can come back from a 6 story fall and watch cuts close, you have a very high tier healing factor.  What you need now is professional training.  You need to learn how to fight and how to be a soldier.  Most importantly, you need to learn to tap into the mom-lifting-cars-off-babies strength your mind is blocking you from.  No ISIS member is getting up when you throw him 20 and threw a stone wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 14:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this assessment.  While Dr Manhattan has never come into contact with magic, his counter part, Captain Atom, has shown complete immunity to magic, be it mental or physical.  

I think Manhattan would enjoy experiencing something new--the feeling of magic and the presence of something that is inherently evil.  But he would quickly unmake it for humanity's sake and move on with his droll existence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 22:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but like Oin, Gimli's second cousin, it's pronounced grow-in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 19:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A big theme in Tolkien's work is power passing through noble and royal bloodlines.  You see this a lot as every hero, from Pippin to Bard, they are all noble or even royal.  Gimli is of the line of Durin, though not the royal line.  His father was Gloin, his father was Groin, his father was Farin, his father was Boran, and his father was king Nain.  Despite not being the Royal bloodline, he is still the dwarf equivalent of noble.

Legolas, son of elven King Thranduil, is naturally a prince.  I don't think his age or if he was the crown prince was ever stated.  But being a prince gives him a lot of power.

Aragorn has a lot of power in his line.  On top of having elves and even Maiar in his ancestry, he is the last of the line of kings of numenor.  This includes being rightful king of Gondor. 

Even with their inherent power, each had a few magic items a piece.

Aragorn had a Lothlorian cloak, the sword of kings, a scabbard that sharpened and cleaned his sword, and the pendent given by Arwen to protect him.

Legolas had a Lothlorian cloak and bow, as well as a quiver that always let him pull the exact arrow he wanted.  His shoes may have been magic as let him run on fresh powder without leaving a foot print, but tolkien later wrote in a letter than elves are as light as a feather.

Gimli had a Lothlorian cloak and we know his arms and armor came from the stores of the lonely mountain, so they likely had magic in them like all mithril seems to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 07:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations to both of you.  You two sound very happy and I hope your family is just as happy for the two of you.  I also hope your SO is fine with the no sexual relationship.  As someone who never 'got' sex, I would highly recommend checking out /r/deadbedrooms to get a firm grasp on what your SO may be going through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 07:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to come off as blunt but I can't think of a nicer way to say it;  perhaps you're being friend zoned?  If these people like your personality, is it possible they dislike something about you physically?

I mean no offense, and there is much better and more likely correct advice in his thread.  I just want to touch on a possibility I haven't seen brought up yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 01:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round one and two go to superman.  While the two fighters are close, superman just hits too hard for piccolo to handle, though he is easily a superior martial artist.

Round 3 and 4 go to piccolo due to his magic.  Specifically the dragon clan of namik is able to use magic materialization and piccolo is a master of the technique.  All piccolo has to do is create a block of kryptonite and its over.  And round four he could always just destroy the sun because blood lusted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 06:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C U C K
U
C
K </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 18:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Tulkas, massive and shirtless, with Gothmog in a headlock and Ungoliat in a scissor hold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
