<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8546</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 15:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1st [Involves how the UK relates to these countries](/hint)

2nd [The percentages represent breakdown within the EU. The EU as a whole represents 44% of the worldwide total](/hint)

3rd [Will probably change drastically after Brexit](/hint) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do these percentages indicate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 15:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 10:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find the Italian Ministry of Economic Development as a funding source even funnier. Company funds study claiming its product isn't bad for you? Cliche. The imagined headline "Study funded by Italian Ministry of Economic Development says pasta is great" still has me chuckling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 20:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In [this interview](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/a-giant-impact-may-have-created-mars-tiny-moons) the lead author says their calculations led them to base their simulation on an impact the same size as the one that created the Borealis basin in Mars' northern hemisphere. He seems to be hinting at the possibility of a connection. Or am I reading too much into that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 15:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only does the UK get more out than it puts in, but UK scientists can more easily collaborate with colleagues in other countries when the money comes from the same place. Let's say you want to do a project that combines your specialty in x with that of a colleague in Germany who's the best in the world at y. Think the UK government is going to fund a research project where half the funds would go to an institute in Germany? No way. But the EU would. Collaboration is SO important in science, and EU funding makes it easier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prominent UK scientist's factual assessment of Brexit's impact on research was followed by another interview dismissing her as "rather hysterical." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 12:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 08:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nooooo. Just the saddle to the frame. Had a proper lock for the frame and wheels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 18:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Some countries like Australia and England have programs in place that are ideal for this kind of research. These teams have embedded scientists, who work partly for a university and partly for a professional club."

I wonder overall how many of the national team doctors collect data for research/advances in sports medicine vs. are just focused on the practical aspects of treating their teams' players.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 16:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should maybe get around to cutting the cable lock off the saddle (forgot the combo). Need that rather less here than I did in NYC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This baby has gotten me through the streets of NYC and the fields of Brandenburg, Germany. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 16:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research in the UK is totally embedded in EU funding structures and collaborations. Five scientists explain how Brexit will affect their work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 16:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Article: 'Employment crisis' for new Ph.D.s is an illusion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 11:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The physicist who studies ISIS communities online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 14:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 01:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew that guy would win from the beginning. Systematic approach, and determined as fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 23:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks everyone for doing this. /u/CyprienVerseux, I loved [your article about the experience](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/the-martian-scientist). You are a funny and great writer. 

Questions for any crew member willing to answer: 

1. Would you really go to Mars to do research if given the chance?

2. Has the experience changed the way you'll do research when you have access to a fully equipped lab again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 16:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a good point. When it first came out, I showed it to a friend in the humanities whose (mostly?) joking reaction was something along the lines of "So you science people do know how to have fun!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 16:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. Rickon was good as dead as soon as the Umbers turned him over to Ramsay. Even if Jon had a better plan that incorporated the Knights of the Vale, The Boltons would have used threats against Rickon as a last resort before defeat. His survival and the Starks taking Winterfell were always mutually exclusive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 16:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My feelings exactly. I'm worried about them going forward. I can't tell if Sansa's expression when she rides up alongside Littlefinger and sees the state of the battle is more worried about Jon or more along the lines of "well this is a fine mess you've gotten yourself into."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING] Predictions about two characters' relationship going forward after the last episode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 15:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you think the Battle of the Bastards will affect Jon's and Sansa's relationship? Will the experience/success/catharsis of ending Ramsay bring them closer together, or will there be mutual resentment over how it went down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 15:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The head to his heart is a great way to describe what I hope will be the dynamics of their relationship going forward. I hope this experience brings them closer together and doesn't drive them apart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is #overlyhonestmethods good or bad for science? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 15:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently rediscovered the old Twitter hashtag #overlyhonestmethods. While it had me laughing out loud, it also made me wonder whether it was good or bad for science? Does it promote lazy research "because everyone does it"? Or is it a healthy reminder that science isn't 100% perfect? Or maybe it's just a good laugh (and it is a good laugh). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 15:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Jon's emotion-driven leadership and battle-style served him fine at Castle Black, but success south of the Wall (in battle and in life) requires a more cold, calculated approach that Sansa seems to be mastering.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 13:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it was so much the trying to save Rickon that was the problem as the reckless, rage-induced charging afterwards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 13:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We fortunately had many allies," Nigel Newton, founder of the book's publisher Bloomsbury, recently told ABC radio in Australia. "GCHQ rang me up and said, 'We've detected an early copy of this book on the internet'... We also had judges and the police on our side." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a British spy agency monitored the internet to try and prevent Dumbledore's death from leaking prior to the book release. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 13:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Competitive pipe smoking in 1960s England. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 12:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 12:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Original study](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160412/ncomms11219/full/ncomms11219.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Socially imposed monogamy in ancient humans emerged as response to endemic STI infections. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 12:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Everything] I think a major point of this episode is getting lost in all the excitement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 12:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm disappointed in Jon, and I think that's the point of the episode. As excited as we are to see Ramsay get his due, it's easy to forget that Jon fucked up big-time.

The take-away effect of BoB to me was to humanize Jon after several episodes of him coming across as unquestionably good and competent. He didn't take Sansa's warnings seriously enough. He endangered all the fighters who had his back by (rather understandably) losing his cool. He was frankly pretty overwhelmed by the battle (again, understandably so--he's still sympathetic, just more imperfect than we're used to seeing him). Davos had to improvise to make up for Jon going off-book, and Tormund kept his head much better than Jon in all the chaos. 

Yes, Sansa probably should have told Jon she'd reached out to Littlefinger. But her expression as she rides up beside him and sees the battlefield is revealing--one part worry for Jon, one part "well, this is a sorry state of affairs." Seeing our beloved warrior Jon bailed out by slimy Littlefinger is not a good look. He pulled it together towards the end and also showed a lot of strength in the episode. E.g., I thought the image Jon muddied by battle was a great foil for Ramsay and highlighted the good in Jon's character. I'm still rooting for Jon, but the episode tarnished him a bit in my eyes. But I'm also okay with that. I like GoT for it's complex, multi-dimensional characters after all.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 17:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have friends who live on the other side of the S-Bahn station than the the HU campus, which has some lovely, pre-war apartments with reasonable rent. I think it's a nice place to be if you like quiet (it's more-or-less dead at night, but safe). I'd especially recommend it if you think you'll be working long hours. Waiting on that platform for the S-Bahn into the city late at night in the winter isn't fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 15:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Physicians for Human Rights does truly inspirational work. [This account of one of their researchers who went to interview the Syrian doctors working in these hospitals](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/syrian-hospitals-under-siege-when-a-red-cross-becomes-a-target) really conveys the magnitude and tragedy of the situation. A lot of their people are just regular doctors who volunteer for them on the side.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 15:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read this a while ago, and thought of it again with the UCLA shooting. I wonder if any of those victims ended up on his operating table.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Los Angeles trauma surgeon speaks out against gun violence and talks about what it's like to operate on shooting victims every day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 15:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 18:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, also: you're not likely to find Vanillezucker in American supermarkets. You can make your own (there are recipes online) or just add a small amount of vanilla extract to the recipe and an equivalent amount of extra white sugar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 18:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you American? If so, this [table](http://cafefernando.com/conversion-tables/#Baking Powder) can help you convert those g amounts to tablespoons and teaspoons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 17:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice launch! I still remember the disappointment of my rocket's sad, tiny trajectory while all the other kids' soared in science camp. Probably taught me something important about the realities of practicing science though. In real life, experiments fail all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 23:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned it in school. Used to be standard typing procedure. A relic from typewriter days. Now that most typing is done for digital documents, most (if not all) style manuals finally changed the rules to a single space, but not in time for my high school typing class in 2003. I got away with double spacing for a long time, since my professors in college and grad school had learned it that way too. Two years ago, I finally admitted I was wrong and got with the picture, but since you don't really think when you type, the habit was hard to unlearn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 15:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine's switching to typing with one space after a period instead of two. Took two weeks of being conscientious about it, but now it comes as naturally as two spaces once did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What small change in habit makes your day a little easier? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 15:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pay Gap, Visualized and Analyzed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 10:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 15:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for offering. Your job sounds really cool as well. Maybe you should consider doing an AMA yourself? I'm sure I'm not the only one who'd have questions, and more people will see it as an AMA post than here in the request.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 14:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, thanks for reaching out to him. This post is just an AMA request (the questions are examples of what might come up in the thread). An official AMA would involve creating a post in the subreddit and providing some kind of proof. [Here's the procedure.](https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/wiki/index). Not sure it's possible with the Mars-like communications set-up. But maybe, as /u/KaneHau mentions it's been done with previous missions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 20:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Would be great if it works out. Based on the post I linked to in the request, I gather they have a great sense of humor and would be good in an AMA. Guess you have to have a sense of humor to survive in a confined space with five other people though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 20:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really great of you to have looked into this! Thanks and Fingers crossed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US reviews plan to infect mosquitoes with bacteria to stop Zika and dengue viruses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 18:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] Someone from the NASA HI-SEAS IV mission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 18:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This NASA researcher](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/the-martian-scientist) and/or some of his colleagues on the "Mars" mission. 

**My 5 Questions:**

1. How did you get selected for the mission?
2. What do you miss most about "Earth"?
3. What are the best and most annoying traits of the colleagues in the bubble with you?
4. Would you really go to Mars to do research if given the chance?
5. Has the experience changed the way you'll do research when you have access to a fully equipped lab again?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 20:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a food snob in many respects, but for some reason I prefer fake maple syrup to real maple syrup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zika virus protein could be vaccine target </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 17:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone ever worked with a pronunciation coach? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 16:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently heard a recording of myself conversing with a German, and my English accent sounded so much stronger than I hear in my head when I speak. I want to work to improve it and am considering working 1:1 with a pronunciation coach (the kind that also helps native German speakers get rid of regional accents, etc.). Anybody have any experience with that? Did it help? Enough to be worth the money?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 22:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're willing to travel a little outside the city, I highly recommend kayaking through the Spreewald. 

Edit: I think I payed like 15 euros per boat for 5 hours or something similar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 18:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. Hated typing class in high school. Now I do a lot of transcribing at work, and the slight speed advantage makes a huge difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 17:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, thanks. I don't have a lot of previous knowledge in this area and was surprised to learn reading the interview that the lack of definitive shore line called the ocean hypothesis into question (right? at least a bit?). Seems pretty big to have sorted that out!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 17:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crazy that the ancient ocean hypothesis was (basically) confirmed by evidence of something so dramatic. The lead author is so restrained in [this interview](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/researchers-find-evidence-of-two-mega-tsunamis-on-mars):

"Then, of course, there is the fact that the discovery of tsunami deposits represents definite evidence for the existence of the early Mars ocean." 

Oh, by the way, we figured that whole giant mystery out. I'd have had a harder time containing myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 17:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, my imagination is going crazy with this one. Tsunamis are just such dramatic events.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 16:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> West Wing. Look past the early 2000s fashion and technology. You won't regret it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have found evidence of mega-tsunamis on Mars, proving the planet once had an ocean. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 16:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Underwater archaeologists unearth pre-Clovis butchering site in Florida </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 16:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girls perform slightly better than boys on STEM test with real-world scenarios. But goal should be more absolute improvement, not just under-performing slightly less than boys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 16:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WHO Warns of Zika Risk in Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 16:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 16:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad was concerned about my protein. He doesn't give me too hard a time about it since my mom's a nurse and doesn't seem worried. I track what I eat in Cronometer (for my own reference, not my family), and was able to sit down with him last time I visited and show him that protein is actually the one thing I get more than the recommended amount of every day. Then we tracked his food for one day and saw that I actually get more vitamins and nutrients than he does (taking D and B12 supplements into account). Probably wouldn't work with all dads, but he seems much less worried now. Maybe some members of your family will respond well to the data-driven approach too if you tracked your nutrients for a week or so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
