<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2522</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 16:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The global norms of what a legitimate government are not what they once were. All governments must derive their legitimacy from somewhere. By being nominally democratic this legitimacy is linked to the will of the people, regardless of how much influence the people directly have. In the past, governments such as monarchies used divine right to derive legitimacy. States such as China rely on economic expansion and prosperity to prop up their legitimacy and tamp down dissent. The West uses regular elections from an informed electorate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 01:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a big problem in the US right now

http://abcnews.go.com/US/story?id=95475

http://m.wbtv.com/wbtv/db_373574/contentdetail.htm?contentguid=SaadPAJ7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is Brazil's president Dilma Rousseff accused of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 06:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 23:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That trickery is the official exchange rate, which no one can use because Venezuela is broke and doesn't have enough dollars. The $16 is from the black market rate, which floats like currency exchanges should and is the real indicator.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 21:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You specifically said US military, not military protocol in general.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 19:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the Citadel isn't affiliated with the US military, it is just a military style school with their own code. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 00:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty pro globalization so free trade is a plus to me. It's a way to set ground rules to build off of. I honestly think they promote global peace and stability. Some trust busting (especially in the tech sector) really needs to start happening though, along with the elimination of tax havens. Panama papers are a huge plus here so let's hope that actually gets something done. Honestly, I started this campaign more proHillary than I am now...she is just the candidate I think is most capable of governing at the moment. I really hope this election can pull off a strong Democrat majority and hopefully  get some good people in the spotlight for the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 23:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you can't tell what I am thinking. I responded to a comment not the person. Turning a conversation into personal attributes is diminishing any value it had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 23:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wanna provide some sources on those claims? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 23:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I believe in this amazing little American ideal called innocent until proven guilty. I don't follow the peoples court, mob justice is just plain immoral. What specifically makes her a terrible human being? What grievous crime is she guilty of committing? Can you substantiate any of it with *primary* evidence? Clinton is a politician that will promise what she can achieve, she is acutely aware of her strengths and weakness.

Sanders is a candidate promising the moon with no way of even getting there, no idea of the economic turmoil he would cause, no clue on the chaos a diminished US global presence would cause. He is too old to be so naive, too inexperienced in building a diverse coalition having sat in the comfort of Vermont for too long. He is a candidate of shallow blind promises. A candidate that sees a disaffected youth and says too them, here have some free stuff but never mind you won't actually benefit from it and the costs will prevent you from achieving anything financially in your lifetime. I'm not saying he's not honest and consistent, I'm just saying he is dead wrong and the government should be kept a million miles away from managing many of the things he wants it to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 22:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the Republican machine has been working on her for a real long time.  I consider her appeal impressive considering the continual onslaught against her pretty much since she became a senator.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 22:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I would say it is the almost 300 pledged delegates and 3 million votes.

http://www.realclearpolitics.com/epolls/2016/president/democratic_vote_count.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 21:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering he has only received 45% so far, I would honestly say completely improbable bordering on impossible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 21:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that is the only way Bernie has a chance to win too...huh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 21:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is winning the pledged delegates, how is that the establishment forcing it down anyone's throat? It is different parts of the Democratic coalition going up against one another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 16:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy what credible sources! The Inquisitor, National Review, The Intercept, by golly that's some quality journalism right there. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 03:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He surprised everyone with that job offer, including Hillary. Check out National Insecurity by David Ropthkopf. Great balanced discussion of both the Bush and Obama administration's, including how HRC worked with Obama as SoS, from a journalist that pretty much has insider connections with everyone in the national security arena.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 21:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really what this means is Russia is not afraid of the collateral costs of war. They don't need to be able to claim moral high ground like the US. This fits in very well with the Arab mentality of how to rule and govern, especially in states like Egypt and Saudi Arabia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 23:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of that article discussed anything substantive. The EU has historically had more issues with meat safety than the US.  Antimicrobial meat washes are a good idea, especially naturally derived ones like lactic acid. The pesticide debate is dubious at best. Everything still sounds like pure protectionism.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 18:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All this GMO fear is no different than the anti-vaccine campaigns.  It's just unscientific political drivel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 20:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I can't. I learned everything about this particular history from a lecture at a symposium. Wish I had a better source for you :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Key chain from Hussey Copper made in 1963 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 20:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 20:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to /u/Epluribusunumidiota and /u/DT81888 for helping figure this out. It means Good Copper using the [Shavian alphabet](http://oldblog.noahburney.com/language-scripts/the-shavian-alphabet/) . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 20:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to  /u/Epluribusunumidiota and /u/DT81888 for helping figure this out. It means Good Copper using the [Shavian alphabet](http://oldblog.noahburney.com/language-scripts/the-shavian-alphabet/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 20:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good copper! That totally makes sense! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 20:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit this is it! It means good copper! That makes a ton of sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 19:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the suggestion!

https://www.reddit.com/r/whatisthisthing/comments/4i5erl/recently_got_this_keychain_from_my_late/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently got this keychain from my late grandfather. Does anyone know what the front means? (x-post from /r/pittsburgh) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 16:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently got this keychain from my late grandfather. Does anyone know what the front means? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 15:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 18:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What protocol? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 17:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think a 3.7% contraction is "slight" in any sense of the word and growth isn't expected until 2017 per the Russian central bank's prediction. The only thing that's improving is the scale of the decline, but it is still declining but has pretty much bottomed out. 

http://www.ft.com/fastft/2016/02/18/russias-recession-may-be-bottoming-out/

http://www.ft.com/fastft/2016/01/25/russian-gdp-contracted-3-7-in-2015/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 16:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know man, she wouldn't have stolen something that wasn't an actual drug. If anything I think she would under report than over report.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 15:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what you call the president. It's not like there is some formal code when referring to the president. In person you can say Mr. President, Mr. Obama, or President Obama. There are no official titles other than the office in which he holds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 15:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, drugs don't really taint your work. Why do you think academia doesn't perform drug tests of any kind. Hell, Watson and Crick admitted to doing LSD while working on the crystallography of DNA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 15:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I was like okay, this all seems reasonable most of these are stimulants...but LSD man, she must have been weird to begin with or only did that one at home to not get caught.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 21:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, many Russians saw the loss of Crimea as a disgrace. I'm not sure any other territory can muster the emotional patriotic support to the same level.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 21:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the latest PPP number I've been able to find is from 2014 and wouldn't be indicative of the economic hardships faced from low oil prices and the Crimean sanctions. 

Russia's budget is stretched thin currently. They have substantially slowed down their modernization campaign to match this. Russia learned it's lesson trying to match the US in military spending, but still realizes how behind its military is after shriveling in the '90s. The most recent issue of Foreign Affairs focuses on Russia's military and foreign policy. It's behind a paywall but a subscription is pretty cheap. I'd highly recommend it. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 20:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's a Russian shill, nothing more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 03:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you know socialism has a different meaning in the States. Kinda like how liber means something different compared to Europe than in the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 22:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should read it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 22:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but don't stick them in cruise missiles. That's just plain reckless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 22:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its also because the baby boomer generation is starting to retire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 19:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook monetizes it's user base. That's the important thing for them, that more and more people use the Facebook platform. Facebook is not open, if it was it could interact with other social media sites, such as Ello. Tesla opened its patents after benefiting from them greatly. Tesla's goal is to increase demand for EV infrastructure which will then create more demand for their product. Overly long patent periods stifle innovation. Patents do not intrinsically stifle innovation. I suggest looking into the history of Saint Gobain and the beginning of patents in France as a good example of why they are necessary. France's industrial sector was lagging behind Britain's which had already established patent protections. Once France did, French industry started to take off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 05:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Viva strong and soft paper towels are ideal for this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 14:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China is passive aggressive. It is more like the slow creep of gangrene. China's territorial claims at sea based on history are tenuous best. China has no history of naval power. They have always been a land power with no need for the sea other than fishing. Claiming on those grounds can't even compete with the history of all the nations surrounding them. Combine this with the Han whitewashing the imperial history of China by saying it has always been Han ruling and there are no historical claims.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 14:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And sent them to labour camps while they razed their cultural heritage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 14:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China's military is untested. It's Navy has no significant tradition or skill. China has no ability to project power and won't be able to any time soon. Their subs are as loud as those America used in the '60s which limits their seafaring stealth. The Chinese military is only capable of defense and area denial. 

China certainly doesn't have a political advantage. Xi's current policies have a chance of being very explosive with the current economic slowdown coupled with the poor demographic situation. 

China has a lot of potential, but the cultural advantage you cited is also one of the main obstacles to transitioning to a consumer based economy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 23:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patent protections are necessary to give companies incentive to report their technology publicly. Otherwise, everything would be kept as a trade secret. This would slow down innovation and technological development, resulting in a concentration of companies that work in their respective fields.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 22:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So both of those examples are essentially arts. Recipes are protected as trade secrets and it's impossible to exactly copy someone's recipe just by tasting. It takes the trade skills too  There is absolutely no correlation with actual technology. Those are just bad examples.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 17:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Commenting because I don't know how to save your comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 03:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely not a libertarian. I support the Fed, hate competing currency, support strong regulations as needed, pro-military/defense industry, anti-gun (gotta live with it in our Constitution but it's a states right thing in my opinion and could be limited on that level). I support IP protections but understand they need reformed. I support mandatory vaccinations. The list goes on... I have not met a member of the Libertarian party I like and Ron Paul is nutso IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 00:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry but I don't know of any project like the ones you are referring to that's primary objective is to make a profit. Every single open concept framework has some sort of stated goal of helping society or being for the greater good. Thinking this would extend to everyone in the market rests on the fatal assumption the majority of people are not selfish and out for just themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the alternative to not having patent protection? Everything is a trade secret and won't be published then. What incentive is there to release your knowledge to the public if it can then just be taken by another? Then technological progress becomes a trade skill again and R D budgets have to focus on reverse-engineering the work of others or reinventing the wheel. 

Patents also protect startups. If a small company invents something large competitors with bigger R D budgets would be able to swoop in copy it and sell it at a lower price and destroy the competition. If I invent something as an individual I'm screwed. I can't make any money off of my work. It just gets "consumed by the market."

I completely and fundamentally disagree with these arguments in the excerpt. I will be honest I'm not going to read that link because it is over 650 pages...and frankly ain't nobody got time for that. But as someone that works in the forefront of technological development, patents are absolutely necessary. Reform is needed to match patent time to better align with current development cycles which have shortened dramatically. Development cycles have shortened thanks to increases in productivity from better characterization and analysis technology as well as process automation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 21:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is possible to have political viewpoints and values that you are absolutely not flexible on and will never compromise. But that doesn't mean you are not willing to compromise on pretty much everything else. Personally, I am socially liberal, but loathe the largess of government promoted by the left. This leaves me in a bit of a conundrum. I am all for progressive social policies and welfare, but through an effectively regulated semi-free market approach. The founders of the US designed our government to be inefficient as a means to limit its power. Efficiency comes from the private sector. I don't want a political crisis to damage our civil society. In my opinion government should serve to create the rules at the will of the people, interpret them in the context of our constitutional and common law framework, and enforce them. That leaves me with no party and struggling to associate with either viewpoint given the current political climate. Just starting your own party is pointless if you can't use it to express yourself in elected office.

Starting a party is a grueling process and in my opinion the biggest mistake third parties make is trying to start from the top down. That's not where the action is. A party needs to start at the local level in the US for it to become successful on a national level. That takes building a network of like minded individuals to run as independents first for things like school boards, city offices, and county offices. If you want a new party that is successful you need to have people with experience and you can't expect to pull any established politicians over without showing significant grassroot support in the electorate. But you build support and name recognition then you will have something to form a coherent party around a platform. This lets you start running party tickets and hopefully garner more support. This is easily a 10-15 year process of extreme passion and dedication from thousands of people. I think the climate is right for this kind of change, we just need people that want to go out and do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 20:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems a bit hyperbolic to me. There is a legitimate case to be made that there is a third path between the platforms of the Republican and Democratic parties. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 20:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is actually a little controversy in France over this because the National Front has taken out loans from a Russian bank [\[1\]](http://www.euractiv.com/section/europe-s-east/news/national-front-s-russian-loans-cause-uproar-in-european-parliament/)[\[2\]](http://www.themoscowtimes.com/news/article/marine-le-pens-party-asks-russia-for-27-million-loan/560066.html)[\[3\]](http://www.politico.eu/article/le-pen-russia-crimea-putin-money-bank-national-front-seeks-russian-cash-for-election-fight/) to finance their campaign and if they meet a minimal threshold of something like 3-5% of the vote the French government pays it back. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 18:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree somewhat with your point. With the fast pace of IT development shorter patent times could boost competition and innovation. Heavy capital investments, however, need more protection than those that require less capital, otherwise the investor takes all the risks without the commensurate return.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 16:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without IP protections, what motivation would there be for investment in research and development? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Agents of the Russian World: Proxy Groups in the Contested Neighbourhood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 20:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 18:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, and if anything is posted with a well articulated and sourced critique of his platform it gets downvoted into oblivion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 18:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Under President Sanders, the Planet Will Feel the Burn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 02:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 03:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clearly have not made a point, I'm not "imagining" anything. You are completely discounting a group of voters because their States are red in the general election. You say this like that means their opinion on the leader of their party is unimportant and only the voters in States that are blue and support Sanders matter. Please point out where you didn't say that. Tell me what you actually meant. Your entire point is that other voters are stupid because they live in a state that Democrats don't win in the general election. You are saying their views within the party don't matter. You say this like only the farthest left parts of the party should matter. Sorry to break the news to your but there are conservative parts to the Democratic party. Sorry you are upset your Socialist candidate is losing because more people disagree with him and are supporting a centrist candidate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 02:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then what? You make it sound like red States don't have Democrats. You haven't made any point. Are you disparaging a group of people solely based on their geographical location? That's just as bad. Stop pretending politics is anything more than demographics. It shows you don't fundamentally understand how politics work in reality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 22:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's really weird. 
https://www.sos.state.oh.us/sos/elections/Voters/FAQ/genFAQs.aspx#declare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 22:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you know, she is actually a Democrat and those people like the party base dont want some outsider coming in and telling them they should be ashamed of calling themselves Democrats and that they don't know what it means to be liberal and progressive. He's kind of a condescending jackwagon in my book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 22:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you mean she won the black vote by huge margins? They are one of the most significant parts of the Democrat's coalition and you seem to be more than willing to just cast them aside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 22:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Primaries are controlled by the states while caucuses are controlled by the parties. State legislatures control primary dates but the parties control delegate counts based on rules decided by the delegates at the convention.  

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_presidential_primary?wprov=sfla1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 21:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really misleading about Ohio if you know how the party system actually works. Ohio party affiliations depend on what primary you voted in the last election. If you don't vote in one you become an independent. Voted in the Republican one last year? Your a Republican. Voted in the Democrat one this year? Now your a Democrat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 21:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Border Tunnels http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-border-tunnels-20150501-htmlstory.html

The failure of alcohol prohibition http://www.cato.org/publications/policy-analysis/alcohol-prohibition-was-failure

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 01:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree the US and China shared a mutual distrust of the USSR.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 01:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's from PBS so it can't be too bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Untouchables: Why its getting harder to stop multinational corporations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 20:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 18:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In response, no. As a result, yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 18:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay okay, go back to your basement and eat your Cheetos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 18:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow you are seriously butt hurt over not getting a joke. Cool down. Sorry you don't have the common knowledge about one of the most famous presidential assassinations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 16:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh, the good ol' he must be a kid that's why I didn't get it. Nah man, sitting here with a PhD. Age isn't the issue, your comprehension is. It wouldn't be a joke if I had to explain it, therefore the gif. Sorry to deflate your ego.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 15:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said.... http://i.imgur.com/axJmn.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 14:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Context clues man. Reading comprehension bro. In your comment: "the president would be able to say nah I'm the god damn President I can do what I want if I want..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 12:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Missed the point...whoosh. He went against the wishes of the secret service by first by going to Dallas and second by riding in a convertible. He "did what he wanted." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 03:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what JFK said and look where it got him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 17:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It means you like the person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 20:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That hits too close to home :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 19:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://ncronline.org/blogs/ncr-today/misogyny-and-catholic-church

http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/religion/11883273/Bigoted-misogynistic-and-controlling-scathing-critique-of-Catholic-Church-by-its-own-members.html

http://www.theguardian.com/world/2014/jun/29/pope-francis-woman-from-rib-avoids-pledge-reform-catholic-church </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 22:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe you are overestimating Russia. They have not had their way in either. Certainly Russia annexed Crimea, but that was a last resort since they lost influence over Ukraine as a whole. The armed conflict is in fact a failure of Russia as a global power. Ukraine is the motherland of Russian culture, but was lost by the greater pull of the West. 

Syria is another situation where Russia is vastly limited in achieving its aims, but Syria has been a thorn in Russia/USSR's side ever since the Assads came to power. They are more than willing to take everything from the Russians but their advice. Russia does not have near as much influence in Syria as it would like. Their recent actions have only served to prevent a further falling in their stature as a global power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 22:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. The UK seems to be shying away from its past global responsibilities in favor of only economic interests. To me it seems like the UK is on a path to just wanting to be the world's bankers without a care about where the money is from or how it was obtained.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 20:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smaller government doesn't necessarily mean smaller spending. It means a more efficient allocation of the resources the government already collects. The tea party and libertarian fringes have distorted what the traditional model of Republican small government really is. Government is inherently inefficient and in the US it was designed to be that way. This is where the big push for privatized social security and health care come from. The government should not be in the business of providing services for its people where market forces are able to replace the government. Rather the role of government should only be defining a set of rules for which the system to work. Privatizing social security would reduce the risk of fiscal mismanagement in the future because Congress would no longer be able to pilfer a fund that isn't there. The only services in which the government should be involved is those where market competition has a negative impact on the outcome of that service. The prime example being the prison system. How anyone thought for profit prisons was a good idea is beyond me. This is what has led to the eroding rights of the imprisoned and the squeezing of money from an already vulnerable population. The for profit system further increases the cycle of incarceration and violence by not really affecting recidivism rates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 18:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life is hard man, everything worth its salt is hard. That doesn't make it impossible and that doesn't mean we shouldn't try. That sentiment is a smack in the face of our forefathers who fought and died to give us the democracy we have today. Their first plan failed, but through hard work and compromise and we arrived at the constitutional democracy we enjoy today. To say it is too hard to vote, too hard to make a difference is to say everything that has happened in the Americas over the last 240+ years was a waste of time. Change begins with the people. Real change requires sacrifice, it requires pain. The change offered by this current administration eschewed pain and we wound up with a system that isn't any better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 17:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The biggest obstacle to equality in democracy is an ill-informed electorate, not some elitist BS of the man putting you down. During the primaries we should vote not only on candidates but the specific issues we want to see answered by the candidates that the FEC then compiles and requires written responses form all candidates for all to read and become informed before the full election. Don't answer them? Well, you don't get to stay on the ballot. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 17:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, things would actually changed if people voted instead of just sitting on their couch complaining.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 00:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This can only be seen as the resurgence of Chinese exceptionalism after the end to the Century of Humiliation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 18:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 13:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's really no problem. I got a "burner" phone when I went to Malaysia last and had to register my ID using my passport. It took all of 5 minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 13:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Countries all over the world do this. It is not inconvenient to non-Americans. You just use your passport. I've had to to this in other countries without a hassle. Linking an identity is different than linking a residency.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 22:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how this would limit your ability to do so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 23:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had people carry in my home during a Christmas party then get pissed off when I kick them out. The only person allowed to have a firearm in my home is me and I only have a long gun. If you can't respect that then I don't trust you to carry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 23:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you also need the right equipment and some dishes can take all day. There are also dishes that can be difficult to make like Chicken Kiev. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 23:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, for me it depends. If it's a meeting that depends on me to run and function I'll get there late because no way in hell am I waiting for someone, I have more important things to do.  If I am going to a meeting to get something out of another person, I'm there early. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 23:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will get into the US regardless of whether or not there is a wall. The only thing a wall would do is increase the reliance of illegal immigrants on criminal networks. Building a wall is just like prohibition. It seems like it would work, but people are very resourceful when they really want something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 22:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should fix our migrant worker system rather than build a wall. During the grow season bring in migrant workers and send them back when they aren't needed. Nations all over the world do this successfully. 

American success is predicated on immigrants. We have some of the highest population growth in the developed world thanks to immigration, which in turn helps slow down the problems caused by the aging baby boomers.  A fence won't be anything more than a money pit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 19:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, tensor calculus is so fucking tedious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 21:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And look how much cheaper things are. People can survive and live quite decently on a smaller budget thanks to places like Walmart. My parents struggled to make ends with 5 kids when I was growing up. They are envious of the low-cost options we have now, which were virtually non-existent in the 1970s through the 1990s.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 18:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a good chance this would have gotten a hearing if Scalia were still around since only 3 justices need to agree to hear a case for it to come before the court.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 16:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummm...sources for those outrageous claims? Mechanisms of action? If this is real, there will be published scientific literature on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
