<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9850</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glass Beach: Natures Way of Recycling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraines National Bank Department director nabbed while accepting $25,000 in bribe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraines National Bank Department director nabbed while accepting $25,000 in bribe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraines National Bank Department director nabbed while accepting $25,000 in bribe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BTW, very similar to Russian GIBDD musor's (traffic police) post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one more pic - https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C3giVg1WAAAGfQD.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cat and dogs warm themselves on the heating line lid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Firefox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Loft Toilet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pension Clash Looms as Ukraine Opposes IMF on Retirement Age </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pension Clash Looms as Ukraine Opposes IMF on Retirement Age </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finland handed over all BUK information to Dutch prosecutor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 51 Must See Historic Photos (since 1861) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photo gallery - 1915-1951 police records </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 13 Stock Photography Tips - how to use your camera lighting, features, surroundings and different techniques </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6 Largest (and Most Expensive) Camera Lenses Ever Created </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nikon D810 as the Best Landscape Photography Camera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Insights from "High Output Management" by Andrew S. Grove </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Master the Basics of Production**

In order to have an effective production system, Grove says that all execs and managers must consider the following three components:

* Time
* Quality
* Cost

The way in which you handle these components will determine how effective your production processes are. Production takes place in three stages:

* Process
* Assembly
* Test

You may also have whats known as a limiting step; or, the process that requires the most amount of time to complete, and therefore deserves the most attention.

While these are basics with which many managers and execs are already very familiar, Groves crash-course on production is especially beneficial for new entrepreneurs.

**Identify Your Indicators**

Grove says that in order to achieve sustainable scalability, youll need to establish some indicators. The best types of indicators measure the actual output  not just the activity itself. They should be measurable, and ideally, they should be accompanied by a metric indicating a timeframe and a quantity. These concepts go hand-in-hand with OKRs, which is the most effective way to integrate indicators in your company.

Grove identifies two main types of indicators:

* Leading Indicators: These should measure and/or evaluate input and predict output
* Trend Indicators: These should measure output within a given period of time, such as a quarter or month

**Implement Managerial Leverage**

Grove defines a managers output as the output of his or her organization combined with the output of neighboring organizations, or other organizations under his or her influence. The managerial leverage, then, is defined as the measure of output created by any of the managers activity. Effective managers have a greater influence on neighboring organizations.

According to Grove, these are the primary responsibilities of a manager:

* Information Gathering
* Information Giving
* Decision Making
* Nudging

Managers can also delegate, but that requires both managers and their direct reports to have access to the same information.

Grove recommends that supervisory managers have 6-8 subordinates. Having fewer subordinates could lead to meddling, while having more creates chaos and confusion.

In addition to the points listed above, Grove believes that managers should do their best to achieve regularity, and avoid interruptions whenever possible. Batch processing is an effective way to complete tasks, and managers must also designate specific me time to complete their duties.

**Get the Most out of your Meetings**

Grove considers meetings to be a high-leverage medium, but only when they are used effectively. He identifies two main types of meetings:

* Process-Oriented Meetings These meetings should consist of an exchange of information, and they should always be scheduled. Grove advocates holding weekly one-on-one meetings between managers and direct reports. Staff meetings should only be held to discuss any matters involving more than two people, all of whom should be present. Operational meetings should open with presentations, and they should be used to review achievements and ongoing processes.
* Mission-Oriented Meetings These meetings can be ad-hoc, but they must be driven by an output, and they require a chairman.

**Become a Strategic Decision-Maker**

When managers and execs make decisions, they typically happen in three stages:

* Free Discussion All parties involved in the decision making process should be able to partake in the discussion as equals. Grove says that one of the greatest challenges that prevents good decision making is the fact that many people are hesitant to speak freely, thereby shielding some of the critical information that could be used to inform important decisions.
* Clear Decision A decision is made based on the free discussion.
* Full Support

While support wont always entail complete agreement by all parties, it should always involve commitment by everyone involved. Grove believes that when making decisions, you should always consult others first.

**Plan Wisely**

In High Output Management, planning is considered to be a three-step process that involves:

* Studying Your Environment
* Predicting the Future
* Reconciling

Grove recommends using MBO to assess your performance, but to take it a step further and optimize efficiency, his OKRs are a suitable practice to aid in planning.

Effective planning is critical to performance. Grove believes that failure to execute is a result of failed planning of the past. Also, he advises that managers and execs bear in mind that their resources are finite. When you approve one project, you are ultimately saying no to something else.

**Determine Your Task-Relevant Maturity (TRM)**

Grove believes that there is no single, optimal style of management. Instead, he argues that your output is a result of a few different variables. These variables make up your Task-Relevant Maturity. It incorporates the following:

* Your Degree of Achievement-Orientation
* Your Readiness to Responsibility
* Training
* Experience

When managers have a high TRM, they are more likely to delegate. As a result, this increases their managerial leverage. They generally have minimal involvement in their direct reports operations, but they establish regular monitoring practices. Individuals with medium TRM tend to have individual-oriented session, and establish consistent, closed-loop communication. Low TRM managers usually rely on task-specific session, and are very specific in their expectations of what, when, and how.

**Tackle Performance Management with this Two-Pronged Approach**

Reviewing performance is the single most important form of task-relevant feedback, according to Grove. Your objective in assessing an employees performance should be to improve his or performance by advancing skills and boosting motivation. This can be achieved in two ways: assessment and delivery.

* Assessment: You can only assess an individuals performance if you provide clarity in your expectations ahead of time. You must specifically define output measures, including productions, reports, designs, and so forth; and you must also establish internal measures, such as hiring, planning, etc. Bear in mind that you must never evaluate people against what you perceive as their potential; rather, you must evaluate them based on their output. Again, Groves OKRs are advantageous in achieving clarity and defining expectations in advance.
* Delivery: When it comes to ensuring delivery, you should aim to achieve commitment from your people. Level with them by focusing on the individual  always listen first, and then try to establish a solution.

**Train Effectively and Compensate Fairly**

Grove believes that motivating and training employees should be the sole responsibility of the boss. Training should always fit with your company culture and processes, and more importantly, training should be approached as an ongoing, evolving process  not simply a one-time event.

Employee compensation can be based on two factors: merit and experience. Many organizations use a blend of the two to determine salary. When an employee receives a promotion, it should always be tied to his or her performance.

**[Source: Book Insights from High Output Management by Andrew S. Grove](https://www.atiim.com/blog/book-insights-from-high-output-management-by-andrew-s-grove/)**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter teams are required to set goals each quarter known as OKRs, an acronym that stands for objectives and key results </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BetterWorks competitor Atiim has quietly made progress with VCs and customers, raises $1M for HR 2.0 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston-area tech companies are making moves at a fast pace in January of 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston-area tech companies are making moves at a furious pace in the early goings of 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgia visa waiver approved by Parliament </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 09:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McCain sent a letter to Trump raising concerns about Russias recent attacks against Ukraine, and urging the president to provide the defensive lethal assistance the Ukrainian forces need to defend themselves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 09:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McCain sent a letter to Trump raising concerns about Russias recent attacks against Ukraine, and urging the president to provide the defensive lethal assistance the Ukrainian forces need to defend themselves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 09:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Allan on the Dr. Oz show talking about GTD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 09:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [David Allens Tips to Tackle the To-Do List](http://www.doctoroz.com/episode/straight-red-carpet-burning-health-questions-country-music-s-biggest-stars?video_id=4609252041001) - 3.5 min video

[The 2-Minute Rule That Helps You Stay Organized](http://www.doctoroz.com/episode/straight-red-carpet-burning-health-questions-country-music-s-biggest-stars?video_id=4611282019001) - 1.5 min video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 14 Portrait Photography Tips Tutorial - Lighting, Features, Surroundings and Poses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 13 stock photography tips - how to use your camera lighting, features, surroundings and different techniques to take better stock photos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Understand Photo Camera Aperture in 5 Easy Steps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photographing Pairs in Nature - 17 Photos to Inspire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time-Lapse Photography - Getting Started Guide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vintage photographs from 1915-1951 police records </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 15:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting started with context lists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukrainian navy aircraft attacked from Russia`s BSF ship in Ukraine`s territory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NATO calls on Russia to help stop spike in violence in east Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukrainian court sabotages fight against judicial corruption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukrainian court sabotages fight against judicial corruption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vinnytsia region residents block road in protest against healthcare reform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No sactions talk between Trump and Putin, - White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cease-Fire Violations in Eastern Ukraine - The U.S. is deeply concerned with the recent spike in violence in eastern Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine can't afford Dozors, Oplots and other up-to-date military hardware, - Ukroboronprom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston-area tech companies are making moves at a furious pace in the early goings of 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making OKRs More Than an Acronym at LinkedIn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Insights from High Output Management by Andrew S. Grove - Intel   OKR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 13:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 Great Insights from the Google OKR Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 13:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 13:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [15 Great Insights from the Google OKR Goals Video](https://www.atiim.com/blog/15-great-insights-from-the-google-okr-video/):

* 2:07  Companies should fight the urge to say: Well, Google did it that way and, Thats Google, we could never be like them, etc. As Klau put it, Google wasnt even Google until they began using OKRs  it was just a young and ambitious company. In other words, it could work for any company.
* 4:40  The reason Google was so attracted to OKRs is because they provide data. The setting, tracking, and measuring of objectives and their corresponding key results provides concrete data, which can be used to benefit any organization.
* 8:50  OKRs are connected across the individual, team, and company levels. Klau uses the example of a football team: the head coach, defensive coordinator, and individual player each has his own set of OKRs, but they are all connected to the overall goals of winning games and selling tickets.
* 12:30  Objectives should be a bit uncomfortable. As Klau puts it, if you know youre going to nail it, youre not trying hard enough.
* 13:50  All OKRs contribute to company-level goals, but each individuals set of OKRs is not necessarily a company-wide priority. Back to the football comparison: although the defensive coordinator may not be concerned with getting a feature in the Sunday paper like the PR team is, each team and individuals OKRs all align back to the main priorities, which are playing well and achieving high attendance.
* 15:52  OKRs inherently create discipline and transparency within an organization, because everyone can see what everyone else is working on.
* 18:37  The writing and collaborating processes of developing OKRs often becomes a cyclical process  Klau uses term virtuous cycle.
* 21:00  Allowing individuals to be a part of the OKR writing process could open up new discussions, and perhaps even provide new insights for upper-level management and other leaders.
* 24:50  More than half of the objectives should come from the bottom up; in order for OKRs to be effective, they cannot all be dictated down from the top.
* 32:30  Its important to understand the difference between objectives and key results; Klau explains the two by using examples of actual OKRs that he composed in the past.
* 42:00  In his examples of past OKRs, Klau refers to making a measurable impact with Blogger  but we wonder if that phrase could be better defined. A measurable impact to him might not be the same to another person. This one wasnt so concrete and failed to have a number  which went against what he said earlier in the presentation, that each OKR should have a number with it.
* 54:00  Low scores on OKRs should not be viewed as failures, because they still provide data and can act as a road map for the following quarters objectives.
* 55:30  According to Klau, OKRs dont take a ton of time. He further says that leaders can establish a rhythm very quickly when it comes to implementing and grading OKRs.
* 1:06:15  Klau says you only need to have 1-2 one-on-one meeting per quarter. Yet, because data and feedback are crucial, weekly one-on-ones may better facilitate the OKR process. Having regular check-ins could prevent the need for the lengthy quarterly meetings Klau kept referring to, as well as formal, antiquated performance reviews.
* 1:16:50  In response to a question about when a management team should adopt OKRs  Klau answers, as soon as possible. He says even if youre a team of five, the earlier you adopt OKRs, the easier it will be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Google Sets Goals Using OKRs - transcript of Google OKR video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 13:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emergency Situation in Avdiivka, Ukraine - Statement of U.S. Mission to the OSCE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 11:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emergency Situation in Avdiivka, Ukraine - Statement of U.S. Mission to the OSCE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 11:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to set OKR in JIRA for effective adoption with UpRaise addon [x-post from /r/okrsoftware/] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [15 Great Insights from the Google OKR Goals Video](https://www.atiim.com/blog/15-great-insights-from-the-google-okr-video/)
* [Top 6 Lessons from Google OKR Video](https://www.atiim.com/blog/top-6-lessons-from-googles-okr-objectives-and-key-results-video/)
* [How Googles OKR Video Inspires Every CEO to Use OKRs](https://www.atiim.com/blog/google-okr-video-inspires-to-use-okrs/)
* [How Googles OKR Video Gave Us More Ideas to Evolve the OKR Process](https://www.atiim.com/blog/ideas-to-evolve-the-okr-process/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Google Sets Goals Using OKRs - transcript of Google OKR video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Pincus, Zynga Co-Founder: Everyone knows their OKRs. And that is a good, simple organizing principle that keeps people focused </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to set OKR in JIRA for effective adoption with UpRaise addon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 12 Shocking (But Beautiful) Photos of Tornadoes and Supercells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why You Need to Discover Iceland With Your Camera (6 Photos) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 12 Nice Photos of Tornadoes and Supercells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 12 Photos of Tornadoes and Supercells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does it take to bring order to chaos? - Allan: "GTD is really not about getting things done. Its about being appropriately engaged with your life and your work." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 13:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 Organization and Productivity Gurus You Should Follow on Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 Organization and Productivity Gurus You Should Follow on Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The exact color to paint your office to become the most productive - is not a color itself that affects your behaviour, its how intense a color is that affects how you respond to it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The history of the to-do list   4 tips for a to-do list that gets things done </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Achieve a Leaner Inbox With These 3 Fit Tips - Curb those constant cravings; Limit your portion sizes; Work off that excess email flab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 10:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rail Road </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 10:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Used to Be a Human Being - An endless bombardment of news and gossip and images has rendered us manic information addicts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allen: Entrepreneurs dont need time, they need space to stay focused. They need room to talk to the right people about the right things. They need room to think. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sharing Economy: Nice. But Does It Create Real Jobs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Allen on 5 Reasons for a Meeting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever find yourself wondering why youre in a meeting or what the meeting is trying to accomplish? Here is a classic article from David Allen on 5 Reasons for a Meeting. Enjoy!

There are five reasons to have a meeting. Each may be a perfectly fine reason. Make sure everyone at your meeting knows and agrees with which of these you are there to accomplish.

1. GIVE INFORMATION
Hello everyone. Ive brought you all together today to let you know whats been going on about the pending lawsuit. Id like you to leave here today understanding whats going on, and with as much background as you need to be able to answer questions that may arise from our customers.

2. GET INFORMATION
Thanks for coming. Weve invited you all here to find out from everyone what we should be aware of thats going on in your division relative to the new product roll-out. We want to know whats happening at all levels in the organization about this, so we can make some adjustments in our plans accordingly.

3. DEVELOP OPTIONS
Wed like to spend this afternoon surfacing, formulating, and exploring as many possible ways to deal with the problem weve just uncovered in the new system implementation. We want to make sure weve got everyones perspectives and all the possible
alternatives formulated.

4. MAKE DECISIONS
Weve brought you all together this morning to present to you the three proposed approaches to launching our new product, and get a consensus decision on which one to pursue.

5. WARM MAGICAL HUMAN CONTACT
There are three agenda items we would like to cover today. And though we could have done this by email, we wanted to have an opportunity to bring the new team together in one place, and get some time to get to know each other between the lines

You may often have more than one of these agendassometimes even all five. Today Im going to share some information with you, and get some information from you as well. Were then going to explore some possible approaches to the situation, and then decide our best course of action. Meanwhile it will give us a chance to get to know each other a little more as real people

Pretty common sense stuff. Right. But, ever sat in a room with someone trying to make a decision, someone else just wanting to do some brainstorming about some possibilities, some people just wanting to get to know who theyre working with, and someone else just wanting to get some information about the situation? And they all wind up wanting to kill each other?

Its very valuable to get clarification and agreement on the front end, as to which of the five reasons for a meeting you have going on.

David Allen

http://gettingthingsdone.com/2016/07/david-allen-on-5-reasons-for-a-meeting/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Praise of the Last Minute - The last minute is not always the worst time to do something </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Cant Anyone Make a Decent Freaking To-Do App? - David Allen: A lot of tech people I know are going back to paper  theres still no better tool than a paper planner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain Obvious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 09:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 08:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://feo.ua/news/26033o-v_feodosii_ocherednoy_skandal_vo_dvore_mnogoetajki_ne_fedko_hodyat_postroit_esche_odin_dom_foto_video.html - more pics from there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 08:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraines government has hired Washington lobbyists to fix its problems with the Trump Administration, but would do better to fix its internal problems, instead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraines government has hired Washington lobbyists to fix its problems with the Trump Administration, but would do better to fix its internal problems, instead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraines government has hired Washington lobbyists to fix its problems with the Trump Administration, but would do better to fix its internal problems, instead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.yescalifornia.org/primary_results_conference_moscow Putin's Cal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin Cal Friends' Statement on the Opening of a Cultural Center in Moscow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexicans propose boycott of American products in response to Trump's border wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexicans propose boycott of American products in response to Trump's border wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.yescalifornia.org/primary_results_conference_moscow
Putin's Cal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cal Putin' Friends' Statement on the Opening of a Cultural Center in Moscow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Squatters turn Russian oligarch's empty London property into homeless shelter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Squatters turn Russian oligarch's empty London property into homeless shelter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OKRs  The Fundamentals. Uber, Youtube and Motorola Examples </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The startups software works like this: you list out your companys largest goals (such as grow the business), then you break them down into smaller goals (like book $3 million in new business), some of which are tied to teams or individual people. From there, employees and teams can update the progress of their individual goals, which automatically impacts the status of those larger goals. With charts breaking down the progress of each goal, the companys leadership team is able to get an overview of its overarching goals and how employees and teams are contributing, including whether anyone is falling behind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The startups software works like this: you list out your companys largest goals (such as grow the business), then you break them down into smaller goals (like book $3 million in new business), some of which are tied to teams or individual people. From there, employees and teams can update the progress of their individual goals, which automatically impacts the status of those larger goals. With charts breaking down the progress of each goal, the companys leadership team is able to get an overview of its overarching goals and how employees and teams are contributing, including whether anyone is falling behind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BetterWorks Competitor Atiim Raises $1M - HR 2.0 for small- to medium-sized businesses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the Canon 5D is the Ultimate Workhorse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 09:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Landscape Photographer's Checklist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 09:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 Breathtaking Examples of Bird Photography - Tips   Advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 09:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anathema as instrument of influence on the Ukrainian politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 08:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump '100% behind Nato', says May at joint White House press conference - as it happened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump plays down prospect of sanctions on Russian being lifted soon, May says Trump has confirmed he is '100% behind Nato' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump '100% behind Nato', says May at joint White House press conference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McCain warns Trump not to lift sanctions on Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Article] These Are the 20 Fastest-Growing Skills in the Online Job Market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These Are the 20 Fastest-Growing Skills in the Online Job Market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 101 tips from professional photographers for portraiture, fashion, photojournalism and wedding photography </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 101 Most Influential Photographers of All Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 14 Portrait Photography Tips - 3 min Video Tutorial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 12 Landscape Photography Tips - 3 min Video Tutorial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Statement concerning the resignation of the Grand Master of the Sovereign Military Order of Malta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 07:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Bishops decry Trump's orders to construct wall on border </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 07:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Bishops decry Trump's orders to construct wall on border </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 07:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Bishops decry Trump's orders to construct wall on border </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 07:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wild hunt: another FSB general found dead in Moscow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 07:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK forces escort passing Russian 'ship of shame' returning from Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 07:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK forces escort passing Russian 'ship of shame' returning from Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 07:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukrainian World Congress calls to support Ulana Suprun and her 'significant contribution' to reforms in Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 07:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, i recently found an article about how to compare such apps - [The 21 Critical Questions to Ask When You Buy OKR Software in 2017](https://www.atiim.com/blog/21-critical-questions-ask-buy-okr-software-2017/) Some of these tips are helpful for personal use also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Is The Internal Grading System Google Uses For Its Employees - short review of Google OKRs video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Google Sets Goals Using OKRs - full transcription of Google OKR video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 06:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Google Sets Goals Using OKRs - Rick Klau covers the value of setting objectives and key results and how this has been done at Google since 1999 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 06:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> :       ,       </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU's court upholds freezing of funds of Russian Almaz-Antey: Russia supplies weapons to separatists in eastern Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 18:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU's court upholds freezing of funds of Russian Almaz-Antey: Russia supplies weapons to separatists in eastern Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 18:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schumer Previews Bill to Curtail Trump's Authority on Russian Sanctions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 18:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukrainian memorials to Ukrainian and Polish victims of NKVD defiled by vandals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 18:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Ukraine court posts for super-rich judges  amp; defender of Yanukovychs dictatorship laws? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
