<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7383</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 05:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Err, I guess I didn't clarify, I meant the overall design; I've made enough practice exams to be familiar with ChemDraw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 04:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're the one that makes these!

I just wanted to say that they're great, especially as a TA looking for easily digestible stuff to help students along. How do you go about making them? Is it just powerpoint or is there some kind of LaTeX for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 06:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I may not have the most authority on the matter, as I'm also a senior undergrad biting my nails over Ph.D. programs, at least I'm in the thick of the stress with you.

You're going to have to come terms with knowing you most likely won't make it through the sieve for applications to most schools, as /u/radiatorcheese said. No matter how good the rest of your app is, places with a high volume of applicants have to do some kind of pre-screening and the easiest metric is a 3.0 GPA cutoff (official or unofficial). However, to the places that won't do that your research and teaching experience will be a huge boon to the adcoms, especially since you'll be applying to lesser-known schools where many students may not have any research at all (and apparently pubs are really rare)!

However, at the risk of being rude, while a C+ in a couple classes seems somewhat dismissable (had a bad semester or absolutely despised the material in a class and you're not applying to do something related to it), having that in every class suggests you have trouble grasping the material or are unmotivated. I would think it will look very strange that you were a TA with that kind of record, and you may be looked at a bit skeptically (this is where your letters come into play).

Try to go to a conference if you can and talk to some professors. Blow your GREs out of the water, get that paper published and you'll have some solid counterweights to the GPA. You won't be going to any big names like Berkeley or MIT, but I think you could find a program somewhere, if you *really* want to do chemistry. Maybe discuss doing a Ph.D. at your current institution with your professors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 05:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As some others have stated, an entire math *major* is a stretch, but the more you know, the better. Barebones, you'll need the calculus sequence. As part of your later coursework, you'll also need to know some differential equations (thermo PChem) and linear algebra (quantum PChem   inorganic); those will likely be covered in your classes, but stuff like symmetry will be way easier to understand with some mathematical understanding of things like group theory.

In the mean time, you can relax and take your time on learning, you probably won't need any math for your organic sequence, and AChem is mostly just the same boring statistics from high school with the occasional atom (sorry if I offend anyone here), so you're looking at another 2 years to flesh out your mathematical prowess.

Also, don't worry about your pre-calc score, I barely scraped a B in that class and thought I was terrible at math too; once I got into calc II I found out I not only could handle it, but it was fun! I added a math minor and have a 3.9 GPA on the required courses (humble-brag mitigated by admitting that I would still totally fail a pre-calc exam). Most of the stuff required for a second major would probably be terribly boring for a physical scientist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 17:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The city or upstate?

Because upstate NY definitely has hardcore rednecks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 17:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you could keep the boots under your desk; I also keep a pair of stained paints in my desk so I can wear shorts to the lab when it's hot out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 16:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm familiar with all the force particles (except the Higgs, because I'm not cool enough).

His explanation was very understandable, I figured it'd be something related to field theory. Quality link, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 16:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't call it simple, this reaction has been giving us trouble for months, this is the first time this ever happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 16:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It got way more intense under the UV lamp and I could see it more clearly after shutting off the hood's light, so I figured it was fluorescence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 06:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More info on virtual vector bosons? I'm new to QM (see: took 2 undergrad classes and read some books) and haven't heard that term, and Google has stuff over my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 06:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's only $34 for a 75g tube.] (http://www.thomassci.com/Thomas-Brand/_/THOMAS-LUBRISEAL-STOPCOCK-GREASE)

Treat yo' self. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 06:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about greasing the stopcock? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 06:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good eye! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 06:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a bunch of worthless internet points for brown stuff once.

I rarely get to see blue fluorescence so this was special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 04:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm, am swimmer.

I used to come home from practice, eat 90 lbs of food and crash from exhaustion at about 9pm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 03:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually not until after this picture, then it made this really weird yellow gel-like emulsion which had to be filtered; it was the first time brine ever made an extraction harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 01:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Bonus picture post separation with more blue/yellow color scheme] (http://imgur.com/0CZm5Qq) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 01:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only dirty because we work so hard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 01:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel so bad for you. We have some ground glass sep funnels but they just sit in a drawer.

Edit: consulted Hooked on Phonics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 01:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subbing a CN for a hydroxyl, but a labmate of mine is doing a completely different reaction and she gets similar outcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colorful Phase Separation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 21:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 16:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible the inner flask is meant to be for reaction and the outer flask is meant to be a cooling jacket, but those stems are insanely long.

/u/CraigMacTG is probably right here; [here's a picture of a similar looking cruet,] (http://imgur.com/qki1yER) and [one of a 2-chamber cruet.] (http://imgur.com/iV4Bvze) Most likely their lovechild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 07:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if you're still looking to do this 2 weeks later, but MIT's Open CourseWare series on linear algebra was phenomenal (better than the lectures at my school!), as was their multivariable calculus, I imagine their single variable/basic calculus would be just as good.

http://ocw.mit.edu/courses/mathematics/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 04:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started Player Piano and haven't decided on the next; what made Galapagos your favorite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 01:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I'm late to the party here, but Vonnegut's work is pretty damn good, though what I've read hasn't been quite as fantastical and far-future as Asimov, I'd highly recommend him!

Cat's Cradle is probably my favorite book by him, but the many stories in "Welcome to Monkey House" are very good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 01:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're both right overall, and Heisenberg *is* attributed to that concept, along with Bohr; I think Heisenberg's original idea was that a waveform exists as a distribution of all states being simultaneously "true," until measured (as detailed in the wiki on the Copenhagen interpretation), which is what Schrdinger was calling absurd. Though I guess I was going off of what everyday people think of when they hear Schrdinger (the cat) and Heisenberg (momentum and time uncertainty). Nobody's wrong as far as the science is concerned, but you'd be right-er I suppose?

Either way, don't feel bad; I wasn't really trying to call out anyone, just trying to shoehorn in QM info since it's all really cool stuff.

Edit: lots of words added. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 00:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were right!

I gave references and some information in another comment if you were curious beyond the legitimacy of puns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 00:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I like your pun, [Heisenberg is attributed to uncertainty,] (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Uncertainty_principle) and [Schrdinger's cat] (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Schrdinger%27s_cat) is mocking the idea of a [wave function existing in all states, then collapsing to an eigenstate upon observation.] (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Copenhagen_interpretation) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-26 04:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case you're not annoyed by people replying yet, I figured I'd weigh in.

I had multiple meetings with this with 8+ people with no issues at all, it worked perfectly fine whether I was on my tablet or laptop (though FYI the tablet version a bit limited). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 04:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His Messenger Series lectures can also be found on YouTube! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 03:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's an assortment of stories about his life more or less; I can't say if you'd like it if you're not into that, but I wasn't sure if I'd like it until I read it though, and I did it in chunks like short stories (it also probably helped that I knew about him as a physicist before the book was recommended). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 23:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, Kyle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 20:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Surely You're Joking, Mr. Feynman"

I approach my own curiosity differently and see that things don't have to follow some arbitrary strict rules when sharing information; it served as a basis for me creating an organization at my school where we informally discuss research results, I've learned a lot more since.

Edit: seeing as quite a few people also liked this book, in case you all didn't know there's a "sequel" to it that's also pretty entertaining titled "What Do You Care What Other People Think?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 21:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should try that; ethics of cross-species mating sounds more exciting than any monotonous party banter.

Keep your new friends away from your pets, though, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 16:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, I think bank robberies, rampaging metal sharks, and biker gangs threatening to remove ears for a hat are at the very least not mundane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 14:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American here, "dry heat" means hot but not humid, humidity makes the heat a lot less bearable.

Source: Florida </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
