<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6959</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 07:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mais pas mademoiselle, mais je l'apprcie. Et toi? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 07:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good horror movie idea. 


Humans hurt the reef with their climate change, but it lives and learns to strike back. Giant Kanytyil swarm from the depths to pull swimmers to their deaths. Venomous  Kuykal sneak out unseen and kill with their sneaky poison. 

A beautiful innocent girl in a bikini is spared and eventually falls in love with her reefy captor. 

The end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 06:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stilton and pinot noir for me. I like my cheese pungent and salty and my wine tasting of socks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 04:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blockchain transactions could make the whole mess obsolete, but transitioning could be hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 03:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, and now Australian taxpayers are about to shell out an additional $20 billion for more low quality internet.

NBN chief executive Bill Morrow released a statement on Friday morning confirming the government, not debt markets, would fund the rest of the roll out. 

http://www.smh.com.au/business/government-loaning-nbn-20-billion-to-finish-rollout-20161118-gssbag.html

You hear that grinding sound?

That's a nation's worth of teeth-gritted dental pain over how badly this government is screwing up our country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Female portion of Microsoft's workforce shrinks again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 03:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple launches repair program for iPhone 6 Plus touch disease flaw </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 03:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 03:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or creating a video of Julian Assange saying, "I am safe and sound, still in the Embassy, oh and the CIA and FBI are really great people."

The people who killed Assange already had this technology. You learning about it makes it less useful, not more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, as usual with this LNP government, he's just poisoning the well for the UN report on Australia's boat policies.

Pushing out a story blaming Fraser allows Australia's flaccid media contingent to waffle over something irrelevant instead of discussing real news.

Mr Crepeau called on Australia to stop intercepting and pushing back asylum-seeker boats, saying the practice does not meet human rights obligations.

He questioned the difference in treatment of asylum seekers who arrive by boat with those who come by plane, despite acknowledging the theory that it sends a message to people smugglers.

"In the human rights doctrine you cannot punish John in order to prevent Bill from doing something," he told reporters.

http://www.sbs.com.au/news/article/2016/11/18/boat-policies-tarnish-rights-record-un </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, real analysis shows that immigrants tend to go into "catch-up" mode when they arrive in Australia, and work hard to earn as quickly as possible to level their wealth with native born Australians.

That means they are effectively contributing the same amount in terms of job creation and infrastructure improvements as native-born Australians, but they're tending to do so over a shorter time span.

Australia also gains the benefit of their prior schooling and experience without having to pay while they're developing those skills.

While this study finds that immigrants accumulate less wealth than their Australian-born counterparts throughout the entire distribution, there is evidence of catch-up. Through greater time in Australia and accumulation of human capital, the disadvantaged wealth position of immigrants appears to recede. 

A further encouraging finding is that children of immigrants appear to experience no discrimination in relation to wealth accumulation. 

PDF warning: 

https://www.melbourneinstitute.com/downloads/hilda/Bibliography/Working_Discussion_Research_Papers/2005/Belkar_The_Wealth_Distributions_of_Migrant_and_Australian-Born_Households.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 01:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely.

They're determined to make Australian workers compete against unregulated work environments.

Mr Ciobo will not countenance a new US posture on trade, despite Mr Trump's campaign rhetoric about joining or retaliating against a "trade war" against China, Vietnam, India and others who export to the US.

"It's crucial for a trade minister, indeed for any government, to make the case for free trade and liberalised trade, to join the dots in a very clear way so that Australians get that as a consequences of trade agreements we undertake," he said.



"It's not about losing jobs or outsourcing work, it's actually about opening markets for Australian exports."


http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-11-18/australia-to-champion-free-trade-as-apec-talks-begin/8036214 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much the earth moved in the massive New Zealand quake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 01:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 09:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, for real. I used my compass to punch out enough chads to make a Fibonacci sequencer. 

After I submitted it via my teacher to a tech in UWA, I got a couple of sheets of fanfold a few weeks later, with the first 50 numbers and a note from the tech telling me to set an counter next time so the computer would know when to stop.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 08:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you think it's a bit deceptive to delete the post that initiated this conversation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 08:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't look here then...

np.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/5dcyp0/australia_ranked_among_worst_developed_countries/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 08:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Base load power: a myth used to defend the fossil fuel industry

According to Tim Buckley, from the Institute of Energy Economics and Financial Analysis, the idea of base load generation as an essential part of the energy mix is becoming redundant, and turning into a myth dreamed up by the fossil fuel industry to protect its interests.

Its as dangerous as the marketing term of clean coal and the idea that coal is good for humanity, Buckley says.


http://reneweconomy.com.au/base-load-power-a-myth-used-to-defend-the-fossil-fuel-industry-96007/

Baseload power is a myth: even intermittent renewables will work


Ben Elliston, Iain MacGill and I have performed thousands of computer simulations of 100% renewable electricity in the National Electricity Market (NEM), using actual hourly data on electricity demand, wind and solar power for 2010. Our latest research, available here and reported here, finds that generating systems comprising a mix of different commercially available renewable energy technologies, located on geographically dispersed sites, do not need base-load power stations to achieve the same reliability as fossil-fuelled systems.

https://theconversation.com/baseload-power-is-a-myth-even-intermittent-renewables-will-work-13210

Can renewables provide baseload power?

What The Science Says:

Numerous case studies on both regional and global scales have determined that renewable energy, if properly implemented, can provide baseload power.


http://www.skepticalscience.com/print.php?r=374 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 08:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solar and wind are cheaper here too.

The LCOE of new coal plants here is well above replacement wind or PV, and many of the existing coal operators are only hanging on to avoid having to pay remediation costs.


http://reneweconomy.com.au/australia-cheapest-in-asia-for-solar-wind-most-expensive-for-coal-91631/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wedge-tailed eagles do battle with mining giant's drones, knocking nine out of sky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 08:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 07:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australian unemployment jumps to 11%

This months unemployment has risen 1% to 11% - now at its highest since February 2015 and 5.2% higher than the current ABS figure for February 2016 (5.8%). This is the first time the Roy Morgan unemployment rate has increased in February for over a decade  since March 2005. Moreover, 2.433 million Australians (18.8% of the workforce) are either unemployed or under-employed.



http://www.roymorgan.com/findings/6739-roy-morgan-unemployment-estimate-march-2016-201604070750

http://www.roymorgan.com/morganpoll/unemployment/underemployment-estimates



Underemployment in Australia is 'widespread' and pushing down wages and inflation

While Australias unemployment rate is trending lower, the nations underemployment rate  which includes the unemployed and people in employment looking to work more hours  remains elevated, and its placing downward pressure on both wage growth and inflation.

http://www.businessinsider.com.au/anz-underemployment-in-australia-is-widespread-and-pushing-down-wages-and-inflation-2016-8

Australia's Lower Jobless Rate is Masking Record Underemployment

The strength of Australia's jobs market is being overstated by a surge in casual positions and an inability by workers to secure more hours.

http://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-08-31/if-you-think-australia-s-jobs-market-looks-healthy-look-again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 07:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I was wondering when /r/Australia's daily advertisement would show up.


Time to promote our dose of overpriced sugar product placement. 

SMM team, flock in and upvote like you actually like this nasty junk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 07:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only job creation happening here is for politicians leaning on the Australian Bureau of Statistics to "massage" employment data.

According to today's ABS data, Australia's official unemployment rate has held steady at 5.6 per cent - a fall of 0.4 per cent over the past year.

It's a result the Government has trumpeted as a ringing endorsement of the strength of the Australian economy. But scratch beneath the surface and you see how misleading the headline numbers are.

http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-11-17/dont-be-fooled-by-the-headlines-new-unemployment-numbers/8033366 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 06:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat, though I'd have cast Peta in that role for your Tony character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 06:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LCOE of wind is lower than coal now, and solar PV is only marginally higher.


Why do you thing so many power utilities in Australia are going into a death-spiral trying to stay profitable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 06:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you play the game with a Malcolm Turnbull mask on? That way you can get everything you want done without having to actually do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 06:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there an option to use a proxy that looks different, but does all the things you'd have done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Turnbull likes to pretend he's all matey with Trump, but don't forget he had to ask a golfer for Trump's phone number...

And of course Australia's ambassador, Joe Hockey, was clearly on the ball with his job representing Australia in the USA. Good to know he's still as capable as ever.

http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-11-17/greg-norman-helped-malcolm-turnbull-contact-donald-trump/8032690 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fortran on punchcards for me, suburban WA.

Oh, and get off my lawn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crushed ants in fizzy urine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernardi, Christiansen, O'Dwyer, etc, etc.


Looks like your barrel's all bottom and no bilge, mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 02:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's cunning as a sewer rat though. His comments are intended to preemptively poison the well for the Climate Action Network report released soon after.


Australia has been singled out again as a climate laggard, being ranked fifth-worst for emissions and policies among developed countries and among the six worst countries in the G20 when it comes to climate action.

In the climate change performance index, released overnight at the UN climate talks in Marrakech, Australia comes ahead of only Kazakhstan, South Korea, Japan and Saudi Arabia.


https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2016/nov/17/australia-ranked-among-worst-developed-countries-for-climate-change-action </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australia ranked among worst developed countries for climate change action </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 01:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Professor Stephen Hawking says humanity has less than 1000 years left until extinction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 09:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're worried about the privacy act, don't look here:

http://www.smh.com.au/business/your-mobile-phone-records-and-home-address-for-sale-20161116-gsqkwe.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your mobile phone records and home address for sale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the latest news from the Turnbull government front, they've decided to make it easier for employers to drive down 457 visa holders' pay.

Dr Howe said todays announcement would result in 457 visa holders having very little freedom of movement in the Australian labour market and increase the power employers could exert over foreign workers.

It effectively gives employers the dual role of both employer and immigration sponsor, she said.

By having two hats, which they dont have with a local worker, the employers power is increased to a point where they can exert pressure over a worker to get them to do whatever they want them to do.


http://www.theaustralian.com.au/national-affairs/immigration/turnbull-government-makes-changes-to-457-visas-for-skilled-foreign-workers/news-story/fe2805b1e20d32a078cdc403447f4021 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what's Turnbull's excuse?

Prime Minister Malcolm Turnbull has confirmed Australian Human Rights Commission president Gillian Triggs will be replaced with a new commissioner when her term expires next year.

http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/gillian-triggs-contract-with-the-human-rights-commission-wont-be-renewed-malcolm-turnbull-20161116-gsqtgy.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if they'll ban headphone wearing on footpaths and roads so people will be able to hear the electric cars?. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Murdoch knows what to do...

http://www.smh.com.au/sport/cricket/rod-marsh-quits-as-cricket-australias-chairman-of-selectors-20161116-gsqr6y.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 06:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you pay for private health insurance, you're doing the same thing, just less efficiently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 06:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gee, I wonder why?

THE International Monetary Fund has fired a broadside at Canberra, urging the Federal Government to accelerate spending on infrastructure while warning against trying to wipe the Budget deficit too quickly.

And it has taken aim at Australias rising household debt levels, claiming the nations tax system encourages households to gorge on debt to invest in property, in turn exacerbating the peaks and troughs of cycles in house prices.

http://www.geelongadvertiser.com.au/news/national/robust-economy-recovers-but-threats-still-exist/news-story/c140ece9b1f5db00131343cf936fa332 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 06:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is a trophy hunter.

Politics has become a rich man's sport, and the winner gets to put the head of the country on their wall for their friends to admire. They don't care what happens to the rest of the carcass.

The bearers will divide the meat amongst themselves and leave the rest of the spoils to the vultures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 06:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's Reddit and /r/Australia...


Nah, just kidding. You'll only discuss what the mods want you to discuss here. Mostly that means a lot of Bunnings, Nabisco and Cadbury adverts.

Post anything out of line and they'll ban you from submitting at all.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 06:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should read more of de Tocqueville's writing before quoting him in this context.

The first lines from the book you've referenced are:

Among  the novel objects which drew my attention during my stay in the United States, none struck me more than the equality of conditions.

Conservatives tend to ignore de Tocqueville's belief that economic and social equality were key to the success of the American experiment (in self-government), and wave the "effect" flag as though it explained away all dissent.

It doesn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 03:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other news...

Australian wages grow at the slowest pace on record. 

The sharp deceleration in wages growth will come as a disappointment to policymakers, placing further pressure on household budgets at a time when theyre expected to lift spending to help with Australias economic transition.

http://www.businessinsider.com.au/australian-wages-are-growing-at-the-slowest-pace-on-record-2016-11


This is terrible, how could this happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Chinese company that wrote the software says they also did it for "research and productivity".


Adups told the Times that the software was not meant for US phones. In June 2016, some Blu Product, Inc. devices applied a version of the ADUPS [firmware] application that inadvertently included the functionality of flagging junk texts and calls that had been requested by other ADUPS clients, the company said in a statement to The Verge. When Blu raised objections, ADUPS took immediate measures to disable that functionality on Blu phones. The company says the data was not provided to others and has been deleted.

Despite the company's statement, it's hard to know whether malicious surveillance  is intended or a byproduct in circumstances like this. 

And I'd have to agree with /u/skidmark-steve that I'd rather have a foreign uninterested government spying on my personal messages than my own government.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, he's installed the same lifers as any other republican president would have. 

He, Turnbull, and perhaps Palmer, are rich trophy hunters. They're after the head for their wall, and happy to leave the meat for their bearers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 09:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is the USA's equivalent to our own Malcolm Turnbull. Elected as a business success. Trumpeted as an agent of change, someone different. We've been down this road before.

He will be about as effective in government  as Turnbull has been. 


It was all a bait   switch.

To sum up, this is the prospect we are facing. A populist but semi-engaged President who is less interested in governing than in soaking up adulation at big rallies. (He might hold more of them even though the campaign is over, the Times story said.) Meanwhile, his cronies and members of the permanent establishment make many of the actual decisions, which will largely benefit the already rich, including the ruling family. Debt mushrooms as El Presidente approves prestige construction projects but not the taxes needed to pay for them. And skilled propagandists, like Bannon, whip up nationalist fervor to keep the masses diverted from what is really going on.

http://www.newyorker.com/news/john-cassidy/donald-trumps-great-bait-and-switch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 08:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that's viciously clever of Turnbull.

If their application fails or the agreement is reversed, they would be blocked from returning to Australia and would have to accept a 20-year Nauru visa, return to their country of origin or accept the Cambodian resettlement deal.

They have to choose to leave safety and go back into the hands of their rapists in the hope that they can finally have a home, but if Trump reneges they lose everything. 

Impressively brutal tactics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 07:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you please provide margin figures for those supermarkets, and explain why Tesco isn't suitable for comparison?

This chart suggests Tesco is fairly typical for UK based supermarkets, and shows that Coles and WW have margins more than double UK averages. 

http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-07-26/ubs-data-show-australian-supermarket-profit-margins/7661072
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 06:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep a bathtub full of them. It's soothing to bathe in as I cogitate on my Cayman Islands investments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 05:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VW may pay the highest price, but pretty much all car makers have been cheating.

http://www.roadandtrack.com/new-cars/car-technology/a29293/vehicle-emissions-testing-scandal-cheating/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thornes and other scary architecture could help **attract** the adventurous.

FTFY. The timid will be the ones who are scared away. It would be an excellent long-term project to breed unassertive Ukrainians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bad chemicals in rubber and plastic fume are mostly dioxin and furans, as well as carbon particulates.

All of these are reduced to carbon monoxide in the high-temperature blast furnaces, and the carbon in them is what turns the iron into steel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over here, having an Aldi open nearby turned the local Woolies and Coles into ghost towns for a while. They've since started to drop their prices to attract people back.

There's a long way to go though. They're still gouging customers as well as workers.

Profit margins in Australian supermarkets are double those at British retailer Tesco even though Coles and Woolworths have invested more than $1 billion into food and grocery prices over the last year.

http://www.afr.com/business/retail/australian-supermarket-margins-double-those-at-tesco-20161012-gs0fxe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 02:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't blame me. I voted for Kodos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 10:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so. Nabisco have always been strong on social media management. They're always promoting their brands on Facebook, Reddit etc, It's the cheapest place to get brand recognition.

See if you can find the actual advert online anywhere. 

But you're right about the "new Coke" trick, which coincidentally had its 35th birthday just last week... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 08:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just more advertising, and should be downvoted as such. 

Nabisco have been flogging their salty junk here for months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 08:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moderators in general are a pox in Reddit. Their role needs to be reviewed and fixed to reduce the abuses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 08:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good question, not sure why you're being downvoted.

I suspect the answer is that its a long way away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 08:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anybody been trying?

I think last time there was one in Pwn2own was 2103. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 04:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

To provide a counterpoint, this is what he's suggesting we shouldn't treat with disdain;

Culleton repeated his intention to represent himself, saying he did not need some lawyer to come in and start sucking off my left tit ... because it dehydrates you.

https://www.theguardian.com/australia-news/2016/nov/14/hanson-brushes-off-complaints-her-staffer-threw-phone-at-rod-culleton-aide


If disdain's out, how should we respond to people like Culleton? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 03:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, can do. Always happy to moon a Briswegian! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 02:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 666. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 01:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem here in Perth, clear and warm.

Come on over - I have cold beer and hot barbecue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 01:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's already started. Basically, the swap deal is already dead. 

All that's left now is for Australia's parliament and press to thrash around for months blamestorming and flogging the pony carcass.


http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/us-refugee-swap-the-kind-of-thing-trump-will-nix-on-day-one-says-washington-think-tank-20161113-gsoi51.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Powerful earthquake hits Christchurch NZ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 13:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 07:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Limitless? Can you begin to comprehend how much karma I can burn in a single day? 

I mock Microsoft and Apple in /r/technology. I criticise nuclear power in /r/worldnews. I've made socialist comments in /r/economics. I've seen attack ships on fire off the shoulder of Orion. I watched C-beams glitter in the dark near the Tannhuser Gate.

Time. Time to go.

Go and check it out. I'll do that, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 06:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much are they paying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 06:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We all know there is no "pro" in these pros

They're not likely to rename them "Macbook Con", no matter how much the Pro label is shown to be a con. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 05:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm one of _these_ people, not one of those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy a binfull of of your favorite shitty confectionery, use the foil to make a hat and throw away the tooth-rotting shit it was wrapped around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Income inequality is a worthless measure given how easily wealthy people hide income. Wealth inequality is also a far greater problem. 

To pretend otherwise is deceptive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 03:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only after I've eaten that Cadburys or Hershey's crap that tastes like sugary stale milk. 

Go and try some real chocolate, barbarian. I mean FFS, Darrell Lea, Haigh and Whittaker's are at least AU/NZ products if you want to be tribal and parochial about manufactured confectionery.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 03:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nein, ich bin ein Australisch.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 03:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Microsoft ARE paying the price for arrogance though.

If you look at device shipments in 2015, it shows that Windows was on less than 12% of them. 

Device Shipments, 2015

1. Android 54.16%
2. iOS/OS X 12.37%
3. Windows 11.79%
4. Other 21.66%





And in fact, actual usage of Windows 10 went backwards in September, so they'll be bleeding installed base as well:


It was expected, that once Windows 10 stopped being free, upgrades would slow significantly. That turned out not to be the case last month when NetMarketShares usage figures showed it, rather surprisingly, to be business as usual. Growth in August was no different from growth in previous months, although I speculated it might have been buoyed by sales of new back to school PCs.

In September though, according to NetMarketShare, Windows 10 didnt just show slower growth, it actually went into reverse gear and lost usage share. Yes, you read that right.

http://betanews.com/2016/10/01/wtf-windows-10-losing-share/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 02:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 02:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm not. I have a very serious face, drive a serious car to a serious job to do serious work, then go home to my serious house and my serious wife.


Seriously.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 02:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a bing? I Googled it, and it looks like a motorcycle carburetor. That can't be right.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Reddit IS getting pretty full... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Choose neither.

This is an advertising post placed by Cadburys marketing team. Both of these low quality confectionery products  are made by the same company. They don't care which you choose, but they want to you be discussing their product.


The specific technique they are using in this instance is intended to get you to look past the sale - eg, not about whether you really want a mediocre chocolate, but which mediocre chocolate you will buy.


The two questions you should really ask are:

1. Do you **really** want or need the snack, given that you're being manipulated into desiring it?


2. Why have shitty oversugared Cadbury chocolate when you can have much nicer treats for the same price?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please explain why wealth inequality is increasing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you please provide evidence to support that assertion?

Peer reviewed studies suggest the opposite:




Conclusion: The total annual direct cost of overweight and obesity in Australia in 2005 was $21 billion, substantially higher than previous estimates. There is financial incentive at both individual and societal levels for overweight and obese people to lose weight and/or reduce WC.

https://www.mja.com.au/journal/2010/192/5/cost-overweight-and-obesity-australia


Health problems related to excess weight impose substantial economic burdens on individuals, families and communities. Data from the Australian Diabetes, Obesity and Lifestyle (AusDiab) study indicate that the total direct cost for overweight and obesity in 2005 was $21 billion ($6.5 billion for overweight and $14.5 billion for obesity). The same study estimated indirect costs of $35.6 billion per year, resulting in an overall total annual cost of $56.6 billion (Colagiuri et al. 2010).

https://www.nhmrc.gov.au/health-topics/obesity-and-overweight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what you're saying is that we should restructure society to make poor people richer by diverting money from people who already have too much. Then more people would be paying tax, and services and infrastructure would get better for all of us.


Good thinking, but the LNP isn't likely to go for such a sensible plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 08:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm asking you for evidence to support your assertion. 

You've suggested average (not median, which is more indicative given increasing inequality) incomes have grown less than 10x. 

You've compared a midrange car with an economy car to support that claim. At the same time as the Cortina you've quoted, a Mini was about $1300, 120Y $2,000, base Escort or Gemini not much more.

You've attempted to conflate the cost of a single item with overall cost of living, but in 1975 fuel was 60 cents a gallon (13.2cpl). Bread was 24c a loaf. A median house in Sydney was $28,000. A newspaper was 12c. 25c would buy you a middy of beer.


People now have to work longer to live as well as they did in the '70s. It's almost impossible to have a single-earner family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Boycott Apple' -- 3 ways a Trump presidency could affect Apple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 05:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 05:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any evidence to support that assertion? 

More people are working longer hours to maintain their living standard, and now that unemployment is rising, projections show living standards falling for almost everyone below median income over the next decade.

Figure 1b shows, in real terms, both the level of and the growth of incomes between 2004 and 2014 and the projection to 2024. The gap between the income of the lowest income households is  substantial and growing through time. Of great concern is that the incomes of the lowest two quintiles are actually projected to fall over the next 10 years.

http://www.abc.net.au/cm/lb/6802166/data/natsem-report-into-living-standard-trends-data.pdf


In addition, the number of hours worked to maintain a median income has been increasing

It is interesting to note that in addition to working longer average hours, the last couple of decades have seen a marked increase in the proportion of persons working very long hours (49+ per week). In 1980 just 21 per cent of all full-timers (male and female) were working very long hours; by 2000 this proportion had risen to 33 per cent. For many white-collar workers, these additional hours are being worked as unpaid overtime.(8)

http://www.aph.gov.au/About_Parliament/Parliamentary_Departments/Parliamentary_Library/Publications_Archive/CIB/cib0001/01CIB04 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cox treated him with respect he didn't deserve. Hopefully Kruszelnicki has learned the lesson, and will be prepared to use mockery and contempt.

Personally, I doubt it though. I don't see Dr Karl as being ruthless enough to decimate Roberts in a debate. We need someone genuinely brutal to step up to the plate. 

I wonder if Andrew Denton's still around? Maybe Garry McDonald could bring back Norman Gunston for a special event... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 04:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not real. It was posted by Airtasker Australia's social media marketing team in an effort to start a viral discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 10:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely he was planning on using ammonium nitrate. There's substitutes, but they're more expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 09:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PDFtk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 07:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some cognitive dissonance here...

However, Apple posted a somewhat disappointing end to its fiscal year last month as iPhone unit sales slipped 5% year over year and revenue slid 13%. Apples Mac business was also down, and its iPad operation was stagnant.

Since the analyst involved counts total global sales numbers, but excludes profits from large Chinese companies that don't report profit figures, I'd take their conclusions with a grain of salt.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 07:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the LNP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 06:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prostitute, after what they're doing to their customers with wildly inconsistent dongle/port shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 06:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it works the same as Gimp, and always has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 06:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're better at randomly banning submitters than making the sub better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 06:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! You haven't used Photoshop either? It works the same in both.


Why are you commenting in a graphics software thread when you have no knowledge of the topic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 04:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what you're saying is that we should call them the:

* MacBook Con

* Windows 10 Con?

I'm ok with that. Make it so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 04:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You used a 4chan thread as a basis for your decision making? You're a very brave man...

And I doubt you actually used Gimp, or you'd have noticed the circle/ellipse tool right there up the top of the tool bar. It's been there since Gimp was first released.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 04:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing isn't a problem for me, it's the sound. I can tolerate commercial TV by muting the sound during ad breaks, but it wastes so much of my time to watch those channels.

Unless there's something really interesting on there, it's just not worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 04:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No true Scotsman fallacy...


Cleverly worded, you'll go far in the marketing department. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 04:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Gimp doesn't even have the very basics like a shape tool for circles.

Huh? Where'd you get that idea?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turn it on full, then light a match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was kind of kidding, but the NodeMCUs are genuinely exciting little gadgets.

I bought them as part of an ongoing project to convert as much of my house   garden to 12v as practical, automate where possible, and to transition to stored solar as advances/cost reductions make it worthwhile. So all lights are now LED, security and entertainment stuff all 12 or 5v, etc etc. Making it simple and friendly (eg via web page, tv screen, phone or tablet) takes lots of relays and electronic controllers. An example is having my driveway and carport lights automatically switch on when it's dark and my phone joins the wifi network as I get back from work or pub.

There's also some potential to use the experience to make salable products (I work in the field).

The benefits of the ESP8266 boards over Arduino are:

USB-TTL included, plug play

10 GPIO, every GPIO can be PWM, I2C, 1-wire

Built-in wifi, incl PCB antenna, gets 40-50m easily

Open source soft, firm and hardware

Easily flashable with scripting environments inc MicroPython, eLua, Basic, etc

FWIW, when I first got them, I flashed one with ESP8266 Basic, wired a 12v relay to an electronic door lock I had spare, scripted a web button to open it, powered up and had it working in less than 15 minutes. And I'm a clod who struggles with Bash scripts...

These little things really put the rapid back in RAD... When you get all that in such a tiny and cheap gadget, it's hard to resist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 02:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abbott was involved in sending and supporting fighters in Syria and other regions in the Middle East. 

If he wasn't eligible to be PM when he did it, doesn't that make him a terrorist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 02:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abbott's more of a cock than a gander, I'd say. 

Or perhaps a budgie would be more appropriate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 10:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but we already know he'd need both hands to find his own arse, so it's just a question of what he's more clueless about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 10:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Feel free to ask me about computers, networks and servers. 

I've just bought half a dozen $5 NodeMCU ESP8266 boards and need to decide which language to use on them. They come with Lua installed, which I'd need to learn. I'm more familiar with Python, but MicroPython doesn't look production ready yet. The ESP8266 Basic project looks useful and has good examples, but may have limits I'm not aware of yet.

What should I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 10:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He means Turnbull, not a theoretical real prime minister. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 10:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The good news is that peer reviews show that Cognitive Behaviour Therapy (CBT) is about as effective as pharmaceuticals, and has lower risks.

What that means though, is that it's not going to work all the time, every time. It's basically learning a new skill, and takes time, patience and practice, not something you want to hear when you're dealing with depression now.

But, like u/Azzanine has said, exercising the injury is really the only way forward, and that means you'll get to deal with the pain and the two-steps-forwards, one-step-backwards frustrations inherent with it.

But, it's worth knowing it **can** work. Just not always and not easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 05:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Porque no los dos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 03:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You think?](http://www.sbs.com.au/news/article/2016/11/07/climate-denier-senator-wants-csiro-inquiry).

How many people voted for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 01:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how I will survive with less than a 6.5 inch screen. 

Then don't. There's plenty of Android phones with 6" and above screens. 

The [Xiaomi Mi Max](http://www.gsmarena.com/xiaomi_mi_max-8057.php) is my personal favourite, but Google will find you pleanty more.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 08:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally the worst? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 08:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, getting rid of them is a simple, sensible decision.

Sounds like we need a plebiscite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 08:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do this often already to correct voiceovers for training and corporate presentations, and to deal with organisation name changes. It's not particularly difficult to do manually, but it's time-consuming.

Having a tool to do it won't change the world. It'll just make life easier for those of us who do it for a living. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 08:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That may well be, though it's not the real reason MS is losing browser share.

If you look at device shipments in 2015, it shows that Windows was on less than 12% of them. It's fair to assume that most of the other 88% of devices  can have Chrome or Firefox installed on them, while IE and Edge can only exist on Windows.

Device Shipments, 2015

Android	54.16%

iOS/OS X	12.37%

Windows	11.79%

Other	21.66%

TLDR:

MS browsers only survive on installed base. New shipments overwhelmingly favour other OSs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 03:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been beaming a subliminal ultrasonic message into your brain making you come looking for a comment like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 02:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the Malaysians. 

MH370's black box has woken up again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Butterflies, how else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a Redmi at the same time that looked and worked far better than the 625. 

Windows phones only made sense if you didn't look outside the carrier-locked system. If you were prepared to buy your phone outright, you had a world of better choices.

That's why they never got any momentum in most of Asia, despite being (subsidised) cheaper in their home markets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 09:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russian government spends around $300 million per year on software. 

ReacOS had about $150,000 in the bank and about $3,000 in donations [in 2014](http://ev.reactos.org/files/GA2014.pdf). Their expenses were about $6,000, so they went backwards.

I suspect it redirecting a tiny proportion of Russia's Microsoft license fees towards ReactOS would provide immediate benefits in terms of functionality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 09:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Googled that. Surprisingly informative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 07:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a list of AOSP 7.0 ROMs in active use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 07:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interestingly enough, the closest competitor to Google's Android is AOSP, with about 25% of the total phone market in 2013. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 06:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  AOSP a less complete OS

Is been a while since Android 7.0 Nougat has been out. If you have a Nexus device which is currently supported, you already have your taste of the latest Android in most cases. But if you are a non-Nexus user, you would be lucky if your OEM even promised you an update, let alone deliver it so soon already.

This is where the developer community comes in  groups of talented individuals working together to achieve the common cause of getting the latest Android onto devices before the OEM can, and in many cases, because the OEM cant.

With the large amount of unofficial builds of Android 7.0 Nougat and CyanogenMod 14 builds rolling in, it was a good idea to to create a big list of devices that have already tasted the dessert success.



http://www.xda-developers.com/the-big-list-of-android-7-0-nougat-on-popular-phones/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 06:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you should ask a woman to explain... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 06:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AOSP is the official Android open source repository. The official website is at Android Open Source Project . If you go and have a look at the URL: Codenames, Tags, and Build Numbers you will find all the builds from Google.(Build here means the android OS files with some supporting files) . Ex: google developed Marshmallow and the complete code is available for downloading as it is open source.

What companies like Samsung, HTC or CM (in this case) do? They download this source code and modify it in the way they want. They will add some extra features on top of the original os and flash it on the devices like HTC, Samsung etc. CM is one such customized ROM.

https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-the-AOSP-and-CyanogenMod-ROMs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
