<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else want to help me build my boat, ok? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 00:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 20:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucked up Algae: Check.

Let's keep doing it until Godzilla emerges from the depths of the Florida waters and starts running amuck on the population.

Then maybe the regulators will learn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apparently Daniels is married, ok? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 20:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walmart employee adjusting his pants / jerking off. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 18:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 08:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moustache and tight white t-shirt.

Sex offender attire to the T.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you love historical war and stuff like that, can't recommend Lindybeige's youtube channel enough. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 22:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 22:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You only wish you could work as hard as I do".

- quoted from a *goober* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 22:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Steam prices are always better. No argument there.

But for console players who want to pick up DS3 for a more affordable price in Canada, this is a fantastic deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Darksouls 3 is $49.99 at Bestbuy.ca. (Regular $79.99) Ends July 28th, 2016. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 20:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PS4 : 

http://www.bestbuy.ca/en-CA/product/dark-souls-iii-ps4/10380437.aspx


Xbox One:

http://www.bestbuy.ca/en-CA/product/dark-souls-iii-xbox-one/10380486.aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Innocent cameraman ridiculed by goobers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 20:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 19:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well played, sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 18:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What professions go well with Pokemon Go? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 20:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bicycle Cop.
Hooker.
Ice Cream truck operator.
Dog Walker.

What else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 15:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure CR was designed as a short term cash grab. The mechanics and psychology they use behind getting players to spend real money will eventually burn out the player base. 

Part of me hopes that Supercell has this backfire on them and their entire line up of games see a huge profit decline to teach them a lesson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 15:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I'm out driving and I see a cop it usually crosses my mind about seeing how long I could evade the cops on a high speed chase. 

I would hit the highway and weave in between slower cars. My music would be blaring and I would be calm like Ryan Gosling in Drive. 

Then you remember how shitty jail would be and come to your senses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 05:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pokemon Go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 23:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real scammers already got you. 

Bell Mobile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reporter doesn't want to be touched by a Mark or Mike, who keeps touching him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 15:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 15:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comic Sans, bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 05:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 05:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck would someone go out of their way to harm wildlife?

Why can't people stop being pointlessly cruel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 19:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leo Laporte's repertoire is a long one:

Showed dickpic on show.

Showed wife's vagina pic on show.

Never mind, it's a short one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 14:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if my nearby was broken, because every single Pokemon shows 3 footprints all the time. 

According to this it's broken. 

Is it just broken for Canadians or are Americans experiencing this as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 00:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damn thats a hot gif.

I miss attack of the show.

Sara Jean Underwood and Candace Bailey are so sexy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to this article:

http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2011/08/appeals-court-says-only-complicated-math-is-patentable/

Complicated math can be patentable. Could the superforumla be considered complicated math? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title and video made me think of this:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Iu90z9Akxgk

"Supa hot fire, I spit dat" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I shouldn't have said that about Beethoven".

*People he's interviewing can't even look at him anymore.*

"What about Zimbabwe?"

"The ruins, they are beautiful."

"Thank you."

*Cuts to commercial*


"CAN SOMEONE FIX THE FUCKING TELEPROMPTER, I CAN'T HANDLE THIS SHIT ANYMORE." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 08:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm playing Pokemon GO, or notice others playing it, I usually leave them alone.

They may smile at me and say hi, I'll say it back, but more or less I don't see it as an ice breaker or an in to talk to people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 06:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL The I'm sweating at the end exhumes desperation and picturing the shitty ride home feeling all that glitter stick to your sweaty arms and legs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 06:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coorral.......glitter Corrral. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 06:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not selling out. It's providing a lot of Pokemon, Zelda, and Metroid fans a way to play their favourite games on their mobile phones.

A huge chunk of the western world has a smart phone now. Imagine if Nintendo released the older beloved titles of Pokemon, Zelda, and Metroid to those fans? They would make many people happy, and earn huge amounts of profit.

Too many people view this as a console war, unfortunately most adults who work, and have the disposable income to spend on these don't see it as a console war, but as a convenience mentality. If I don't feel like carrying a nintendo hand held with me, I'm not going to buy one, nor buy the games that come with it. Now if Nintendo released these older titles for iOS and Android, I would in a heart beat pay $10 to $30 for each title, since I can install them neatly into my mobile phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 06:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read this link, it answers your questions near the bottom.

https://www.reddit.com/r/pokemongo/comments/4snrnu/lv22_player_giving_small_tips_of_advice_also/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think Nintendo will eventually launch Pokemon [colour], Zelda, and Metroid games for iOS and Android because of these market caps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went into my local grocery store. Caught a nidoran in the produce section, a pigdy in the cereal aisle, and a squirtle in the feminine hygiene aisle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 01:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a Canadian, and I just got the game. I know for a fact I'm going to be kicked out by a businesses security, and/or hit by a car on my way to the grocery store one day.

At least I walked instead of drove. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 07:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get he's a chauvinist, but this idiot woman isn't doing the women's side any favours with her delusional ranting and raving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 07:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always remember this one because not the woman, but the man she married.

He seems so mentally and emotionally adjusted, yet he's married to an imbecile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 07:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing about Chomsky that I adore is his writing style. It's so intelligent yet easily digestible. It saddens me that he's old, and may kick the bucket soon and I don't think anyone will ever fill his shoes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 07:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when Hockey and Baseball cards were a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 07:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I normally don't care about celebrities dying, but when Bill Murray dies, I may actually be really sad.

He seems like a really great guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 06:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The price for traveling there, did you pay the iron price or gold? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 06:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does Graphene replace lithium entirely? Or does lithium still have an advantage in other areas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 06:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude......I didn't know a video or concept like that existed. Now I do.... :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 04:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a "special" charmander if I've ever saw one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 11:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like The Rock Nicholas Cage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING] Was Tywin afraid of anyone? Everyone feared and respected him, but was that always so? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 03:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 01:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been recommending it to my cousin, but he never gets around to watching it. He rather watch shows like The 100 etc.

He does like Suits though. 

It makes me wonder if he ever gets into it, will he say, "I can't believe I didn't watch Game of Thrones before"

Me personally, I've never ever ever watched a show in terms of keeping up with new episodes. Game of Thrones is the only show I've ever kept current on. Even Breaking Bad I watched through netflix, and only one season of Better Call Saul, the second season I haven't even touched.

It's just something about Game of Thrones that makes me irritable if I miss it. It's like a drug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 01:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats my main hatred and love for this show. It kills people off......but when it kills someone off like Oberyn, I FUCKING hate it.....and love it.

I don't know what I love and hate anymore thanks to this show. I do miss Oberyn though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING] The Baratheon family tree is really depressing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 01:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://gameofthrones.wikia.com/wiki/Robert_Baratheon#Family_tree

Everyone's dead, Robert is tied to Various women AND Cersei. He has a dead baby named Barra in his tree too, killed by that prick, Janos Slynt.

Only the Lannisters and Gendry are left alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 01:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Hollywood movies, it's usually the reporter who calls the shots, and bosses the cameraman around.

I guess it's not true in real news reporting. Sounds like news reporters are treated like shit.


*Starts report*

"You're done, you're done. Step out please, step out." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 00:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew this was going to be another Reckful video.

I don't know if this is just an act for his streams or not, but he's turned into a serious clown.

Gone are the days of Reckful Rogue PvP WoW days when he was quiet and to the point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING] Listening to Aemon Targaryan during the nights watch scenes shows how wise and "good" he was, but it made me wonder... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 00:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an HBO show watcher, was it actually wise and good for him not to become king? Why would someone who was clearly wise and good as he comes off as, give up the throne to another Targaryan?

Wouldn't he had made an excellent leader? Even to the point, of resonating through his kin to become better leaders after him? Maybe even avoiding the "mad king" phase that caused the downfall of the Targaryans?

My point being, wouldn't the world had been better off with Aemon Targaryan as the king at one point in the GOT history? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 00:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never noticed him before, pleading with Joeffrey to spare Ned.

I wonder why? Was it concern for Ned because he was an honourable man? Varys telling Tyrion that he had a quality and compassion for diplomacy during one of the episodes in season 4 or 5 expresses that Varys respects "good" leaders, including honourable ones.

The question is, doesn't Dranarys have a sense of honour much like Ned did? She is even more compassionate than he was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 00:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It must be such an experience to be an mainstream actor on this show.

The places they go to seem so exotic and amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 00:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canadians have area codes as well but I rarely hear anyone reference that as their location. Must be an American thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 00:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best fights are when you get ALL 3 factions fighting hard for a single base.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 00:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lord of light works in mysterious ways.

Or is it lord of fire? I can't remember. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 00:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's probably one of those clutch fighters, where he can overcome great odds against him to pull through and save the ones he cares about and fights for, instead of someone with incredible prowess like Dayne etc.

I was really hoping he would have had magical powers during the battle of the bastards, but alas he's "normal". I still don't understand what the point of the "Prince that was promised", if he can't do some funky magic shit. But then again, people rally behind him and respect him. They put their lives on the line for him because they know he would do the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING] Is it possible Draenarys will follow in her fathers footsteps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 23:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At times she becomes full of emotion and clearly isn't making the best judgement on issues at hand. You can tell one of her weaknesses is this explosiveness.

Was her father always a mad king? Or at one time he was a great leader? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 23:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jon Snow looks a little like Prince in this rendition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 23:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually. I'm the guy inside the printer who makes the "rrrrrrtRRrrrrnnnnnnnnnrrrrRrrrrNnnn" sound as it prints. I also drain the ink cartridge twice as fast, by magically making the ink disappear when you're not using it for long periods. 

They put about 2 or 3 of us in every printer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 08:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It almost looks like he goes for his crotch momentarily.

Really awkward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 08:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has some nice melons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 08:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "For this mornings trick, I'm going to jam this nail in someones hand........ "

5 minutes later...

*ta da* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 03:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing with Penn and Teller though, they give off this feeling that everything is going to be ok.

If it had been one of them holding this poor hosts hand over the nail, I know the trick is going to go off without a hitch. It's just something about them and their act that just expresses competency and care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 06:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to know what he says right after he turns to her to remove the nail from her hand, then turns to the camera and says something.

Sounds like "shua sha" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 02:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Settle down, alright? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 04:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. Funniest thing I've read today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 22:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious!

I bought my PS4 for Bloodborne too when it came out.

I played DS1 on my Xbox 360, so I had a bit of emotional and mental preparation for the anal pounding these games do to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 20:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember this.

This is a perfect example of why console companies can learn from software/game developers.

They need to work together to provide us with great games and great features. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 16:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This never gets old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 05:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ocarina of Time was the game changer, not Mario 64.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 05:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RNG is both a curse and blessing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 04:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good eye. The similarities are striking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 03:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can do whatever he wants as long as he gives Burrows another year.

Burrows belongs on the Canucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 03:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is awesome!

Is this part of the new Minecraft Realms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 00:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't fans just go and watch their teams play soccer without beating each other up.

These matches are meant to be fun and entertaining. Sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING] If Renly survived... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 07:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 03:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing how he maintains control on such rough terrain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 02:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Settle down, alright.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 12:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a movie hit job if I ever saw one.

http://www.relatably.com/q/img/karl-quotes-from-sling-blade/5f15076cba5b56f604b64d4f893a863a.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING] Is Ramsay as much of a jerk in the book as he is in the show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 02:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the show he's probably one of the top guys you can't wait to see die. In the book is he the same way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 02:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similar look the bear gave Leonardo DiCaprio in The Revenant before mauling him.

Goodfellas quote:

If you're part of a crew, nobody ever tells you that they're going to kill you. It doesn't happen that way. There weren't any arguments or curses like in the movies. **So your murderers come with smiles.** They come as your friends, the people who have cared for you all of your life, and they always seem to come at a time when you're at your weakest and most in need of their help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 02:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really a smile I would be happy to see in person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 02:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing I never understood about pedophiles is how they prefer prepubescent bodies compared to:

https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CAdCnpFU8AAvpAQ.jpg

https://pbs.twimg.com/media/BhJZOEyIQAAkfoG.jpg

http://media1.santabanta.com/full1/global%20celebrities(f)/sarah%20jean%20underwood/sarah-jean-underwood-0a.jpg

It really must be a deeply ingrained mental disease, because this guy was semi wealthy and could afford some top class escorts if he wanted. 

His life and the lives of the children he victimized are ruined because of whatever the fuck causes him to prefer children over beautiful women 20+ years old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 00:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy Shit!

This was perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 00:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CwsFNOHGABA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 00:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume people with social anxiety don't really want to interact with interviewers like this guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 01:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a piece of trash.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 08:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. I read about these guys who troll streamers with these chargebacks.

It's one thing to troll people for fun where no permanent damage is caused, but when you mess with people on a monetary level, it's going too far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING] From everything you've watched and read about GOT, Who would make the best king? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 08:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently made a post about Ned being king instead of Robert, and how that would have affected the realm. It seems like Ned would have been a better option, but not ultimately the "best" king.

Some mentioned John Arryn would have been a better king than Ned.

My question is, from the period of the Mad King being dethroned and killed, all the way till the period of the latest HBO Game of Thrones episode [Episode 7 Season 6], who would make the best King?

All characters are fair game.

Maybe also define what kind of qualities a king in the GOT universe would need to survive and rule successfully.

Personally, I don't know enough about the books to have input, I was always partial to Ned, and now I'm partial to Jon Snow. Jon Snow seems lately to get discouraged too easily, but he stands up for what he believes in (even dies for what he believes in), and values peoples lives.

I flip back and forth with Daenerys, she lacks that subtleness that John Snow has, where he seems to inspire peoples loyalty from his actions and demeanour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EP7S6][Spoilers] Ian McShane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 07:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the show, but how in the hell do you bring Ian McShane in, and kill him off in the same episode.

When I saw him and dog conversing, I was ecstatic. Then you ripped that away from me.

Why?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 04:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't play gta online anymore, the sticky bomb was a great tool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MAIN SPOILERS] Had Ned sat on the throne instead, would Kings Landing been like Winterfell in season one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 07:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been re watching season one with my mom. 

I got her hooked on the show in season 3, and therefore she only watched new episodes. 

Decided to show her season one onwards while we have it on demand (streaming for free with the HBO subscription). 

She's been dreading the imminent death of Ned, and keeps saying, "why would anyone kill Ned?" 

It got me thinking. If instead of Robert Baratheon sitting on the iron throne, what if Ned did?

Would the situation in Kings Landing be better? Would it have been in debt? Would there have been as much backstabbing and scheming?  

Winterfell in season one seems so peaceful and prosperous. Would Ned have made Kings Landing the same way?

In The Republic by Plato, he states that the best rulers are the ones who do not want to rule, but rule because they are the best suited. Ned didn't sit on the iron throne, even though he could have. He also didn't want to be the hand of the king. 

During the series they mention potential replacements for Robert, but each one has a fault. Does Ned have any faults as a king? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PS4][NA][PVE] New player looking for active guild. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 06:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently level 13, but steadily making my way towards 50.

Thanks in advance for your consideration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 00:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like the bug.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 21:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Mini nuke beep is a cause for pause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Vancouver, Canada] A couple of days ago had a hundred or so of these swarming our patio. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 21:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the PS4 ESO go on sale very often? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 22:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking of picking this up for PS4, and I'm wondering if this game goes on sale very often?

Or if there is an impending sale where ESO PS4 would likely go on sale.

Thanks in advance for any input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the M60A1 still coming? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 18:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't heard much about it since devs mused about it last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heaviest parts of modern tanks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 18:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ballpark percentage for these three facets of modern tanks:

Turret %

Hull %

Components/Equipment/Engine/Ammunition/Crew %

What would each one comprise of weight within the tank? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 17:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First he should have tried not being sick.

If that didn't work, then he should have tried not being poor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 17:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well done!

Hopefully you can send it out to find the reason why HL3 just up and disappeared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time Home seller. BC Canada. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 17:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

Dealing with selling a home in Vancouver, BC Canada. 

The home has been owned for over 8 years. It's also about 10 years old.

I have two questions:

We have a pending offer. According to the offer, after subjects are removed, and all the proper documents are signed, there will be a deposit held in escrow until the deal is completed and closed in September.

The proper documents are done by the lawyer in June, and the entire sum of money will be transferred in September.

Lets say, the couple buying the house doesn't have the money by September. Do we get to keep the deposit? How much of the deposit does the real estate agent keep?

The second question is according to the dual agency agreement:

The seller pays various fees. The two I have a question about are the:

Realestate Commission Commission (plus GST)

Goods and Services Tax (If applicable)

What are the difference between the GST on the Realestate Commission and the Goods and Services tax? 

Also, why are there brackets around If Applicable beside Goods and Services Tax? When is this not applicable?

Thanks in advance for any input. I really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 15:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 04:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sling blade and fallout 4. Match made in heaven.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 14:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just noticed it, thanks for pointing that out. 

Is that a huge problem with services like redbox and game fly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 12:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His looks are not his strong suit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 12:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look on the cats face is priceless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 12:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should killing minorities and people of colour in a multiplayer death match video game be considered a hate crime?

Al Sharpton may think so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 12:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a clown. 

If the guy doesn't dish out beta keys, then he doesn't dish out beta keys. What's so hard to grasp about that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 12:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone enlighten a non redbox user what this post is about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 21:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome!

I wonder if the M1 Abrams has the same composition? It seems to be missing from the cross sections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 20:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 20:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hockey is supposed to be fun. Watching it, playing it, and talking about it. Sure team loyalties and passions can get out of hand, but at the end of the day, it's still supposed to be about fun. 

When people get out of hand about sports related debates, it's time to take a break.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 20:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the best DLC's ever released of any game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 20:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a picture of an M60 with a square hole cut out of the front of the hull. Blows my mind every time I see these tank cross sections. 

Would be interesting to see what modern tank cross sections look like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 18:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theon lost his cock. 

It's pretty hard to bounce back from that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 18:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My biggest problem is that Kyle was a compulsive liar, yet people worship the guy as a hero.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 18:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people eat rabbits. Never heard of people eating horse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 06:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://24.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m60r2zuAnw1qko9h3o7_250.gif

I wonder if she enjoyed kissing Viggo or Ben Affleck?

Viggo is more brooding, mysterious. Ben Affleck is ....Ben Affleck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 06:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow this is brutal.

Following her around and groping her when she clearly doesn't want any of it. Idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 06:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "So you're saying that Area 51 is housing Aliens? And these Aliens want to impregnate our human female women? And then these Alien babies will become Walmart CEO's? Walmart will then avoid at all costs to pay a livable wage? Thats what you're saying? That Alien offspring Walmart CEO's are out to get the 99%?"

*Schiff* - ".... What?"

"So you want to go back to slavery? You want to build a time machine, and utilize the butterfly effect to assassinate Lincoln, in an attempt to permeate slavery into modern times? Is that what you're saying? That you're going to manufacture a T-800 from the Terminator movie to fuck with us 99%?"

*Schiff* - "..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 08:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It almost looks like the driver was waving them away. 

Surprised no one was seriously injured from this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not gay. 

*Let's leave it at that* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
