<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6186</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 20:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you have a very inflated opinion of the first Fast   Furious movie...  I don't consider the first movie anywhere NEAR the quality of a Star Wars.  It's good, but it ain't THAT good.  Shiiiit, it was a remake of Point Blank for fuck's sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 20:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sequels go stupid in all the RIGHT ways.  Seriously, it's one of the most entertaining franchises to grace film, and I think they've really settled into the schlock with the last three films.

For fucks sake, The Rock FLEXES out of a cast?  How can you not love that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 20:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the Statham scene at the beginning of Furious 7.  It's so ridiculous and insane:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cSwN4P3tBO4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 19:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BOTH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 18:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, he's wearing dark clothing.  All he needs now is an emo haircut! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 17:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesssss...  I love the idea of it too.  This is supposed to be the time line Okabe doesn't go back at the end right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 17:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there going to be a new show released alongside it? I keep hearing back and forth on it...

Steins;Gate is one of the best time travel stories ever told.  I know for sure Life is Strange snagged a bunch of ideas from it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 15:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 22:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stannis burning his daughter is actually very out of character.  The last we see him in the books, he states that A. That there will be no more burnings.  and B. That he will put Shireen on the Iron Throne.  Don't even get me started on the 20 men thing...  Ugh...

And Sansa...  She has been through her 'little girl' arc already.  It was time for her to start bucking up and making some decisions for herself- Oh, no we have to have her get raped and rescued.  Ok.  Despite being a chilling and disturbing scene, Sansa being the recipient of the abuse just completely derails her character.  I'm glad she's being more headstrong now, but what they did to her character before was terrible.

How is Selmy getting killed a bad decision?  Really?  First off, both the actor and the editor of the books HATED that, seeing as how there were important parts where he is involved.  Plus, having him killed by a bunch of rich snobs with little to no combat experience, when he is the best fighter in the land?  THAT SHIT MAKES NO SENSE.  

Yara's story and the Kingsmoot were some of my fan favorites from the book, and having them stripped from the overall context of the story annoyed the hell out of me.  And I can just feel that Euron is going to build a whole fleet of ships in a matter of a couple of episodes, when this story could have been placed in season 5 and Euron have his ships ready NOW.  

The Faith Militant should not have power at all.  The moment the kidnapped The Queen and the Queen's wife, they should have all been killed.  The idea that it's still going is completely stupid and inconceivable.  If some 99% 'Will of the People' group kidnapped Obama's Mother and Wife today, you'd bet your ass they wouldn't be living tomorrow.  I don't care how riotous the citizens are, the Lannisters (Kevan especially) would NEVER allow that to happen.  The only reason it happens in the books is because Kevan hates Cersei, and thinks that the Faith's grip on her will do her some good.  Tommen is a child so he doesn't care.  It's supposed to be a big changing moment for Cersei, where she gains a bit of humility...  But in the show she's still as cold as she ever was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 22:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, but I seriously thought Season 5 was bad television.  Stannis making stupid decisions, the butchering of Sansa's character, Sand Snakes, the Faith Militant having ANY power at all and that making NO SENSE, cutting out Bran and Yara completely from the season, Selmy being killed...  There were a series of baffling and stupid storytelling decisions made during that season that poisoned the entirety of it.  If not for Dany's Dragon scene, Hardhome, and good Arya stuff, I may have dropped the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 21:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 5 was REAAAAAAALLLY bad.  Thankfully Hardhome turned it around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 21:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Then he looks at the camera like I said he couldn't do it..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This trailer for Bucktown (1975) is one of the most badass trailers I've ever seen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 21:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 20:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't there actually evidence of rigging in at least New York?  I have friends in NYC who are still pissed they couldn't go vote because of how big a cluster fuck it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 20:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Utopia.

Fuck whoever thought canceling that was a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 19:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Context?  Hit some birds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 17:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should play this before every movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 17:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes it's like watching people being tortured though.  The Gopher shooting episode is a good example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 17:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't Portal take place hundreds of years after Half-life though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 16:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I think would work.  James Bond, at his core, is a MALE character.

People should watch Haywire for what a female Bond might look like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 03:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna be a part of clan hotboy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 22:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Soviets had a Cannibalism Squad of their police force during the Siege of Leningrad.

I've always thought it would make an excellent horror game/movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 19:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Editor needs to reupload.  They have a double audio thing going.

Also, I love how relieved he looks after he starts fighting.  It looks like such a release to beat on those dudes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 16:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a cynical book reader, let's be clear that this isn't CONFIRMED as the reasoning for Hodor's name.  This is just the show's interpretation.  The book could be very different, like most of the plot lines going into this season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 07:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like a mix of Eddie Izzard and Brendan Fraser. (The Good Years) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 09:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only that, but they're using the great character development device of splitting up and pairing characters up who normally wouldn't be together.  I love that trope, honestly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 22:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People also commonly bring up her combat and piloting skills.

For one thing, she has been on her own since she was like 5 fighting thugs and scavenging ships.  We even see her using her staff to fight off a group of muggers.  She knows how to fight...  And if she is going to be a ship scavenger, she has to know a lot about ships to sell those parts to the junk guy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 21:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They better have really attentive staff...  Those things build up sweat and possibly mucus, so they need people who are willing to wipe down the fluids left over from a previous viewing.

I don't know how many people are willing to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 21:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking of Looper, I listened to a podcast where Kevin Smith and the director or Looper were comparing and contrasting their Bruce Willis experiences.

Looper guy said he was a dream to work with...  So maybe it depends on the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 20:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, looking at his other videos I'm seeing titles like, "WHY LIBERALS HATE FREEDOM," "THE WAR ON MEN," and "THEY CAN'T STOP TRUMP."

Soooo, is he really a philosopher?  I feel like a REAL philosopher would know better than to take political stances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]Those who have won a free vacation from a game show, how was the trip? Did the game show skimp out on anything? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 20:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 17:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT Big Men who would actually scream like little bitches in the same situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 00:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hate Mob" = Disagreeing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 00:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... about stupid movies and inconsequential bullshit.  I guess you really should remind him of the darkest time in his life for that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 00:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cringed though all of what you just wrote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 22:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a professional comedian, bro.  At some point, he's gotta get back to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 22:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this one bombs, they need to give this franchise to Neveldine and Taylor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 22:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, I'm actually only interested in this game for a possible Game of Thrones/Song of Ice and Fire themed mod?

You have undead warriors, dragons, giants, etc...  Plenty to work with in making the GoT assets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 21:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shit people said about his wife in the replies to that tweet were just sick...  What the fuck man... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 21:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES, this is awesome.  I'll use all of these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 21:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, that obvious?

But yeah, I really liked that element of on the fly storytelling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 20:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, you have to Fast Travel to get back?  Egh, I figured, but thanks for confirming.

Though it would suck to pay 1000 crowns over and over to get between lands... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 20:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno man, I was having a great time seeing large castles on islands in the distance, sailing there, finding a place to dock, trying to get around the steep drops, and making my way up the side of the mountain.  I've also stumbled upon some crazy drops (For my level 15 character at least) by just wandering around.  The most recent one I found did like +600 Vitality, plus a high armor rating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 20:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, I never fast travel.  I like to explore new areas and make my way by horse.  One instance where I was completely immersed was having to ride around Velen, doing different Monster Hunts to pay my way to Skellige. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 19:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those work, but I was thinking of like cover identities...  Like a band on tour, or a transport carrying exotic creatures, stuff like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for burner identities for my Smuggler Crew to use in game... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 18:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'll be giving my players a ship soon, given to them by the rebels.  On the ship, it'll have a number of burner identity tags they can scan through Imperial territory.  I was thinking of writing these all down and putting them in a hat for them to draw in game, and be forced to assume those identities when trying to stay clear of the empire.

I'll take every suggestion posted in this thread.  Make them as wacky, over-the-top or lore friendly as you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 18:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much how I pictured her.  [Lost Stars Spoiler](/s "I'd like her in a Officer's uniform as well, nose diving a ISD into Jakku...")

I wonder what Thane Kyrell looks like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 17:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started playing the Witcher 3, and I'm blown away how the game can create diverse, yet familiar fantasy locales.  B W looks no different.  I just found my way to Skellige, and it's like I'm playing a different game.  Instead of riding from place to place, I'm sailing...

This game is a wonderful achievement.  And it's also the one year anniversary of it being released today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 15:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if you consider character development silly, then sure.  Darth Maul is better in Clone Wars/Rebels to me than he was in the film.  He's just a voiceless baddie for the good guys to fight.  In the show he's a rage fueled monster, who actually gets some sympathy due to his affection for his brother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 08:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rollin' deep in that Snickers money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 04:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But in these modern times where manned space travel seems furthest from our collective minds, would it even matter?  No one is getting killed or displaced by an invasion of the moon.  There's nothing to lose, except maybe mining minerals...  If anything, we could just form a colony on another part of the moon, and start breaking the moon up into little territories.  Something like Antarctica.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If another country flew to the moon, knocked down the U.S. flag, and planted their own as an unorthodox attempt to take over U.S. territory, would/could they even stop them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 04:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 18:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone should make a mod where Doomguy screams out those fucking bonkers quotes he says from the comic everytime he does a glory kill.

I'M COOKING WITH GAS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 16:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly though, wouldn't placing Battlefront near the release of Rogue One make more sense?  Rogue One is set during the Galactic Civil War...  There's nothing really connecting Battlefront to TFA save for Jakku. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Know absolutely NOTHING about bikes... Looking to get a bike for commuting to work within Atlanta. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 15:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

So, I currently live in Buckhead, and I commute to work most days.  It's 2.5 miles to get there, so I usually just walk to work.  Though I'll probably be moving to Midtown at some point this year, and I'd like to keep up with the physical activity.  It seems like a bike would be best to do that.

I'm looking for a bike that's not too professional, something simple...  It seems like Fixed Gear bikes are what appeal to me those most right now.  I like the look of the Pure Fix bikes, but I also hear a lot of trash being talked about them.  I'd like to sift through the white noise and get a genuine bike recommendation if possible.

Thanks, I appreciate any feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars vs. Star Trek </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 18:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you want out of a hypothetical Star Wars: Galaxies 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 18:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ran my first game this weekend! Our group assassinated Jar Jar Binks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 22:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'm still learning, but I got a group of five together to play this past weekend.  My story revolved around a military blockade that was hovering over Coruscant due to a bombing at the Imperial Palace.  My players were contracted by the Empire to investigate the bombing, seeing as how the Empire was stretched across the galaxy looking for Rebels post-Death Star I destruction. 

Part of the story involved my miscreants, who were pushed to the fringe by how restricted everything is in Coruscant, going to an Imperial Ball.  The ball was celebrating the new graduates of the Imperial Academy, much like a scene in Lost Stars.  They were outfitted with uniforms, and had to somehow blend in despite being all weird aliens and a droid.

I wanted to have each player run a charm check, and that determined who they danced with.  One player rolled good, so he danced with Mara Jade.  After they stopped dancing, they went about to the food.  I had hoped that a player would roll bad in an attempt to dance, so that they could be forced to dance with Jar Jar.  But they decided to hover at the bar.  So, I introduced Jar Jar there, having him approach a 4'3 Gungan player, Dani DaVoorti, a character with a Build like: Not Attractive and Eyes: Dead.  Dani was so greasy, that when Jar Jar tried to pull him to the dance floor, Jar Jar couldn't take him with him. (A Brawn check created that.)

So, with Jar Jar making a fool, I introduced a man who handed off a contract to kill Jar Jar, an address given on the data pad. Saying something along the lines of, "Jar Jar is an embarrassment...  It would be great if he just, disappeared."

I had planned out a whole scenario at Jar Jar's apartment, but Dani decided he needed to die as soon as possible and went about circumventing that.  I had forgotten, but Dani had bought a bunch of poison when he created his character, and wanted to use it on Jar Jar's punch.  I rolled with it, going, "OOOH, MESA NOT FEELS SOSA GOOD" Or whatever he says...  And the group escorted sick Jar Jar to the bathroom.  There, the group tried to murder him in the toilet, but kept failing, and Jar Jar began to panic.  I think I faintly remember  character failing to punch the back of Jar Jar's head twice.  It seriously went about 2 rounds of turns before our Zabrak, walked into the bathroom (She was guarding the door.) And then blew his head off with a rifle.  It was a hilarious, weird, unscripted moment that I'm glad I figured out...

Now I just have to figure out what to do next session. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would a GM be willing to post their story for me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 19:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm running a game next week, and I want to make sure I'm prepared.  So, I was wondering if any GM's on here could give me an example of their stories, and how much preparation I should actually have.  At this moment, I have the opening and call to adventure pretty much set to go...  

This first game is going to take place in Coruscant under an Imperial blockade.  I want to give the players freedom in a somewhat controlled environment, because I'm still in the process of learning vehicle rules.  I'm trying to anticipate what my players will want to do, so I'm jotting down a few locations and what could happen at them.

I'd appreciate any advice or possible examples.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giant Bomb does their best to break The Oculus Rift. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 18:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TV Series] Lassie is an alien inhabiting a dog's body. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 22:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throughout the Television program, Lassie is seen having a uncharactistic amount of reason and deduction for a dog.  So much so that she at times seems super intelligent, even picking up on situations that the humans around her can't understand.  She's able to deduce what's about to happen from humans talking to each other, or about what they have planned if they're villains, or if something/thing is in danger.  Honestly, I think she can just understand English at times.  She feels guilt when she realizes she has done something wrong, and is able to understand what her owners are saying to her at times.  She also has the ability to communicate with other animal species through whines and barks.  I would think that any animal would be intimidated by a dog barking at them, no matter the context.  But Lassie seems to have this overwhelming power to calm them and interact with them in a way that seems unnatural.  Usually, these animals start trusting Lassie after a few nondescript barks towards their direction.  My theory is that she's speaking with them telepathically.  It would also explain why, almost comically, the humans seem to be able to pick up on what she's saying by her barks, "What's that Lassie?  Timmy's in the well?" Despite the obvious trope, it has foundations in reality of how Lassie communicates in the series.  I believe that those she affects telepathically don't even realize that's what she's doing.

There's also the supposed age of the dog.  The Lassie TV program ran from 1954-71, with it being set during the modern times of the respective era.  They have replaced the dog actor numerous times, but the assumption is that Lassie is the same dog in the canon of the show.  Lassie would have been an old, withering dog by the time of the 70s, unable to do the grand adventuring the dog was known for.  She also spent time with a number of different owners, such as The Martin Family, The Millers, and the Forest Service.  My theory is that Lassie switched her supposed 'owners' every few years to throw off the scent that she wasn't aging like a normal dog would.  Towards the end of the series, she has decided to go at it alone, possibly because she realized human attachments were too painful to keep up with.  The alien creature inside her grew too close to the humans, and felt detachment was a better solution.

If you take in the run of The New Lassie as canon as well, then her age extends well into the 80s and early 90s.  Also, in The New Lassie show, there's an older grown man version of Timmy from the older series.  Lassie, though, is inexplicably younger and still alive...  What other explanation could there be of this?  They say that the dog is a present day decedent of the older dog, but my thoughts are that the dog in New Lassie is the older dog, and that's the excuse they apply to a dog living that long because the alternative is impossible.  Lassie was exploring out in the wild the majority of the time in the later seasons.  Where would she find a pure bred Sheltie out in the middle of nowhere to breed with and create this supposed offspring?  The remake of Lassie in 97 can be considered non-canon with the earlier series.

So, if Lassie were an alien, what would be her objective?  It seems to be that Lassie is a benevolent creature, helping out where she can and being friend to both human and animal.  She takes on an almost Superman responsibility, though the creature who inhabits her body is only able to do justice in the form of a dog.  A much harder task than being a God among mortals, like Superman.

Perhaps the alien is like The Thing in John Carpenter's The Thing, able to shape shift into the form of whatever creature in infects on first contact.  Only this alien is stuck with Lassie.

Another curious thought...  If the film Lassie Come Home is supposed to be considered canon, then how did Lassie get across the ocean from England to America?  Could she have swam with alien powers?  Or perhaps snuck aboard a freighter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I use the AoR GM Kit on a Edge of the Empire game, or will it be useless? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 20:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you all haven't noticed, the Edge of the Empire GM Kit is incredibly hard to find or expensive.

I was wondering if there's any real difference between the Age of Rebellion Kit and the Edge of the Empire one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers]Star Wars Rebels - Ending montage of Twilight of the Apprentice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 19:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman: Mask of the Phantasm - The first time Bruce puts on the cowl still gives me shivers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 19:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just wanted to give a shout out to our State's Governor, Nathan Deal. (R-GA) He vetoed the discriminitory House Bill 757 which would have allowed businesses to deny service and jobs to LGBT citizens. Proud to be from the south for once! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 20:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apocalypse Now - "Go get the Roach!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 21:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This scene from Michael Clayton really unsettles me for how clinical the murder in it is. It also happens to be one continuous shot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 20:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The hospital scene from Lost in Translation is one of my favorites in the film. The two ladies in the background just kill me... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 06:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something America gets away with that the rest of the world does not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 17:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planning a trip to Japan! Questions about Secret Flying and saving money... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 07:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, a few friends and I are planning a trip to Japan sometime this year.  I personally want to shoot for September to save money and possibly spend two weeks there.

My friend got interested in the prospect of going April-May due to some Secret Flying deals we found online.  I'm thinking that those deals might be there when September comes around, plus I hear Japan is great that time of year, yet my friend thinks that we'd save money going in April using this secret deal, and that we may miss out and have to pay double for a ticket in September.

So, our concerns are:

1. How frequent are deals like this to come up on Secret Flying?  The current two deals we can see are flights out of Chicago for around 500 USD.  Will a deal like that come up again?

2. Are there any benefits besides the weather to going to Japan in Spring rather than Autumn or vice versa?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS]In Son of Saul, something happens in the background that is completely unsettling, but mostly ignored by the characters. What other movies make effective use of the background? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 19:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scene I'm speaking of, which you may have even missed, is when Saul is walking back to a corner of the underground gas chambers to speak to a comrade about his son.  When he passes the main room, you can hear dozens if not hundreds of people vomiting all at the same time.  It's completely unnerving and terrifying to think about, but the film largely ignores it as cavalier as Saul goes about his plan to bury his son.

It's incredibly effective at showing how the sonderkommando unit is just used to the horrors within Auschwitz.  That they don't even really think about it anymore...

Are there other films that take advantage of this idea?  Not necessarily for disturbing content, but other things as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mickey vs. Gorgeous George - Snatch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 20:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What person from history would you like a biopic film about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 18:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the Chili's/TGI Fridays/Applebee's of Japan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 21:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being a fan of the Hitman games, this scene still makes me upset from the movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 07:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IO Interactive Explains the 'Live Components' of Hitman 2016 on the Hitman subreddit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 20:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have noticed that flights to Hong Kong are incredibly cheap lately. Why is this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 16:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is because of the protests currently going on, but I remember looking it up months ago and they were similarly cheap then as they are now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going to be seeing St. Thomas, St. Kitts, St. Lucia and Barbados next week. What should I see? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 15:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going to be on a cruise next week, and our boat is stopping at these places.  What are some cool things to check out?  We'll probably only have a day on each, and we already have a few things planned, but we're open to ideas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Life Aquatic with Steve Zissou - "I wonder if it remembers me..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 22:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS]Now that The Expanse has finished its first season, what did you think of it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 15:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally really enjoyed the finale.  As a book reader, I'm psyched to know they have plenty of content to keep using with the second season, and they haven't even gotten to the 2nd book yet.

Although, I am very aware by what seems like an almost viral push to get this show better ratings.  There have been lots of articles posted here about how The Expanse is the second coming of Christ, and all that.  I can see how some people my be turned off by that aggressive push to get attention.  But honestly?  This is one of the best shows to come out of SyFy in years, and it's honestly worth checking out.

So, what did you all think of the series as a whole? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RLM darling Cameron Mitchell gets a lot of snickers thrown his way, but I was surprised to find that the man can act pretty damn well... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 16:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Permadeath in Games! What's your opinion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 20:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With XCOM 2 and Fire Emblem coming out, I thought it would be interesting to hear /r/games' opinion on the gameplay mechanic of permadeath.

What I mean in this context is when a game character dies and is no longer able to be used...  This is usually prominent in tactical/strategy games, but I remember Diablo 3 having a 'Hardcore' mode as well.

I have been experimenting with both Classic mode in Fire Emblem and Ironman mode in XCOM Enemy Within, and while I find myself getting annoyed and restarting a game before it has a chance to save when I've lost too many troops...  It's a more nerve wracking experience, and something truly unique.  We're too accustomed to restarting when we don't get our way, but now these games have consequences.  I'm already fearful of my soldier's lives in both games...  I'm nervous that I'll make a stupid mistake in the future.

What do you all think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few friends play a bad skiing game. They find the edge of the map and eclipse the event horizon... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 00:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is $100 a good rate for voice work between 30-60 minutes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 19:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do a short fiction podcast that mostly revolves around my voice, but I need voice work done for episodes where other characters come in.  Each episode usually lasts 30-60 minutes, but I'm considering using shorter episodes.  I have used people who volunteer to do VO work for a bit, but now I'm having trouble getting a good turn around...  I have two scripts out in the ether at the moment that I haven't had a return on.  I'm figuring paying my VAs might motivate them a bit more...

Problem is, I work a 9-5 entry level job, and I could only really afford to pay actors between $100-200 a month, depending on how many I use.  I was wondering if paying a $100 would be appropriate...

Is that a decent rate for amateur voice work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: The Soviet Afghan War (1979-1989) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 17:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some fantastic podcasts that no one seems to talk about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 15:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Sicario Spoilers] I'm pretty sad Benicio Del Toro didn't get nominated for best supporting actor this year. This scene in Sicario left me breathless. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 19:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should Rockstar remove the 'comedy' from GTA? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 21:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a lot of people are feeling that their use of comedy is becoming juvenile and actually taking away from the dramatic stories that they want to tell.  I feel like 'missed potential' comes up a lot in discussions of GTA V's writing.  I feel as if Rockstar is unwilling to shake this schtick that the worlds that GTA lives in have to be ridiculous.  There's this belief that the over-the-top comedic world that the GTA titles live in act as a buffer for the horrific violence you commit within them, but I believe that gamers have matured enough to which that argument just isn't valid anymore.  The Jack Thompson's of the world have realized they've lost.  Violence in video games is here to stay, and plenty of studies find that violent video games are more cathartic than anger-inducing.  

The creative comedy writing actually worked in GTA 3's benefit because they still weren't willing to go into the crassness of swearing, sexual humor, and racial humor.  They had to think of clever jokes that didn't rely on cursing and other lewd humor.  I think that worked to their benefit, and it eased players into this silly world better...

Their humor now comes off at a poor man's attempt at South Park humor...  And they want to say something 'important' about American society, but people are so aware of it and it's so blatant that fans are just getting tired of it.  I know I am.

Of course, I could be wrong.  I thought GTA V's Lamar was a fantastic character, and his use of crass over-the-top humor really worked in his favor.  It's just the world itself...  the advertisements, radio stations, car names...  GTA V feels like a new Adam Sandler movie.  We get it, you're known for your crass humor...  But we're almost 30 now.  It isn't funny anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Louis Theroux realizes how emotionally devastating it is working in a kill shelter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 19:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]Professional Cameraman of Reddit, what are some of your interesting stories of out filming in public? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 19:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you write hacking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 03:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the one subject matter that every piece of media, besides perhaps The Social Network and Mr. Robot, seems to get wrong.  I'm pretty open to messing  it as well, seeing as how I like to write pulpy Science-Fiction...  But with this generation growing in technological knowledge, it won't be appropriate in the future to say, 'Hack the mainframe!' or whatever CSI and those other cop procedurals say.

What are some basic ways a writer can write computer hacking somewhat believable?  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haing S. Ngor, the Academy Award winning actor who performed in the harrowing film 'The Killing Fields,' was murdered by gang violence in L.A. during the 90s. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 21:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Thing (2011) wasn't very good, but I completely LOVED how they connected to The Thing (1982) in the ending credits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 06:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the scene that sticks out to me in Clone Wars. You can actually understand how Anakin fell to the dark side after this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 16:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS] Those who think Star Wars: The Force Awakens is a bad movie: Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 16:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed that a lot of the praise and excitement of TFA has seemed to have died down, and now there are a lot of critics suddenly becoming more vocal.  Heh, I just literally had a co-worker come in and tell me it sucked.

I've noticed that it's either people who hate that the EU was scrubbed, or that it was basically a soft reboot of the original.  

But I could be missing another piece of the criticism of this film.  Why do you not like it members of /r/movies?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good places to take cooking classes around Buckhead? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 15:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Self-explanatory.  I live near Buckhead, and I'm looking for a place to take beginner classes on the Weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ANSWER THE QUESTION STEVEN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 02:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting your band signed before the internet... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 02:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes a performance 'Oscar Worthy?' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 16:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found myself getting into an argument on another thread about what particularly makes a film performance Oscar Worthy.  I'm fairly open to the idea that if the film is excellent and the acting is excellent, then no matter what genre or type of movie it is, it should be 'Oscar Worthy.' 

I think others think the Oscar should go to more tasteful films perhaps?  What do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Hateful Eight Spoilers] I seriously believe Walton Goggins deserves an oscar nod for Hateful Eight. He stole the show for me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 20:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wouldn't have thought it, seeing as how his character seemed like he was barely in the trailers, but he turns out to be a main character and the one with the biggest arc out of the whole cast.


I've always thought Goggins was great, Justified proves that, but I can totally see big things for him as a major star. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there's a old Soviet Era prison in Riga, Latvia where tourists can come and experience the torture used on prisoners by the KGB. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 18:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scenes like this were why The Wire was one of the greatest shows on television... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 05:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The opening scene to Menace II Society still unsettles me. How it shifts your perspective within minutes from pitying with the prejudiced teens to being horrified by them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 22:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some Audiobooks you'd consider better experiences than actually reading the book? Part 2! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 21:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted a thread like this a few years ago, and it was an awesome success.  It has been a year or so, and there have been an awesome amount of audiobooks released in that time.

Some of my recommendations:

Any of the new Star Wars books are pretty great.  They include John Williams fanfare and sound effects.  I've listened to Lost Stars, and it was a lot of fun.  Planning on listening to the Battlefront book next, because I hear it has the same deal.  I've even heard the production quality makes Aftermath bearable.  

American Gods:
This one was recommended to me the last thread, and I have to say it is a definite winner.  Having a full cast doing an unabridged novel actually sucks you into the story really well.  Same goes for books like World War Z.

I've actually really enjoyed the Expanse series partially because of narrator Jefferson Mays.  He really knows how to give each character a specific voice, and he knows how to do female voices very subtly.  Definite recommend for hard sci-fi fans.

What are your recommendations /r/books? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WILL YOU COMPLY - Fallout 4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 19:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been reading Star Wars: Lost Stars. Though I'm enjoying the book, I feel my cover design is more appropiate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 18:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Instead of a Die Hard prequel, they should do a Die Hard/Lethal Weapon crossover. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 19:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone in Atlanta doing NaNoWriMo next month? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 17:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the site for details: http://nanowrimo.org

I was wondering if there were any fellow aspiring writers in the city who might be up for meeting every so often during the month to work on our novels, chat about writing, whatever...  It'd be cool to get a group together at Dr. Bombay's, Inman Perk Coffee, or somewhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Bad Guys are right - The Network of Utopia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 23:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Story of Bass Reeves - Drunk History </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 18:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I installed a GTA V Zombie mod and things... Got a bit crazy... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 07:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the most unsettling things about Sicario had to be the score... Johann Johannsson is a genius at making you feel gross. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 00:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why on earth has there not been a proper release of Come and See (1985) on Bluray? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 16:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It blows my mind that this film isn't on the Criterion Collection.  Or that no company has pushed for a proper blurry release...  Not only is it one of the best and most gut wrenching holocaust movies to ever be made, but it also is from a perspective of the holocaust we don't usually see.  

There's a large focus on the Jewish losses in World War Two in Americanized history, and while those are important, I think it's completely flabbergasting that people don't know how much more the Russians lost in the war.  Not only by the Nazis, but also by their own government.  It's thought that the civilian death toll in Russia was around 14 million, but the shocking thing is they aren't even sure...  So many people died on the Eastern Front, and media usually tends to ignore that part of history for the American side.

This film made quite an impression on me when I first saw it.  It is unashamed with its devastating imagery, and it conveys that devastation through a protagonist that not only suffered as a character but also as an actor.  The folk stories behind this film about the lead actor's hair turning white from all the PTSD-inducing artillery they surrounded him with is incredibly interesting to read about and reflective of Soviet film making.

I highly recommend this film, and it just bothers me that it's such a hidden little film...  I really hope someone picks up the rights to the film so it can get a proper blurry distribution.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This fucking thing at the bottom of youtube... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 02:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This scene from Wolfenstein: The New Order made me have a mini existential crisis... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 02:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My local mexican resturant has the right idea... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 02:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think Skull Face knew more then what was presented... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 07:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Skull Face knew that Venom was a imposter.

There's a scene during the mission where you take a car ride with Skull Face that kind of threw me off. When you first approach him, he pushes his guards aside, and then the camera pulls in real close to his face. There's this weird noise as he utters the phrase, "You hope hatred might someday replace the pain. But it never goes away. It makes a man hideous, inside and out." The camera zooms into his face, and locks there in a way the camera normally doesn't do...  Usually, the camera is following snake along like a handi-cam, but this time it is completely locked on his head.

After he utters this phrase, Venom puts down his gun. Miller assumes that Snake is going to go along with him to get his shot, but during that cutscene/gameplay, Venom can get no where near Skull Face. You have to follow a set path to the car, and you can only go a set speed. You also can't get anywhere near Skull Face.  It's the mechanics telling you that you are no longer really in control of Venom.  If you think about how Venom interacts with his men, he knocks them around and jumps into them, etc...  But here Snake is locked down.  He can't do anything.  It's a very strange moment. I think that's why Venom is so silent during the car ride. He's under some kind of Sleeper agent activation code. 

The only thing Skull Face didn't expect was Volgin and Psycho Mantis turning on him. If you notice, even if you shoot Skull Face when he's under the rubble, you can't kill him.  Snake never goes for the kill shot, and Miller even has to try and help him to make it happen. Instead, he goes for the next best thing, crippling him.

The idea of sleeper agents in this isn't too crazy.  The idea is very popular in Cold War fiction, starting with Manchurian Candidate.  In fact, at the end of the game, 'The Man Who Sold the World' tape seems to be the only thing that brings Venom out of his Big Boss trance, which also could be considered a sleeper agent activation.  

tl;dr Skull Face knew Venom was a doppelganger, and he knew a sleeper agent activation code to stop him from killing him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Kerbal related image to have up on second monitor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 15:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'm just starting with Kerbal Program, and I want to play it RIGHT.  I have a joystick hooked up, and a dual monitor set up, but I'm trying to think of what I could put up on the second monitor.

I'm thinking a reference image with the appropriate vectors and what they mean, but I was wondering if there was something the community would recommend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any dangers to modding Metal Gear Solid V? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 22:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GTA V made me wonder.  I imagine the FOB missions would lead to bans if playing a modded game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are we not talking about Metal Gear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 07:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the weirdest thing you've heard/seen in a public bathroom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 18:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what are you currently working on creatively? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 23:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bojack Horseman, a show about a depressed cartoon horse, is a better written tragedy than Walking Dead, a show that is nothing but tragedy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 01:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Places in Atlanta to learn boxing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 15:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking to try out Boxing.  Beginner level preferably.  Anyone know of a good gym or class? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] Someone who has witnessed an atom/nuclear/hydrogen bomb detonation first hand. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know there have been many test nuclear/atomic/hydrogen detonations in the past 60 years or so, and I was curious if anyone knew of family that have witnessed a mushroom cloud first hand.

1. How were you able to witness it?  Military?  Vegas citizen?
2. What were your immediate feelings after viewing the detonation?
3. Any adverse effects from being that close?  Cancer?  Radiation poisoning?
4. Did it change your opinion of nuclear armament?  If so, how?
5. What physical things happened to your body?  Did you ears ring?  Did they pop?  Could you feel the explosion in the earth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Fallout 4 getting everyone riled up, now is the perfect time to jump into the exquisite, broken weirdness that is Fallout: New Vegas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 06:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitman Q A: "What we release on December 8th is not the full game. Its a sizeable chunk of it. Throughout 2016 well release more locations and missions until the story arc is done and finished." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 17:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today I discovered a Back to the Future-like film from the female perspective called, 'Peggy Sue Got Married.' It stars Kathleen Turner, Nick Cage, Jim Carrey and Joan Allen... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 21:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HELP] I think a Niner quest is either broken, or I'm missing something... Help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, Ive been playing through Niner's quest, and he has us dressing like NCR troopers and sneaking around at the Mojave Outpost.

We've gotten to the point where we're in this room, and Niner says to get rid of this 'Gormless Idiot' that's in the room with us.  Every time I talk to him though, all the NPC says is, "What do you need?" Before the conversation ends.

I feel like I'm supposed to kill him or something, but I'm not sure, and when I talk to Niner, he is just his normal self with orders and what not...

Am I missing something, or is Niner glitched? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new Hitman trailer makes murder look sexy as hell... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 15:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moving to new place 2.5 miles away from work. What benefits can I see from walking 5 miles a day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am moving to a new place in a few days that's down the street from where I work.  It's a 2.5 mile walk, which Google tells me will take 50 minutes.  That's totally fine with me, because I already wrestled with traffic for an hour to an hour and a half at my previous residence.  Plus having an audible account helps a lot...

I'm curious about what effects I may see in the few weeks following, and perhaps in the months to come if I make this a routine.

I'm 250 lbs, 6'1, Male and 26 years old.  I want to lose weight.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NO SPOILERS] After watching episodes 7   8 of this season, I only have one thing to say about director Miguel Sapochnik... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I miss the Drew Carey Show.. A lot... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 17:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DragonCon is coming up. How about getting an Expanse group of cosplayers together? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 22:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anyone is going to be in the Atlanta area, it'd be neat to get together a group for a Expanse cosplay.  

It'd be nice to get a head start on all the fans that are sure to start cosplaying when the show comes out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woolie Swallows A Ghost Pepper And Reviews Mortal Kombat X, Instantly Regrets It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 02:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Momocon brought me closer to the lord, and for that I'm eternally grateful. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 18:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You are the operator of the Mars Curiosity Rover. On a routine photo survey, you find something unbelievable... A Roman Gladius sword stuck in the dirt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 06:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever done something that was accidentally racist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 05:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I cut together a fanedit of Elysium that makes it look like an 80s VHS film. There's also new music added to specific scenes in the movie. Here's a link to the trailer! (A Link to the actual cut is in the Trailer's description.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 18:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scenes like this are why I can't completely dismiss Man of Steel. It's not perfect, but I still think it's a good movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 16:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hotline Miami 2 is hard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 08:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cougar Town has to have one of the worst advertising campaigns of all time. It's always unfunny jokes about red wine, which makes me hate the show without seeing it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 04:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Admiral Ackbar is a space racist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 03:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the best day of Peter's life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 01:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the best day of Peter's life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 01:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS]After seeing Calvary, I really want to see Chris O'Dowd tackle more dramatic roles. This scene was a wonderful example of his range to change tones on a dime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 09:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I remember this commercial for the Sci-Fi channel freaking me out as a kid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 05:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A display of the worst band in the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 21:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Looking for a female voice actor for a possible reoccurring part in my short fiction podcast: The Morning Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 20:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Morning Report is a podcast that takes place inside the top secret facility Area 51.  The host, Simon, gives the morning announcements: Birthdays, deaths, news etc. and then he tells a story...  The stories are declassified files he is given by the management of Area 51.  

Here is my website where you can listen to the first episode:

https://themorningreport.squarespace.com

Currently, the podcast is only one episode deep, and I had a friend lined up to do the voice work of a character I'm writing currently.  Unfortunately, things fell through, and I want to keep to a strict timeline of updating every 2 weeks.  This character, named Raquel, would possibly be a reoccurring character that would appear from time to time as the story goes on.

Here are some details on the character:

Raquel is an Army private who has just come home from her first tour in Iraq to celebrate with her family and her boyfriend's family.  Her family is Dominican, and very traditional, but she was born and raised in the States with her brothers.  So, if she had any kind of accent to her voice, it would be barely noticeable.  Her brothers are all vets as well, so I want to give the audience the sense that this character is a disciplined, military minded woman, who has been surrounded by the lifestyle all her life.  In the context of the podcast though, this episode will refer to her debriefing after surviving a paranormal event.

Here's a line of dialogue you can send me if interested:

"Was I mad about it, yeah I was...  I mean, I'm not the boasting type, but I felt like I was as tough as any of those other boys in the Rangers.  Wallace included..." (Pause)

"Wallace would be tripping right now if he was here.  He was always into those conspiracy shows, like that one about Aliens in Ancient Egypt.  What was it called?  I don't know...  Heh, you know it's funny, it's not his smile or the way he kissed me that I miss...  It's stupid shit like that."

Feel free to message me on Reddit.
I'm also available at the following email address:
the.morning.report.podcast@gmail.com

**I should mention that I don't really have the income to pay someone.  If things go well, and I start making donations or getting advertisements, then I will draft percentages to be taken out of the lump sum for every month.  Until then, I'm doing this for free.  I'm up on iTunes and I have a pretty decent site.  It's about building content and finding an audience right now.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
