<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2044</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 10:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I compare two situations to see who is more likely losing at life:    
- an emetophobe who is willing to openly discuss it with strangers   
- someone who unnecessarily insults that person   
The latter is far more probable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 10:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had "ARE CHAVS HAVING SEX WITH THE QUEEN?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot Shots Part Deux is much better than the first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Beautiful Mind does a great job of shifting the tone from paranoid thriller to tragedy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be happy for the older Arnie to play endless Liam Neeson style kick-ass roles. Just endless revenge films with stupid stunts and quips (except for "I'm getting too old for this shit", I wouldn't want to hear that). I don't care for him trying to act like he's grieving, being emotional, reflecting or any shit like that, it just doesn't work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting you can assume the intent of someone you didn't know, 30 years ago! She was into witchy shit all the time so I don't think that was her intention. I'd also argue that any benefit of waving a crystal (placebo, distraction or otherwise) is offset by a teacher letting kids believe in complete nonsense - surely it would be better to put the girl to a distraction task of some kind like "here, help me do this for a minute" if that was the intention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? Psycho 2 and 3 are great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thoughts:  
- Scoot McNairy seems to be in everything these days  
- This looks like a spin-off of S2 of Breaking Bad  
- This doesn't feel like a good role for Arnie, it seems more like a Jack Nicholson role (e.g. same character as The Crossing Guard) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember this girl having a nosebleed around age 8, and the teacher (older plump cat lady kinda teacher) sat her down and waved a rose quartz around her nose. Eventually the bleeding stopped (the girl also had a tissue stuffed up there) and the teacher said to everyone "there you go... see?" All the eager-to-impress-teacher kids went "woooooowwww". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shep Proudfoot in Fargo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something I did realise is that most of the "lost/stolen" ones are from where people had them go "missing" in the mail, ordered a replacement from Amazon (which they will do, except they also blacklist the first one), then the original ends up getting sold - except its blacklisted. This is why these Echos can still be boxed, sealed even. Ones that are legitimately lost or stolen are unlikely to be neatly boxed etc, so should already raise huge suspicion if sold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the troll thing is just an excuse. Some executive idiots probably analysed the traffic-to-revenue ratios from the messageboards and decided they weren't profitable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 09:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats one fatal flaw of the "spark joy" method, it doesnt account for those times (which often trigger decluttering) where you feel completely emotionally detached from your whole life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 08:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Your asking Amazon to give you their address though...   

No, I'm not. I've already repeated myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't diagnosed with a disorder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you need to overcome the unhappiness in the present time?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find comic book films completely boring at the cinema. The size and blurriness of all the CGI just makes my mind glaze over. I much prefer them on the small screen. I like atmospheric films that benefit from full absorption, like Midnight Special, Green Room, Sicario, Nocturnal Animals, that kind of thing. I wouldn't see a romcom or a talking heads (eg documentary) kind of film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 12:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a documentary called **Capturing the Friedman's**. It starts of about this guy making a documentary about people who make money as clowns for birthday parties. Then the documentary maker stumbles upon something massively dark and disturbing, and it gets extremely weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 12:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mum looks after injured and orphaned hedgehogs and must have saved more than 100 in her time. So that should help a little, she's amazing at what she does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 12:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's question was asked almost verbatim yesterday, where I mentioned Brad Pitt's uncredited role as a background waiter in Charlie Sheen's [No Man's Land](http://gossipbrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/charlie-sheen-brad-pitt-insert-.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 11:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Customers wouldn't be exposed to each other at all, I never mentioned that.  

*"or giving me a return label so it can be sent back in, to then be sent back out to the original owner"*  

If I had bought new from Amazon, I would like to know there's an added service whereby I had the option to recover it - via Amazon - if it was lost/stolen and later handed back in to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't Amazon help with lost/stolen Echos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 10:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a second hand Echo that turns out to be blacklisted, i.e. the serial number reports it as lost/stolen (the error code is "10:2:12:3:1" when registering, in case anyone else searches for the same error code and isn't sure what it means). No problem, I'll claim for a Paypal refund.   

However, I do feel bad for the original owners, and worse that there is absolutely nothing that can be done to reunite them with their Echo. Once a device is registered as lost/stolen, the only option for the owner is to find it/retrieve it again, and call Amazon to unblock it.   

Amazon aren't interested in sending an email to the original owner saying "hey, we know where your Amazon is", or giving me a return label so it can be sent back in, to then be sent back out to the original owner (even for a small postage fee from the original owner). Doesn't this seem like a tragic waste? I will end up having to throw this away, despite the fact that it belongs to someone else.  

Surely in the age of serial numbered, blockable wifi devices, it wouldn't take much to offer a recovery service to customers, because sooner or later their serial number is bound to be called in from the new unlucky "customer".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 10:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're replying to the wrong person, but also she clearly didn't notice or else it wouldn't have happened. *"It was about 5 in the morning. I finish pumping when all of a sudden I notice movement on the other side of my car through the windows."* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 08:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the first dvd I ever bought. What I remember about the commentary is that almost every scene starts with Kurt saying something like "oh, this is where things really go up a gear" or "up a level" or "start to get really intense" or something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 11:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now blocked, the beeb must be redditors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely! Its so subtle and careful, yet was shot so quickly and cheaply by a tv crew. Have you seen the sequels? Theyre not classics, but really good fun ans engaging. Psycho II and III each have their own creepy atmospheres, and I think Perkins did a great job of directing the third.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In The Valley Of Elah, Delores Clairbourne </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to spoiler alert that?  

Also, a mature american film I saw recently was Christine, amazing. Similar to MBTS in that it shows a very well drawn and incredibly acred character, complete with anxieties, insecurities etc. Something you rarely find in scripts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Psycho, I just have a weird nostalgic relationship to it and love its atmospheres and music. Its also really watchable and fascinating whenever Anthony Perkins is onscreen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep I have the same thoughts. There are so many little internal battles. Some epiphanies: you shouldnt live in a museum. Being distracted by the past will blind you to the present of who you are, and slow down progress. The value of those little moments of nostalgia doesnt outweigh the disadvantage of lost space and past-distraction. Really, those little nostalgia moments are never more than "huh, look at that, gee". One day, sooner or later, you probably will throw it away, so why not do it sooner. Waiting to feel ready is just continuing to be a slave to it. Somewhere in time, youre always enjoying your stuff, when you enjoyed it. Getting rid of it doesnt change that.  

My current niggle is value - I find it hard to throw something away, I feel I should sell it (which can be a hassle) or find someone who would benefit from it, but that becomes time consuming. E.g a bunch of dvds, it feels weird to just take them to a charity shop but eventually thats what needs to done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, his little bit role as the thief in Thelma and Louise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw Lost Highway at the cinema as part of an art course when I was 17. Everyone (including the teacher) hated it, but I loved it. I watched it loads since, and listened to the excellent soundtrack probably more than any film. I love how the first half is a moody noirish arthouse mystery thriller, with the videotapes building this weird tension as you wonder about Renee having an affair and Pullman's growing awareness of it. Then the second half goes in all sorts of directions. Its so weird and wonderful. I don't understand why Mulholland Drive overshadows it so much in terms of talk, LH for me is a much more interesting film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brad Pitt plays an uncredited waiter in the background of a scene in Charlie Sheen's 80s Porsche stealing movie called NO MANS LAND </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 12:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did this turn out for you? I'm having the same error code  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 12:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it seems weak anyhow to actually allow the moronic minority to have their way and destroy something. There were plenty of alternatives, e.g. a paid up membership. Some executives likely realised there wasn't much money in it, or that messageboard hits are affecting their advertising click-through stats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 10:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's terrifying. Its worse also that on top of the safety aspect you had to deal with the mental frustration of a fucking weirdo like that blaming *you* for whats happening. There's something so rage-provoking about someone in absolute ignorance/denial of their actions, where anything you do or say to explain just leads to more hostile defensiveness.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you considered getting rid of it? What stops you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No sarcasm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find Operation Daybreak, the earlier (and much better) film of the Anthropoid story. Also, Where Eagles Dare, Eye of the Needle, Black Book </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt the same way about it after seeing it in theatres. I rated it 8 on IMDB, and forever more whenever I constructively criticised a film on a messageboard, I would get "well you liked sucker punch so there goes your credibility".  

Well, at least that wont be happening anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? They were amazing. Any obscure film you just happened to watch, you could count on reading a whole load of interesting stuff and discussions afterwards. Intepretations of some ambiguity, a thread written by an extra, a link to some news story about where the main actor is now, all that weird and wonderful stuff. Theres no substitute for it anywhere else, its a really sad loss.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. It was absolutely a part of my film watching routine, and I loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just found out and am gutted. The boards were perfect for exploring details and sharing info with like minded fans. You could go on a board for an old obscure 80s movie after watching and delve into a trove of discussion, read something from an extra, a relative of an actor or something, and learn all sorts. NOTHING will replace it for those post-viewing indulgences. I even made some friends by spotting familiar names on boards I visited for favourite films. Im absolutely gutted.  

Its such a shame that a bunch of trolls led to its demise. Im sure outside of the 10% bloated traffic that the big new movies get on the boards, the rest of the boards were pretty sensible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its so true. I've learned so much through decluttering. Its like "stuff" ends up having this subtle unconscious influence over your identity or something, because its always a reminder of the past, of perceived value, of something that will eventually need sorting or getting rid of. I find that minimizing gives that free, light feeling like being on vacation, where you're in the present and focused on the few things around you that you actually chose to be there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it such a rewatchable film. You can watch it for the technical direction wizardry, the mystery story, or as a character development film. The character journeys are so well drawn and brilliantly acted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate films that turn shit at the end. You invest all that time and engagement then it fucks you over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nil By Mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know, I feel the music, script and story make SPR a bit unrealistic beyond the combat scenes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 10:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's weird, I saw the title of your post and started thinking on this, settling on Adam Driver, then read your post and saw you made the same conclusion. I think Driver would do a great job, capturing that slightly offbeat quirk and underlying aggression/discontent really well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 09:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for referencing those books! I hadn't heard of them before but they look great, and perfectly in sync with my decluttering right now. Did you get the more recent illustrated one, and if so which one would you recommend?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, just wow. So you PM me with "ahahahahahaha! it didn't work out for you did it?" then try to make out that I pm'ed you insults. Seriously, FUCK OFF.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you feel about the part where you completely neglect to acknowledge that I pasted forum rules because you'd explicitly argued against them, with hostility, rather than just commented? Or the part where you develop a convenient blindspot to the fact that your "evidence" against me had absolutely no bearing, at all, to what you had done to garner my response?   

You probably don't feel anything about those aspects because you don't have the capacity to even be aware of them. You're one of those assholes who distorts as much as he can in an argument, making as much literal and figurative noise as possible because you're too dumb to accept any accountability.  

Honestly I'm bored with this and won't comment again, so please fuck off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so its moan, whinge and insult until the other guy gets bored, then stand there like an idiot thinking you've won something. Impressive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you aware of your glaring inadequacy issues?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. But had someone suggested I see the movie, I wouldn't have gotten all weakly defensive and immature about it like yourself, you tool. You have absolutely no clue how to make an argument, do you? You throw your toys out the pram like you probably have done your whole life, hoping if you shout and moan loudly enough someone will take you seriously. Except they won't, because you're a twat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm just pointing out how much complete fucking bullshit you've written. And no, your comments aren't exactly innocent, you're a complete and utter ignorant asshole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it's also intended for people to read about the movie and get an idea if it's worth taking a trip to the theater or not

Really? Because that seems contrary to this bit at the top of the page:

**If you haven't seen the film LEAVE NOW. If you want to see the opinions of redditors check the poll below. Also any comments that clearly show the commenter has not seen the film IT WILL BE REMOVED.**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you give a fuck about your possessions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 12:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently I started decluttering, and selling stuff. Blurays that I haven't really cared about, old books, furniture, xbox, electronics etc. Its felt very liberating. The weird thing though is that the more I get rid of, the less I give a fuck about what's left. There's a momentum to the detachment.   

The process has led to a few inner discussions, like is something purely for me, or for the idea of what someone else might think. Like I had a bunch of movie stuff in the garage - it was actually getting in the way of my using my gym equipment, but I liked the idea of it, but mostly because of impressing others or expressing myself. Really though, no one gives a shit, and the things it says about it are probably way off what I was intending.   

Also, I love the feeling of not being distracted by stuff - it means that I'm only aware of/focusing on whatever is there at the time - a particular book or project for example. All this other shit used to be there lurking in the background, of reality as well as my subconscious mind.  

So Im wondering what other people's relationship is to "stuff". Do you collect, hoard, minimize?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 12:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you like that? I started decluttering recently and the idea of a shelf of elephant statues would drive me nuts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 11:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zero. A big company would never instantly go bankrupt, even if sales suddenly ceased. Big companies have lots of cash reserves, and it would take time to get to the point of being bankrupt. But I see what you're getting at, so I'll say Apple, Pixar, Disney, all major film studios, Starbucks, Facebook.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 11:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll second that. The story development is meticulous and astonishing. Season 4 in particular, the influences and cause-effect chain of events is so fascinating to watch play out. The characters are all so well drawn and acted that you forget they're made up. People bash season 5, but only in comparison to the other seasons - its still a highly intelligent, fascinating season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 11:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  i came here to see what people's opinion of the movie was, that's why it's called *official discussion*

You think its called *official discussion* because you came here to see what people's opinion of it was? I can't agree with your logic there. Its obviously a spoiler-heavy zone, and is clearly intended for people who have seen the film, to *discuss* it. /u/jasonfahy simply encouraged you to see the movie, and you see that as the douchiest comment you've ever seen in this sub? I would say that your response was far douchier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 11:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask if you have a thing about poo too? In my experience people with emetophobia normally have a thing about pooing too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 11:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree, and felt the same. T1 was such a cornerstone cultural experience if seen whilst at college, it really captured that pre-millennial era. Watching the sequel now is a total joy, especially how it ties in with our own experiences of aging, potential lost etc. I really felt like Boyle and co had given us a great gift, and I haven't been so happy to pay full price on opening night for a movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Titanic shoot was incredible. The extras on the bluray are amazing, especially the time lapse building of the half of a ship that they made. Its just mindblowing what they did to achieve various shots, and 20 years ago too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you check your phone whilst watching La Jetee? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you stay, I might hurt you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly theres a lot of room for improvement. Proof read, I cant stand seeing typos on blogs. Dont write to an audience, write to an individual. By that I mean dont be safe in writing in broad strokes, get into some details about themes and nuances and make it more personal and heart-felt. People dont give a shit about your synopsis for the film and broad stuff like an actor being "superb", explain why. Superlatives become invisible and boring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that on a plane and loved it. It was just perfect at the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant a month in the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't you ask this again a month from now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 09:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The film of The Walk is about the backstory to a true event. How can you not know that? Have you not seen the film? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 09:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It dawned on me yesterday that the rerelease is half way between now and the original release. The second half went so much quicker than the first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's WRONG with you? Here, look at this book of burns whilst I get some bad pot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. I always saw that moment as highlighting her ultimate vulnerability, which is what allowed her to be exploited - needing to be liked and approved of. The perp uses flattery/recognition/validation and the threat of disapproval/shame/frustration to keep her in line at all times. In the interview at the end, she attempts to earn that same approval by being informally chatty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be great to have a documentary like that. There are a few that focus on individual elements (e.g. Stanley Milgrams Obedience to Authority) or examples, but not one that brings it all together. I think that's why I like Compliance so much, despite being a fictionalised account it does a great job at showing so many techniques at once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this were true, I'm pretty sure they would have had a moment in the cafe scene where Walter shouts "if there's one thing I can't stand, its warm fucking beer!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Martin Scorsese's After Hours. Its a brilliant and timeless 80s film that hasn't dated at all. The story is so funny and fast-paced, but also existentially interesting and nightmarish. There are loads of familiar faces and quirky moments. The music and cinematography are brilliant too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe if you're Leanard Shelby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this film, and have a framed quad poster of it in my bedroom.   

The human mind is essentially very automatic, and responds to cues (whether internal or external). The perp takes advantage (in a skilled, knowing way) of certain contexts and responses - e.g. obedience to authority, fear of being or doing wrong, time pressure, wanting to help, response to flattery, reciprocal favors. He uses various shaming/pressure techniques to change the person's self-image to push those responses in his favor. I was really impressed with the writer/directors grasp of unconscious influence.  

As an aside, there were a whole series of similar real-world pranks, the recordings of which are available. Hotel guests were influenced to throw their TVs out of the window, drink urine, and even smear faeces on the windows. It sounds utterly insane, but when a person's reality is gradually altered, insanity can happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drugstore feat Thom Yorke - El President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 11:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I still find myself humming the Nirvana style ad to Pantysmile, or "she's an uzi lover".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strangely, no. The internet has grown hugely in areas of social networking and porn, but online retail is still something that has yet to happen. Hopefully, one day, there will be some large shops, that you can browse through *online*. I have no idea how all the stocking and delivery side of things will work, perhaps thats why no one has had the balls to approach it yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like Ryan Adams cover of "Shake It Off" on his cover album of 1989. It gives it such a different tone, sombre and almost sarcastic in knowing the futility with which some things can't be shaken off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CHESSSSSNEY HAWKES! "I am the one and only". I also like that its used as Sam Rockwell's alarm clock in Moon, as well as featuring in dir. Duncan Jone's Source Code.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 13:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I agree, not every movie should be fun to watch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 12:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Lion is the story worth knowing, being that its true and more honest (i.e. less contrived). But I think Slumdog is the film that is more rewarding to rewatch - Boyle's vibrant, energetic and dynamic creativity when it comes to directing makes it much more fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SCINECE, BITCH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what I mean about having a prior bias against Bay - but here that tendency for obnoxious characters was perfect for the film. Pain and Gain wasn't written by Bay - the characters were [i]written[/i] as completely obnoxious and moronic.  

Its a strange thing to say that you found the characters unlikable, but hate it because you [i]believe[/i] Bay was trying to make them likable? That's kind of my original point about bias. Anyone who does like the characters is part of the target of the satire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. I LOVE Danny Boyle's direction, he never lets it get boring, there's always so much attention to detail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You found them likable? I'm not sure that was the intention, they were portrayed as fucking moronic dickheads.  

The real life incident was a complete farce, that's the point. Except the screenplay uses the farcical element to make a satirical statement about the american dream (and greed culture in general).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good work. I like your thorough and meticulous standards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! I loved the soundtrack, was such a fun film and a great night out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 13:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pain and Gain. Genuinely, I think most people completely overlooked it and didn't really pay attention, being that its a Michael Bay film. But if you watch it without prior bias or filters, it really is a brilliantly written and produced satire, with excellent editing and music.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 13:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 09:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear ya. One other thing I love about Rear Window is its relevance. The guy has a broken leg and this beautiful girl he doesn't quite feel the same way about (i.e. life problems), so procrastinates and distracts himself via these square shapes that stimulate with the banal details of other peoples lives (i.e. internet screens/ipad/facebook etc).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Pain and Gain was quite severely snubbed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's interesting, I felt that way about Rear Window on first watch, but appreciated it more on the second watch (and third also). Hitchcock really does add a whole load of subtext, symbolism and psychology. Deliverance also holds up well in a timeless way. I think any film about universal concepts, or core truths about the human condition, if made well will be timeless. But AWIL was more just a shock piece of its time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 11:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to sort of go back to its time of release to appreciate it in context. Also, it helps to appreciate the films of John Landis to be in sync with it. Watching it now expecting some meta commentary, satire/irony or deeper meaning is going to disappoint.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to see a more industrial based soundtrack, not quite the consistent crunching of Quake but something more dynamic and courageous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I agree, I phrased that wrong. I just meant that the ethereal drone scapes (when not accompanied by piano) are the best bits, but still don't really suit the film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah I see your point. I think that's just a coincidence. San Junipero is as well though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 12:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think such entitled cheapskates will ever really understand that unfortunately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 12:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if its really allowed, as you should really pay for it like everyone else. [But here you go](https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/71dyxSCKeqL._SY355_.jpg). Hope that helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for that link, loved it. Also your preferences are the same as mine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for that link, loved it. Also your preferences are the same as mine. 
Edit - I downloaded their album, $3.69 for FLAC seems highly reasonable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think of Trent's score for Patriots Day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Psycho for sure. Let those quotes soak in so you can have fun on the IMDB messageboard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a great film. I love how Tommy Lee Jone's character, and his whole team, all have depth of character with quirky personalities. They feel real, which is something I don't feel in most movies. The action is efficient and tight, the story compelling and engaging. The only thing I wish is that Jerome Krabbe had more of a come-uppance at the end, after all that Kimble has been through. The music, direction and cinematography is brilliant too - all those high-rise city sweeps. Also, Julianne Moore's cool little cameo as a doctor. And that bit that was re-used in 24 where he gets shot in the face but with bullet-proof glass in the way.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
