<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4635</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 19:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just FYI to anybody asking why they didn't get killed easily. You cant shoot through the bars they were standing next to (the ones at chest height). Yes it is pretty sad they didn't kill them though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 19:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I love the winning music at the end of the round (the music seems bug a lot of the time for me and it plays the wrong music, usually the losing music all the time for russians even if they win). You see the your team won and then the winning music comes on. It's great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 19:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started to learn how to snipe (got a service star with the M98B and the L96). I find myself just camping now. It takes a lot of skill to be able to use a sniper rifle in close quarters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 19:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they are useful in many more situations. You just need to focus on staying hidden and flanking much more to get right next to the enemy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 19:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edited post to state the fact I actually have not used the M320 buck as much as I should have. I don't really know much about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 17:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoover Dam! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 17:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before the nerf it was like this. Now it takes 5 body shots to kill someone. 2 with pump shotguns. They are only useful if you can splash damage your way to victory. If your target is in the open you will usually lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 17:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it is not that awesome because in BC2 it was amazing. I had so much fun with it in BC2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 15:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the BtK weapons are bugged and have unlocked attachments they should not have. That is why the MK3A1 "has" a suppressor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guide to Shotguns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 03:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shotguns are awesome. In the right circumstances you can take down many enemies very quickly. In the wrong circumstances you will be killed quickly. Each shotgun fills a specific role and has different play styles.

**Ammunition**

**NOTE: All shotguns give 240% damage in the head, 100% damage for body and arm shots, and 90% damage for legs.**

**Buckshot**

The default ammo for all shotguns. Each shell has 12 pellets (except for the MK3A1) and each pellet gives 20 damage up to 5 meters and then drops off to 6 damage at 25 meters.

Usually this is the go to ammo for me. When used in the proper situation (up close) an enemy goes down fairly quickly.

**Flechette**

The first ammo unlock for all shotguns (except the DAO which comes with it and the M320 which only has buckshot). Also has 12 arrows in each shell (except for the MK3A1) and each arrow gives 14.3 damage out to 12 meters and then drops off to 8.4 damage at 25 meters.

I do not use this ammo as much because it deals less damage up close. However it does deal more damage farther away.

**Frag**

The second ammo unlock for all shotguns (except the M320). Fires an explosive round at the target. For pump shotguns it gives 60 damage up to 9 meters then drops down to 10 damage at 40 meters. For semi auto and auto shotguns it gives 20 damage at 9 meters and then drops down to 10 damage at 40 meters. Frag rounds also deal blast 30 blast damage up to 3 meters away. However blast damage and direct damage do not compound. If you directly hit your target they will only receive the direct damage and no blast damage.

EDIT: The blast damage can also hurt you if you are too close. If you hit a wall or person that is really close to you, you will be damaged. Also the explosive damage lingers around for a second or two so if you wander into an area you just shot at you may still be damaged.

It was awesome with semi autos and full autos before it was nerfed. I do not use it as much now, if at all because direct damage is so small now. (It takes 5 body shots to kill somebody).

**Slug**

The last ammo unlock for all shotguns (except the M320). Fires a large metal slug at the target. For pump shotguns it gives 100 damage up to 9 meters and then drops off to 34 damage at 40 meters. For semi auto and auto shotguns it gives 50 damage at 9 meters and then drops off to 10 damage at 40 meters.

Rarely use this one. It requires very good aim because you are only firing 1 "bullet" at somebody and it takes a longer time for you to fire again than most other guns.

**Pump Shotguns**

**NOTE: Pump shotguns have a smaller cone of 2.0 compared to the cone of 4.0 for semi auto and auto shotguns. This means your bullets travel closer together and you will deal more damage at range. (On http://symthic.com it only says that this applies to the 870MCS but it probably also applies to the other pump shotguns).**

**870MCS**

Takes up the primary slot, and is an all kit weapon. It takes 0.55 seconds between shots. It has a reload time of 0.67 seconds (per shell) and an empty reload time of 1.3 seconds (the first round you reload will take 1.3 seconds, every other shell will take 0.67). It is unlocked at rank 1. Because the cone is smaller it will give more damage farther away than the semi auto and auto shotguns. It however takes more time to fire between shots so getting in close and not missing when firing is very important. This shotgun also has the added bonus of being able to stop the reload action and fire. If you are reloading and you see an enemy you can stop the reload and fire again.

This gun is best used in close quarters when you behind the enemy, if you can surprise your target you can finish them off quickly and move to the next one. If somebody gets too close to you, you can take them out quickly.

**M320 Buck**

Assualt only. Yes the M320 has a buckshot option. It is unlocked with 10 kills with the M320 frag (M320 is unlocked with 11,000 assault score). It should behave like a pump action shotgun but I am not sure. It takes a long time to fire between shots (same reload time as the M320 frag and smoke). It can be used with an underslung rail which allows it to have the same scope you are using for your assault rifle, the scope that comes with it is the same as the M320 frag and smoke scope. Would not recommend because of the slow reload time and the fact there are better options for shotguns. It its ammo also count as a frag so more ammo is obtained by using the frag perk, not the ammo perk. Has 4 rounds with no frag perk and 7 rounds with frag perk.

EDIT: I have not used the M320 Buck as much. Apparently it is better than I have said. Go have fun and try it out.

**M26 MASS**

Assault only. This is an interesting shotgun. It is listed as a semi auto shotgun in Battlelog but it feels like a pump shotgun. You pump the shotgun in game and I have also killed people at longer ranges than other semi auto shotguns so I assume it behaves like a pump shotgun in game. Can also be used with the underslung rail. Much better than the M320 buckshot. It is also much more quiet than other shotguns so it is great if you can get behind the enemy. Has 5 + 1 rounds and has 18 extra shells for a total of 24. Squad ammo gives it 30 extra rounds. It is unlocked with 38,000 assault score.

This is a really fun shotgun to use. It does replace the medic pack however. Great to use in close range situations. Perfect for maps that have long range and short range encounters (you can have an assault rifle and also carry the MASS).

**Semi Auto Shotguns**

**NOTE: All semi auto shotguns fire at 200 RPM and have a cone of 4.0.**

**M1014**

Fun shotgun to use. Has 4 + 1 rounds without extended mags and 6 + 1 with extended rounds. It has a reload rate of 0.55 seconds when not empty and 1 second when empty. It is unlocked at rank 22. It behaves like the 870MCS in that you can stop the reload animation and start firing again. That is what makes this gun fun to use. It is great for running into the action and getting up close and personal with the enemy. If you need to reload you can start reloading but then start firing again whenever you need to.

**SAIGA 12K**

Has 5 + 1 rounds without extended mags and 8 + 1 rounds with. It has a reload rate 2.2 seconds when not empty and 3.5 seconds when empty. It is unlocked at rank 34. I do not see a big reason to use this shotgun. It does not have any special feature which makes it awesome or fun to use. Would not recommend.

**DAO-12**

Also a fun shotgun to use. Has 7 + 1 rounds without extended mags and has 11 + 1 rounds with extended mags. It comes with the Physical Warfare Pack but is also unlocked at rank 38. Has a reload time of 0.69 seconds when not empty and 2.15 seconds when empty. It behaves like the M1014 and the 870MCS in the fact that you can stop the reload animation and start firing again when needed. Also good for running into the action and getting up close to the enemy.

**Auto Shotguns**

**USAS-12**

A very fun weapon to use. It fires at a rate of 275 RPM, has 5 + 1 rounds without extended mags, and 10 + 1 with extended mags. It is unlocked at rank 43. This weapon is used for crowd control, if there are multiple enemies bunched up in a small area you can take them down quickly and easily.

This was very fun and very overpowered when used with frag rounds before they were nerfed. (Yes, I was one of the people using, USAS, frag rounds, and IRNV) I normally use buckshot with it now.

**MK3A1**

Looks awesome, sounds awesome, isn't that awesome to use. It is similar to the USAS but it only fires at 255 RPM and has the same amount of rounds as the USAS. Unlike all other shotguns it only fires 9 pellets instead of 12 pellets. It also seems to be bugged in game which gives it a higher spread than the USAS. I see no reason to use this shotgun. Like the SAIGA it has nothing to make it stand out. To unlock you need 10 Kills with the PP-19, 5 Kills with the DPV Jeep, 10 Kills with the BTR-90 APC, 2 Hours played on Sharqi Peninsula, and 2 Hours played on Gulf of Oman. Before you can unlock this weapon you must also unlock the PP-19 which requires you to, ARM 10 MCOM stations, get 10 Flag captures, and play 2 hours on Strike at Karkand.

Overall shotguns are awesome. I got my first recon service star with only shotguns and PDW's. I never touched a sniper rifle when getting the first service star (aggressive recon FTW). They need to be used in close quarter situations and you need to aim well. If used in the right situation you will dominate the battlefield.

Happy shooting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 00:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love all shotguns (also PDW's). I have service stars for all of them and 10 service stars for the USAS (yes yes  #3232;\_ #3232;). Frag rounds were awesome (and overpowered) before they were nerfed. Now they really aren't scary unless you get attacked from the back. Each shotgun fits a certain role which is awesome (except for the SAIGA, doesn't seem like there is any reason to use it).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 00:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. It is much harder to hit somebody with the actual round than to just hit around them at a certain range. Semi auto and full auto frag rounds only give 20 damage at 10 meters and drop down to 10 damage at 40. They got a crazy nerf. (The blast damage is 30. I would trade blast damage for more direct damage in a heartbeat.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-31 07:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic. A++. Would Leo again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-31 04:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the accessories are supposed to be accessories, they modify your play style or you add accessories on to fit your play style, you like "running and gunning" behind enemy lines, add a laser sight and a suppressor. Want to defend a MCOM, add a flash suppressor and bipod. Scopes are just a matter of preference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-31 00:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...if it was possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-30 14:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes you don't even have to fire a shot. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RULv6HbgEjY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-29 01:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "They are on me like flies on shit over here!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-28 18:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gets annoying when 5 stingers and 2 soflam's are trying to lock on to you though :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-27 18:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Windows 7. Windows Developer Preview (Windows 8) is pretty awesome too. It is the main OS on my laptop right now (I had Vista on it before).

2. Windows Phone 7. Made a couple of apps for the platform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-25 18:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats my battlelog...what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 Dr. Pepper codes to give away! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-25 18:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be giving away 3 Dr. Pepper codes today. Comment in this thread by [10:00 PM EST](http://www.timeanddate.com/worldclock/converter.html) with a link to your Battlelog profile, like [this](http://battlelog.battlefield.com/bf3/user/subject4635/).

I will be using random.org to choose winners at 10 PM. Post more than once and you will be disqualified. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Listen to your environment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-25 02:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sound in Battlefield 3 is really good, it allows you to listen for the enemy while looking for him. If you are trying to capture a flag and you know an enemy is somewhere listen for him reloading, shouting, or moving around (footstep sounds sometimes are not that loud or do not work at all sometimes). You can throw a grenade and if it lands near them they will yell something about a grenade.

You can also listen for recon devices. The spawn beacon will make a beeping sound. If you are sneaking up on an area listen for a T-UGS or a MAV. They will make one beeping noise if no enemy is near it and another beeping noise if an enemy is near it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-25 02:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why it did not happen. http://www.reddit.com/r/battlefield3/comments/n9edz/there_needs_to_be_a_transport_vehicle_and_pistol/c37edej </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-24 16:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still show up on the map, your soldier still calls out enemies going through the smoke, playing hardcore does not just automatically fix everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-23 07:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess they don't believe in gravity either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 02:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, on PS3 it has 14 rounds but on PC it has 11 with extended mag. I am not sure about PC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 00:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep I just checked and the MK3A1 and the USAS have the same amount of ammo with no extended mags and extended mags. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any reason to use the MK3A1 over the USAS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 00:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~The only thing the MK3A1 has going for it is the extra bullet. With extended mags they have the same amount of ammo.~~ **EDIT: They both have the same amount of rounds.** The MK3A1 shoots slower than the USAS and also seems to have more spread than the USAS. It also has a longer reload time than the USAS. It seems there are no advantages to the MK3A1 over the USAS. Is it worth using? **EDIT 2: Just found out the MK3A1 only fires 9 pellets instead of 12 when using buckshot.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Play Metro Rush As Attackers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-20 17:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-19 18:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry it was not completely deadline related.

http://www.reddit.com/r/battlefield3/comments/n9edz/there_needs_to_be_a_transport_vehicle_and_pistol/c37edej </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a difference between a recon and a sniper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-19 17:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sniper class has to very different play styles. You can either be a sniper, the style people usually think of when they see a recon, or an actual recon. Many snipers I see just camp out somewhere far away from the objectives with a spawn beacon and a motion sensor. Yes there are some snipers who can actually hit targets without missing 3 times first and that are an asset to their team.

Then there are the recons, people who use a PDW or a shotgun and are on the front lines. Sneaking around, not blowing up tanks because recons do not have C4, capping points, spotting people, setting up a MAV at a point right before the rest of the squad tries to take it. These people are often a great asset to their team if played correctly.

Then we also have subsets of those play styles. A mobile sniper can still be moving around, setting up at points before their squad gets there and proving support and spotting when they are capturing. An aggressive recon can have a sniper rifle but can be on the front lines sniping up close, taking out objectives and enemies.

My favorite time to be a recon is on rush, especially Metro rush (8 v 8). I can flank and get behind the enemy, plant a spawn beacon behind their lines, get to the MCOM and plant a motion sensor, arm it, then defend it from the waves of enemies with my shotgun or PDW, always knowing where they are. I got my recon service star without even touching a sniper rifle.

We all sometimes just want to stay back and snipe people, after I got the M98B I did this, but when you play he recon class or see a recon don't just assume sniper, you can actually be a great asset to your team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-19 17:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They wanted to have customizable pistols but deadlines had to be met so they could not put it in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-19 17:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that you can spot through smoke. Pop a smoke an press Q to see enemies or when you see smoke press Q to spot and then kill the enemies going through it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-19 17:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I think it would be better to only get the revive points when they stand up or accept the revive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lag Spikes in Battlefield 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-19 01:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-18 15:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, we lost the round with 1 MCOM left (in the TV station). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arm and Destroy both MCOM's with 1 ticket left </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-17 23:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-16 02:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he was capping Forest on Capsian Border it looked fucking amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-14 03:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very Portable Devices. Smartphones and tablets. Smartphones are getting better and better and tablets are now getting big. Windows 8 will probably change the tablet market because it is now being built for touch and will have more power than any tablet out there (the x86 and x64 versions).

These portable devices will need apps and app development is really big right now. Making apps is getting easier and easier, it is just about getting noticed. Games are getting smaller and are being played for only 5-10 minutes on the bus or on the subway.

The final thing is really the internet. **Everything** is being connected to the internet. CD are now being replaced by digital downloads. New netbooks and laptops are not being installed with CD drives. The last time I used a CD was when I first got my computer about 6 months ago to re install my old games. Every portable device will be connected to the internet, to each other. Mobile service providers (cellphone companies) are going to do very well by offering services to these devices. Actual 4G will push us into the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-13 23:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be awesome to see this for all guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-10 19:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOOOOOVE Providence, NY. I visit there all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-09 05:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear this so much at my school ( I go to a prep school). It makes me want to hurt people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-07 02:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's dungeons all the way down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-02 23:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metro Rush Assault (8 v 8 works the best)

* General Tip: Arm as quickly as possible and arm both objectives at the same time.

* General Tip: Listen for the enemy disarming the charge. If they are you can usually rush in and kill them because they are distracted and stop the disarm.



First Set of Objectives - Rush down the right side along the path right of B or in the water right along the ground so it is harder to see you. Usually the defenders rush middle. When you are just past B along the path stay far right, right of the rocks and set up a spawn beacon right before the out of bounds area, usually on the path not the grass. Next 1 or 2 players should watch defender spawn while the rest of the squad checks the area and goes for B. To go for A run right along the defender out of bounds area and check the bridge, the rocks on the left (between A and B), and right of the bridge. When defending the objective stay in front of the objectives (closer to defender spawn) because you want to see them first.

Second Set of Objectives - Rush down the right side tunnel (above the subway) and check for any enemies in the subway area. Run across to the middle tunnel or go all the way across and go through the boarded up area. If in the middle tunnel take the first left to be right before the subway cars on the left. Place a spawn beacon right before the cars on the right side of that tunnel right behind the wall. Usually the enemy is past you by now so you can either run for the middle escalators or run straight for A. Arm A and you can run right for B because you are on the escalators. Defend B from on top of the stairs and check the escalator for enemies. With A some people can camp in the bathroom but some other people should be checking for enemies constantly from their spawn. Also one person can stay left A and left of the subway cars and look right though the A bathroom to kill enemies who are entering.

Third Set of Objectives - To go for B run to the right side stairs and go through the right hallway. Arm B. If there are many enemies over there then run right next to that hallway on the wall right of the middle escalator. You can get around the enemy team and shoot them in the back and then arm B. The best way to arm A is to either run up the first escalators and go straight for A while another squad is going up the middle escalators and checking for enemies from there. You can also attack A from the middle escalators.

Last Set of Objectives - Exit the metro building from either the right or left doors. The center ones usually get you killed. To attack A get into the left side building and run around to the defender facing side. Place a spawn beacon somewhere on that side. Break though the wood and arm A. You can leave the building and sit right inside the stairwell right next to the MCOM or go through the other set of windows next to the MCOM and listen to enemies disarm the MCOM from there. If they are rush in and kill them. To attack B either go down the far left set of stairs or go down the far right street. Run all the way across to the bushes and check for enemies in the MCOM area and in their spawn. Make sure it is clear and arm B. Then go back into the bush area and kill enemies that go for the MCOM. When attacking B it is also very helpful to have people in the buildings facing the defender  spawn high up killing enemies who are going for the MCOM. The earlier you kill them the better it is.

GOOD LUCK AND HAVE FUN!

For defenders it really just consists of continuous movement and never staying in the same place. Only one or two people should try to get behind the enemy and shoot them in the back. If you don't find anybody then keep going towards an objective to see if the enemy is closer to the objective than you think. If the MCOM is armed and you are not behind the enemy go straight for the MCOM and kill any enemies you see along the way. Don't kill the enemies first. The priority is the MCOM. If you are behind the enemy run your usual path behind the enemy, don't go straight for the MCOM. You will usually surprise the enemy who is defending your spawn. When somebody is disarming defend them at all costs. The MCOM is the most important thing, not your KDR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-02 22:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you first join a game from Battlelog right when Battlefield opens on the taskbar you can click it and watch the whole loading process, this also allows you to listen to the map loading music for longer because it usually takes longer to load a map for the first time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-01 01:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a very large Sony Internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-30 21:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If FiOS is available in your area (it isn't in all areas) then go for it. My family was paying about the same price for Cox before as before we are paying for FiOS now. Faster internet (usually better than advertised speeds), more TV channels, good phone service. Do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  G  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-29 23:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-29 23:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's destroyed on respawn so you can't have 5 spawn points and 20 t-ugs or mavs laying around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-29 23:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am pretty sure the rockets from helicopters provide "suppression". I have never gotten supression points but when I am getting shot by a helicopter's rockets (not gunner bullets) it is really chaotic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-28 23:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So maybe DICE should make it easier to spot people without IRNV. Make the shadows less dark, make people stand out more. I don't want to play a game where I run around and just cap points and don't shoot anybody (I cap many points but I like killing people too). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-19 00:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alto Saxophone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-18 06:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks really nice. Really want to see this finished! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-17 01:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should probably tell administration about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you are done with your computer do you shut down, hibernate, sleep, or leave it on and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-15 23:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-15 02:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also the higher helicopter has more room to speed up and get closer to their target. If you are close enough if you fire heat seekers the flares will do nothing to distract the missiles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-14 22:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=20ZYkYiCdrg#t=275s

This explains the process. Just wanted to provide a little more context. (Also watch the whole series of videos, really great presentation!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-09 21:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rhode Island! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-08 06:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grinding allowed, no hands below the waist. Not very crazy dances. Chaperons usually are weirded out by how we dance no matter what. Grinding is also pretty much the norm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-08 03:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-07 22:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AA3 is really buggy still which takes away from the fun :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-07 22:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trees on the outskirts of Caspian Border (Battlefield 3). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-07 22:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been doing this too. I would much rather have a computer science major from a good college. I applied to Northeastern because I know they have Computer Science as a major but you can pair it with Game Design in their Arts section. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-07 05:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Windows Phone :D I got a HTC Surround about a week after they launched. Windows phone is an awesome OS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-07 05:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I applied to 3 early, need to send in another one for 11/11 early then probably 4-6 more regular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-07 05:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject4635 PC I play a lot so I should be on most of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-06 20:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I'm just happy resolutions that low are even in the game. BC2 sure didn't have 800x600 (what I'm playing at now). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-06 17:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a B in AP Calc (AB) but that is because I got a 54 on my first test. Without that first test I would have an A-. I know it's not really failing but it still sucks :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-06 17:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Battlefield 3 Limited Edition :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-03 23:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dxtory has 0 performance hit though which makes it bearable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 11:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really know what can and cannot lock on with below radar but if you fly low and far off the map (behind the hills, or near the fires in Caspian) you should not get locked onto. Their lock on range only goes so far. This world apply to Kharg Island as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 05:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just let go of throttle and level off to slow down when attacking tanks. I know a little power is needed to stay up but really I just know when to press things. It's hard to describe. Maybe I could get a keypress recorder to show what I am pressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 04:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was all in one match. The first clip is when i first got in and the last clip is near the end (look at the ticket count). I was rushing and I could make a better video but I just wanted to get something out quickly. This was a Caspian Border Conquest Large 16/16 player server. If you want me to make another video I will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 04:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keyboard and mouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 03:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Refer to the video I just made. I think you can see how I fly.

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KcpmJvsb114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 03:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the video I made of me flying.

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KcpmJvsb114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 03:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> P.s. If someone has all of the chopper unlocks I have a few questions.

I made this [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/battlefield3/comments/lvsum/i_am_a_attack_helicopter_pilot_with_all_the/). Ask away :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 01:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I can see how a gamepad would be hard to fly helicopter (Yes I do play on PC). However using a forward speed technique also can work. If you can spot your target from far away enough then if you aim well enough you can hit them while flying towards them pretty fast. You really need to make sure you can turn around quick enough after roaring past them because usually they will jump out and repair. Also if they are moving then it is also harder because you have to lead your shots. Practicing on the second Co-Op mission (Fire From the Sky) as pilot is a good idea. It lets you fight infantry, tanks, and AA. I will try to make a video of me flying helicopter ASAP so you can see my technique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 01:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your preferred set up as pilot / gunner?

Pilot

* Upgrade: Air Radar
* Gadget: Extinguisher
* Weapon: Heat Seekers

Gunner

* Upgrade: Maintenance
* Gadget: Thermal Optics
* Weapon: TV Missile

Is it worth giving up flares for another upgrade, or is flares a must have?

The three gadgets for pilot are IR Flares, Extinguisher, and ECM Jammer. ECM Jammer seems to do nothing so don't use that. Flares are nice but they really can't help you when you are getting hit by bullets (from a tank, or AA, or jet). Once you get down below 50% you have to bail or land and repair. With extinguisher you run the risk of being taken down really quickly with heat seekers if you get locked on to twice and get fired upon really quickly. Usually you get hit with two missiles or one stinger missile and get disabled. Then you can pop extinguisher and fly away really quickly and let your helicopter heal itself. Extinguisher usually reloads when your helicopter gets to about 80% without getting hit again. It really just helps you stay in the air longer than IR Flares.

And if so should both have flares or just one?

I think that is up to you and your gunner. If you are actually cooperating and planning out your loadouts (for me its hard to find somebody to do that) it is up to what you want. The gunner gadgets are IR Flares, Zoom Optics, and Thermal Optics. If you can pick out people and tanks in the map easily then the gunner should use IR Flares. Thermal Optics makes it really easy to see people though so I personally use that. I do not know if gunner and pilot have flares then the helicopter has two sets. I would think not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 01:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 01:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your favorite setup?

Pilot

* Upgrade: Air Radar
* Gadget: Extinguisher
* Weapon: Heat Seekers

Gunner

* Upgrade: Maintenance
* Gadget: Thermal Optics
* Weapon: TV Missile

What setup gets you the most points?

The one I use currently :D . For pilot air radar lets me see all vehicles within a certain area which is really nice. Extinguisher lets me stay in the air longer than flares do. If I get down below 50% I can pop extinguisher and heal up somewhere away from the action. With IR Flares you have to land and repair once you get down past 50%. Heat Seekers are the only weapon for the pilot and that is a must.

For gunner maintenance helps the helicopter recover faster which helps out. Thermal optics light up any vehicle and person (they show up as white). This really helps with people cause it is hard to see them usually when flying. TV Missile is the last unlock and it has a further range than guided missiles and can travel a further distance than guided missiles. You don't have to be as close to your target to hit it. Use guided missiles when you don't have TV missiles.

What one tip helped you get all teh unlocks?

Practice. I first learned how to fly during the second CO-OP mission. My partner went AFK and I did the whole mission in the pilot seat. After that I just kept playing on a Caspian Border only server. Getting all the unlocks. One thing that you really need to get down is control of the helicopter. Being able to slowly hover over to a tank unleash a volley of rockets behind it disabling it, flying past it and quickly turning around, firing another volley of rockets to finish it off is a really good skill to learn. (This also helps with those pesky AA tanks, sneak up behind it and doing this technique helps take them down quickly without really damaging yourself).

How do all-unlocked choppers stand up to all-unlocked jets?

I don't really know because I don't think I have fought an all-unlocked jet. However jets can be annoying if they see you from far away. The best tactic is to get down low and fly fast in the direction the jet is coming from. They turn around slowly so if you fly under them going in the opposite direction as them, they usually lose sight of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a Attack Helicopter Pilot with all the unlocks. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 00:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inspiration from [this](http://www.reddit.com/r/battlefield3/comments/lvl6i/i_am_a_tank_driver_with_all_the_unlocks_ama/). Ask away. [My Battlelog profile.](http://battlelog.battlefield.com/bf3/user/subject4635/)

EDIT: Heading to bed now. Will answer any more later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 00:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be advised! Helicopters pilots can equip Laser Painter and it works the same as the SOFLAM! (Painting targets for javelin and such). Over! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 00:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not my video. Was retweeted by Crash7800. http://twitter.com/crash7800/status/131138729518706690 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The definition of PTFO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 00:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-31 23:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only tactic that seems to work for that is to know exactly where it is and then sneak up behind it. I've been playing on Caspian Border a lot so if you die to it and it is camping out in a field fly on the far outskirts (behind the hills) and sneak up on it. Then when attacking make sure you disable it in the first volley of rockets. Reload and hit it again. That should take care of it. A good AA gunner will probably fuck your shit up what ever you try to do :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-31 23:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep it only took me about 10 hours logged in an attack helicopter to unlock everything. That's not too long. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-27 04:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Did anybody actually think about killing Cole before shooting him or did you just shoot him. I actually stopped and didn't shoot him the first time and died. Or did anybody not care and just shoot and go on with the game?](/spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-27 04:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [At the very end with Dima it looks like he is going to commit suicide but then he says you can only die once which probably means you must die for the right reasons. Then he hears the knock at his door. He was probably expecting it.](/spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-26 05:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was awesome and fucking WTF at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-26 04:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of sat there in shock over what happened in single player. Then I said hooray when I saw crash7800's name in the credits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-25 02:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked 2 times before to get my game transferred from one of my accounts to the other but it seems like the third time worked! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Persistence pays off in EA support chats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-25 02:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-20 23:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the Metro UI inspired design. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-20 02:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [That is all.](http://i.imgur.com/SJgWn.jpg)

[Here is another version.](http://i.imgur.com/SeVo3.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-19 00:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a newer version of the game? It had the vehicle on Metro. Also I went back to check for a beta/alpha bar on the top and it was covered up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trailer I made from Battlefield 3 DICE videos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-18 20:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-18 05:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played with the HD5450. Was fine for me. Probably not fine for other people. But I still enjoyed it. Not cancelling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-17 05:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OS: Windows 7 64bit

CPU: AMD Phenom II X4 830 @ 2.80 GHz

RAM: 8GB

GPU: ATI Radeon HD 5450 with 2GB RAM

Running at all low settings, 800x600, at 30 FPS.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-16 15:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a good game when it was closed beta and early open beta. There were no pay to win weapons. I watched a video Ben Cousins gave about why they changed from their balanced weapon shop to a pay to win weapon shop.

Basically they weren't making enough money and EA was going to shut their whole studio down if they didn't start making more money. They really didn't want to put in pay to win weapons. Their original plan was to only put in cosmetic items for pay but they really didn't want to lose their jobs either so they put in the pay to win weapons. After that there was some backlash but they made much much more money.

It's still fun to play every once in a while but I wouldn't spend money on that game. I have BF3 to look forward to :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would anybody else want this as the loading screen song for Gulf of Oman in BF3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-14 22:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
