<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2599</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recent leak of Coca-Cola Execs emails reveal Coca-Colas Policy Priorities. Surprise! Your friendly, neighbor soda company is actually lobbying against your health and environment protections. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Face Recognition Systems Threaten the Privacy of Millions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VeraCrypt has been audited. Here are the results. Also Ask Us Anything! -OSTIF  (x-post /r/privacy) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Appeal Court Revives Lawyer's Lawsuit Against The NSA's Email Dragnet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 07:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Project Include drops Y Combinator as Peter Thiel pledges $1.25m to Trump in wake of Trumps sexual misconduct revelations; Ellen Pao says group that pushes for inclusion in tech is ending its relationship with Thiel, a part-time partner, since their values are not aligned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK security agencies unlawfully collected data for 17 years, court rules. Investigatory powers tribunal says secret collection of citizens personal data breached human rights law. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 20:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Airbnb is driving up the rent in your urban neighborhood. Elizabeth Warren is right. Unless this trend reverses, our cities will become cheap places to stay for tourists  and unaffordable for the rest of us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 20:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Airbnb is driving up the rent in your urban neighborhood. Elizabeth Warren is right. Unless this trend reverses, our cities will become cheap places to stay for tourists  and unaffordable for the rest of us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 20:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook education software spurs privacy fears  Im not comfortable with having my kids personally identifiable information going to I dont even know where, to be used for Im not sure what. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Psychologist Analyzes Donald Trumps Personality. Narcissism, disagreeableness, grandiosityhow Trumps extraordinary personality might shape his possible presidency. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 00:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Alt-Right Was Conjured Out of Pearl Clutching and Media Attention </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 00:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Alt-Right Was Conjured Out of Pearl Clutching   Media Attention </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 00:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do Not Resist: The Police Militarization Documentary Everyone Should See </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 21:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wealthy San Francisco tech investors  Sequoia Capitals Michael Moritz, investors Ron Conway   William Oberndorf  bankroll bid to ban homeless camps. The proposed law would ban tent encampments from San Franciscos sidewalks  a visceral reminder of the citys gaping inequality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beverage-Industry Playbook Expands as Big Soda Spends Large to Defeat Oakland   SF Taxes. Everything theyre putting out is a lie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beverage-Industry Playbook Expands as Big Soda Spends Large to Defeat Oakland   SF Taxes. Everything theyre putting out is a lie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Tallinn experiment: what happens when a city makes public transport free? Has Estonias scheme achieved its ambitions of reducing traffic and saving people money? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 23:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Security Economics of the Internet of Things  IoT Will Require International Govt Rules to Save Internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 20:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Security Economics of the Internet of Things  IoT Will Require International Govt Rules to Save Internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 20:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The lies Trump told this week: taxes, bankruptcy and the Great Depression of the 1990s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Francisco Bay Guardian ENDORSEMENTS! The case for 6 progressive supes, Kim for state Senate Our in-depth analysis of 16 state   24 local initiatives Yes on D, H, L   M. No on P, Q   O. Relax, you can now vote in peace! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 06:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to the machine  Yahoo mail scanning exposes another US spy tool; Surveillance by machine doesn't count as spying unless youre guilty, right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to the machine  Yahoo mail scanning exposes another US spy tool; Surveillance by machine doesn't count as spying unless youre guilty, right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-NSA Hacker Creates Tool To Warn You Of Webcam Spies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 21:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yahoo email surveillance: who approved the secret scanning program? FISA court and FBI are possibilities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yahoo email surveillance: who approved the secret scanning program? FISA court and FBI are possibilities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yahoo email scanning prompts European ire; Europe questions whether EU citizens' data compromised, could help derail a new trans-Atlantic data sharing deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYTimes Editorial comes out in favor of Oakland   SF Soda Tax: More soda taxes and less soda drinking will make for a healthier country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYTimes Editorial comes out in favor of Oakland   SF Soda Tax: More soda taxes and less soda drinking will make for a healthier country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYTimes Editorial comes out in favor of Oakland   SF Soda Tax: More soda taxes and less soda drinking will make for a healthier country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yahoo email scanning prompts European ire; Europe questions whether EU citizens' data compromised, could help derail a new trans-Atlantic data sharing deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yahoo email scanning prompts European ire; Europe questions whether EU citizens' data compromised, could help derail a new trans-Atlantic data sharing deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yahoo email scanning prompts European ire; Europe questions whether EU citizens' data compromised, could help derail a new trans-Atlantic data sharing deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Revealed: The FBIs Secret Methods for Recruiting Informants at the Border </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 22:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Revealed: The FBIs Secret Methods for Recruiting Informants at the Border </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 22:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA Contractor Arrested in Possible New Theft of Secrets  Second NSA Leak in Three Years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 20:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA Contractor Arrested in Possible New Theft of Secrets  Classified Computer Codes Developed to Hack into the Networks of Foreign Governments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 20:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (We now know that a Yahoo account is a toxic surveillance liability so) Delete Your Yahoo Account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 20:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trevor Timm: Yahoo may have let the government spy on emails. Now will we embrace encryption? Not only would this likely violate the fourth amendment; giving the NSA or the FBI a backdoor into a tech companys innards could let hackers in too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 00:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yahoo may have let the government spy on emails. Now will we embrace encryption? Not only would this likely violate the fourth amendment; giving the NSA or the FBI a backdoor into a tech companys innards could let hackers in too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 00:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yahoo secretly monitored emails on behalf of the US government. Company complied with a classified directive, scanning hundreds of millions of Yahoo Mail accounts at the behest of NSA or FBI, say former employees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 21:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brexit: Theresa May prioritises immigration curbs over single market; Prime minister tells Tory conference that controlling immigration would be key basis for departure from EU. May: We are not leaving the European Union only to give up control of immigration again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 01:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buk at bedtime: Russian firm launches missile-launcher child's bed; CaroBus future defenders of the motherland range salutes Buk of the kind used to shoot down Malaysia airlines flight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 01:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowden disclosures helped reverse expansion of Patriot Act provision. Leaks in 2013 helped shift FBI away from using controversial Section 215 to acquire email and other metadata, US justice department watchdog finds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowden disclosures helped reverse expansion of Patriot Act provision. Leaks in 2013 helped shift FBI away from using controversial Section 215 to acquire email and other metadata, US justice department watchdog finds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Soda-Tax Battle Bubbles Up in San Francisco Bay Area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Soda-Tax Battle Bubbles Up in San Francisco Bay Area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five EFF Tools to Help You Protect Yourself Online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 20:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Logs Your iMessage Contacts  and May Share Them With Police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Oakland Almost Became an Orwellian Surveillance Cityand Citizens Stopped It From Happening. Pay attention. Watch the agenda. Watch what local govt is doing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 22:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Oakland Almost Became an Orwellian Surveillance Cityand Citizens Stopped It From Happening. Pay attention. Watch the agenda. Watch what local govt is doing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 22:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Costly campaigns could turn out most expensive in our historythanks to four high-profile ballot measures; Two Oakland store owners regret being included by No on HH for their anti-Soda Tax ads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 21:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video claiming drilling into iPhone 7 will reveal hidden headphone port goes viral. Prank video destroying new Apple smartphone receives 10m views, with some seemingly tricked into making 3.5mm hole in the bottom of their devices. (Duh: Dont do this!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 20:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian town steams over Nestl bid to control local spring water well. Activists in Centre Wellington plan to block Ontario pump tests after bottled-water makers overtook communitys attempt to secure long-term water source </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 17:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is Palmer Luckey, and why is he funding pro-Trump trolls? Under the name NimbleRichMan, Oculus founder secretly funded Reddit users dedicated to electing Trump by flooding threads with negative Clinton memes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 07:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is Palmer Luckey, and why is he funding pro-Trump trolls? Under the name NimbleRichMan, Oculus founder secretly funded Reddit users dedicated to electing Trump by flooding threads with negative Clinton memes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 07:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VR Devs Pull Support for Oculus Rift Until Palmer Luckey Steps Down </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 22:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret report reveals: German BND also uses XKEYSCORE for data collection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 21:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret report reveals: German BND also uses XKEYSCORE for data collection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 21:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Palmer Luckey: The Facebook Near Billionaire Secretly Funding Trumps Meme Machine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 11:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Palantir Is Taking Over New York City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 08:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Palantir Is Taking Over New York City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 08:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google backs off on previously announced Allo privacy feature; The app will log conversations, use cleartext chat, by default after all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 00:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] How large would a bowl of Skittles have to be to hold 3.65 billion candies? According to some, our lives may very well depend on a prompt answer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 07:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The son of [a noted statistics expert](https://twitter.com/donaldjtrumpjr/status/778016283342307328) (Trump Tweet Trigger Warning) compared eating a Skittles candy to our odds of experiencing Death-By-Immigrant-Terrorist. Presumably, a *horrible* death-by-immigrant-terrorist, versus say, a puppy avalanche.

Yet, [the odds of this are quite low](http://object.cato.org/sites/cato.org/files/pubs/pdf/pa798_1_1.pdf) (PDF), 3,640,000,000:1 to be exact, according to the Cato Institute. 

So, how large would a bowl of Skittles have to be to hold 3.65 billion candies?

Let's say, a Skittles bag is 6oz of tangy, chewy goodness and these 25 pieces fill 1/4 of a cup.

3,650 million Skittles may require a bowl outside most of our scales of references (keep that waving hand **down**, Ms. Astronomer!). So for those unused to very large numbers, can you provide an equivalently sized object (e.g., a cow, a truck, a moon the size of Endor, etc.)

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Film Tells the Story of Edward Snowden; Here Are the Surveillance Programs He Helped Expose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 10:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WashPost Makes History: First Paper to Call for Prosecution of Its Own Source (After Accepting Pulitzer) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 00:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowdens bias is blatantbut Gordon-Levitt makes its message powerful; Proper technology treatment helps, but main star saves an otherwise rocky ship. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 21:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla disputes Mobileyes accusations, Mobileye shoots back; The sensor maker and the autonomous car maker are on the outs publicly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 21:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop Defending Soda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 09:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowden  Official Movie Site </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowden  Official Film Site </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oliver Stone on the Personal Inspiration Behind Snowden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazilian politician who led Rousseff impeachment is expelled from office amid perjury and corruption claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 10:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long-Secret Stingray Manuals Detail How Police Can Spy on Phones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Privacy Wars Are About to Get A Whole Lot Worse (Cory Doctorow) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Current International Trade Secretary Liam Fox: 'Fat and lazy' Britain is ill-prepared to secure future outside EU, business leaders have no appetite for the deals and exports needed to survive after the vote for Brexit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 05:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook fact-check: from Hillary's health to 9/11, the latest lies The Guardian read  bogus stories, clickbait and disinformation framed as legitimate trending news by one of the most powerful companies on Earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 05:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/Privacy: spreading the word to neophytes   experts for privacy, freedom   technology in a sometimes hostile world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 20:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, all 

Thanks **so** much. Really honored and grateful.

We are /r/privacy,

Dedicated to the intersection of technology, privacy   freedom in the digital world

With 67K subscribers. And it's *killing* us that we can't say "70K" because it rolls off the tongue *so* much better

I'm a Mod there.

A link to [our ad is here](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/51yomr/rprivacy_ad_v3_3rd_is_the_charm/)

I can't think of any longer term issue affecting Redditors than the issue of privacy, required to develop as people, as we share our evolving, uncensored thoughts with peers. Except for cats, but I don't mod /r/kittehpictures.

We're a busy Sub but we're very rigorous in keeping the tone and quality high, with no personal horribleness, promotion or flames. We put special care in ensuring newbies are welcome and encouraged to ask all the "stupid" questions we asked when we were in their position. And we're very glad to see neophytes become more aware of how to empower themselves and others as they learn more about being private while engaging in our digital (and physical!) worlds. We're also fortunate to have many experts and some journalists covering the digital security beat who contribute. We *really* work hard to be a home for both kinds of people.

We humbly think Reddit will become a better place as more people become aware of how to protect themselves and those they care for living in our digital world. We'd like to think /r/Privacy contributes to this. We'd like to contribute more. 

Please use our ad! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/privacy ad v3 (3rd is the charm!!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 19:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/Privacy ad, v2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 03:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ferguson protest leader Darren Seals shot and found dead in a burning car. Community mourned activist who protested the police killing of unarmed black teenager Michael Brown in 2014 and were troubled by parallels to a similar death. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 21:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hands on with the iPhone 7: A brief peek at the wireless future. The headphone jack conversation overshadows some really useful changes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 20:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/Privacy Reddit Ad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 02:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New Censorship  How did Google become the internets censor and master manipulator, blocking access to millions of websites? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 19:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the CIA made Google. Inside the secret network behind mass surveillance, endless war, and Skynet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the CIA made Google. Inside the secret network behind mass surveillance, endless war, and Skynet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free Isn't Freedom: Big Tech's Big Trick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free Isn't Freedom: Big Tech's Big Trick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Met police to start using spit hoods on suspects within weeks. Critics say hoods to protect officers from suspects who try to spit at or bite them are primitive, cruel and degrading </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 09:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaked Catalogue Reveals a Vast Array of Military Spy Gear Offered to US Police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 22:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So much for counter-phishing training: Half of people click anything sent to them. Even people who claimed to be aware of risks clicked out of curiosity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So much for counter-phishing training: Half of people click anything sent to them  Even people who claimed to be aware of risks clicked out of curiosity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook fires trending team, and Facebooks algorithms w/o humans goes crazy. Module pushes out false story about Foxs Megyn Kelly, offensive Ann Coulter headline and a story link about a man masturbating with a McDonalds sandwich </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 20:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook fires trending team, and Facebooks algorithms w/o humans goes crazy. Module pushes out false story about Foxs Megyn Kelly, offensive Ann Coulter headline and a story link about a man masturbating with a McDonalds sandwich </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 20:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theresa May acting like Tudor monarch in refusing MPs vote over Brexit. Prime ministers lawyers argue that parliamentary approval is not required to trigger Article 50. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 00:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL an academic study of 7000 internet cat video watchers found that viewing online cat media involves happenstance vs seeking but it improves mood. And the more one watches them, the more one enjoys Internet cats. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 20:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy 101: What makes you truly anonymous and leaves next to no trace in the internet? Advantages/disadvantages of using Proxy vs VPN vs TOR, vs TOR   VPN together </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 01:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy 101: What makes you truly anonymous and leaves next to no trace in the internet? Advantages/disadvantages of using Proxy vs VPN vs TOR, vs TOR   VPN together. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 01:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Ed Lee is unpopular. He is electoral poison  because his policies are less popular with the voters than almost anything anyone else is offering. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 20:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Companies Are Selling Advanced Spy Tech to Authoritarian Regimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 20:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Companies Are Selling Advanced Spy Tech to Authoritarian Regimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 20:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Companies Are Selling Advanced Spy Tech to Authoritarian Regimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 20:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Living in Australia comes with some caveats, such as the constant threat of being burgled by the worlds deadliest bird </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 23:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rock Against the TPP! Free concert   rally to protest the Trans-Pacific Partnership at SF Regency Ballroom. Featuring Jello Biafra, La Santa Cecilia,   more! RSVP to get your FREE ticket! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 01:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Equation Group Initial Impressions (A computer Science Prof Grades ShadowBrokers NSA Leak) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 20:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am Joseph Gordon-Levitt, just posted a short film I directed featuring Edward Snowden. So, AMA (/r/IAmA x-post) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 03:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ShadowBrokers NSA Leak Is Real, New Snowden Documents Confirm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 19:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowden speculates leak of NSA spying tools is tied to Russian DNC hack. Former NSA security scientist concurs exposure by Equation Group connected to DNC leak. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 00:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hack of NSA-Linked Group Signals a New, Cyber Cold War, But This Time Played In the Public, Not Shadows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 00:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bruce Schneier: That major NSA/Equation Group leak is real, probably by govt (Russia?)   done in 2013. A VERY bad day for NSA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bruce Schneier: That major NSA/Equation Group leak is real, probably by govt (Russia?)   done in 2013. A VERY bad day for NSA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bruce Schneier: That major NSA/Equation Group leak is real, probably by govt (Russia?)   done in 2013. A VERY bad day for NSA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian Cops Want a Law That Forces People to Hand Over Encryption Passwords </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 20:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian Cops Want a Law That Forces People to Hand Over Encryption Passwords </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 20:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian Cops Want a Law That Forces People to Hand Over Encryption Passwords </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 20:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [New Zealand] SIS targeted a group of pro-democracy campaigners it mistakenly thought were planning to overthrow the military government in Fiji; multiple intelligence agencies (GCSB, NSA) may have been illegally spying on this   other NZ pro-democracy groups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 23:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Raid  In Bungled Spying Operation, NSA Targeted Pro-Democracy Campaigner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 23:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hackers Say They Hacked NSA-Linked Group, Want 1 Million Bitcoins to Share More </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 22:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hackers Say They Hacked NSA-Linked Group, Want 1 Million Bitcoins to Share More </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 22:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit tells label it wont cough up IP address of prerelease music pirate. Music label has embarked on "an impermissible fishing expedition," Reddit says. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UKIP aide indicted in US on charges of blackmail and money laundering. George Cottrell allegedly agreed to launder money for undercover law enforcement posing as drug traffickers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 19:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Local Police In Canada Used Stingray' Surveillance Device Without a Warrant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 20:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Local Police In Canada Used Stingray' Surveillance Device Without a Warrant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 20:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumponomics: Giving the rich a gold-plated tax holiday. The plan is the lovechild of Reagan middle class-killing voodoo and George W. Bushs budget-busting tax cuts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brilliant UK documentary, The Mad World of Donald Trump (video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook Removes Potential Evidence of Police Brutality Too Readily, Activists Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 22:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump surrogate Scottie Nell Hughes: Ban abortion for Zika because birth defects are nothing new. And, We dont have the research, we dont know what Zika is going to do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 21:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marco Rubio: women with Zika should not be allowed abortions. Florida senator and former presidential candidate says he will err on the side of life even if babies will have microcephaly. Meanwhile GOP Gov Scott has spent $2m of $26m of anti-mosquito funds after prior 40% cut. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 21:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Director Oliver Stone talks about government spying in this new Snowden PSA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 07:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How   when did the Asian-American Model Minority representation take hold, and when? When did it fall into mass disfavor, and what caused this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 06:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US history books seem to go from a series of very negative stereotypes for Asian-Americans (i.e., Chinese-Americans during the building of the US railroads, or WWII Japanese-Americans being interned and their property largely forfeited) to becoming, collectively, a Model Minority. 

This conception is problematic for a variety of reasons, but is more positive than previous stereotypes. Yay?

Were there any significant events that caused this shift, or did it emerge organically? When did this shift happen? When did broader society realize it was offensive and what caused the term to fall into disfavor when it did? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI releases 18 hours of secret spy plane footage of Freddie Gray protests offering a rare, comprehensive view of the workings of govt surveillance operation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 06:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When briefed by senior intelligence official, Trump asked him three times during hourlong briefing, If we have nuclear weapons, why cant we use them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 03:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Motherboard guide to not getting hacked: basic steps that can keep you generally safe on the internet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 00:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Motherboard guide to not getting hacked: basic steps that can keep you generally safe on the internet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 00:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anthrax outbreak triggered by climate change sickens dozens in Arctic Circle. Seventy-two nomadic herders, including 41 children, were hospitalized in far north Russia after the region began experiencing abnormally high temperatures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 22:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News had no time for Khizr Khan's amazing speech. Benghazi ads and Katy Perry, though ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 20:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump suddenly disowns the crappy convention he planned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 20:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going forward, Tor Group will now have a new anti-harassment policy, among other changes. Their inquiry found: Many people reported being humiliated by Appelbaum. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going forward, Tor Group will now have a new anti-harassment policy, among other changes. Their inquiry found: Many people reported being humiliated by Appelbaum. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DEF CON 23 Dec '15 Lecture by Bruce Schneier: Questions   Answers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 20:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apples Touch ID blocks fedsarmed with warrantfrom unlocking iPhone; Supreme Court has not ruled about compelled unlocking of fingerprint-locked devices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 18:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apples Touch ID blocks fedsarmed with warrantfrom unlocking iPhone; Supreme Court has not ruled about compelled unlocking of fingerprint-locked devices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 18:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debbie Wasserman Schultz to resign as DNC chair as email scandal rocks Democrats. Sanders calls for new leader as Clinton camp blames Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 23:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check out "Bad Government, No Freedom" -- a subreddit for news and stories about various governments stomping on your rights and rights you expect - /r/badgovnofreedom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 20:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Agents Went Undercover To Spy on Anti-Fracking Movement, Emails Reveal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 21:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LGBT history is coming to California classrooms, a first in the nation. California approves the USs first requirements for public schools to include prominent gay Americans and LGBT rights milestones in history classes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 01:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elizabeth Warren takes on Airbnb, urging scrutiny of large-scale renters. Senator wants the federal government to investigate the extent to which the short-term lodging market actually consists of commercial rental firms. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 19:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In first, U.S. judge throws out cell phone 'stingray' evidence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 03:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oakland Activists Launch Recall Campaign Against Mayor Libby Schaaf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 19:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Documents Show Govt Censorship of WikiLeaks and Law Enforcement Proceedings Against Reader of Snowden Docs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 03:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA classifies Linux Journal readers, Tor and Tails Linux users as "extremists" (Republished News) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to use Snapchat to embarrass your children. The over-35s have discovered Snapchat  much to their kids utter horror: We young people need another social media migration anyway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 19:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We know people care about privacy, so why won't they pay for it? With fewer than 6,000 units sold, Silent Circles privacy-focused Blackphone was a huge flop. It highlights a bigger problem with how people value security. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 19:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We know people care about privacy, so why won't they pay for it? With fewer than 6,000 units sold, Silent Circles privacy-focused Blackphone was a huge flop. It highlights a bigger problem with how people value security. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 19:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voters in EU referendum did not know what they were voting for  Labours Oona King tells House of Lords that 2nd plebiscite on negotiated Brexit deal is only fair   democratic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 01:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attorneys debate use of warrantless surveillance in Portland bomb appeal. Case is first court review of a conviction based on Section 702 law underpinning spy programs revealed by whistleblower Edward Snowden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 01:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attorneys debate use of warrantless surveillance in Portland bomb appeal. Mohamed Osman Mohamud case is first court review of a conviction based on law underpinning spy programs revealed by whistleblower Edward Snowden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 01:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dont have a canary: Why Silent Circle dropped its warrant warning page. When you dont keep customer data to begin with, the warrant canary is redundant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 20:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dont have a canary: Why Silent Circle dropped its warrant warning page. When you dont keep customer data to begin with, the warrant canary is redundant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 20:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Securing a travel iPhone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Securing a travel iPhone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 50-year-old gay bar The Stud  the Stonewall of San Francisco  faces closure as rent triples. Building sold, rent hiked, and owner ready to retire: Will the SF nightlife classic survive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 23:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Googles My Activity shows everything that company knows about its users  a lot. The new site collects every website youve been on, everything youve searched and many of the things youve done with your phone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 22:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Googles My Activity shows everything that company knows about its users  a lot. The new site collects every website youve been on, everything youve searched and many of the things youve done with your phone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 22:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feds   Cops Encountered Encryption in Only 13 Wiretaps in 2015. For 2nd straight year, the number of times wiretaps involving encryption has decreased. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 22:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feds   Cops Encountered Encryption in Only 13 Wiretaps in 2015. For 2nd straight year, the number of times wiretaps involving encryption has decreased. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 22:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook chipping away at privacy, profiles newly exposed. My secret account is now not so private after Facebook updated its search engine without warning, and theres nothing I can do about it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 00:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US report critical of fellow lawmakers' efforts to regulate encryption. Weighing in on the encryption debate, new government report says that lawmakers need to to learn more about technology before trying to regulate it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 00:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US report critical of fellow lawmakers' efforts to regulate encryption. Weighing in on the encryption debate, new government report says that lawmakers need to to learn more about technology before trying to regulate it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 00:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terrorism Database Used by Governments and Banks Leaked Online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 22:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terrorism Database Used by Governments and Banks Leaked Online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 22:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeremy Corbyn to face no-confidence vote as Labour rebellion builds. Despairing mood at PLP meeting as leader names new shadow cabinet members while protesters outside voice support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 00:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Airbnb and house-sharing firms reduced New York housing stock by 10%. Research by affordable housing advocacy groups finds more than 55% of listings in city on Airbnb are illegal, and 30% are listed by commercial hosts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 00:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Airbnb and house-sharing firms reduced New York housing stock by 10%. Research by affordable housing advocacy groups finds more than 55% of listings in city on Airbnb are illegal, and 30% are listed by commercial hosts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 00:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tor Project Battled Over Hiring Ex-CIA Agent, Chat Logs Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 21:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Labour in crisis: Tom Watson criticises Hilary Benn sacking. Jeremy Corbyns deputy to meet party leader after dismissal of shadow foreign secretary is followed by resignations of several high-profile MPs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 20:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US-UK security officials cement intelligence partnership after 'leave' vote. Brexit will not affect planned project as US will still consolidate its analysis complex within a Royal Air Force hub for intelligence on security threats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 21:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battle of the Secure Messaging Apps: How Signal Beats WhatsApp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 20:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battle of the Secure Messaging Apps: How Signal Beats WhatsApp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 20:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LGBT people of color alienated by San Francisco Pride's plan for more police. Some members of LGBT community who faced harassment and disparate treatment from police say increased security doesnt mean they feel more safe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 19:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Silicon Valley is embracing universal basic income. Influential incubator Y Combinator pilot study will hand over cash monthly to 100 families in Oakland, California. Whats UBIs payoff for tech entrepreneurs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 19:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tell the Norwegian Government: Let Edward Snowden Come to Norway to Accept PEN Prize </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The shadowy war on the press: How the rich silence journalists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 20:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to seamlessly, easily, migrate all my data/settings from my Admin account to a new, user one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 20:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, wise people.

Years back, I did a common, but mildly reckless thing. Rather than create a user account, I ran everything out of the Admin one. Fast forward 10 years and I've got a *lot* of files and settings. I'm running El Capitan.

I now realize it's better practices to not run everything from Admin, so I'd like to fix that. The thing is, I don't want to spend eons moving all my data   settings from Admin to User.

So, I'd like to end up with my Admin to be bare bones, perhaps with all my apps, fonts, extensions. Then my new User account with (ideally) my data and settings. But Apps there if I must.

Can someone provide a link to a way to simply, easily do this?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take that, FBI: Apple goes all in on encryption. Apples newest encryption tool better secures files on all its devices, just the latest in a move to widespread encryption in the tech industry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 21:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take that, FBI: Apple goes all in on encryption. Apples newest encryption tool better secures files on all its devices, just the latest in a move to widespread encryption in the tech industry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take that, FBI: Apple goes all in on encryption. Apples newest encryption tool better secures files on all its devices, just the latest in a move to widespread encryption in the tech industry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take that, FBI: Apple goes all in on encryption. Apples newest encryption tool better secures files on all its devices, just the latest in a move to widespread encryption in the tech industry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Olympics Are Turning Rio into a Military State. The air is electric in Rio right now, and not just because of the surveillance cameras scattered all around the city. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 00:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Microsoft-LinkedIn hookup will be the END of DAYS, I tell you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 19:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Startup That Sends Dossiers On Your Private Social Media Profiles To Potential Landlords Should Be Illegal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 06:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9th Circuit Court rules in CA case, No Constitutional right to carry concealed guns in public </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 04:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BlackBerry hands over user data to help police 'kick ass,' insider says. CBC gets peek into how secretive office answers requests from police around the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 23:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BlackBerry hands over user data to help police 'kick ass,' insider says. CBC gets peek into how secretive office answers requests from police around the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 23:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scandal-prone Brazil government casts doubt on impeachment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 22:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facing Data Deluge, Secret UK Spying Report Warned of Intelligence Failure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 01:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Airbnb regulations, forcing them to reject illegal listings, pass  unanimously. Surprise vote could force a dramatic change in the cannibalization of housing in SF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 00:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/NYC IMA 6/8/16: We are ACLU/NYCLU lawyers   reporter Kim Zetter of Wired. Were here to talk about law enforcements warrantless searches of your personal electronic data. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 02:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We will be at /r/NYC tomorrow, June 8th to discuss [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/nyc/comments/4n0pnk/we_are_aclunyclu_lawyers_and_reporter_kim_zetter/) law enforcements current practice of getting your personal digital information without a warrant from websites, cell providers or internet service providers and why this matters. Law enforcement agencies can sometimes get more information about your life from the way you use your cell phone and browse the internet than from looking through what you keep in your home.

All is not lost! The New York State Legislature is considering legislation, the [New York Electronic Communications Privacy Act](http://www.nyclu.org/ecpa), which would require law enforcement to obtain a warrant before accessing your electronic data and restore American principles to privacy in the 21st century.


You can *ask us anything* about these privacy issues, why they matter, or what the legislation will do! 

*/r/Privacy Mod note: We're sure that the ACLU would happily ask any questions related to privacy, civil rights, public accountability and the like.*

*While this is of specific concern to Manhattan residents, the technologies   policies are widespread and designed to scale, so we all should be concerned and take action wherever they live. But do try to keep your questions generally applicable to everyone.*

We'll be back tomorrow, at /r/NYC, at 3:30pm EST.

Wait. What?! Better boldface this part: **You can post your questions NOW and come back to see the answers at the IMA TOMORROW.** 

Its Its Its like time travel! No, it *is* time travel!

[Submit your questions now](https://www.reddit.com/r/nyc/comments/4n0pnk/we_are_aclunyclu_lawyers_and_reporter_kim_zetter/) and we'll be back tomorrow!

Proof:

ACLUs   NYCLU: [here](https://twitter.com/NYCLU/status/740250252054278144)

Kim Zetter: https://twitter.com/KimZetter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Facebook trying to force you to use its Messenger app? Social network to phase out mobile web version, forcing App install. But whats in it for Zuckerberg and co? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 21:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> June 6 Jacob Appelbaum Statement Re Allegations: A calculated and targeted attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 20:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
