<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject130</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 15:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you connect that Blanche was raped ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 15:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and I have always depended on the kindness of stangers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 15:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No not at all, spoils your opinion of 3 great actors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 15:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually Norton was good, I just couldn't stand Brando and De Niro for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 14:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the score </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 14:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh, hope you find the correct one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 14:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its from 2008 i think, https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gte3BoXKwP0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 14:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The others have done it over and over again; stormed the trenches, taken Montauban   Flats redoubt a dozen times, down by Picquigny  where it was all marked out with flags   shallow trenches exactly to scale. They know every house (as it was before we bombarded the village with 12 inch shells). They know every yard where every man is to go and they have passed most of it on to me. Tonight in the dark we assemble  brigades and brigades and more and more brigades  tomorrow in the pale dawn we go over the lid. Montauban is a mile or so away  we the 17 take Montauban. It is an honoured post  there is a soldiers song running through my head  we were singing it last night   I cant get it out of the head.


https://livesofthefirstworldwar.org/lifestory/2742240
I love soldier's letters too, hope you find the quote ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 11:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed out loud when I read this, a conversation with Cersie, Jaime and Pycelle
    Pycelle looked desperately uncomfortable. There has been a bird, he said. From Stokeworth. Lady Tanda sends word that her daughter Lollys has been delivered of a strong, healthy son.
 And you will never guess what they have named the little bastard, brother.
 They wanted to name him Tywin, I recall.
  Yes, but I forbade it. I told Falyse that I would not have our fathers noble name bestowed upon the ill-gotten spawn of some pig boy and a feeble-witted sow.
Lady Stokeworth insists the childs name was not her doing, Grand Maester Pycelle put in. Perspiration dotted his wrinkled forehead. Lollyss husband made the choice, she writes. This man Bronn, he  it would seem that he 
Tyrion, ventured Jaime. He named the child Tyrion.
The old man gave a tremulous nod, mopping at his brow with the sleeve of his robe.
Jaime had to laugh. There you are, sweet sister. You have been looking everywhere for Tyrion, and all the time hes been hiding in Lollyss womb.
 Droll. You and Bronn are both so droll. No doubt the bastard is sucking on one of Lollys Lackwits dugs even as we speak, whilst this sellsword looks on, smirking at his little insolence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 01:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I love this guy too, for me his best movies are tree lounge and ghost world. (In these movies he plays the role of a looser to perfection, who can be empathized with so easily, his only redeeming quality being he is not a hypocrite.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 11:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man, I like these kind of conclusions best. No conjecture, direct evidence, exclusively from asoiaf, that slipped from many reader's eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 10:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/asoiaf/comments/4luqf8/spoilers_everything_why_arya_and_the_waif_are_the/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 00:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fifth element ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that one is good too, actually I think only starks had good childhood memories (Jeoffery/Tommen/Myrcella, Jamie/Cersie/Tyrion, Renly/Stannis/Robert all are horror stories), hey but a while a ago someone posted this as Lannister kids childhood https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AjPau5QYtYs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Waif is Arya theory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is, just makes me angry that people can't accept that man's beauty the way it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 15:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making a living as leeches, hope they do it out of desperation than greed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 12:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great man enjoy ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 12:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Song is from Mike and the Mechanics, maybe check for more covers if this does not work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 11:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah definitely, Rickon too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 09:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> np :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did that in pulp fiction and some other movie also I cant recall right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I see, that makes sense. I was actually comparing it to the world series videos which they watched in the movies, but yeah you were right they were not cons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry it's a bit long, but this is one of the few instances when all stark kids are together, and it's a kind of childhood memory that usually siblings share, I'm sure if you have brothers/sisters/close friends as kids then this will remind you of them:
Fear cuts deeper than swords, the quiet voice inside her whispered. Suddenly Arya remembered the crypts at Winterfell. They were a lot scarier than this place, she told herself. She'd been just a little girl the first time she saw them. Her brother Robb had taken them down, her and Sansa and baby Bran, who'd been no bigger than Rickon was now. They'd only had one candle between them, and Bran's eyes had gotten as big as saucers as he stared at the stone faces of the Kings of Winter, with their wolves at their feet and their iron swords across their laps.
Robb took them all the way down to the end, past Grandfather and Brandon and Lyanna, to show them their own tombs. Sansa kept looking at the stubby little candle, anxious that it might go out. Old Nan had told her there were spiders down here, and rats as big as dogs. Robb smiled when she said that. "There are worse things than spiders and rats," he whispered. "This is where the dead walk." That was when they heard the sound, low and deep and shivery. Baby Bran had clutched at Arya's hand.
When the spirit stepped out of the open tomb, pale white and moaning for blood, Sansa ran shrieking for the stairs, and Bran wrapped himself around Robb's leg, sobbing. Arya stood her ground and gave the spirit a punch. It was only Jon, covered with flour. "You stupid," she told him, "you scared the baby," but Jon and Robb just laughed and laughed, and pretty soon Bran and Arya were laughing too.
The memory made Arya smile, and after that the darkness held no more terrors for her. The stableboy was dead, she'd killed him, and if he jumped out at her she'd kill him again. She was going home. Everything would be better once she was home again, safe behind Winterfell's grey granite walls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 01:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun movie, but would have liked to see more "poker face" from all the mentioned actors, instead those guys were totally animated about everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 01:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It became predictable during climax, yeah one of those books where you say not boring, not bad, not this, not that instead of it was great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The searchers ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 14:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys this maybe off the point, but is there any evidence of why Iron bank is so powerful and how it manages to collect its debts ? Are there any instances of its great power mentioned in the books ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 12:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My beloved monster and me , shrek ? https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LlSE1DLkE-s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 12:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big Hero 6 ? https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1DIiBzHn-Ps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the mood for love, https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZgO_sCXrK4s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slaughter house five gravestone epitaph reading, "Everything was beautiful and nothing hurt" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tender Mercies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect my friend ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Death should hold no fear for a man as old as me, but it does. Isn't that silly? It is always dark where I am, so why should I fear the darkness? Yet I cannot help but wonder what will follow, when the last warmth leaves my body. Will I feast forever in the Father's golden hall as the septons say? Will I talk with Egg again, find Dareon whole and happy, hear my sisters singing to their children? What if the horselords have the truth of it? Will I ride through the night sky forever on a stallion made of flame? Or must I return again to this vale of sorrow? Who can say, truly? Who has been beyond the wall of death to see? Only the wights, and we know what they are like. We know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k016mR9tQdI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 13:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Double whammy ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 13:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> moonlight shadow ? https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e80qhyovOnA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 00:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Groundhog day ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 20:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> np :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 20:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zwartboek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 13:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the president's men, JFK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 13:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool Hand Luke - Nothing like freedom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 12:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey which movie is that ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 12:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love that movie too and Eddie Vedder's music </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 12:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it was one of the 'Bran interventions' ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 12:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any theories as how Jon and Tyrion could become enemies ? Previously it was the love triangle thing, so any parallels from there maybe ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 00:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, well, you know, that's just, like, your opinion, man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 00:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes there's so much beauty in the world, I feel like I can't take it, and my heart is just going to cave in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 23:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apocalypse Now - Marlon Brando - Last half an hour may be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 23:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not forsake me oh my darling - High Noon - Tex Ritter,

Local Hero -Local Hero - Mark Knofler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 23:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's not who you are underneath, it's what you do that defines you... Batman Begins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 23:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly my friend, I came to know Mel because of his work, and I refuse to judge him by what he does outside of that, that's his private life. If I don't like what he says in his interviews, I have freedom to change the channel. I am grateful to him for all those moments of pure brilliance and perfection that he made me experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 13:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she didn't do any cruelty to other people except Joffrey (indirectly), for which everyone was grateful I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 10:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I don't have the books anymore so I was also pulling it off the memory, btw 6th re-read awesome ! I think who-knows-what was half the intrigue in the riverlands in ASOS, I forget most of the equations now ! Hope you find the answer.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 03:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Roose himself proclaims that Ramsay is his son, then what's there to question him ? Everyone assumes that wartime news has a lot of confusion. Iirc, the team sent to depose Ramsay got massacred at winterfell right when they tried to take the castle back from Theon, so who is to confirm the story that they killed someone who looked exactly like Ramsay. Further, well if Northmen didn;t question as to why Roose murdered Robb, then why should they have the guts to question him about son ? Maybe there is more factual evidence but this is all I could construct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 01:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Born on a blue day is about a homosexual autistic guy, but there is no story about floorboards and test tubes in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 22:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, egomaniac sounds fair enough, though I'm no expert maybe other ppl could comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 22:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh actually people exhibit superiority because inside they are insecure and not confident about about themselves, mostly because they have a tendency of constant comparison, I am not too sure but thats what I remember </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 22:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah there is one more interesting thing about it someone told me, that there is actually no superiority complex only inferiority </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 22:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superiority (inferiority) complex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 15:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and that song with the little girl singing was so perfect for Pitt's role </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 14:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have read that book, I mostly remember how the guy experienced total freedom when he spent a summer at his girlfriend's parents house. I felt that is true, and for many of us living in not so bright places, for us our lives just go on earning a living, taking care of responsibilities, family etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [Kids Book] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 14:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was an illustrated book, I read it in early 90s. It was printed in landscape. I remember a lot of drawings had a moon, and a guy wore a clown cap. I think he was supposed to be cunning/evil. The story may have been about hiding/stealing the moon. Chances are the book was by some English author. I was a kid and my sister got the book from her school (which btw leaned towards christanity). I used to read it a lot. The drawings had a black background and were mostly done with white and had little color. Sometimes I think this is my earliest childhood memory, it would be great help if someone tells me the name of the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 13:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The three idiots, i guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 11:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the plans were too long term, the mountain would have got gout by the time they would have matured. If you want revenge, there is no way but to step into the jungle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 11:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe Jake is one of the few people who have made that 'transformation' from young actor to a terrific adult actor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 11:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope you saw Primal fear if you are a Norton fan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 11:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great choice my friend, I loved him in Capote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 11:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope Naomi Watts gets better scripts, she is very good
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 03:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not sure, but I assumed it was a classic hence the rankings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and Michael Caine too !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ADRIAN !!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love actually - every christmas, Terminator - It's always on TV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I watch the Jesus Quintana - Hotel California scene on youtube for hours repeatedly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary Swank - Boys don't cry, Steve Buscemi - Trees Lounge/Ghost World </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aso Jerry Mcguire, Collateral, The last Samurai, all different roles and I loved him and the movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the most fucked up thing I have ever read on this sub ! What is troubling is it can't be cast aside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like what you wrote both times, great quote ! I agree I also have been conditioned to think good/evil and judge myself and others unfortunately Jamie is a victim of the judgement of ppl like us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally like Jamie too but I think most ppl arw justified in not liking him. You say he is a bad guy going good and in the end u contradict urself saying good and evil are artificial. I tend to agree with the conclusion and liking/hating for me is more a matter of whether I identify with the character. I don't care either whether he does evil or good so long as I feel I would have done exactly the same in his situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 23:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though I am a big fan of Jamie Lannister ( but I concede that it is because I like the self loathing Marlon Brando stereotype rogue), I must say that redemption can start only when someone goes the gravedigger (hound) mode, you know there is always a reason to justify violence and it keeps circulating, so redemption arc is well mere dilution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 15:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is more of a question, is grapes of wrath the first 'crossing the country with a car' american novel ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 13:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call me biased but she is portrayed too loud/shrill/aggressive for a kid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 13:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would also like to add that while pushing Bran out, it is argued many times that it was a do or die situation for J C Co., but it is forgotten how he would have killed Arya (during the whole Mycah episode) had he found her just to please Cersie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 12:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its close to yellow leadbetter (which they did use in one episode) but its, not maybe some other pearl jam track </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][Book]Self critical book about a guy who who leaves a girl and his kid in England to pose as a doctor in Switzerland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I read this book about 5 years ago. It was not contemporary. Most probably by an English writer. There was this guy who leaves town (England) because his best girl can't marry him due to some reason. He goes to Switzerland and has an affair with an air hostess where he poses as a doctor. His girl visits him in Switzerland later it is revealed that the narrator cheated the readers by not revealing the full truth about himself at all, as he knocked up the girl before leaving town. He comes back to England seeking redemption and stuff. Thanks for the help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 20:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah character wise you are right but he was the best schemer and responsible for a lot of the intrigue in ACOK and ASOS, I miss that in the books after he died, OK Martells and Euron are doing their thing but its not the same level. For me he is like the rug who tied the room together man ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 19:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they gave Arya plot line with Roose to him, and he ran with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 16:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not every fan, but yeah love for Tywin in not as universal as Jon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 14:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tywin, asoiaf wasn't the same once he died (for me) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 14:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Graffiti </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 14:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realistic and unpopular </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 13:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that poem for the first time, thanks a lot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 13:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Edd, fetch me a block" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 13:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great read thanks, I love these debatable topics and the way while trying to draw conclusions we end up questioning the premise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 00:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=258fDJ7EvVU, Tarantino himself said in this interview at 26:19 to 28:00, how at least one film for every director is very personal and if they don't get appreciated for than one single movie, their quality starts deteriorating  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zoe Bell \m/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah valid point, but I liked him in the role you know, I am a big fan of these books, and they are more about action and justice (no grey character stuff). Also felt that it was one of the better Tom cruise movies in the recent past </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice catch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video makes me sad though, his kind of writing is becoming vintage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 02:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Martin Scorsese </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 01:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Steinbeck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 00:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with your post, it can also be added that separating work from real emotions is the hardest part for sex workers and that's the only way they can go on doing what they do. They deserve so much more understanding and respect than they get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
