<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7521</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't say how it lather since I haven't used it yet, but I really like the smell! It's a beautiful pungent jasmine. If you like floral scents you'll definitely like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm scared of that too after I watched Donnie Darko. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 10:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The chocolate lip scrub smells exactly like whip stick! I really like it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is very large and heavy. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do 

Edit: just tried it and it smells kind of like a new pair of sneakers and it's kind of hard to lather up. But it did leave my skin really soft and didn't dry my skin out like most cleansers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Easter lush haul came in this evening! Carrot gift glows in the dark :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's so beautiful! She looks like my boy oscar :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes of course </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find that speed builds have been really helping with my anxiety lately so I do enjoy them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> City living and get to work are my favorites. I found get together really boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 08:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 08:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I'm kind of taking a break from life, I just finished over a year of chemo last month and I'm just trying to gain back my health and motivation so I can do something great with my life :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 08:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I know what you mean. I'm still trying to figure out which way I should go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 08:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for that! I'm definitely considering it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 08:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds tough :/ hope it works out for you though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 07:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you work hard, that's a great attribute to have! My father is a mechanical engineer and he works basically 24/7 because he teaches online classes and he has to reply to so many emails and do extra unpaid classes. I kind of get what you mean about the machine part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 07:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit I'm just like you except at least you have a job. Same age, same attitude. Also interested in writing and film! But I hope you can find a way to get back in school and do something you love!

Edit: way not war </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 07:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome :) glad you were able to do well for yourself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 07:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally applaud you for that, sounds awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
