<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 10:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back at you man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 10:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I don't have much of a plan or any dreams. I guess my plan is to try the homeless game again soon because things are not working out financially and that looks inevitable.

I think I want to try a "real" city this time. Nashville is the closest major city so I might try to see what that feels like. There's a ton of people so it seems like it could be great or terrible depending on my luck. 

But then again I really don't have anything other than family, and I don't see them regularly as it is. I guess I could try to snag rides to any city regardless of distance. It sounds pretty dramatic but it sounds kinda exciting too. 

Edit

I don't want anything particular out of life. I guess I DO, since I feel like things are missing, and I definitely want them. I just don't know what they are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I've ended up where I'm stuck at now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 07:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 18, I graduated highschool and my dad lost his job at the exact same time. So we had to move, and I went with since I didn't have a job.

We moved to a new town out of my old state. I lived here without a job or car for over a year. I never met anyone, never talked to my old friends, or anything. The only people I talked to was my family, outside of cashiers and such. I ended up doing a lot of OTC drugs to get fucked up and just pass time. Everyday was the same. Sometimes I would walk miles to town and hangout at the park to see people my age, but I must've went to the wrong park or at the wrong time, since all I found were families with little kids.

Then my dad lost the house, but he had a girlfriend to live with. By now I'm depressed, developing social anxiety, and I'm homeless. So I go back to my old town. Not many friends are still around, it was a small town and a lot of my circle went off to college or just left to live in a bigger city. There were still plenty of familiar faces, but I couldn't talk to them anymore. Social anxiety was strong enough now that I spent all of my time wandering around along, or looking for odd jobs to buy food. I didn't have clean clothes most of the time, or a car, so I couldn't find a real job. I didn't try TOO hard though because I just didn't have the motivation. I did this for about 4 months, and then moved on to another bigger town with more people.

Pretty much did the same as above for 6 more months. Finally my mom let me live with her. I lived with her for 2 years in another town I didn't know. She got me a car so I could drive places, but I didn't have anyone to visit. But I did get a job at a factory to keep busy and make money. There weren't many people in my section, but I met this one dude who talked to me a bit. Like went out of his way to make effort, even though I could never think of what to say and couldn't hold an actual conversation. It was always "oh yeah?" "Really?""cool". 

Anyway, mom loses her job and I can't pay all the bills. We lose the house and she goes to a friends to live and I'm about to be homeless. My friend let's me live on his couch now, but we're not really friends. We don't talk, see eachother (he works somewhere else now), or anything. Sometimes I think he avoids me but whatever.

So here I am, in a town I don't know with no friends and I'm not optimistic about the future. My mind is so dull, and I don't have a personality anymore. My intellect is lowering too. Sometimes I wonder if I've got some condition or something just ruining my brain. I don't think I can redevelop my social skills and connect with people again.

I just miss it all. I spend a lot of time doing stuff like listening to songs me and friends used to get down to, or songs that remind me of old girlfriends, and wonder when the last time any of them thought about me was. Sometimes I want to get in touch, but then I remember I am not who I was. I've lost my wits, humor, aspirations, personality, just everything. And I'm sure they're different too. 

And then I remember that we are young adults and their lives probably move fast. This shit was all 5 (or more) years ago. They've moved on. And then I feel fucking pathetic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My weed has black smoke? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 07:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright so me and a friend picked up a dub of some shit and decided to blaze out tonight. Just some mids, they look/smell/feel all normal.

So we load up a bowl this ceramic bong and my friend rips it. He instantly loses his shit and coughs everywhere, but he coughs out black smoke. It was pretty thick too.

So this is new to us, we've never had some shit like this to us. It seemed sketchy, but we finished the bowl (had to take small hits to keep control). I definitely got pretty high for some mids, but it gave each of us a headache.

About an hour later we roll the rest into a flat blunt and spark it up. This fucking thing is burning crazy as a thick black smoke just bellows off of it. From the amount of smoke it looked like it was burning fast, but it smoked at a normal speed. 

Towards the end of the L I had a coughing fit and ended up throwing up and getting a horrible headache. But I'm still high.

So now I'm home wondering what the fuck that was. It was fire but it was so harsh. I've smoked a lot of weed and never seen this. Do some strains just burn black instead of white? If not is it safe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
