<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject983</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 22:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, this is the sort of stuff I was looking for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 21:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm namely looking for studies that have hard data about Obamas policies. There is a lot of flak for Romney for not having any evidence for his plan; I'd like to see some hard data for Obama's plan. I already know Romneys policies are BS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A lot of people say that Mitt Romney's tax plan is bogus because no legitimate studies back up his proposals.  What are some studies that show that Obama's policies are factually sound? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 19:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 18:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm a 19 male at 6 feet 0 inches, what would an optimal weight be?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 16:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Newfag doesn't know about ID </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 01:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would hire Morgan Freeman to summarize my day for me right before I go to bed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 00:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sultans of swing.  I'm a fan of heavy metal, but I always enjoy listening to the sultans of swing.  Its a classic rock piece.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-15 20:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For deadlifts, once I completely lift the bar and stand up, am I supposed to drop the bar or am I supposed to reverse the motion and go back down?  In my high school weight lifting classes we were taught to only extend up and then drop the bar.  However, upon watching all of the intro videos on the SS wiki it looks like they are reversing and taking the bar down.  Second question, alternating or match grip? I was always taught alternating, but all the SS videos showed a match grip.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-14 06:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red wings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-14 01:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you guys want to get a musical benefit from this, head over to /r/drums and look up the rudiment exercises.  Work on mastering them and you'll be on you way to becoming a great drummer.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-13 18:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you a social democrat or so you actually support all workers owning equal shares in the means of production? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-12 21:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was known as The Silver Fox. Foxy for short. My friends gave me the nickname because I started getting gray hair at age 15.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-12 04:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started getting gray hair at 15. At age 19 I'm rocking a head that's about 1/5 gray. No fucks given  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 20:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repost-First post I ever saw on Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 19:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope TPA destroys those frost cheaters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 19:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they get their cheating asses beat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 05:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sabian APX 10" splash and clamp arm.  $50 on craigslist.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-09 20:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about a proxy server then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-09 17:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learn to read music.  When I played guitar I would play purely off tabs.  Learning the actual notation makes it much easier to learn new instruments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 23:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally have a 16" ZBT crash that sounds amazing. I also have a 18" ZXT rock crash that sounds like shit. Really depends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 20:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My penis in someone else's vagina sounds like a good place to start </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 03:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beetle Juice.  I was like 6 and that movie freaked me out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 02:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try to lower the tom angle on the rack tom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 18:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me a lot of the 2000 election.  More swing voters agreed with Al Gore on the issues, but they voted for Bush because they liked him more in the debates.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 15:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure that your calves are perpendicular to the ground.  When I first got my double bass pedals I sat farther back and my calves had about a 20 degree angle between the back of my calves and the ground.  After moving my seat up, the speed at which I could play increased pretty significantly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 01:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly look at the face, then boobs. Ass is an afterthought to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 00:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A girls ass. I know, I'll show myself out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-02 05:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Nicolas Cage was in SWTOR, he would be Nicolas Sage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 03:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at the floor tom.  Is it just me or is it on a very strange angle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 03:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/incest 

Yes folks it exists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 20:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to win friends and influence people by Dale Carnegie. Completely changes your view of social interactions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 19:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100-82-70-95 here.  Really weird because the description of "deadhead" doesnt fit me at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 04:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I just checked Newegg and I can get the 7950 for $80 cheaper then Microcenter.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help]  Would like to build gaming PC + monitor for under 1k  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 01:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was looking around, and was thinking on running a 7970 + 3570k.  However, when I put together the build with HDD, RAM, PS, Case, Cooling, Monitor and Optical Drive, it goes up to about $1300-$1400.  I know PD is due out in a couple weeks so I'm not sure if that affects the situation at all.  I would prefer to be able to overclock but I'll sacrifice that if necessary. What would you guys recommend cutting back on in order to reign in my budget? Also, I would prefer to do all my shopping at Microcenter if possible.

General specs I was looking at that were putting me over budget:

(2x4GB) RAM: 1600mhz if Intel, 1866mhz if AMD

Generic optical drive

CM Storm Scout Case

XFX 650W power supply

CM Hyper 212+

2TB Seagate HDD

3570k + Motherboard

Diamond 7970 ($380 at my local microcenter)

1920x1080 monitor ($200ish)

I already have a gaming mouse and keyboard.  

If you guys say wait for PD do you think it would be ok to buy the graphics card and use it on my current machine temporarily? My current system is a phenom 1 tricore with 8GB RAM, but the 5770 card died on it and I figured it was time for a full system upgrade. I'm planning on giving the old machine to my dad and having it run of integrated graphics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-25 21:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this apply in Illinois as well as long as I have a FOID?

Edit: a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 00:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT IS WRONG WITH MY EYES?!?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 04:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend throwing in a few ice cubes.  Great for texture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 04:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of my wats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-16 03:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't exactly pack up my drum kit and carry it around campus with me.  One of the downfalls of being a drummer.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-16 03:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually want to take a class and become a wine concierge, but I'm not 21 yet : ( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-16 00:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People still play?!?  I remember playing when I was like 12 but I thought it was dead now. Still got my 11/11 indestructible dark steel colossus : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about hobbies for INTP's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-15 21:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So for as long as I can remember, I've been doing typical INTP hobbies.  Reading, watching documentaries on the discovery and history channels, playing video games, etc.  However, this last summer, a lot of these started getting really boring for me, and I really wanted to get out and do stuff that involved being with other people.  At first I thought maybe I had become an extrovert, however, after some analysis I came to the conclusion that I was not. I knew this for sure because after being in social situations, I would always be exhausted and would go straight to some alone time to recharge. After reading all the stuff you guys posted on here, I really began to doubt that I was an INTP because of how much closer to the "textbook" INTP you guys were over me. Just yesterday, for the first time I stumbled across the cognitive functions for each type, and after reading about it I believe that I have a very developed Extroverted Feeling function (Fe).  

My question is to all of you guys out there with really strong (Fe) functions, what are some hobbies that I can get involved in that will click well with my personality?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-15 20:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scar with EOTech is a free rental? Hook me up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 23:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A penis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 05:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh most definitely not body armor.  One of my friends told me he had a plate carrier so I was operating under that assumption.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 05:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting a runtime error on that link-think its dead.  Got another one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 04:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah-Stop going off script </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 01:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purely speculative, as he could have been wearing all of that gear to last longer against the police.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do we bake cookies and cook bacon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 23:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 17:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I am an independent.  I don't think the title was misleading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama on GOP and economy: "Have a cold? Take two tax cuts, roll back a few regulations and call me in the morning" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 04:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 03:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Gaben! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 00:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally have been thinking of taking up archery.  My local forest preserve has a free range that is about 5 mins from my house.  (I'm a community college student).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-06 15:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check your local craigslist.  I picked up near mint iron cobras for $150.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-06 14:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A constitutional amendment can be proposed by the states at a constitutional convention called for by 3/4 of the state legislatures.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 23:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brawl. I tried playing him as falco today, but still no success. Its really frustrating to play him because all he does is shield/dodge/roll/counterattack until i strike first, then he rapes me with his side c-stick.  If I dont attack first he never does anything except run away like a pussy.  I was able to grab him a few times and mess up his pattern but he still wins in the long run.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 19:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its in brawl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help beating my brother when he is Marth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 05:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother just recently started playing super smash, and now all he does is play Marth and counterattack, dodge and shield until I'm 75%+ then he edgecamps me until I die.  How can I beat him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 02:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally love my ZBT 16" crash.  Sounds absolutely killer. 

Edit: I accidentally I word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-02 05:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you in a club/bar environment or day-gaming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-02 04:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> implying people text me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 15:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See what you can find on craigslist.  I got a pair of Iron Cobras in near mint condition (I just had to tighten a few screws) for $150.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 01:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No hi-hat? Now I'm just impressed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 05:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe he was in the catholic seminary but I am not certain.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 05:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My teacher got his masters in art and then studied for a little while to become a priest, but he never completed becoming a priest.  He told us thats what they were taught in the seminary, and he translated some of hit himself (He was always quoting the hebrew version in class) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 00:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a graduate of a catholic high school, I can definitively say that genesis was never meant to be a literal story. When translated into English, it comes across as being literal truth. However, when looked at in Hebrew, the language used makes it very clear that genesis is only a metaphor for the creation story.  For comparison, the language used in the book of kings presents things in a very factual manner. We had a king, he sucked. We get a new king, he sucked even more. The language used in genesis, however, presents a very metaphorical image that was meant to answer the question "WHY" are we here, not to answer the question "HOW" did we get here. Sorry for any typos I'm on my phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 20:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get involved! With anything! Don't sit on your ass and play world of warcraft for your first two years like I did, you'll regret it later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 20:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never kissed a girl or even been on a date for that matter at age 19. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 20:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a child is driving a parents car and crashes should the parents have to serve a jail sentence as well since it was their car?

Answer to both questions is no.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 17:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as possible.  The clockwork metronome app for iOS was made free for a limited time (not sure if it still is or not).  The nice thing about this app is that the downbeat is really sharp and without headphones on the downbeat still cuts through the rest of the sound really nicely (I have dampeners on my toms and snare but not my cymbals, don't ask me why).    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 17:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His goal is to develop a good sense of inner time.  His theory is that once your inner clock is well developed and calibrated, it will make it much easier to keep time when practicing rudiments at higher speeds or learning more complex patterns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 17:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two questions here:

One:  In Illinois, if my dad purchased a handgun and gave it to me as a gift, would I be able to legally shoot it at a range (I'm 19).  I know you have to be 21 to buy from a FFL but I'm not sure about shooting it.

Two:  If I can indeed get a handgun, what are you guys thoughts on the colt 1911 .22 lr?  I'm looking to get a 22 handgun just for plinking and I really liked the look of the colt, but I haven't been able to find much about the reliability and such of the gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 17:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing to work on would be what my drum teacher calls the "placement" of the notes.  I've been taking lessons since the beginning of the summer and this has been my teachers big focus for me, as he hasn't even started me on rudiments yet.  By "placement" what I mean is that if your playing 8ths on the hi-hat and you play a bass drum in-between two of the hi-hat hits, it falls exactly where the 16th note should be, and not too fast or too slow.

Some of you might think my teacher is bad for not teaching me rudiments sooner, but seeing as he has been a professional musician for over 15 years and that he has gigs every weekend I'm willing to take his word on this.  I have been practicing paradiddles (I think thats what they are called, RLRR LRLL) as well as 5 stroke rolls on my own to build up stick control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 17:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RLRR LRLL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want this shirt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 04:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 04:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That guys tom setup is amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 17:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After hearing the Meinl B20 20" china on their website its second on my purchase list after getting a secondary crash, as I only have a 16" crash atm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 02:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides every conversation I have with a woman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 19:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like I could use another drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 16:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pearl exports are also a great choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 16:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outlawing abortion with exceptions would be pointless and hypocritical.  Is basically saying "We think a child's right to life is important, except in cases where we say it isn't important".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 00:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess another question would be how to find out about parties.  At a regular university it seems like it would be really easy to find out just by talking to other people in your dorm, but you don't have that environment at cc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 00:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now I'm planning my chances to transfer to my states four year school to major in comp sci.  

A lot of my friends tell me "that I'm making the smart choice" by going to a CC, but I feel like shit going there.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 00:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if your college's selection of clubs sucks? The majority of clubs at my school are religious or language related and there are no inter-mural sports </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 23:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess I'll just have to suck it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 23:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the idea of just doing classwork and sitting at home for two years seems pretty boring.  Maybe I would have been better off going to a regular university.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 23:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all my classes no one was talking or socializing.  I had an hour between my first class and second classes and two between my second and third and all I did was browse Reddit because everyone was walking around or sitting in huge groups and it seemed as though there was no where to fit in. My community college also has an extreme lack of clubs and activities (I would say more then half of the ones on campus are language or religion related and no inter-mural sports).  It seemed as though I was wearing an invisibility cloak most of the day. I guess the feeling of insignificance is what is getting to me. My one great fear about going to a CC was that I would have absolutely no social life and it appears to be coming true.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, today was my first day of community college and it sucked.  What are your tips and tricks to having a successful community college experience?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 23:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 17:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the one with no experience start with basic music theory.  Start by explaining how notes break down (One whole = two halves = four quarters...) and have him play them on the snare drum.  After that I would move onto basic beats.  When I started drums I had been playing guitar for five years so I was already familiar with basic music theory so my teacher started me with variations on the standard rock grove.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 17:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like I could use another drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 01:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At age 19 I have yet to be given the talk.  Considering I haven't even held hands with a girl I'd say that I won't need it anytime soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 23:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering its a 320gb drive and it has 7gb free I definitely want to wipe the drive. Plus I plan on getting an SSD and using the current drive as a data/time machine drive by purchasing an enclosure for the current drive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 20:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would one unlisense office? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help regarding OS X CD.  Fast response appreciated.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 20:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought a 2010 macbook from my friend as he had received a new 2012 macbook pro as a graduation present.  However, he cannot find the old CD for the 2010 macbook and we were wondering if I could use the disk from the 2012 to format the drive and then re-install the OS.  I think this might work since OS X doesn't require product keys but I wanted to check here as this is my first Mac and I don't want to mess anything up for me or him.  

A second question is he can't find the product key for the office copy that came with it and I'll need the key to reinstall office.  Are there any ways to get the key from inside office or in the OS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 17:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you rather dip your balls in battery acid or drink a gallon of period blood? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 00:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I go in and order my first meal.  This was actually a legit meal as I hadn't eaten since 7 that morning and I went in there around 6.  The whole time I keep making subtle references to white grapes, but without actually mentioning white grapes.  For example, I would say stuff along the lines of "Wow, looks like you guys have a great variety of fruit here" and asking questions about how busy their day had been and stuff.  

After completion of my meal I went back up to the counter.  

Her: "How can I help you?"

Me: "I'd like a McDouble please"

Her: "Yep"

Me:  "This might seem like a strange request but I absolutely hate onions.  Would it be possible to get my sandwich without them?"

Her: "Sure thing"

Me:  "This is the weird part; would it be possible for me to get some diced up white grapes in place of the onions."

Her: (In an audibly angry tone) "WHAT did you say?"

Me:  "Sorry I must not have spoken clearly enough.  I'd like to have diced up white grapes in place on my onions."

Her:  "Get out."

Me:  "Geeze, whats the big deal? I asked for a simple change..."

Her: (Cutting me off) "Get out NOW"

Me:  "Fine, since you wont take my business here I'll head over to Burger King where they let me have it MY WAY"

*I exit* 


PS: There phones are back up.  Call away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 20:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went there but since I was eating inside there was no way to get video.  I'll post a transcript when I get off work as I'm posting with alien blue atm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 17:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their phone is back up.  Call away! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 18:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This McDonald's is on my way home from work.  I'll make sure to stop by and post a video if I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 19:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it really depends on how he is using the double bass.  If he uses the double bass to hit fast doubles and triples then it will be very beneficial for him to remove it, but if he is blasting consecutive 16th notes at a high bpm there is no way he can go without it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 19:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hammerfall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
