<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8985</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly they wouldn't

How so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, if you swapped the alphabet agency for an American or UK or Chinese... etc... agency and press outlet, it would still be SOP.

The difference maybe, would be that Stewart and Brooker don't get poisoned or shot, when they commented on the press' lack of commentary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the only person to say, "Primitive" though.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  These so called "stone age" and "primitives" have a lot more sense and are a lot more like us than we think. 

I think most humans are mostly alike, from our dim history to the present. Who are you talking about?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This question gets asked a lot here, and sometimes in ELI5; not saying you're wrong to ask again, but you might find literally years of detailed answers with a quick google search that looks like, "Reddit human civilization ended could humans rebuild?" and tune with other terms to your taste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could just as easily argue that I'm trying to press the "self-control" button... I think we can all agree that the trying to control *other* people's reproductive rights ends badly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/explainlikeimfive/comments/4rtdvu/eli5_why_does_a_strong_punch_to_the_jaw_or_face/

Searching is your friend!

It really is... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Egg yolks are incredible emulsifiers; they help fat-based and water-based substances form finer blends. If you took a (pasteurized) raw egg yolk and added to it your salad dressing of oil and vinegar, you'd find that the the whole thing would form a creamy suspension that would stay together for a while. 

Meanwhile the egg white are basically water and protein, which as /u/mb34i said can do some pretty impressive tricks. The bonus is that the fat in the yolks, and the water in the whites already have an emulsifier in the yolk; the egg is a complete kit to emulsify itself and anything else. An omelette, or scrambled eggs, is just such an emulsion, cooked. On its own, the white can also be whipped up into a tight froth and used to add air and volume to something that would otherwise not be raised, such as meringue, souffle, or mousse. 

When you add all of those things and use them in different combinations, you have the reason for eggs popularity in cuisine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://lovelace-media.imgix.net/uploads/92/d0deb610-6c52-0132-1829-0a7dfd902b7c.gif?w=740 h=481 fit=max auto=format

;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...That's nice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll be fine, neo-Nazis are a notoriously easygoing and forgiving group.

http://i.imgur.com/6QXtPyI.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Stone-Age" isn't a value judgement, it's just a technological classification... and it is what is is. The primary tools of the indigenous peoples of the Americas were *not* metal, but stone, wood, and animal products.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean... they're not magically noble or anything; they'd behave the same way given time and the same resources... that's humanity. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The life of a *loooot* of bitter assholes, including as you say, the Conspiratard. You can spot a truly vacant fuckhead by the litany of other people who've failed to recognize their genius, and/or dicked them over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shitstains... they're gonna spread until you clean them *thoroughly*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're still assuming *attenuating* circumstances.

https://m.popkey.co/b91743/DQ3Rx.gif


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Join an Antifa crowd? *lol*

I'll be like 99.9999% of people, getting on with my life. If neo-nazis ever really start to rear your heads again, nobody who really cares is going to march; you know this... it's why you hide. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the courts will, not an anonymous neo-nazi on Reddit like yourself. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.makeagif.com/media/2-16-2015/KLjU76.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not a very good Poe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how many of ^these newbie account trolls are just the same person, or same couple of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.democracynow.org/2017/4/26/headlines/seattle_2_charged_in_shooting_of_antifa_protester_at_milo_yiannopoulos_speech </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Armed Neo-Nazi Terrorists" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be both! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those days never ended, just ask Israel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lap Full of Kittens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone should complain about Nazis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^1 hour old account.

So brave! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Glances at posting history*

http://i.imgur.com/7i6s1hc.gif

...Jesus, I'm not sure what I expected though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Armed Neo-Nazis prepare for potential clash in small Kentucky town </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next time someone talks about "The Gay Agenda" I'm sending them this pic. *lol* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems like a fine way to catch a truly epic beating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at that huuuge bunny feet! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On one hand, it's basically the tail end of the genocide that began hundreds of years ago; a real tragedy. On the other hand, the fact that stone-age civilizations have managed to survive this long is astonishing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "   " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're absolutely right, and more broadly: http://nationalpsychologist.com/2009/03/tarasoff-%E2%80%9Cduty-to-warn%E2%80%9D-clarified/101056.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh! Turtleman!!! *Unloads Quad-Rockets* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Authorities Deploy Riot Police in Moscow Ahead of Opposition Protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^This is why we need more experienced FPS and Survival-Horror players in congress!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally speaking I'd agree with you, but there are exceptions to rules, and an obvious and proven lunatic who's offered decades of his public and private life for scrutiny could be one of them. When that lunatic is president, said scrutiny increases, and evidence of his instability mounts along with the existential risk to everyone on the planet... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey... don't judge him until after he tells us which drugs he's taking, in which doses! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^This. Sadly any topic such as this will inevitably summon the two horns of the dilemma... the nuts on the left, and the ideologically orientated hydrocephalics. You'll have people on one side trying to convince you that it's how their corn was grown for corn syrup that makes them fat, not the vast quantities of soda they drink that's to blame. On the other side you'll have people earnestly telling you that the only thing between feeding all of the hungry and not, is GMO... which is also laughable crap; see Somalia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A prohibitive, highly unrealistic amount; you'd burn about 3-4 calories a minute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are portable magnetic detectors, but a small REE magnet at 2 meters is... a lot to ask of them. Maybe a metal detector would be a better choice, but even that is going to have to be a hell of a lot close than 2 meters; you can't escape the rapid dropoff of EM intensity with distance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/65ogwp/in_the_face_of_cuts_for_the_needy_trumps_3m_trips/dgc5qhj/

You also think shit like that... it's *almost* as though you have an agenda that overrides any sense or reality... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they do, but most of them go through it much earlier and much quicker than we do, and it's generally defined purely in terms of sexual maturity (i.e. puberty is the line between being able to, and not being able to breed).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dr Gartner rejected any suggestion his dystopian vision of America as a devastated wasteland post-Trump was political sour grapes.

He said: I dont accept it. I dont think that it holds water. This is a Black Swan situation. Its not losing an election.

From election day on, basically half the country has been experiencing a psychological disorder. Half of America is undergoing continuous panic attacks.

Im not telling them anything they dont already know. Its not controversial to the more than 50 per cent of people who know the person in control is out of control. They know theyre in danger.

Its not even like George Bush stealing the election. We were mad. Not like this. People are scared. I would be grateful for a President Pence. Hes just a conservative, hes not crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTL is almost certainly not in the cards, sorry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Basically it is saying

"Basically"

aka... Lets make up some shit and see what sticks!

And still... no actual evidence that you *read* the article form either of your posts... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you even read the first line of the article?

One therapist tells of flood of 'very crude hate mail' after he went public </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/7i6s1hc.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's probably some middle ground between "throwing out" bibles (something I certainly wouldn't suggest) and simply... not putting them in every room as a rule. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never forget, never again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the life in the ocean exists in the regions we have explored, and most of it is pretty straightforward as life goes. If the ocean becomes acidic enough, carbonate shells are going to dissolve... it's not exactly a mysterious thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on the supernova, but looking at one which leaves a compact remnant (neutron star or black hole) the magnetic field of the core is conserved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Birds have a fundamentally different structure from our "voice-box"; whereas humans have a larynx, birds have a syrinx: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Syrinx_(bird_anatomy)

The syrinx enables some species of birds (such as parrots, crows, and mynas) to mimic human speech. Unlike the larynx of mammals, the syrinx is located where the trachea forks into the lungs. Thus, lateralization of bird song is possible and some songbirds can produce more than one sound at a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen both, so I'm inclined to agree; if you're lucky it's a great option.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem you're going to keep running into here is that the "puzzle" is phrased vaguely; when in doubt you can always retreat to a semantic argument, or a metaphysical one. To give a rigorous answer the question would be need to be posed rigorously, and then it would lose its semantic "magic"... and of course most of the people involved wouldn't understand it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her family owns a *ton* of the UK, and she's the figurehead of the state, opening parliament and all of that nonsense. She was born, and she waves sometimes. Occasionally she cuts ribbons, and in previous years, had execrable offspring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you resuscitate someone knowing they have a DNR, you're probably going to jail; you're certainly being sued, and may well lose your license to practice. If you don't know about a DNR, that's unfortunate for everyone involved, and if there was a responsibility for someone to know/inform then they might be on the hook civilly, but otherwise... shit happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is very good, but unfortunately *sometimes* the news does get very hectic, and they're not well positioned for those moments. Besides, most people won't watch it... maybe there's a middle ground between PBS and festering dog shit on the bottom of a Murdoch shoe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To not have them is to be anti-christian

No, it is anti-christian to take donated bibles and throw them away.

Which is it? 

Either way, having something donated to you doesn't impose an obligation to put one in each of your rooms. You were being most honest when you pointed out that it's just about avoiding boycotts from enraged bible belters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You've got to admire both. They just want everyone to curl up with a Good Book.

Have you read the bible? It's not *really* that good... it suffers from the problem of being translated and re-translated, it's quite archaic, and it gets bogged down in a lot of irrelevant details. 

If you want good timeless epics, try the Illiad and the Odyssey; they're much better and deal with similar themes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's anti-christian not to keep a copy of the bible in stock? So... Muslims, Jews, Hindus... the rest should be pretty offended then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BBC America is dog shit; the BBC in general has a lot of issues frankly, although it covers some things well (notably not itself). I certainly wouldn't describe the UK state broadcaster as "unbiased" though; if you want a good breakdown of that, see Charlie Brooker's "Yearly Wipes".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody in the TV news world seems to understand that the only untapped niche left is... a real attempt at unbiased, uncensored, news. That's sooooo far from MSNBC or Fox or CNN's remit that it doesn't even factor into their thinking.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's been the plan since Reagan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's sort of how Saville got his thing on after the 70's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/I9lsC9c.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...If that's not politics, what is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh... I'm sure you at least feel a deep sense of fulfillment, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Trying to make an example that was actually relevant. Murder doesn't leave the victim actually living to accuse anyone. It's a false equivalency on your front.

You say that, but wasn't Anthony's life disrupted *just* in the way you're talking about? Isn't she still in hiding even though the legal system exonerated her?

Sounds... almost exactly the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.nytimes.com/2017/02/20/us/politics/cpac-milo-yiannopoulos.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you'll find that the very same people who love Donald Trump for his propensity to attack women, will hate a gay man for his propensity to attack boys. It's not fair, but there it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/xo2KVfR.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our drug problems wouldn't disappear... there would still be a lot of people on drugs, but it would be a step in the right direction to decriminalize drugs, at the very least. Talking about a lack of "magic processes," if you think that somehow making drugs legal is the path to a happy and easy life for society, you're nuts. 

It's not a *good* way of dealing with the problem, it just happens to be the *only* way... it's still going to be very hard and costly, and take a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you won?! Cool, I keep hearing about that; what do you think you won? Does it come in the mail? Is it *shiny*?

*lol* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how ignoring someone who's vocally in favor of raping children helps anyone; that's sort of how Saville got his thing on after the 70's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, even the old GG crowd wouldn't be shocked if Milo's crawlspace turned out to be stuffed with boys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah Thiel... that creepy vampire... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was an attention and money whore before he was even out of uni... nothing has changed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Him: https://www.nytimes.com/2017/02/20/us/politics/cpac-milo-yiannopoulos.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a guy who's vocally in favor of raping children... publicize the shit out of him, and tar everyone around him with his brush.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tl;dr ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're *really* comfortable making wild assumptions based on minimal info, hm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do accused murderers not have similar issues? 

*Checks with Casey Anthony*

No no... they definitely have these problems too. Why the focus on rape, chum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't *both* bear some responsibility?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, anyone looks functional when the guy down the hall is painting himself and everything he can reach with his own feces.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! Preying on grieving families to give your own empty lives some semblance of significance? Assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  my reading habits.

My claim is that your reading habits don't exist.

A claim made that way can be rebutted like this:

Nuh uh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the second person who's claiming to have intimidate knowledge of my reading habits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Yeah, there couldn't be any reason why they wouldn't want to deal with nuts like you... it must be a conspiracy!

It's not that no one wants to go to school in that building, that no parent wants to talk *AGAIN* to people who "just want to ask questions" and in general, are fools. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I love you, but NO! No! I still love you though, but NO!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The post? Sure... the quote on the other hand?... 

Huxley was talking about a lot of things, but not most of the torrid crap that comes from this sub. Accepting war and poverty, the worst of human misery because "that's how it is," and blind accession to government, religious, and social authority had a lot more to do with his point than, "Wake up sheeple and smell the chemtrails!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Thirty minutes? *That's* your standard? Less time than you'd sink into a GoT episode, before you feel comfortable running with this shit?

*smh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, right, my bad... Alex Jones is a vehicle for 'The Truth' not a shambolic liar and failed comedian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huxley certainly was, but do you think that's what most of the comments here are saying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's pretty crazy. The first time I heard about Carfentanil (citrate) was when it was still an large game animal tranq... and you had to have the reversal agent in the kit just in case you accidentally dosed yourself. 

The idea of people recreationally taking this shit... crazy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happens in a lot of subs when people think they can get an edge on their own submissions by downvoting other submissions.

Or yeah... 8th dimension paedo lizards, whichever you find easier to swallow... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Didn't the guy who dreamed up this crap admit that he plays a character... and then lose his kids?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoken like someone who's never visited or worked in a intensive treatment ward of a psych unit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My claim is that consumer spending is always down in Q1.

Yes... a very accurate, yet dishonest claim in the context I offered you, which is that this is the *lowest* it's been in Q1 since 2014. 

Here, have a third citation.

http://www.bbc.com/news/business-39748165 

GDP expanded at an annual rate of 0.7% in the first quarter - the slowest rate since the first quarter of 2014.

Math. Facts. 

Counterpoint, /u/bardwick ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Debunking my claim?
I sent you to the Federal Reserve Bank, you send me to a magazine article. Hmm, which source should I go for?

You sent me to something that taken in context, didn't support your claim; I gave you that context. 

If you're taking issue with the facts presented in the dfx or NYMag analysis, you should be clear though; what don't you agree with?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.dailyfx.com/forex/market_alert/2017/03/28/US-Consumer-Confidence-Soars-Yet-Again-Without-the-Backing-of-Hard-Data.html

And to debunk your claim of "normal" dips: http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2017/04/american-economic-growth-has-slowed-to-a-crawl.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck explaining that to someone in T_D.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Bullshit, and that article is light on anything other than, "Pie-Eyed lunatic said..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Well... I mean... yeah kind of. 
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm... self defense/survival? I don't want to make money at it, but it would be nice to never have to worry about it at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wcy8uLjRHPM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wcy8uLjRHPM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those aren't "Alt-Right" those are the original fascists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed; it does seem like a "disaster zone" from the perspective of people who think that anything short of a gated community is a "disaster" to live in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Accurate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not "alt", original.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consumer confidence is at a 16 year high.

Really... and yet spending is markedly down... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing spinning harder than you would be the founding fathers in their graves... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like toxicity is what the OP was trying to ask about rather than symptoms but if it is symptoms it's basically unanswerable.

Yeah I know that's how you feel, the problem is that isn't what was written.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean people who couldn't vote because they were removed from the voter registration lists. FTFY

No, that's not what I mean... the majority of people who didn't vote were not disenfranchised, they just... didn't vote. A *majority* of Americans didn't vote, and frankly, unless you're seriously trying to bullshit that the *MAJORITY* of Americans were disenfranchise... 

More people didn't vote, than voted... and I'd love a citation on these numbers of yours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
