<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9743</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 06:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-27 17:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~Hehehe the name looks like Dildo.~~ 
But thanks, I have like 0 avvies on my account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 05:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I opened the picture and thought it wasn't loading because it already is my desktop background! Haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 05:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure where you work but the Special Education system in my area is probably the shittiest thing I've ever had to go through. It's not my own experience alone, but the experience of my brother as well.

In my high school days I was severely depressed and I was finally diagnosed with Bi-Polar disorder when I turned 18. Before the diagnosis, my teachers didn't know what to do with me because I was either acting out or sleeping through class. They put me into a "special program" in order to help me. There was really nothing special about it, seeing as the people who were supposed to check up on me never did and I ended up dropping out.

My brother has been an odd child since he was born, and in about 2nd grade it was determined he was Autistic. Not so bad to the point where he couldn't talk, but he is a social recluse, extremely awkward, and couldn't read/write until about 5th grade. He had an aid for most of his middle school years, and due to the lack of help that I got at my high school he went to another one in a different town where they assured he would be taken care of. As of right now he is a junior and I hear all the time how he is bullied. I have recently learned that the person who was his aid through freshman and sophomore year got fired and replaced due to the poor performance rating of the school. Since they were let go, it seems my brother has been forgotten about. We no longer get updates on his progress and I don't think he's getting the counseling he needs any more.

As you may be able to tell, I have little faith in the special education system. My question to you is, do you have faith in it? I know as a special ed teacher you must have some, but do you ever see the students you are supposed to be helping forgotten about either by the teachers faults or the fault of the system? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 05:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh, I see what they did. They took a [simple white mask](http://www.masksz.com/images/white-mask/white-mask-2.jpg) and painted it. Then put toilet paper rolls for eyes and cardboard for the spiky parts? Weird. Would have been easier with paper mache.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 05:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He made all the individual masks. Very dedicated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 20:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [These three](http://i.imgur.com/4g8RV.jpg) pulled off the best MM cosplay I've seen in person. Met them back at Anime Boston 2009. They were all super nice and dedicated, the Happy Mask Salesman even had music playing from his back pack! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 05:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *How I discovered KPop:*

My friends and I were sitting around a computer late at night surfing through youtube. Somehow we ended up on Haru Haru and we were all in love. We scrolled through the related videos for hours. This was right around 2ne1's debut, so we watched Fire over and over. That night we discovered some of my favorite bands, BigBang, Wonder Girls, 2ne1, Girls Generation, Super Junior, and so on. In all honesty, I'm happier than I've ever been since I found kpop. It sounds lame, but the obsession that my friends and I all share has brought us closer together.

*How I discovered /r/kpop:* 

At first I didn't really understand reddit. I didn't know you could subscribe to subreddits, or unsubscribe from the default ones. About a month into my membership, I was getting the hang of it and started following literally everything that interested me. Of course I subscribed to /r/kpop. I also subscribed to /r/asianladyboners, which has a lot of those sexy kpop stars. I don't really post on this subreddit a lot but I love it when it shows up on my front page. If I don't have the time or forget to check koreaboo/allkpop, I get my news here. It's actually quite convenient. Thanks to all those people who keep this subreddit up to date! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 08:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This woman claims her size 38 KKK breast implants saved her life by acting as air bags in a car accident.](http://mommysdirtylittlesecret.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/article-0-11A35AC3000005DC-708_468x515-e1328847980537.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 07:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To hyperlink, put the text you want the link to say in brackets [ ] and right next to it put the image/website/whatever link in parentheses. ( )

If you forget, click formatting help under the comment box. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 06:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend's son loves Batman. [I hope yours does too.](http://i.imgur.com/p8pYT.jpg)

Also: [worse edit, but more kid's face.](http://i.imgur.com/fv1dP.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-15 21:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first time I've seen his face, I always imagined him to [never be facing the camera.](http://www.cinecultist.com/archives/lemony.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-15 17:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Had to be done.](http://i.imgur.com/uaFem.jpg)

EDIT:

[This one too.](http://i.imgur.com/fEu9S.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 05:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I know this one does. I've heard people say things like, "boys will be boys" and "it'll help you in the long run!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 04:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mary is a human and all humans are children of God. So God impregnated his daughter and made her the mother of himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Maury show looking for guests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 21:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-02 07:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love transparent pets, although I'm not a big fan of Moehogs. I think I'll keep zapping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-02 07:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, she was a pound find! I'd like a nicely colored Poogle as well, but I'm scared of a species change. I waited all day poogle day 2009 to get him!

Edit: I got a gender change the other day and I keep forgetting that he's a she now D:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Decided to give the lab another shot, after 4 days of zapping I got this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 19:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 01:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened to me as well, although I'm pretty sure I'm one of the few success stories. It was my lab account and had a lot of NP / priceless items, so I was really upset. Although, the only thing I wanted from the account was the RN RG Kacheek named after my sister. I told them what happened and they froze the account, and after about 6 months they granted the account back to me. I was lucky none of my pets were transferred away, but I was out about 2mil. Oh well.

In order to further protect myself from future incidents like this I no longer keep my passwords saved and I always log out. I also make sure anything I click on the site does not direct me to another site or anything like that, because that can lead to password phishing. It's kind of pathetic that people use those skills on Neopets of all places.

I would just say to keep pestering them, otherwise they'll forget it and move on. Provide as much information as you can (dates, times, usernames, accounts, etc) and it should work. Keep in mind, TNT is not very good at quick results.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being an adult on this website is difficult sometimes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 21:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 06:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Adalia's mother who has to deal with all the hate she gets from kids like these. Not only is she going to outlive her child but now she has to see people say terrible things about her. Their will seems to be to make Adalia and Natalia feel bad, which is exactly what they are achieving.

I would also like to add that I in no way support what Natalia is doing to her daughter by making her an internet icon for Progeria. It's sort of a shame that she's being so exposed, at least in my opinion. It's also rude for her to ask people to tell her that her daughter is beautiful - because by social standards she is no way *physically beautiful*. She may be beautiful on the inside, I can't tell you that because I don't know the girl. What I can say is people like the girl in this picture may be beautiful on the outside, but they are in no way beautiful on the inside. I suppose I could say that they look on the inside the way Adalia does on the outside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 06:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free will is only truly free until it starts imposing on the free wills of others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 06:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not even about that. No girl that young should spread such hate... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Troy and Abed Krumping to Yelle [YouTube] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 20:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 19:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 16 years old is way too early to classify yourself as a failure. I don't know many people who knew what they wanted out of life at 16 years old. You're at the age where you're just discovering what life has to offer. Don't limit yourself to just one thing right now. Look around, try new things, read new books, do things you'd never expect yourself to do. You'll never know what you love until you try it. 

In short, *you* need to go live *your* life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 18:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like me at 16. I got out of bed, went to school, and left early due to stress-migraines. I never stayed past lunch time. Once I was home, I would crawl into bed and sleep until it was time to start the cycle over again. As stated earlier, I dropped out of school soon after. Once I was out of school, away from that environment I found a sense of freedom and actual happiness. After a while out of school I found enough courage to complete it. That was what worked for me, and I have no idea what will work for you. You will never know until you try. 

At 16 years old, nothing feels like it will ever get better. From what I've experienced, it does get better. It gets a lot better! Don't do anything for anybody else, do everything for you. If you are happy then it will spread to the people around you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 18:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what you've said, they seem a bit hypocritical. They tell you to go do something you enjoy - but only if you can get a career from it? What are you, 18 or 19? You don't need a career right now! You need to live your live and experience a little bit of everything. 

I don't believe you'll disappoint them, I think they're just worried about your future. The world is a scary place and it seems like they'd rather you be in a stable environment. That's just what parents do, it's their job to worry about your future and hope for the best. The thing is, you do not have to listen to them. I'm not sure if a child can ever disappoint their parents, at least not for long. 

My grandfather went to Yale and hoped that his sons would follow in his footsteps. The fact that his younger son died of cancer only heightened his expectations for the other boys. My father wanted nothing to do with that, instead he threw away the Yale legacy and chose a smaller college and got a degree in botany - very different from the doctorate degree in engineering that his father held. This gave the other boys the courage to follow their own dreams. None of them went to Yale and none of them cured cancer, but their father still loves them all.

They just want you to be happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 18:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate it when people say that to me. I've had therapists say things like, "you have no reason to be sad!" I feel like out of all the people out there, a therapist would know that there doesn't have to be *severe* emotional trauma to be depressed. It's something that happens, to some people more than others. Sure, I have thought that I have "no right" to be as sad as I am, but I'm not going to deny these feelings and neither should you.

As a human being, you have every right to feel what you feel and express it the way you want. However, life is a two-way street and others have every right to tell you to "toughen up." My advice? Fuck 'em. They're not inside your head and they can't comprehend what goes on in there. Heck, half the time I have no idea what's going on in my own head.

In my opinion, you don't need to toughen up. You already seem tough enough, you just need to keep your head up a little bit longer. I know this is hard but life is difficult at times. Smile about the little things, enjoy everything while you can. You never know what will happen next, things might get better, or things might get worse - but they will change. Most of that change is up to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 18:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, your parents need to realize that you are a separate being from them. Yes, they created you but they cannot in any way experience your life. Sure, they're probably just doing what they think is best for you but how would they know that? Only you know what is best for you. I hate to use this term, but you only live once. If you don't want to be in school right now, don't waste your time with it and hope that you find your calling. That's not how life works.

For instance, I found my passion after a huge mental break down and a  failed suicide attempt. (Never use Tylenol, it is slow acting and will only shut down a couple of organs causing a painful and prolonged death. Luckily I was found in time to be helped.) Anyway, after a short time in inpatient care and months of outpatient, my parents thought it was best I found something to occupy my time. I had already dropped out of school so they suggested community service. There is a local charity in my town that helps raise money for the homeless every October through a haunted house. I figured I might as well do something while everybody else was finishing up school. A friend took me down there, and I fell in love. After months of building throughout the summer I got to know the owner and I was a scare actress all October. I never thought I would find myself in a place like that but life has a way of surprising you.

I am now in college for creative writing and I hope to some day be able to scare millions of people with my stories. I hope you are able to find the same passion I have. Don't go looking for it - it will find you. I suggest you talk to your parents and tell them you want to find yourself. Assure them that you are not giving up, but let them know that college isn't the only road to happiness. If they want you to be happy they will agree. (Probably not at first though!) Show them you mean what you say and then go on an adventure. 

If you need somebody to talk to, there are many genuine people on Reddit. That includes me. :)

EDIT: Wording. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 06:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is three months late but I thought I would share.

When I was a a freshman in high school I was tormented by a group of girls in my AP bio class. The way the curriculum in my town is set up, that is mostly for sophomore students. I had transferred from a different school in a different town earlier that year (due to bullying - go figure,) so an exception was made for me. I don't know if it was because the girls felt threatened by a younger student being in their class, or maybe because they didn't like my face (I've been told I have a constant scowl on my face and intimidating eyes,) either way they decided to hate me. Two girls from my bio class would give me dirty looks and laugh whenever I passed by, but it was something I was used to so I let it slip. They were the standard "popular girls" you see in a movie, the tanned to the bone type with a ringleader, a lackey, and multiple followers.

I began to receive random friend requests on social media sites and I was hopeful that people from my new school wanted to be friends with me. Well, I was wrong. I got constant messages and comments from the two girls and their friends. (I should probably mention that this was around the fall of myspace and the rise of facebook, so most of the bullying happened online.) This was over 4 years ago so the conversations aren't fresh in my mind, but there are still snippets that I remember clearly. Most of the comments consisted of the classic "you're an ugly bitch!" and evolved into "you don't have any friends" sometimes degrading into "kill yourself, nobody would even come to your funeral!"

I never had any real encounters with them until the week before Christmas break my freshman year. I was looking for a place to eat lunch, I usually ate with my older sister in the hallway but somebody had been pestering us so we went into the lunch room. We saw an empty table, and since it was already half way through the lunch period we figured nobody else would be sitting there. I bought a pretzel and sat down. Next thing I know, the two girls from my bio class were sitting at the table across from me and staring daggers. I continued eating, but they didn't look away. I look up again and we make eye contact, the ring leader started yelling at my sister and I. She called my sister names and told us we had taken her table. I still had a mouth full of pretzel when she was yelling at my sister, so I stood up and spit a whole chunk in her face. She screamed and security escorted me out of the cafeteria. I don't know if the lunch room was clapping because I was being escorted out by the Rent-a-Cop or because I had spit at the bitchy popular girls. I was not suspended because it was so close to Christmas vacation.

What I didn't realize at that moment was the fact that since I had reacted to their bullying that would only fuel the fire. Over Christmas break I got more and more messages from the girls, many from a girl I had never met before. I'm not going to post her name here, but it started with an M. M went on and on about what a disgusting person I was. I snapped, after the messages from earlier in the school year, the rumors they spread, the sniggers and giggles behind my back, the shouts across the hallway, and finally the incident the week before I refused to take any more. I told her flat out that she and her friends should just die and make the world a better place. She didn't message me back after that. In fact, she didn't come to school after that. She died later that year due to a heart disease that she had been struggling with in secret all her life. She was only 16 years old.

When I heard that she had died I was overcome with a lot of emotions. At first, I was elated. I thought she had gotten what she deserved, I felt that I had won. After a bit of time, I cried. I came to realize that she was a girl who hadn't even gotten to live her life yet, she was a beautiful person, maybe not mentally but physically she was gorgeous. I thought about the things she was going to miss out on and the roads her life could have taken. In my mind, she is no longer my bully or my enemy but a fellow human being. I wish she was here to grow up and maybe see the mistakes she had made and repent for them. I've already forgiven her.

I regret the words I used that day and I'm glad, for your sake - not theirs, that you didn't didn't get a chance to follow through with your plan.

**TL;DR:** I told a bully I wished she was dead and she died shortly after. Crazy realization ensued. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 03:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. What is your favorite installation in the Zelda series?

2. Who is your favorite Zelda pairing?

**EDIT**  Really glad I follow you on tumblr, otherwise I'd miss this D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You graduated collage? [FB] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 03:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're going to die anyway, just go pee. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 02:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 11:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a couple of these saved on my other computer but never knew who the artist was. Yay! Thanks so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 10:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! I love them all :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 09:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rage Face x Finger Bump is my OTP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm making a Yaoi 'Bingo' game for a panel at a convention! Any pictures you think should be included? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 09:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sinentests would say... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 06:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-12 01:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost it when the dog wiggled away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-11 19:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you crack your knuckles, the sound is gasses in the knuckles being pushed and released. As we all know, an excess of gasses can cause pressure and pressure can cause an uncomfortable feeling. When the pressure from the knuckles is released, it gives you a sensation of relief.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 22:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My heart sank while reading this. I know as a single human being I can't even make a dent in all the terrible things that we do to one another, and I know I haven't been the best person either. After reading all the tweets last night, a the ones specifically mentioning Hiroshima and Nagasaki were the ones that offended me. It being 3 am combined with the fact that I had slept all day, I decided it might be beneficial to reply to the people who had spouted such offensive nonsense. I went to Hiroshima and Nagasaki websites and found medical photos of the victims and sent them to the original tweeters. The way I saw it, maybe if they saw that the events they were joking about contained real people who suffered extreme pain, they might think differently.

[This](http://imgur.com/5DFTC) was the conversation I had with one of the boys whose tweets you can see on that article. I was extremely discouraged with the fact that he continued to joke and try to validate his opinions, even try to persuade me at one point. I took these screenshots to send to his mother and father. After I told him that, he deleted all the posts. Later on today we had [this](http://imgur.com/ya03k) conversation with him and another friend. I'm not saying I feel defeated, because maybe the things I've said will settle in the back of his mind and one day he'll have an epiphany - but that's nowhere close in the future. The sad thing is, this boy is 17 years old. No 17 year old should be filled with so much hatred for a country that did nothing other to him than make the cars that killed his friends dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 20:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, I didn't take into account that the picture could be quite old. Also, after a quick internet search I found a [$30 fetal pig dissection kit](http://www.enasco.com/product/LS03815M) complete with a (from what I can tell, real) 4"-7" preserved fetal pig. Even though what you said earlier about how going to a butcher would be easier is true, apparently it's easier to get preserved fetal pigs than I had thought.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
