<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8145</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are there no Walmarts in Iraq? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 02:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they're all Targets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] If Shane was still with the group, how would things with the Woodbury have panned out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 07:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watching The Talking Dead and they mentioned how Rick was doing a lot of Shane-like things in tonight's episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYCC Melissa McBride question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 19:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know the source to this? Why was she tearing up? 

[Its the 4 gifs. You gotta scroll down a little](http://zuzzolek.tumblr.com/post/99763850164) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys, it's tonight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 19:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grammar/Style question. What's a good way to organize a flashback? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 21:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Person A in a car with Person B. Person A says something that reminds Person B about Person C. Person B remembers an event (and dialogue) that happened with Person C. Person A interrupts their thoughts and brings them back. 

I'm already in a past tense. What do I do for the past past tense? And how do I handle the transition back from flashback to present, where the story is taking place. 

Thank you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extreme haunted house where you are bound, gagged, terrified ... "Live your own Horror Movie" [xpost from r/wtf] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 01:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] conspiracy theory about balloons in the air that manipulate the weather or something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 17:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like last year I was talking to this girl at Publix. And my friend from the Netherlands was with her. And we had super cold weather at the time. And they started talking back and forth about how some type of balloon or something in the sky was leeching out chemicals that were effing with the weather. And they were looking at me like I was dumb for not going along with it. But it was a specific word they used and I cant even think of it right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NOTW] Plot question and motivation, Ch 82. [Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 16:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please no spoilers after ch. 82!!

I'm listening to the audiobook version of Kingkiller Chronicles (which is so good btw! The narrator is awesome). 

I started to get a little lost on why Kvothe left the arcanium (or the school he was at). 

1. Why did he leave the arcanium? It seems like there was $$ motivation. But he's not making any money (with the exception of the draccus scales and I guess some other poison or something they found at that abandoned fort/greystone rock place they were hiding). 

2. Can someone remind me how Denna came into the picture again during their current excursion? She's looking for her patron, but that seemed to get brought up AFTER Kvothe found her. Why was she injured?

3. What's the deal with the wedding? Why does Kvothe care? 

4. Did Kvothe think the Draccus's destruction was the Chandrian and then he was like ... crap, it's a Draccus. I guess I'll kill that since I'm already here and it's causing destruction. 

5. Ch82 specifically. Kvothe woke up all bandaged up. The innkeeper was like "you need to stay here" but Kvothe did something with "drab" and something melted ... this seemed to convince the innkeeper to let him go. What did Kvothe do? 


I've been following along pretty well until then. But this current storyline has me a bit confused about what's going on. 

Thank you guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vince Vaughn and Colin Farrell confirmed, with Rachel McAdams rumored to be joining them. TD: The Rom-Com? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 22:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nicolas Cage is starring in a reboot of the spiritual thriller Left Behind. Ummm, why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 22:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Geico commercial totally made me laugh. Common horror hiding places ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 22:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have about $50 worth of unused tokens from TomorrowWorld. Do I get automatically reimbursed or do I have to do something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 21:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When do most people on ff.net tend to browse fanfics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 01:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words, when is the best time to post your material?

Like I get the whole "if you write good stuff they will come" idea. But my friend would make sure her items on eBay ended on a weekend bc that's when The bids got higher.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andrew Lincoln, Behind the Scenes for Mens Fitness (a few more pics in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 02:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aside from your house, where do you end up spending the most time reading, recreationally? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 21:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hot to Trot (1988). Or lesser known "Movies So Bad They're Good". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 04:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like in the 80s they must have greenlit everything. 

Starring: Bobcat Goldthwait and John Candy's voice as the horse. 

Fred P. Chaney (Bobcat Goldthwait) receives as inheritance after the death of his mother a speaking horse (John Candy) that also has good knowledge about the stock-market. With the help of this horse Fred gains a lot at the stock-market of Chicago.

[Trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-mRE4Hoe5dQ)

Do you have any other gems? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone expand on this comment about bench press by Sam Briggs? What video is she talking about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 02:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elizabeth or "Epiphanies dont make appointments." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 01:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FREE: California by Edan Lepucki, Limited time offer by Ford Motor through goodreads. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 18:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buster Keaton? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 06:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who reads current releases? Where do you go to find upcoming, new releases for books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 15:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I typically use Entertainment Weekly ... 

I was just wondering what those of you who stay updated on current releases go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McSweeney's: William Blake, Color Analyst for the Atlanta Braves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 17:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did you first get introduced to fanfiction? And what fandom did you first get introduced to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 15:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had honestly never even heard of fan fiction until a few years ago (Uh, I'm 33, female, btw). I'm curious if certain types of fandoms tend to hear about fanfics before other types (like My Little Pony people will get into fanfics a lot earlier than, say, Supernatural or Battlestar Galactica type folk ....) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Big Driver" from Stephen King's Full Dark, No Stars getting the Lifetime treatment, Oct 18 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 04:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I searched the subreddit but didnt see any threads about this sooooo ... http://www.mylifetime.com/movies/big-driver

Lifetime's first go at a Stephen King work. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Kindle] Angelbound, FREE. Over 800 four and five star ratings on goodreads. Paranormal, dark fantasy, romance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 20:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fall TV Preview: 6 new series premiering. What are you going to check out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 17:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. The Flash (CW, Tuesdays, 8pm) - egghead nerd guy turns into fastest man alive. Superheros, hello!

2. Marry Me (NBC, Tuesdays, 9pm) - opposites attract style rom-com. 

3. Red Band Society (FOX, Wednesdays, 9pm) - teen, hospital drama. Reminds me of Glee for some reason

4. Transparent (Amazon, Sept 26th) - This family drama is about an LA dad hasn't told his adult kids that he's now living as a woman. Created by Jill Soloway of Six Feet Under

5. How to Get Away With Murder (ABC, Thursdays, 10pm) - hyperambitious law students (including Alfred Enoch from harry potter and Matt McGorry from OITNB) get mixed up in a homicide that involves their criminal law profressor (Viola Davis). "sexy and suspenseful", Viola Davis commands attention "even when she's just writing *very forcefully* on the blackboard"

6. The Affair (Showtime, Sundays, 10pm) - the "high concept serial", Noah (Dominic West) is a writer with a wife (Maura Tierney) and 4 kids - and a mistress, Alison (Ruth Wilson), who's married to a rancher (Joshua Jackson). During the pilots first half, a detective interrogates Noah about his affair. The 2nd half shifts to Alison's perspective, allowing her to revise Noah's story. Who do you trust? Who knows?!


Pulled from latest issue of Entertainment Weekly! 

edit: Gotham, Constantine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Kindle] The Interestings by Meg Wolitzer, $4.99. Cheapest I've seen it ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 15:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Music] [IYL] John Legend "All of Me", [YML] Nick Hakim "I Don't Know" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 02:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3xt54qePa8c

:D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women taking a stab at directing horror films. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 02:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grabbed an Entertainment Weekly magazine and they have a snippet on women directors of horror movies coming up this fall. Here are some of the points they made. 

* In the past 5 years, only 5% of studio releases had a woman director
* BUT THIS FALL! FIVE female directors are taking a stab at the "unladylike" genre of horror, including: *Honeymoon*/Leigh Janiak, starring Rose Leslie (GoT), cabin in the woods vacay goes wrong; *See No Evil 2*/Jen and Sylvia Soska, DVD release; *A Girl Walks Home Alone At Night*/Lily Amirpour, Elijah Wood is is an executive producer, described as a "vampire Western"; *The Babadook*/Jennifer Kent, children's book that comes to life. 
* Women make up 51% of the audience at horror films according to PosTrak
* Jennifer Kent told people about Babadook and said "Their faces would drop. It was like I was saying I was directing a porno." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] [Spoilers] The Martian by Andy Weir, directed by Ridley Scott ... will it lose it's humorous edge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 02:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked the book. And I think it would do well adapted as a movie with its catastrophe after catastrophe tense plot. Ridley Scott directing this is a bit conflicting for me because I'm so used to Aliens, Promotheus. And those are just full of a dark, sinister, humorless world. And I thought Mark, the main character of The Martian, was pretty calm and optimistic about all the crap that happened to him.

I thought I'd get a better discussion here ... than in movies. I think Matt Damon is supposed to be Mark Watney. And there's talks of Jessica Chastain and Kristen Wiig (who, for the love of me, I cant figure out who'd she be cast as!) also starring. 


One last thing! i think the martian was also self-published? Which is awesome for self publishing. And I thought Scott was also affiliated with Hugh Howey's Silo series. So, yay for self-publishing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2014 Cast announced this morning! Scroll down for list. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 15:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So is Jillian done with TBL? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 21:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know the specifics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Lifetime] Is anyone going to watch The Unauthorized Saved by the Bell Story tonight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 02:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Entertainment Weekly asked the actors "How do you want to die?" Here are their answers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 00:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Andrew Lincoln:** Maybe a kid should take me out. I texted Scott Gimple yesterday and said, "Promise me, when I die, on the credits sequence, you play Johnny Cash's version of "Hurt.'" And he said, "I can't make that promise." So when I die, even if Scott Gimple decides not to do it, please everybody [at home] play "Hurt."

**Lauren Cohan:** Maggie and Glenn are running through a forest, and there's a horde behind them, and there's nowhere else to go - just a cliff. They hold hands and jump off the cliff and scream all the way down. And it freeze-frames on them with their arms up in the air. 

**Norman Reedus:** If I had my druthers on how I would go, I would just walk away. You would just see me walk down a road like Mad Max and I'd get smaller and smaller and smaller and smaller, and then a little dog woudl run on the road with me and just start following me off into the sunset, and you'd never know what happened to him. 

**Chad Coleman [Tyreese]:** I know I would want it to be heroic. Sacrificing myself for the others would probably be the most compelling way to me. One of those "Everybody go! Just go!"

**Danai Gurira:** She's not going to go down without a pretty epic fight. That's how I see Michonne. That's what I want for her. 

**Michael Cudlitz [Abraham]:** As with everyone, I know it's coming. At some point everyone dies on TWD. I would hope that his death would be befitting of his life, and Abraham did everything hard. As they say in Spinal Tap, it goes to 11. 

edit: formatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitt Romney might run again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 05:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EBOOK READERS: First 5 Sookie Stackhouse books are $2 each on amazon today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 00:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you write good/satisfying endings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 17:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm outlining a story. I have a beginning, a buildup, and a climax. The people have done the thing. And now I'm left with this mess. How do you write a satisfying ending? It's like the party happened and now the janitor is coming in to clean it all up. All the excitement is gone. Who wants to read about the janitor? I'm at a loss here. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I prefer fanfiction.net over archiveofourown.org </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 02:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I posted a new chapter to one of my fics yesterday.  

I get 800 views on fanfiction.net. And I get less than 10 on archive of our own ... 

Does anyone prefer archive of our own over ff.net? 

edit: my bad, it was 21 views on ao3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you have any recommends for "better listens than reads". (ie. well produced, wonderful narrators) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 16:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got finished with Unbroken by Laura Hillenbrand. The story was amazing but the narrator, Edward Hermann, was excellent. 

Super enjoyable to listen to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever listened to The Great Courses (lecture series)? Any suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 17:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about [these guys](http://www.audible.com/search/ref=a_pd_Scienc_c2_1_auth?searchAuthor=The+Great+Courses). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writers of fanfiction - what's your process? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 18:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm finding as I write more and more stuff, I'm following this trend of Post, rough draft, edit, post, rough draft, edit. Which is all fine and good. But I find I stagger my chapters a bit so I dont get tunnel vision working on just one chapter. 

It looks something like: Post ch 1, write initial draft for ch 3, edit/revise ch 2, post ch 2, initial draft for ch 4, edit/revise ch 3, post ch 3, etc ... 

I think it helps break up the process. Since Im doing my final revisions on previous chapters while I'm about to post the next chapter, I think it helps me with continuity mistakes as well. 

I was just curious how other people write their fanfics. I follow some writing subreddits, but those people tend to write novels and are a bit more "serious" about things ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fanfiction.net question: If you signed up to be a betareader, where do the requests show up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 19:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how do you submit your stuff for other people to betaread?

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If TWD was real, who do you think would be making out on the down low? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 02:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homeland - watching the first season and just wanted to fangirl with some people ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 23:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, Someone lent me the Homeland DVDs and Im about 8 episodes in on the first season (so no spoilers please!) 

But watching some of the show reminds me of my job. I do chemistry stuff and we basically have to prove everything. Even when everyone's hunch is correct on the manufacturing floor ... it's like you gotta still prove it to convince to other people. So seeing Carrie struggle through that was something I could kind of connect with. And I have a "Sal" at work who kind of talks me through that so I can present a better case to management. 

Anyways, it was just a dumb thought I had but I wanted to share. 

Also, I have recently watched the first season of The Americans. And I found it easier to "get into" The Americans where Homeland took me a bit longer. But I really do prefer the season long story like Homeland has versus the (mainly) episode by episode plot of The Americans. 

Last thing: the show is really interesting to me because Carrie is nuts but in a realistic way. And I had heard so much buzz about the show but her character was not at all what I was expecting! I thought she was going to be smooth and calm and collected, but NOPE! Her character is really great. 

I cant wait to see how this season ends! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Books into TV: OUTLANDER by Diana Gabaldon. Yay or nay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 15:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a commercial that they're going to make OUTLANDER by Diana Gabaldon into a television series on [Starz](http://www.starz.com/originals/outlander).

I've heard good buzz about Outlander but I guess I was under the impression it was a Harlequin Romance type thing ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know where these pants are from? Julie Foucher from Regionals. Sorry dont have a bigger pic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 03:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rainbow Rowell (author of Fangirl and Eleanor   Parks) speaks out on writing Harry Potter fan fiction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 23:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't mind hairy guys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 06:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you embed twitter posts and youtubes in the live updates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 01:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the nba one. I'll add the link later bc I'm on mobile  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We're live! 2014 CrossFit Games! Message me if you'd like to update and contribute! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 23:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laura Lippman: Hardly Knew Her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 17:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Darren Aronofsky reportedly adapting Margaret Atwood's Oryx and Crake books for HBO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 16:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any thoughts on this? I have read Oryx and Crake and never once thought, "Hey, this would make a great tv show!" Needless to say, I'm intrigued. I hope Aronofsky is more Black Swan and less Noah ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Viewing the 2012 election from the perspective of today ... OR what are your thoughts about the ideal foreign policy in light of Russia/Ukraine   Israel/Hamas situations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 02:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, 

I was remember the 2012 election when Romney was like "Obama isnt a great supporter of Isreal" (loosely quoted) and how Obama ridiculed Romney for calling Russia a geopolitical threat ... 

And I wonder if US would have stated we were strong supporters of Israel from the get-go if some of this escalation would have happened. Its like the parents have turned their backs and now the kids are slapping each other. 

What is the conservative way to look at foreign policy these days? And what do liberals have to offer? It seems to be a mixed bag with neither party having a consistent platform.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Printable Nutritarian checklist! [PDF] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 19:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you sync between your audible app bookmarks and kindle paperwhite? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 16:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello!

I have seen Amazon be like, "Hey you can sync seamlessly between audiobook and ereader and not lose your place!" or something like that. 

But I have an audible account. And I have a paperwhite. All under the same amazon account. And my bookmarks, as far as I can tell, arent carrying over to my ereader if I listen to a chapter on the audible app. 

I expected it to just work automatically but it's not doing it. Am I confused about the capabilities of amazon or do I need to do something extra to execute this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are movies you thought were really good growing up but realize now they totally weren't? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 18:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mac and Me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Season 1 Recap by Eli Roth. Started watching S2.E1 and this helped me a lil bit .... [Season 1 spoilers only plz] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 20:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did you know Sally Ride had blue eyes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 22:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, one blew this way and one blew that way. 



[Someone wrote a biography about her so I thought I'd throw this one out there to commemorate - Sally Ride:America's First Woman in Space] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy made his pet lizard Peperonie a birthday treat and it just made me smile that's all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 02:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FYI: Season 2 premiers on July 11th, this Thursday! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 19:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mechanical car question for my fanfic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 23:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! Im writing a storyline in a post apocalyptic world (okay its the walking dead). And I want them to get a flat tire. Can you just find any ole other car and fit another tire on it? I just need my characters to go for a stroll but be able to fix the tire. Can you fit a tire from a Honda on a Ford? I dont know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Genius! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-29 19:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mortified Nation (2013) - a documentary where people read from their adolescent journal. Funny and sometimes touching. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 06:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where are you going to watch the World Cup match on Sunday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 15:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to go all the way downtown. I was curious if you guys knew of any places (aside from Taco Mac ...) that are fun to go to, World Cup viewing, and beer friendly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have any good suggestions for funny fanfictions? Like Arrested Development, Modern Family? Or any laugh out loud? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 18:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preferably not rated M! 

I just dont know of m[any]. 

Even based off of: the office, married with children, anchorman, ... anything really.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FREE: Go The F--k to Sleep narrated by Sam L Jackson (just 6 min long) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 23:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you give me a vampire diaries lineage and origin tldr? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 14:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I feel like I should know this but I really dont. 

Can you tell me who made the following people vampires: Elena, Damon, Stefan, Katherine, Caroline, Lexi? 

And Silas is the "first" vampire? And Klaus was made a vampire from a separate curse?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Random venting! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 00:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Gabe is smart and he's powerful in his own sense. I just think it's really annoying how Cat is always like "Vincent we cant be together" and she stays there and stares at him until they make out. And like every single episode seems to end with Vincent and Cat talking on her roof! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CrossFit (or whatever you like to do) is probably cheaper than a bad diet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 05:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know where the other thread went, but I tried to comment and it got deleted. 

This is probably super embarrassing. I spend SO MUCH on fast food. But maybe this might be interesting to some people (who don't EVER eat out) to understand how expensive it can be to eat out. 

For me, eating unhealthy costs a lot of money. 

On a typical day through the week, I will spend: 

*Breakfast: $11 for a coffee, sandwich, and cheesecake brownie at SBUX

*Lunch: $10-15 (sushi, Wendys salad and soda with fries, etc, you name it)

*Dinner: Skip or do some $7-$11 fast food deal. 

 And I've done a "where does your money go" on my checking account and my food/alcohol spending averages right at $700 PER MONTH (on just food!).  I spend most of it M-F when I go to work. 

I have to make changes with my diet because it's killing my pocketbook AND my physique. 

And I have changed my eating since June. I have stopped the morning coffee runs. And I'm buying grocery store food and actually preparing meals. So I'll see how the money works out this month! But I spent like $50 at the grocery store this week and I'm still eating off the food after 4 days. (When before, I'd probably be at around $100 already).  And just after these 4 days, I FEEL better. 

At this rate, I should have an extra $350 just in food savings alone. My membership at a CrossFit costs less than $150. 

TLDR: If you have a shitty diet full of fast food, you can probably afford CrossFit. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BJ Upton seems to be showing SOME signs of improvement. Are any of you guys optimistic that this might be long-term? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 05:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Homerun tonight and the last 5 games, he's had some sort of RBI. Do you think this is a fluke? Has he changed something over the past few games? 

I havent been TOO up on the games this season. But I've seen the last few (including the game on May 22 where the Braves actually came from behind and won! BJ did wonderful that night). Is this a new BJ I'm seeing or has he just been lucky?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crossfit is not a sport - judges are volunteers, the athletes have to pay to compete, and the rulebook has stupid rules. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 04:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it acceptable to write FF on reality tv shows? ie "real people" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 16:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that fanfiction.net does not really have any reality tv shows. 

Is it uncool to do like Survivor fan fics? or Real World? Is that kind of stuff welcome on Archive of Our Own? 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can CrossFit HQ learn anything from yoga (Yoga Alliance)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 03:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that CrossFit and yoga are pretty different. But I was reading [this article](http://americanyogaschool.com/yoga-alliance-ruining-yoga/) and came across the following quote: 

There are great teachers out there. But they are great in spite of Yoga Alliance, not because of it. These skilled teachers pushed themselves, and their teachers pushed them, beyond the mild standard that Yoga Alliance created. We need a body that ensures that all yoga teachers are appropriately educated. 

and there's also this: 

Since 1999, minimum standards for yoga teacher training have been authored and administered by Yoga Alliance. According to Pam Weber, their Director of Credentialing, Yoga Alliance currently has about 40,000 yoga teachers and 3,000 yoga schools registered as being in compliance with their standards, far more than any other such organization. To the untrained eye, they seem to be the gold standard for yoga teacher training standards. But, the standard that they set for yoga teacher training is nowhere near adequate. And it's ending up with a lot of people getting hurt, and far more people walking away from their first yoga classes disappointed and wondering what all the hype is about.

How often do you hear something like that about CrossFit?! Well, William Broad of the New York Times has written quite a few articles on the dangers of yoga (and there's no weight involved in yoga .... so I am not surprised by the hate CrossFit gets). 

Instead of telling trainings what should be taught, Yoga Alliance simply requires that a certain number of hours be spent covering each of five areas of study, with no specificity given on how to fill those hours. As listed on their website, registered 200-hour trainings (the level that 85% of their registered yoga teachers hold) must include 100 hours of practice, 25 hours of teaching methodology, 20 hours of anatomy, 30 hours of philosophy and ethics, and 10 hours of practice teaching. But, the content of each area of study is left up to the school. As Weber explains, "How do you monitor such diverse populations? 

My friend's 200 hour yoga teacher training was like bootcamp whereas mine was more like group therapy (like seriously every week someone would cry). Huge differences between the studios and what they teach exist. There is no standard work on how to run a teacher training.  (Which reminds me of the workouts you get at boxes. This guy focuses more on strength, but these guys sure do a lot of metcons ...)

And thinking about how I got my 200 hour certification at a studio recognized by Yoga Alliance (and I'm sure that studio pays some money to YA every year to keep that ability to stamp my certificate with the Yoga Alliance logo), I have a hard time not thinking about boxes paying money to HQ to keep that "CrossFit" name on their box. 

I dont know if this will really impact anyone. But I think HQ could look to yoga and see what their organization could learn from it. 

The yoga postures came from India (just like the CrossFit movements have existed in some form or the other outside of CrossFit ... ). And I fear that CrossFit will just do what some of the more annoying figures in yoga history have done. Like Bikram Chodhuroy patented yoga postures (26 postures done in a specific temperature in a specific order but still.... kind of a dick move but he made a lot of money). And now yogaglo has also filed a patent on how to film a yoga class and that really created a lot of ire within the yoga community. 

Anyways, blah blah thanks for reading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do we think about all the pic posts? Please upvote for visibility! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 01:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

Thank you guys so much for making this subreddit what it is. I really love seeing all the pics and advice here. 

The mods have received a few complaints about all the pic posts. Especially the "hey, look at my hair" ones. I dont really know how to stop these. And I personally don't know if I want to. All the other health and beauty subreddits seem to allow the "hey check me out" posts. And I dont want this to be a text only subreddit. 

But I know the pic posts can be super annoying and gratuitous. There's a fine line b/n showing your locks and karma whoring. 

Do you guys have any suggestions or input on this situation? 

Edit: thank you guys for all your comments and suggestions! We will keep everything the same. In the future, we might add some type of filters to hide link posts. Or we will can add a weekly/biweekly look at my hair posts. Again, thank you for contributing to our community! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trending story on Facebook: McCann leads Yankees homer barrage in win vs Red Sox. Kinda happy but kinda hurts :/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 02:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [MOVIE] a group of 20-somethings are hunted by some military power? fairly recent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 00:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm watching a movie called Tomorrow When the War Began and it reminded me of a trailer I saw about 2 or 3 years ago. 

It was just a trailer but I felt like the movie was about this attractive group of 20-somethings (around Jessica Biel's age? A little younger) running away from a military/government power. I cant recall there being any supernatural/mutant powers involved. I remember wanting to see the movie but I never heard about it after it got released. I also recall surburbia, guns, people hiding while getting shot at ... 

I felt like there were attractive people in it - like Jessica Biel and the actor who plays Captain America (but I doubt it bc the movie would have been more popular if it really had them in the movie)

Ugh, I hope that's enough. This is really bugging me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> mrw when i heard james franco texted a 17 year old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 06:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heads up! Rifftrax (MST3K) are going to be on NatGeo for 3 hours on April Fools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 07:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Total Riff Off](http://channel.nationalgeographic.com/channel/total-riff-off/)

We'll see how this goes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What qualifies a movie as "torture porn" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 21:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I would assume Serbian Film and things like that. 

But then I heard someone say that Hostel was torture porn. Along those lines, would Saw then be considered as torture porn?

Or is TP something that's different depending on who the watcher of the film is? Is there an agreed upon def'n of TP?

Sorry I'm on my cell so hopefully I make sense! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Season 4 Questions. Confused about Rick and the whole farm-on-the-prison thing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 00:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What to Watch This Week? Jim Henson's Creature Shop - Syfy, Tuesday Mar 25 10pm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 22:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a weekly post on the weekends that tells us what to watch out for on tv this week? 

Well, Jim Henson's Creature Shop is premiering this week on Tuesday. Just thought I'd throw that out there! (Mar 25th, 10pm, Syfy). 
I dont know why I'm so excited about this show! I feel like it'll be what I wanted Face Off to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Agents of Shield: Did anyone stick with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 01:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Marvel: Agents of Shield was poorly received on this subreddit. Especially with Arrow around ...

I personally feel like Agents of Shield got a lot better. I like that Skye isnt romantically involved with anyone right now (even though she seems the obvious choice). They're starting to introduce some other worldly elements. I am just curious if anyone that didnt like the show stuck with it and like it a lot better or is the show still a disappointment to you 

Tag spoilers!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] "Alone" - writer's intentions concerning two of the characters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 17:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of the new characters my favorite has been Liv, the witch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 22:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering what everyone's thoughts were on her! I think she adds "comedy relief" that Damon and Caroline used to do quite a bit. I just hope all her motives don't surround trying to get with Jeremy ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 14.2 - Camille or Taylana? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 18:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's gonna take it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [spoiler] "Time of Death" - I don't understand why Oliver and Sara thought this was a good idea ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 01:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, I've never read the comic and my only experience with Arrow is just with the show! But why would Sara and Oliver show up to the Lance's place together when Laurel was there? 

I love Sara's character and I was not a huge fan of Laurel but, damn, that's cold. Like Sara just showed up in town and then she brings her sister's ex boyfriend to a family event? That's cold! Were we supposed to get upset with Laurel for reacting that way? I think that's really a valid reaction. So I'm not sure how I'm supposed to view Oliver and Sara and Laurel right now honestly. Because I have not really read the comics. But it came across like Laurel is really on her own right now emotionally. She seems to have pushed everyone away. And even when she's right, she's wrong ... pretty much ?

I know this is a little middle school-y but goddamn if that happened in real life shit would hit the fan. Anyways, [bonus fun gif from the episode](https://24.media.tumblr.com/8c64080d0a456e13323efaaebf6dd7e2/tumblr_n1u2s7smqa1tspgq4o1_500.gif).  Thanks for letting me rant a little bit ... 

edit: I thought Felicity and Sara had great chemistry in this episode! I love seeing them be friendly but Felicity having that twinge of jealousy about Sara just being "better" most of the time!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moment of Reflection: Obama mocking Romney for calling Russia a geo-political foe during the election. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 01:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [spoilers 1x07] Who was the victim in the recent Lake Charles murder? Theory towards the end of the article </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 21:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burial Rites by Hannah Kent follows Agnes, a murderess as she awaits her final punishment. Slated to become a movie starring Jennifer Lawrence! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 01:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just an FYI. 

I've been buying a lot of crap on my Kindle so when I picked this book up, I had a hard time switching to a better writing style! The writing follows around thoughts a lot and retellings of the past. So that might not be everyone's cup of tea. And it's also a total downer. But it's gotten decent reviews. 

[pic of the article talking about the movie.](http://i.imgur.com/3GMk7I9.jpg) I like to read books BEFORE the movie so I just thought I'd share! 

Happy reading :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CrossFit 14.1 Open - I was there and here are some pics of my experience! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 06:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoiler] 1X06 Light of the Way yearbook photo ... 4 females identified elsewhere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 00:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Saw was filmed in 18 days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 03:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a well known thing in the horror community? Thought I'd share. 

Found it from [this link](http://inktank.fi/82-mind-blowing-movies-facts-you-probably-didnt-know/#more-4281)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Ryan Gosling was cast as Noah in The Notebook because the director wanted someone not handsome. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 02:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> True Bromance ... from se01ep06 "Haunted House" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 06:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret Santa LunchBox exchange! Pleasantly surprised - bento boxes and ice tray because why not </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 23:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regarding "anorexic" Rachel on The Biggest Loser controversy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 20:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another question about Tabata - how do you "score" it and is one way preferred over another? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 05:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So at my gym, we record our reps for each 20 seconds of work. After the workout, for the board, you record your LOWEST amount of reps during those 8 sets on the board. 

Example 

Person 1: 7-6-5-5-4-4-4-5 would record 4.  
Person 2: 12-10-8-5-5-3-0-2 would record 0. 

So Person 1 looks better on the board. However, Person 2 ended up doing more reps than Person 1. But, boy, they sured petered out at the end. 

I have always assumed the answer is "well, depends on what you're working on". But thought I'd put it out to the community anyways bc it has kind of bugged me. 

(Also, if you're on the t-shirt swap, I'm sending out the emails tomorrow! Got a bit busy today). 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Bachelor: Clare sleeps with Juan Pablo, exposes the shows weird sexual issues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 04:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a reason Legend of Korra is nowhere to be found on Netflix? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 06:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Haiku] kitten almost falls asleep while gazing at a swinging bell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 05:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any other Kindle or e-readers finding this true? "My Kindle has totally enabled my trashy novel addiction" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 17:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gym T-Shirt Swap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 16:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From [this thread](http://www.reddit.com/r/crossfit/comments/1vw5qx/anyone_up_for_doing_a_gym_tshirt_swap/) there seemed to be bit of an interest in a gym t-shirt swap. 

I want to plan a gift exchange for a blog I have, so I thought this would be great prep for that! 

If you'd like to receive a shirt from another gym and are willing to ship out one from yours, email (theposhest at gmail dot com) me the following, and I will match you up with another redditor. Have the subject line include your Reddit username. 

Name: 

Reddit username: 

Address: EDIT: [OPTIONAL] - at least give me your state and/or country
 
T-shirt Size: (if you're a female, please request your size in a male size shirt as well ... some boxes might only carry just unisex). 

Extras but not required: 

- Can you ship to another country? Keeping in mind, this can be expensive. 

- Can you re-gift? Sometimes people don't follow through on their commitment. Would you be willing to send another shirt out to someone who sent a shirt out but did not receive one in the first place? Essentially, you would ship out two shirts but only receive one (if people do not hold up their end of the bargain, that is). 


I plan on having this one-for-one ...  you ship to the person who is shipping to you. But if you guys want this randomized, we can do that too (where it's a true gift exchange ... where you ship to someone and they ship to someone else). 


Upvote for visibility! 
You'll have until Feb 5th to submit  your name to me. I'll get your your name by Feb 8, 9th and we'd like to have everything shipped out by Feb 22nd? 

I can also set up a google doc and show which username is gifting to whom. Only the usernames will be posted on the Google document. 

What will I do with your information? 
I will have to email your address to your match. I don't use that gmail account for anything. I will delete the emails I receive for this gift swap in March. 

Again, you are making a commitment to ship out a shirt. Don't be a douche. Follow through. Thanks!

EDIT: Hi! I haven't forgot! I'm sending these out tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did any of you guys watch Lifetime's Lizzie Borden? Christina Ricci does "is she cray?" so well </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 19:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Lizzie Borden and Lifetime might not be catered to reddit's demographic BUT.... if any females are out there ... Lizzie Borden was fun to watch. I thought it was fairly graphic for a Lifetime movie. Flowers in the Attic got a lot of buzz but Heather Graham was horrible in it. Christina Ricci (and Clea Duvall) make Lizzie Borden a treat to watch. And the soundtrack is hilarious. 

"Arent you a Sunday School teacher?"

"Only on Sundays"

[sips drink]

Check out the reruns if you get a chance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some helpful tips for those looking to get into porn (nsfw) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 05:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question: female, casual crossfitter, has access to globo ... what do i do at the globo gym considering my goals? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 23:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little more info 

I am about 50 lbs over my desired weight. I'm 5'10" about a size 14. 

I go to CrossFit 2 times a week. Ive been debating whether to go 3 times a week. 

I teach yoga and have access to a globo gym about two times a week. At my previous gyms I've belonged to, I had a real hard time limiting my workout routine and I'd be taking like 2 hours to work out. It's not something I want to do after already spending an hour there teaching yoga. But I would typically do a group fitness class and then spend another hour jumping from machine to machine lifting weights. 

Diet is bad but getting better. I am not the paleo type. If anything I'm more of a whole foods/not processed, minimal meat person. I will not do a diet that forbids things like beans. So paleo is not for me. 

Goals: I'd like to get better at pullups. Right now Im doing ring rows during the WODs. 
I'd also like to lose weight. 
I love lifting weight! So I would like to do that more than twice a week at CrossFit. 

Do any of you guys go to a globo and to CrossFit as well? 

Mine has access to C2 rowers, squat racks, free weights, etc. But no kettlebells, no olympic lifting (or anything using "momentum")

What type of workout do you do at the globo? Do you have any framework you could give me to do at the globo that wont take hours? 

Someone told me if I lift then do the treadmill or elliptical for 30-40 minutes that the cardio will kind of "work against" what I just did in the squat rack. 

But I typically do two lifts. Like Press and Squats. And then I'll jump rope or do sit ups or work on my pullups with the assisted machine. It just seems as if my "programming" makes no sense at the globo gym! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "More Deaths in Surabaya Zoo causing public anger" I've never heard of this Zoo. aka "Zoo of Death" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 17:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jessica Chastain as Princess Merida from Brave (Disney Dream Portrait series, Annie Leibovitz) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 02:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we make this happen? Save Clearly Canadian! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 06:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: Reading a Novel Changes Your Brain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 05:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So who should Falcons fans root for in the postseason? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 22:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! I really don't know that much about football outside of the Falcons. I know I should hate the Saints. 

But which team would a good Falcons fan root for?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> S1E07 question [spoilers obv] about Lady Jayne </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 05:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did she ask that question to Dracula about her husband cheating and then give that advice to Lucy later on? What is her investment in Lucy? I think I missed Jayne's connection to Lucy and Mina .... 

Sidenote - This was a fun episode! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] Is the 3rd book in the Divergent trilogy worth a read if you didn't particularly like the 2nd book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 17:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition I know what happens to Tris at the end (but that's really all I know about the 3rd). 

I liked the 1st book. But the 2nd one was really hard for me to get into. I think Tris is a really confusing character. 

She's supposed to be reliable and multi-factioned which would insinuate to me that she'd be smarter than your average bear. Egs, keeping things from Tobias while at the same time getting mad at Tobias for keeping things from her ... so stupid. 

And she just always seems to fall into some forced conflict by Veronica Roth (especially the arguments between Tris and Tobias. Also, I don't really get Tris' motivations for putting herself in danger all the time .... ). I just honestly don't get the character of Tris (like her motivations). 

Anyways, I thought this sub would be better to ask than the Divergent sub! 

Let me know your thoughts!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REQUEST for hair dryer with a diffuser? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-29 21:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, 

So my hair dryer died. I just need something that actually has some wattage, will last a bit, and has a diffuser (and my last hair dryer, the diffuser wouldnt screw on so I had to duct tape it onto the dryer!). I really just use the dryer to get my hair like 70% dry before I go to bed. Especially in the winter!

I did love my old one though! Vidal Sassoon - it looked a lot like [this one](http://www.amazon.com/Vidal-Sasson-VS505-1875W-Turbo/dp/B000PXYC6U/ref=sr_1_3?ie=UTF8 qid=1388348967 sr=8-3 keywords=vidal+sassoon+dryer) but before I drop a whole $15 on a dryer, I thought I'd hear if there was an obvious better well known choice in the curly hair community! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watching Breaking Bad for the first time. Only in season 2 [season 2 spoilers]. Skyler? Am I supposed to kinda hate her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-29 05:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andrea Ager interview. Talks about SoCal being tough region, stalkers, and how steroid testing in CF is a joke. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 20:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [META] What are you binge watching over the holidays? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 19:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished the first seasons of Breaking Bad. 
Thinking about going into American Horror Story Coven ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tulane Univ sends their doctors-to-be J W to work rounds in the kitchen to learn how to cook healthfully! Food heals :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 03:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kelly Clarkson (Trisha Yearwood, Reba McEntire) - Silent Night [Christmas] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 06:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trayvon Martins Parents Are Planning a Book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 23:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once thought to be un-marketable for organic and whole foods, Whole Foods finds it can play in Boise, ID </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 22:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone posted this and I'm just trying to find the source of this Atlanta map of the neighborhoods. Help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 05:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Butt-hurt Braves fan, enjoy Brian McCann. He was wonderful for the Braves! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 02:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly expected McCann to be a lifetime Braves. But, alas, he's gone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Dean Ornish: Eating for Health, Not Weight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 20:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Generic Questions about Faux Fur Vests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 06:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please help! 

So first off are they still in style? Secondly, if so, would it look okay on a taller girl that is 32 who is not plus size but not a rail thin either? And where could I get one that is still stylish but cheaper? 

Thanks for your help! I want one pretty bad. But I feel like they might be a bit trendy and I dont do trendy very well. 

I'm specifically talking about these types, [longer style from free people](http://www.freepeople.com/swagger-fur-vest/_/searchString/vest/QUERYID/529c1a038570a32bea000144/SEARCHPOSITION/6/CMCATEGORYID/683d4023-53f5-4900-b5ce-ecf465df31a9/STYLEID/29308053/productOptionIDs/F41043CA-B93C-4663-9E51-620B10B9F1F6) (I'd prefer longer because it might help cover up my thighs but I feel like the shorter ones might be easier to find). [Example](http://31.media.tumblr.com/16bffc71a00730cf2223af237481f874/tumblr_mx34nw2jzV1sffuyjo1_500.jpg) OR [laid back Example](http://31.media.tumblr.com/74f38ab758bcb133f4af6d63474e23e0/tumblr_mwrk5q9sOG1r00al8o1_500.jpg) or [Example](http://31.media.tumblr.com/40aca6233e18c61d455c65c94baa1019/tumblr_mx2ogbi8mP1s7b4gco1_500.jpg) or [Example](http://25.media.tumblr.com/ca9c83599da8d9760e577da21861f736/tumblr_mj6zl9RDOi1qj6yu8o1_500.jpg)

Thank you ladies so much! Love this sub  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Santa's sack so big? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 06:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he only comes once a year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you handle mail and errant papers in common areas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 19:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

I am curious how you guys prevent your kitchen table from becoming a dumping ground for bills and other stuff that comes from the mail. Some times I find myself even putting groceries on the table and leaving it there for awhile. 

Let me know if there's a better subreddit for this organization type question! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> layers, ponytail, or a bun ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 04:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/curlyhair - growing sub that needs a mod or 2! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 17:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,

I started a sub that was aimed for people with curly hair. And about a year later, we're at about 6k subscribers! 

Currently, I am looking for someone who can help jazz up the subreddit a bit as well as the reddit alien. 

As far as design abilities, I'm looking for CSS that is close to http://www.reddit.com/r/TrollXChromosomes/ but not as much as http://www.reddit.com/r/fancyfollicles

Also, we do have guys in this sub ... so I would like the design update to not look so feminine. Would like people who are interested in health, beauty, malefashionadvice/femalefashionadvice, etc

Bonus if you can help remove spam and be an active moderator. 

Thank you. 

edit: [r/curlyhair](http://www.reddit.com/r/curlyhair)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Foods that Prevent or Reverse Diabetes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 20:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Dr. Fuhrman's Post](http://www.drfuhrman.com/library/anti_diabetes_foods.aspx)

The list is 

* Leafy green vegetables

* Non-starchy vegetables

* Beans

* Nuts and Seeds

* Fresh Fruits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [Movie] There was a slew of "Beach Party" movies. I can't remember which particular one I saw ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 16:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi. Growing up in the late 80s/early 90s, there was this one particular 'Beach Party' type movie playing on TBS or one of those channels all the time. 

All I got is that it happened at the beach. There was singing. And it seems like the mom and pop were the "famous" actors of that time. And they had teenagers with them (like their kids)? But all the Beach Party movies I've seen are where Avalon and Annette Funnicello are the stars and they don't have kids. I don't know if it was specifically Avalon and Funnicello in the movie either. I just had this impression that they used to be famous (by my mom). 

Since I've only seen one of many beach party movies, I am sure I'm describing them all. But I thought I'd take a stab at it anyways.

But this movie did make rounds in the late 80s early 90s on basic cable! So I feel like someone should know what Im talking about?! 

edit: and I think they TRAVELED to the beach. Like, they didn't live at the beach. but it was a vacation or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Care to take a guess on what the new stadium will be called? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 03:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is gonna get the licensing deal?!

Plz be Costco Stadium  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another perspective: Braves making wise decision. "What are you thinking if you're the Rays? They can't even get one stadium -- and the Braves have two?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 01:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't we find out today if McCann stays a Brave? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 13:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard Ron Gant say that this morning on the news. Such a tease. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What books (w/in the last 5 years ...) would make a good television series? Cast the main players. What network would show it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 06:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just curious what books are out there that might make good tv shows? 

And if you want to add a TLDR of the book series (if it's relatively unknown) that would be super. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "7 stars too talented for their humdrum TV series." Do you have any more to add? Or disagree with the list? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 15:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gawker is not a fan, but I think there's a place for "Slow TV" on television </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 18:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Friday deal. Alien Anthology on blu-ray for under $20! 12 hours only. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 19:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if this is appropriate for this subreddit for "deals" but Amazon is hosting daily black Friday stuff (I guess). And right now we have [the Alien Anthology](http://www.amazon.com/Alien-Anthology-Blu-ray-Sigourney-Weaver/dp/B001AQO3QA/ref=br_lf_m_1001421631_1_1_ttl?ie=UTF8 m=ATVPDKIKX0DER s=movies-tv pf_rd_p=1626807722 pf_rd_s=center-2 pf_rd_t=1401 pf_rd_i=1001421631 pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER pf_rd_r=184Z1XXDTC3VMVTX40MN) for $19.49
It typically runs you about $70

6 Discs, including Alien, Aliens, Alien 3, Alien Resurrection and 2 bonus discs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new book is out. The Simpsons and Their Mathematical Secrets. Author argues there's a lot of math in The Simpsons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 22:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi, I'm Chucky. Wanna play? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 02:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got a sandblasted wine glass from Rabbit Run Road. I wasnt expecting something so personalized for a Halloween Exchange! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 02:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dont usually read TMZ but did today. Apparently Matt's baby mama is in jail (and we thought Elena liked the bad ones), and he won sole custody of their child. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 02:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Poetry] cat gets spooked by windshield wipers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 05:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Delena fans - how do you feel about Elena and Damon now that their love is out and no longer secret or "forbidden"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 18:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like when couples get together in shows, it kills the tension between them. 

I guess I'm wondering since you've had a taste of Delena if you're ready for the wrench to get thrown in their relationship! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found this oddly spiritual/yogic: David Bohm (a scientist) on perception </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 00:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weightlifting - It's a Hard Knock Life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 04:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're interested: Kanye is going to be on Kimmel tonight! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 18:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Letting Beauty Speak Up Itself - good vid by CrossFit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 07:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dane DeHaan looks like the next Leonardo Dicaprio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 06:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who watches Arrow? According to EW, Summer Glau is joining the cast (she was Serenity in Firefly) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 05:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt know that and I'm just excited bc I loved Firefly!

Arrow grew on me its first season. I'm intrigued to see where this season goes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best face of NLDS Game 2. Dee Gordon's reaction to getting called out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 03:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justin Bieber's Bodyguards Carry Him Up the Great Wall of China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 04:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can you go to find (specifically) new horror releases? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 03:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I'm honestly curious about movies on the Paranormal Activity 3 or The Conjuring or REC ... movies like that. Not so much B rated Microwave Massacre type movies. 

I realized I have no clue what's about to release on DVD. Not all theaters really carry a lot of the horror genre so I was wondering if there were good online resources? 

Does anyone have any suggestions?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baselines (sung to the tune of Blurred Lines). Featuring Javy Lopez, Homer, and others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 14:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Periods. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 02:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suggestions for something to wear inside shoes so you don't have to wear socks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 17:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi FFA!

Do you ladies have any suggestions on what to wear with shoes so they don't become smelly! I really like wearing flats. Those [small socks](http://www.aldoshoes.com/us/accessories/mens/socks/93321355-jamar/98) tend to slide off my heel while I'm wearing them; and the ones that don't are too high and they peek up on my heel or front of the shoe sometimes. 

I was wearing these from ALDO - http://www.aldoshoes.com/us/accessories/shoe-care/comfort-fit/56076573-471_072/0
However, they've been sliding forward and bunching up at the toes. Plus, the rubber on the bottom of the terry cloth stuck to my shoe and ripped the ALDO liner apart! And now I have rubber attached to my shoe sole now. But I really liked how I could wash the terry cloth insoles and my foot wouldn't slip. (The ALDO ppl told me to cut the terry cloth insole a little smaller than what I wore. I wonder if that caused the bunching up ... )

Anyways, I was just wondering what you ladies liked to use or if you had any suggestions of good alternatives. 
My major goals are to have some type of liner I can wash or throw away (so I can go sockless!). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just thought this was a fun pic of Bobby Cox. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 04:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MEME] Regarding the sweep of the Nats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 19:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starting to play Braves math ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 16:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Nats play 500 ball for their remaining 50 games, the Braves only need to win 12 of their last 49 to clinch (clench?).

Source: Facebook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Realistically, what should the Braves do with this lineup when Upton gets off the DL? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 01:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to me that the lineup scenarios typically include BJ *or* Gattis (unless Gattis is catching and we know that Fredi is going to keep McCann in for the most part). 

This lineup is golden right now. I'm sure we'll keep it the same til it cools off a little bit. 

But jeez. You're paying Upton $15 million. He got hot at the end of last season. He's *supposed* to be in the lineup. You'll still have Gattis for the bench. Call him up in those pinch hit situations ... 

What would you do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These sandals that Amanda Seyfried is wearing. Or something super similar in the $50-100 range. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 02:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most interesting thing you've ever won? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 20:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dinner with a celebrity? McD's fries? 

Lemme hear it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Better in Black and White: "Raiders of the Lost Ark" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 01:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sookie and Warlow: Where do you WANT it to go versus where do you THINK it will go? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 17:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYC Doctors Are Now Prescribing Fruits And Veggies : The Salt : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 13:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone ever run with a water bottle in bn their back and shorts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 03:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like a win-win. I got water. And I dont have to hold it in my hands. I saw someone on tv do this (sporting event) and they looked like they crushed a little bit of the air out and just had about 1/3 of the bottle sticking out of the back of their shorts. Just wondering if anyone actually did this while running and if the bottle would stay.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dean Ornish: Healing through diet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 00:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [conversation] What benefit or purpose are you seeking with a 30 day water fast? Safe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 04:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I'm a new subscriber to this subreddit, but I have read about and done quite a few fasts in my day. 

I'm seeing a lot of posts about 30 day water fasts. I am a huge fan of Dr. Joel Fuhrman and he has done a lot of amazing things with his medical fasts. But anything that's going to last a month long, he has that patient stay under supervision. 

I have always read that 1-3 days is a good enough length of time for water fasts. I have personally done a 7 day water fast. 

I'm just curious why someone would do a medically unsupervised 30 day water fast? Or maybe, what benefit are you getting for a 30 day water fast that you wouldnt get from a 3 day water fast or even a 7 day water fast? 

Maybe I'm confused on what a 30 day water fast consists of here (I've heard people say they are water fasting ... but find out they are actually eating or drinking calories. To me, that's not a water fast). But a 30 day water fast, woo, I've honestly never have heard anyone suggest that unless they were on the old pro-ana/mia websites. I have read absolutely zero literature on fasting that suggests 30 day water fasts (edit: this is false. I should have inserted "medically unsupervised"). Everything I've read suggests nothing longer than 7 days, max. Most suggest 3 days. If you do the month long "fasts", books I read suggest getting that 800 cals through juicing or fruit/veggies. 

I really am not trying to attack. (I do have preconceived notions if your answer is purely to "lose weight"). But I'm curious about other reasons (like religious or spiritual, etc). Also, if anyone has comments about "detoxing", I'm curious about what literature you've read. Or what influenced you to go the fasting route to detox. 

Anyways, hi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have any suggestions on how to recreate this lemonade recipe with cayenne pepper in it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 15:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ingredients: filtered water, organic lemon, organic agave nectar, cayenne extract (Mexican habanero, jalapeo, African, Chinese, Thai, Korean, and Japanese peppers).

It's basically off the blueprintcleanse.com bottles. I am not quite sure of the ratios. And was curious if someone knew or had a similar recipe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who has a Vitamix? Recipes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 06:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love mine for smoothies!

Do you guys have any recipes? I've tried a few gazpacho recipes but none are really GREAT ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CrossFit trainer has cerebral palsy (CNN) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 05:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> whats ur coming out story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 07:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cosplay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 01:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 21 Photos Of George W. Bush's Visit To Zambia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 23:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FYI: A few articles going around about the downfall of Francouer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 22:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. [The moral of the Jeff Francoeur story](http://www.baseballnation.com/2013/7/1/4483594/jeff-francoeur-royals-designated) (baseballnation.com)
2. [A Requiem for Jeff Francoeur](http://hardballtalk.nbcsports.com/2013/07/01/a-requiem-for-jeff-francoeur/) (hardballtalk.nbcsports.com)
3. [The Jeff Francoeur Era ends in Kansas City](http://sports.yahoo.com/blogs/mlb-big-league-stew/jeff-francoeur-era-ends-kansas-city-royals-designate-082653344.html) (sports.yahoo.com)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the reasons I watch Vampire Diaries. Hint: It's not Ian Sommerhalder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 02:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most interesting/worst thing you've heard after, "Hey, can I talk to you for a second?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 23:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to be usually bad. Especially if you hear it at work ... :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad Luck Braves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 04:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does AO3 have the 'Major Character Death' tag? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 03:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not really deep into the fan fiction world. 

I was wondering why this tag exists. 

To me, it's kind of like a spoiler. Why would someone put it up in the first place?

And is it expected for a work to have this tag if a character dies? 

How about if it is a major character in the real storyline, but not so much one in your fan fiction?

Curious is all. 
Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If my cat could communicate with me in English, would we even get along? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 02:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like she's chill and stuff and always sleeps like right under my armpit at night. But sometimes when I move her bc my arm is going to sleep, she hisses at me. Or she'll sit in between my legs when I'm about to get up (and I think she knows I'm about to get up so she rushes at the last moment to get there), and then I move her and she hisses at me. 

I think if she spoke English, we'd hate each other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I dont want to enter in my CC info on this website. Where can I find glasses similar to these? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 04:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Elvis Presley had a megacolon. His colon was 2 to 3 times larger than average. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 17:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Camille Leblanc Bazinet on the cover of Oxygen magazine! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 15:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Splits? Is this accessible to everyone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 00:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! 

So this ballet guy told me "If you cant do splits by the time you're 30, then you'll never be able to get into them"

I was not able to do a lot of flexibility things ... but with patience and consistency I've been able to move from not being able to touch the ground in a forward fold (at 19) to now being able to palm the ground at 32 years old. 

I was just wondering if anyone knows about the logistics of splits. And if they're possible to most people at most ages. Or do you age out of this one? Are some people's body's just not able to get into this one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any of you guys watch True Blood? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-17 16:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last night I was wondering if the vamps got in a fight, who would win?

It seems as if the Vampire Diaries are younger (not only in the time they were turned ... but as in AGE). The oldest in Vampire Diaries is probably Klaus. From a wiki, he is from the 1400's. 

True Blood characters ... Eric Northman is 900 AD (and he isnt even the oldest). 

And it seems like the True Blood vamps are more brutal and they seem stronger and faster (prob due to HBO's effects budgets but whatevs).

However, I DO think the Vampire Diaries MIGHT be able to have an upper hand because they have the sun rings. If those rings didnt work on the type of vampires in the True Blood realm, I think the Vampire Diaries type of vampires would eventually win out. They are probably fast and strong enough to elude the True Blood guys at night. Enough to wait until day to pull the True Blood guys into the sunlight!

Sorry, things I think about in the off season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Vampire Diaries Audition Videos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-16 02:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joseph Morgan will star in upcoming movie 'Dermaphoria' - a cult Craig Clevenger novel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 05:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Guy Boss: I work in a laboratory. Showed up to work with a sunburn today ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 18:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Falling off the wagon ... (or, "yo yo dieting") </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 06:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, 

I dont know if this is the best subreddit to talk about this. 

But I have been going through this phase of eating right for a week. Then binging for a week. Then eating "normal" (for me, still overeating) for a week. And then starting the cycle over. Sometimes I skip one of these steps or the other, but it's pretty much the same.

And I guess it's frustrating because I just got out of a binge-fest after eating GREAT for a week. And I have an event this weekend. And I wondered where I could have been if I had kept at the correct diet for this week (instead of binging). That week I had eaten correctly, I had lost 3 lbs. It might have been water, but it was much appreciated dammit! And from this bad week, I've gained it all back! What if I had eaten correctly this week? Could I have been 5 lbs down?!

I can start eating well all the time. It's just the damn sticking with it! I never stick around to see what happens. 

But today is a new day! All I know to do is to keep trying. I'm not going to be like, "well eff it. I guess I'm just not meant to eat healthy." 
"What could have been?" I dont want to be asking myself this same question 2 weeks from now. I should BE who I want to be today. And not let a hasty decision ruin my efforts of getting to a cleaner diet. 

I can put action to things. I just have this pesky problem with the whole "dedication" part ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First World Problems: eating healthy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 06:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can you get this belt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 01:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey,

I got this [albeit, shitty] screengrab http://i.imgur.com/Gz5zBB2.png

It looks like a velcro belt. And it has a little plus sign on the side. A lot of the Gamers look to be wearing it. Where can you get one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Braves let a janitor play ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 03:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should women wear bikinis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 23:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Try to fast before you train. Needing to eat before, during, or after training is bulshit hype pushed on us from the bodybuilding/supplement industry. - Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 19:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From this link: http://agymlife.com/get-better-at-crossfit/

#9

I was just wondering if any of you had strong feelings one way or the other. Especially those who have tried fasting before a workout versus eating a protein bar/shake ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
