<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7937</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OK 90's kids! Who remembers the "SPY TECH" series toys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 05:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I was young I used to swap heads on my collectibles and repackage them so that it looked like they had removable helmets to try and impress my friends by saying I had uber limited edition toys, found a few of them today organizing my basement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 05:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 19:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i miss these so much! and o'boises too!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 23:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, i photoshopped the logos out for wallpaper purposes lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 17:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6.3 x 14.6 x 6.3 inches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With all these fb posts about left-brain and right-brain tests, I present to you an old Mercedes ad campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 17:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 02:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all the edges are duller than a 10yr old butter knife =]

build quality is quite good, this thing seems like it good take a pretty good beating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally got around to consolidating all of my building supplies! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 02:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 18:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's my goal! so many compromises but the main goal is to mainstream non-cigalikes =P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 18:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we're not affiliated with vaporX in any way but FAZE liquids at least come from florida =] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 18:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> man you have no idea how hard i fought not to use "e hookah" and now we have an e-hookah line [[sighs]] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 18:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> trying very hard to main-stream non-ciga-likes - we've got a ton more of other displays too =P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 18:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> packaging used to be way better: http://i.imgur.com/jUsD2Yd.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 18:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I design everything for FAZE, my goal is to try and normalize ecigs, i've been vaping since forever (first youtube video was like 4 years ago) - I try and influence as much of the decision  making as I can but it's hard to make cases when the higher-ups don't understand anything. I've been pushing for low-res clearos, variable voltage and even pitched a proposal to developing a mod!

There's just too many factors when working for a big company that still thinks ciga-likes are "in"; after convincing the execs to at least start with ego-style batteries I freshened up form-factor of the ego and threw a micro-usb-passthrough port on it instead of that outdated mini USB. The packaging used to be sleek and mature too until the execs changed it to that POS you see now http://i.imgur.com/jUsD2Yd.jpg 

I feel so ashamed when I read all the negative things about my product line because I've fought tooth and nail to get it right but at the end of the day I've got to follow what the owner of the company wants and so much compromise is made =[

This particular display was designed for a different company to add their juice above ours but we have no affiliation with vaporX, in fact, they are our direct competition - our juices are ok, they aren't bad but as a person who sells a ton of DiY to friends and family, the FAZE line of juices doesn't compare.

Awesome to see my work show up in the wild! =] 

TLDR: I design all facets of the FAZE brand and I influence as much as I can but execs shoot it all down and many compromises are made, I feel bad and do apologize. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 17:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have one right in the middle of my lower back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 19:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is very VERY similar to how i make my popcorn http://instagram.com/p/bFNo4TB86u/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 21:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I throw a grinding tip on a drill and smooth out the holes, here's the set i bought from fasttech: https://www.fasttech.com/p/1471000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 02:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry, i forgot to mention that i've got the combat balance mod of the devs as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 02:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm using Better Texture Environment by Jimmy High - his environment and weapons are both installed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 02:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cool cool, as long as it's not important i'm completely fine with it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 07:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the only mod i'm using is the hi-res texture mod - the save is no biggie though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 07:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, as i mentioned earlier i've already fixed the yrden glitch but was wondering about this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 05:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my saves also look similar to that http://i.imgur.com/4bU3m7y.jpg 

also, i did manage to fix the yrden glitch that was happening from using the texture mod

sorry, i'm completely new to the witcher series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> can someone tell me if this is a texture glitch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 05:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All crabs are stereotypical Italians because of their claws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 19:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you know, like http://dailypicksandflicks.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/italian-speaking-mode-on.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An older video I just ran into today "Vapers be like" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 17:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've got a question about DACs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 22:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently on a S4 and with the stock t-mobile rom: my portable DAC/AMP FiiO e17 worked fine with an OTG cable (system-wide actually, not just media apps) but i recently upgraded to a kitkat rom (KOT49H to be exact) and suddenly my OTG functionality stopped working! 

I currently use PlayerPRO to listen to my audio which used to work fine with the e17 but now it doesn't recognize it as an audio output; my assumption was that it was broken system wide but then i downloaded a trial version of "USB Audio Player PRO" (https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.extreamsd.usbaudioplayerpro) and this app recognizes my e17 fine! So this leads be to believe it's app dependent.  I downloaded the trial version of Poweamp (https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.maxmpz.audioplayer) and this app doesn't recognize the e17 either!

USB Audio Player PRO seems to be the only app that works with the DAC but the UI is horrendous and the media browser is absolutely minimal (you can't even browse directories). 

TLDR: Anyone know of a good audio player that will let me set the audio output to USB that doesn't have a terrible UI?

Love the show! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> first attempt at an octo-coil on a friends igo-w3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 17:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 21:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they wired all the boards with reverse polarity and it was shorting out also, the power supply isn't powerful enough to run the board. the reversed polarities are completely inconsistent: sometimes it's this wire that's backwards then sometimes it's another. lastly, there's this strange interference the board is picking up that seems to only come through on certain speakers. 

we're short on manpower and weeding out all those wires on 200 different boards just isn't cost-effective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 16:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the recommendation but they recommended Nova 4pcb doesn't do any design, they just take gerber files and fulfill orders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 16:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 14 days =/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 00:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks, i've already contacted sparkfun and the lead time is too great but thank you for the info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HELP!] Looking for a group or company to build 200 boards that will play audio off an SD card when a button is pressed! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 22:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work for a small company in wheat ridge that is trying to make an interactive display for bluetooth speakers and headphones. We've already built the displays but the Chinese electronics are faulty and we're looking to replace the "guts" of the display. 

We've talked about building an arduino board that will house a single SD card and components that will allow us to switch between outputs but have hit a wall.

Does anyone know of a place locally that can produce 200 units fairly quickly? 

Any other solutions/suggestions would be great!

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Omega 24g dual coil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 20:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first attempt at vietnamese calligraphy (instagram video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 19:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 18:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I use Flatten imageconvert to RGBsave asjpgdesktop all the freaking time

on a similar note, mapping CMD+f18 to "tile all windows" and CMD+F19 to "consolidate all to tabs" is one of my most used non-traditional shortcuts ever! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 22:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't get mine to fire for some reason, well, actually, it fires but it's pitiful. 18650 extension on a nimbus - i'm this thing just can't handle sub-ohm vaping due to that crap 510 center pin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make it rain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 17:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 17:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://instagram.com/p/i5FQG5B801/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 21:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ludovico Einaudi - divenire](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9qvglWAHDak) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I took a picture of every meal I had in 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 23:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Mod and Driptip is that? (Mos Eisley Cantina) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 17:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 18:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30yr old Asian male from colorado (youtube.com/phee303) haven't made a video in years as work has gotten me swamped. 

Smoked about 2 packs of reds a day (newport when i'm in the mood) for 11 years; started exclusively vaping around mid 2009(?) Designer/Photographer/Videographer, gamer, car enthusiast, all around geek/nerd. 

Me in my office (yes, they allow me to fog up my office all day at work!) http://instagram.com/p/fyDz_5h8w8/ 

Currently trying my hardest to normalize non-cig-alike products to the masses with my FAZEvapor line.

Daily driver: Hcigar duo-tone Nemesis with authentic Nimbus, 28g-twisted-dual-coil with cotton at .4 I still sell huge amount of DiY juice to friend and family.

Nice to meet everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 22:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> look for the MKB-TS  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first time making an ugly sweater, nailed it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 01:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> mid-season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 22:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After seeing the trailer for "Jupiter Ascending" this is all I could think of </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 23:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No popcorn popper? No problem. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 00:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Instagram video i did a few months ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 21:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 18:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have a BM42, love benchmades =] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What brands do swear by for mundane items? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 17:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, Maggi Soy Sauce and the Hon Phan Thiet (one-crab) Fish sauce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At my work there's an elk that greets you when you first come in, someone put a hat on him so I decided to go one better </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 18:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know what "instoremercial" uses to encrypt their SD cards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 19:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 17:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's also piratevaper? or something like that, went there and just stepped back out, i know they're trying but they could definitely do better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 17:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sell juice out of my house and live right down the street from you guys! I'm on 64th and Wads, same zip! lol I'ma stop by and check u guys out after work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 23:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this turned out to be very useful, thank you! i've been using illustrator for over a decade and never used the selectsame  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 18:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unfortunately there are some of the same colors that must stay so i could not recolour artwork but thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 18:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you i'll check out this "selectsame" thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] Is there a way to import saved selections from one ai doc to another? also is there a way to remove ALL drop shadows at once? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 23:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've got a couple dozen ai package artwork I have to change colors on and I would like to save a selection and then import the saved selection into another art file so i can just make the selection to change the color. the documents are identical in dimensions and vector placement. It's just a PIA to go in and click 20 elements and then change the color on 24 different files that are almost identical.

I also need to remove all drop shadows from every file, is there a way i can rid them w/o finding every culprit one by one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 22:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for the most part my drip tips are too small for the iGO-L from FT - what i do to solve this is to take off the o-ring on the drip-tip, grab some floss and do a few wraps and then throw the o-ring back on it: adjust as needed. 

I haven't run into any drip-tips that are too big, just too small.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 07:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is me! thank you for watching! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 21:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, the atmos is definitely a rip-off but i got the kit through a co-op for $30, very glad I didn't pay anything near full-price for the damn thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 21:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 21:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it comes with a glass filter to put over the heating coil in the ceramic chamber. it doesn't work like you think, you have to prime it twice for about six seconds before you can vape it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 17:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm debating on getting a russian 91% or a kayfun against the nimbus it'll be a while til i get any of them as the budget has weathered away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 16:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the threads are just slighty off, if you're handy you can retro fit it with an old clearomizer tank or something =] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 16:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes! my first mech was the prodigy v1 then the silver bullet and yes, omg yes vaping has come so damn far yet it's not; we may have gone a long way but the ecig industry itself is still stuck on cig-alikes =/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 16:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> works decent for what it is but it's more of a novelty for me, i still prefer having an RDA on my mods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 16:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol nice! i envy those who can do that, my wallet especially does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 16:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually it's pick-and-pluck foam, it looks like everything's form-fitted but in reality it's not, very versatile little thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 16:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i've had a friend try it and he liked it, i've personally haven't used it myself just yet. the threading is slightly different from egos so you cannot use it on an ego.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 16:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i kno i kno, but i will =P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 16:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's a dual-coil wrapped around silica at .7 ohms - no stainless, it's a drip-atty =] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 06:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, i'm way the hell out in colorado =P

I once sent juice to vaporcast (ep 65 i think) just to prove to them they've never had "the worse juice in the world" until they've tried this monster I made lol but yeah, thanks, I think I do ok with my recipes =D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 06:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alas i don't ship any juices =/ i've been thinking about it but people coming to pick stuff up at my apt has been working ok for now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 06:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol! yeah, at the moment my Igo-L with my KTS+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 06:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sadly i havent had much non-DiY juice, i sell juices locally to friends and family so I haven't tried much of anyone else's stuff in years =/ but my the second fridge is a full size fridge lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 06:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that was my very first ecig! even before the titan510 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 06:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a second fridge full of DiY stuff =P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been vaping since 2009, here's the way I excessively store my mods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 05:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tryptophan, caffeine and other "active" additives to juices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 20:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've got a bottle of 5ml bottle "Relaxation" from herbs2vape that I have yet to vape. Their ingredients list tryptophan, GABA, and melatonin; what do you guys think about these "functional" additives to juices? 

I'm guessing the dosage is minimal which means the effect must also be minimal. My guess is absorbing via lungs for these ingredients have to minuscule as our lungs don't really "metabolize" these type things as well as our digestive system. Maybe to have an effect there needs to be some sort of calculation of strength like what we do with our nicotine? 

How safe and effective can juices like this be?

On their site they're listing all kinds of "active juices" like 'Alert', 'Energy', 'Breathe', 'Flex', 'Intamcy', and 'Lean' - I feel like this type of evolution is the kind of thing that takes us closer to FDA coming down hard on us vapers. 

herbs2vape and nutricigs are the only two I know that making these type juices in the "mainstream" - I've also heard of some off-brand juice-makers doing the same thing.

Thoughts? comments?

(sorry for my unstructured rambling) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 22:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also, if it's really bright, like extra shiny looking, it's galvanized  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 22:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> drop it in some drano and wait for bit, if it starts fizzing you've got galvanized steel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 18:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, it almost wicks too fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 18:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ordered some XS sleeves and am eagerly waiting for it to come in =] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 03:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stainless rope: https://www.amazonsupply.com/dp/B0013HGP9Y

Kanthal Ribbon: http://www.ebay.com/itm/261217580592?ssPageName=STRK:MEWNX:IT _trksid=p3984.m1497.l2649 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After months and months of fiddling with the AGA-T2 I've finally found a setup that works for me (Kanthal A Ribbon .6x.07 + Stainless Steel 7x7 Rope) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 03:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 18:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dispite all of my efforts, being single now for almost 6 years - living with just my cat, it's driven me to the brink of insanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HELP! Anyone know to make this path normal again? (ie apply a regular stroke) it seems to just be stuck - I don't want someone to do this for me, just explain to me why it's this way and how do I revert it back to normal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 19:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 05:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input - after hours and hours of forum searching I've come up with an idea. I took the PCB off of the drive and some of the leads look burned, I'm guessing this is what's causing intermittent power. I've tried to clean the leads but with no avail.

I scoured the internet and found several sites that offer replacement PCBs for the drive and have made an order, found one for $20 after shipping - hopefully I can just replace the PCB and this will be the end of it; it'd be a great bonus if the PCB restored the drive functionality completely!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mom's hard drive needs help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 00:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom's hard drive has thousands of family photos and I've been working for days to recover the photos. The data on the drive is fine but something's shorted with the interface; I have it mounted via Seagate external mount (SATA to USB3) and the drive mounts fine and stays mounted so long as I'm not pulling data, when I start to pull data it runs for about two minutes, sometimes a little longer but it always ends up losing power - it takes about a minute or so for the drive to come back and mount and the cycle starts all over again when I try and pull pictures.

I've got about 600GB of data that I'm trying to move into my local drive before I move it to a portable drive for her but it's annoying to say the least to have to sit there and watch for when the drive loses power in order to continue copying. 

It's strange, the drive has its moments where it'll run and read for 10minutes and when it loses power it wont read a single file unless I detach it from my Seagate interface for a while. I've tried all kinds of other ways to mount the bare drive but it seems that the issue is clearly with the drive itself. 

I figured it could be a temperature issue so now I've got the whole setup sitting on top of a ziplock container full of ice but it doesn't seem to make a difference. 

Any suggestions aside from bringing the drive to professionals? I looked into doing a platter transfer but it seems way too risky. I'd be extremely grateful for any input, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-01 22:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i still have it taped to my workstation http://i.imgur.com/JxDBnUE.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-01 22:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i got the same damn fortune a year ago lol http://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/ibk26/until_now_ive_never_had_a_fortune_cookie_tell_me/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 22:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> still limited to 5V and 10sec? come'on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 21:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is how i do mine http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8379/8641154127_bce4f058b6_o.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 18:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I have not tried the Joy yet but my Pilot Parallels are great! My Lamys are all everyday carries so I won't likely be getting a Joy although one of my Lamy Al-stars does have a 1.9mm nib =P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 18:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sadly it's an inexpensive epiphone special II  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 18:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's pretty bad-ass! If I had an actual desk maybe I'd look into getting something similar to that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 18:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serwex 101 =P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 18:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like my Lamys because I carry one everyday, I have multiple ones so I can coordinate with my shirt =P and yes, they all vary in inks and nibs =] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is how I keep mine. reddit, where do you keep yours? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 06:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is a very old picture, not trying to be racist (I'm Asian myself) but is this Justin? LOL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 20:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 19:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol also, the R2 skin you have, that's what inspired me to make [my own R2 skin](https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-roycKH_OIUQ/URFENGss27I/AAAAAAAAEEg/fFz4ctMS4oo/s1047/2013-02-05+10.40.07.jpg) which then I changed the design to the Iron-R2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 19:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmmm I may look into that - thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 19:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol - it does doesn't it? I've made a TARDIS one for a friend but the material I have, the prints just don't sustain too well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 19:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've made a TARDIS one and sold it to my friend (just material cost) but no, I don't really have any plans to sell these =P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 19:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alon from Jwraps has seen it on my G+ page, didn't offer anything for it - I don't really have any motivation to push a sale on him =P check out his site though, he has a bunch of wraps=] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 19:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 19:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> generic chinese tank for standard boge cartos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 23:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol! rarely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made my own Iron-R2 skin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 22:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This vacuum is fly like a </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 19:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 17:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that was absolutely hilarious! i've never made that association before, i was chuckling randomly thinking about this for like 20min! lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE peel their clementine like this? (OC) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 05:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Majestic as fuck (moved from r/cats) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 20:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She grabbed my phone to take a selfie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 01:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 19:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot to add: these are from pizza hut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad pizza or good pizza? You guys have this in NY yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 19:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 19:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> let's see someone make a guide like this for thai, lao and khmer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 16:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> throwback joke when the first tomb raiders were rumored to have a 'naked code' - eidos did an interview and showed her 'naked' (wireframe only) =P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was finishing up Tomb Raider when suddenly... naked Lara </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 06:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 22:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/qIMjGSu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 22:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/qIMjGSu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's here! It's here! 580 1.5mm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 20:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 18:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, my first pen over $30 is the TWSBI 580 (which I ordered yesterday as soon as I heard they were available) and won't be investing in anymore pens for a very long while much less vintage flex pens or custom pens.

I've been fiddling with the Noodler's flex pens on and off for a couple of months and I cannot get them to write properly. I've tried carving out the channels for better flow, moved the nibs up and down, tried various speeds and pressures in my writing but I cannot replicate anything on youtube - as soon as I flex the nib it'll be ok for about 3-4 strokes and it railroads and won't write for quite a long time. 

I've done the "fill-with-water" and then draw the water out through a paper-towel and I *do* get bubbles, so the feed *seems* fine - so maybe my tines aren't set right? (I've never adjusted the nib tines, ever.) I have no idea why it's so inconsistant, even non-flex writing my two noodler's flex pens dont flow right regardless of how fast/slow I'm writing. 

Any pointers or suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My new Gmail =] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 23:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 17:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice! any flex pens/nibs you recommend?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 17:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my table was severely damaged, i painted it, then the paint chipped - tried to sand it made it look even worse so i decided to go on ebay and buy myself some fake 3D carbon fiber vinyl for cars and wrap the damn thing - only cost $25 lol now my table looks completely bad ass. as a bonus when i wipe the table it makes this cool zipping noise hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 21:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks =P I don't find the need for anything smaller than 3.8mm; I'm looking for a nice flex nib that will compensate for lines at the 2.4mm range  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 21:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the bottom up: Lamy Al-Star Blue, Lamy Al-Star Red, Lamy Al-Star Aluminum, Lamy Vista, Lamy Safari Charcoal, Lamy Safari Black, Noodler's Konrad, Noodler's Ahab, 3x Pilot Parallel 6.0mm and 2x Pilot Parallel 3.8mm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 21:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yezzir, although there's a couple of Safaris: the black and charcoal; Ahab Flex and Konrad (which I still can't get either to write/flex properly) - it's funny I only bought the Diamond ink bottle because of how the tops sound when you're assembling and disassembling it (ASMR) lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 21:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes! i am eagerly waitng for a TWSBI 580, it will be my first venture into a pen over $30, it'll also likely be my last for quite a while =/

as for paper, i know nothing of it, i'm writing and doodling on just whatever I find laying around which ranges from old sketchbooks to cheap printer paper; being an underpaid designer i dont think i'll be able to afford any upper-tier paper for a very, very long time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 21:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, it is a red Al-Star - think they were a limited edition run </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 18:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unfortunately i don't have total access to the printer, it's in the productions department and i'm in graphics, I've only been able to print out a few things =/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 18:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't think i can say, the 3D printer we have is just for production shop to make mock-ups of our product lines - not a service that we offer =P thanks for inquiry though   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 18:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm a broad or bigger fan myself but if you go goulet they sell just nibs and you could swap out your fine for an extra-fine for like $13

http://www.gouletpens.com/Lamy_Extra_Nibs_Converters_s/938.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 16:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> definitely will look into that =] thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 16:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i like to have one that matches my shirt when i'm out lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't own anything vintage or special but this is my army </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 04:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 18:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, from getglue  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 21:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's a mighty mugg, you should be able to buy him on amazon or directly from hasbro http://www.hasbro.com/search/_/Ntt-mighty%20muggs?Ntk=All Ntx=mode+matchallpartial </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 21:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, i'm definitely seeing that in comments now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 21:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> awesome! google sent me that one and I ended up buying a black one as well, not shown here because it's at home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
