<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6654</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silly question (maybe not?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 18:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why in all the Apollo missions, and early space missions, do photographs have large plus signs on them? Did they act as a grid for astronauts to level their pictures or something?

i.e., http://www.techdaily.com.au/b2/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/Neil-Armstrong.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 15:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dumb question (maybe not?) but why in all the Apollo missions, and early space missions, do photographs have the large plus signs on them?  Does it act as a grid for astronauts to level their pictures or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 00:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/penis would be the penis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 23:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what does this mean, "the most atmospheric"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 16:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does this hitch fair with the whole  "you should never tow in an 86"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 17:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may or may not be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 20:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My buddy told me the same thing.  Thanks a bunch- lots of useful info here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 20:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah a police report was filed.  Whatever, it has an accident on its record.  I'm just trying to get back what was (will be?) lost down the road (pun intended, lol).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't want to deal with that trouble later on when I might actually *need* the money.  It's a Subaru BRZ, yeah it's not a luxury vehicle but it was a limited edition that they only made a certain amount of, which brings the price up opposed to the normal model.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 17:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Jersey.  Was not up for sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ok, I was like "damn that's a lot" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30k in 2 months?  bruh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  Totaled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is excellent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diminished Value claim. Where do I begin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was recently in an accident (rear ended) and was obviously not at fault.  My car was in the shop for a week and after $1500 in repairs, it looks good as new.  In the end, it was really only a fender bender with no frame damage.  I was okay.

It's a new car, and had only 12k miles on it.  It was probably worth $22-23k prior to the accident.  

The repairs are now complete and they look great, but I obviously have to deal with the fact that it has an accident on its record and the  diminished value that comes with it.  I'm going to get an appraisal sometime soon, but my guess is that when I try to sell it in the future, I'm going to run into some problems i.e., getting less than it should because of the accident.  My first thought is to contact my insurance to get as many details as possible, then contact the other insurance company involved.

I want to settle this as soon as possible, where do I begin?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Das auto? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.  All of this.  As a recent college graduate (21) who just bought an 86 in February, I can easily say I definitely enjoyed my Altima during school much more than I would have my BRZ.  Although I did have it the past spring semester.

Bottom line, for a first car, start with something more practical.  I run into challenges fitting people/things into the thing, so there are definitely more people-friendly options out there.  

What is it that you want essentially?  RWD?  Manual?  You might want to look into some older   used German cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been looking for a WRB BRZ one...  anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 16:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's at 2.49%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 04:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know my mom has experience in the stock market and is offering to help me there...  Not sure how to/where to invest otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 03:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have $23k in savings otherwise and a $9500 car loan (which I can pay off whenever).  I'm 21 and have a job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have $7,000 that I would like to invest. How would I go about doing this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 03:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Background: I have some leftover college funds that my parents saved for me and finally gave the rest to me as a graduation present.  I have about $7,000 and no student loan debt (very fortunate).  What can I do with this to make it more?  I have $23k in savings otherwise and a $9500 car loan (which I can pay off whenever). I'm 21 and have a job.

edit: more info </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have $7,000 that I would like to invest. How would I go about doing this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 01:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 20:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am the Jersey 86. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is which? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 16:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ask Mother Nature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made a friend in Atlantic City last night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 16:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corn cob with no symmetry. (xpost from r/mildlyintersting) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 15:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Back, and even bluer than before! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 14:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 23:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 21:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What club? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 21:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can Confirm- Series.Blue does have knee pads.  I believe they came standard in all 2015 models, along with the larger exhaust tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 22:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It knew you were going to Subway and tried to stop you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is that one character in the movie that everyone hates, and what movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 16:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is that one character in the movie that everyone hates? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 15:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 19:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being that he has California plates...  I would say "no". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huh?  I found the article and copied its title because Reddit could not check for titles for whatever reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 15:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interior is pretty nice.  It's weird, now I actually have room to breathe in the car haha.  Visibility is A+ (but that's any sedan) and compared to the 86, it feels like you're driving a boat while at the height of a tractor trailer.  You're much more driving "on top of" the road rather than "on" the road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got this sweet new rental ride. Where's the flair for Camry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 15:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 06:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only they could launch fireworks in space... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Collins, the astronaut who took this photo, is the only human, alive or dead that isn't in the frame of this picture, 1969 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 05:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 00:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing was said about it, and nothing can be proven.  But, prior to him hitting me, I saw him look up and down at his lap- he was *at least* texting.

edit: typo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 21:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure.  Looks like just the bumper (crosses fingers) because it's not out of place.  It's drivable and doesn't feel like there's anything wrong but I'm not an auto body mechanic so I don't know.  

It felt like a 10-15 mph hit, I was cruising at 40mph, and the dude behind me didn't think to look out the front windshield.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't play Pokemon Go while driving, you'll hit innocent drivers such as myself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 20:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: This Playground in Sweden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 19:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 00:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exhaust is fine, I think it's just the angle of picture.  Both tips stick out the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 22:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy who hit me was in a 2004 Ford Focus rental.  Wasn't fucking paying attention and "hit the accelerator instead of the gas".  I was going about 40 and it felt like a 20mph hit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 21:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course.  It doesn't look too bad, I don't *expect* there to be frame damage but I really don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 21:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the phone with claims now.  I was rear ended and not at fault so I'll be covered.  That's how it worked out last time I was rear ended in my previous car. 

I'm on my parent's insurance policy and they have good coverage so I'm not worried.  It's gonna need a new bumper and aero kit.  I'm just upset that it now has an accident under its belt.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 20:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rear fucking ended.  Shooken up as I'm posting this but I'm pissed.  I'm okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FUCK. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 20:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going the extra what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 16:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 20:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It came like that...  new? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 02:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats!  Shoulda found a Series.Blue, almost all that stuff comes standard.  Prob woulda been a bit cheaper with a couple thousand miles on it.  But they are kinda hard to find, I lucked out with mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 19:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since February of 2016, it's a 6 year loan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Car payments... Pay off now or continue monthly payments? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 18:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi!  I just bought a new car back in February.  I'm 21, and I paid the majority as a down payment (trade in, $7k and about another $12k down) and thus my monthly's are just about $150, with 2.49% financing.

Although I have the savings to pay it off, I chose to go with monthly payments to give myself some breathing room.  I have just under $10k that I owe on the car.

I have about $22,000 saved up (and in my mind, it's really $12,000 of savings and $10,000 of debt).  My question is, should I just pay it off?  The benefits I see here is that I don't have to pay the interest and that the monthly payments go away (by obviously paying off $10k).  Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oversteer shmoversteer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 17:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this mean that Juno will be so close to Jupiter that it will only be able to see that small section? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red, White, and World Rally Blue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 16:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 15:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were rocks everywhere song just assumed...  if anything I thought they'd be in the muffler or something but I have no clue, I'll see what's up in a week or so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rocks in exhaust? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 02:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, had some fun on a dirt road today (video to come later) but somewhere along the way rocks got stuck in my exhaust.  Now it rattles like crazy and I don't want any damage to come from it.  What do you recommend I do?  I do have to service it soon for other things (oil, allignment), is this something Subaru can fix? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 02:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote because I was gonna post this here too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 02:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Series.Blue.  Series.Blue.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SFTP vs FTPS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 21:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What port do each protocol run on?  What are the differences?  I'm confusing myself.  

From what I understand, SFTP runs on port 22, and FTPS runs on 990/989, correct?

Which one is more secure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 17:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last I heard, this was just a [concept](http://www.evo.co.uk/toyota/gt-86/13048/toyota-ft-86-open-concept-previews-gt86-cabriolet) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How vocabulary-oriented are these exams? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 16:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there- Studying for Security+!  Using the textbook "Security+ Guide to Network Security Fundamentals" by Mark Ciampa.  

I've been studying the vocabulary/key terms from each chapter, but on the exam, will there be any questions regarding **just the definition** of such terms?  Or are they all situational based questions that you have to apply the vocabulary?

i.e., might I see a question as such?:

Q:  Employees, contractors, and business partners who can be responsible for an attack

A: Insiders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 07:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that residual shadow tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 04:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does Apple.  I was wondering this the other day and couldn't quite figure out where Hooli fits in (or what company it was mocking). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 22:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say I'm opposed to the bar scene, but I don't have any friends in my area anymore to go out with.  I don't want to come off as the lonely guy going to the bar to meet girls on his own.  Also, I'm not entirely looking for a one nighter really, hoping for something more meaningful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to get "out there"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 22:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recent college grad here.  Just got a job and am now living on my own, and man is it starting to get a bit lonely.

I've been on dating sites and apps (Tinder, Bumble, OkCupid to name a few), but honestly, the area I live in (South Jersey) is really sparse when it comes to women on social dating sites.  

Honestly, the main problem here is just finding people.  What would you recommend, being that dating sites really are not too powerful in this area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Where is "Euthanasia"? I can't seem to find it anywhere on my map. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 15:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 00:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First car of my own.  Drove a '10 altima before for 5 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Temperature for hamsters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 17:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking to get a hamster soon, but am curious as to the temperature they can live in.  Trying to conserve energy, I'll only run the A/C when I get home from work, at which the apartment can be up to 80 F.  Is this too hot of an environment to keep a hamster?  I don't want to kill the thing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 17:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ding ding ding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 22:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/CSG_Mike </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 21:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha same, I just saw an opportunity and I took it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain this? I saw two Jeeps today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 17:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 17:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This
The car itself is insignificant unless you really know how to drive it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A turtle in its natural habitat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 17:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Britain leaving the EU help me lose those extra pounds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 16:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 16:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not hyper.blue?  only 500 made IIRC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the difference between the two search methods? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 16:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i.e., pulling down from the home screen or going all the way to the left for search.  The left one has some more suggestions but is there any more functionality differences between the two?  They both do the job for me (mainly finding an app or contact quickly).  iOS 9.x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snake trapped in circle of its own skin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 23:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snake trapped in endless circle of its own skin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 23:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Took advantage of some pretty clouds last night. Bonus Subie in the back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 22:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Took advantage of some pretty clouds last night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 16:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 06:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 5'8 and don't sit very far back.  Someone can sit (relatively) comfortably behind me for a little while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legal recreational marijuana can help save Atlantic City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 18:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 06:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cost? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The NYPD is getting smarter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 19:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 18:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did it, plugged the hole and took away the pipe leading to it (and plugged those holes from removing the pipe).  Noise has been the same, but hey, car is now ~1lb lighter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 16:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hole in the floor- a sound tube going from the engine bay directly into the cabin, out of a little hole under the glove box.  Just to make the engine noise sound louder.  Can be plugged up and pipes leading to it can be deleted.  

Sound isolation- you can buy things like Dynomat for sound dampening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do Vets get a discount on education? Didn't they already go to school to become animal doctors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 02:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mini! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 01:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup- when we drove through Sugar City on the way back.  Had to turn off the AC for like an hour, which was rough in 95* weather.  We found a gas station luckily, but even if we didn't, we had a spare jerry can with 2 gallons of gas.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 22:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, i70.  9 hours of Kansas was pretty boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IamA recent college graduate who just completed a cross-country road trip to the Four Corners from New Jersey. AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 21:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 05:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my lord.  Regardless of if it were covered under insurance or not, I wouldn't want to touch that thing with a 10 foot pole.  Was this in that mega pile up I remember reading about sorta recently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 00:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked it up and all the signs point to synchronicity.  What is it trying to tell me?!  I can't decipher any of it.  The past few weeks have been filled with an incredible amount of anxiety (I'm an anxious person though). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 18:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 40 is for international plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 06:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like:

NW 1400 min T T = $100

L1: UDP CED = 09/19/17, $10 + $30 = $40

L2: UDP CED , Intl Trvl 100mb, International Value Plan, Total Equipment Coverage Asurion = 06/29/17, $10 + $30 + $40 +3.99 _ $9= $92.17

L3: Verizon Max 6GB CED, International Value Plan = 12/06/16, $10 + $30 + $3.99 = $43.98

L4: 5GB CED, Asurion Wireless Phone Protection = 09/19/17, $10 + $50 + $7.15= $67.15

L5: Basic CED = 09/13/2016, $10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 05:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish I could understand all of this a bit better.  Like, what do I do with it?  I'd like to learn more but these things are so subtle it's hard to interpret them.  When they happen, I always acknowledge that they occurred. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 05:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another thing!

A while back I was feeling depressed about some silly mistakes I've made in my yesteryears.  It depressed me for days.  Then, this came in the mail: http://imgur.com/gallery/PGOhFOM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 02:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Series.Blue ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 01:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since a young age, I've noticed weird coincidences in my life.  I think of a song, I'll hear it on the radio.  Think of a particular TV episode?  That's on TV that day.  Sometimes I think of what someone might say (mid conversation), and they'll say it (or something along those lines).

A few weeks ago, my roommate and I were in our backyard when he noticed an interesting looking spider.  I said to him, "remember the time we saw that black widow here"?  And what do you know, a black widow crawls right in front of my feet.

Today, I went to the bank for a deposit.  My friend from high school, Brett worked there so I thought I would see him and say hi.

I didn't see Brett working.  Then when I'm pulling out of the bank, there he was.  But here's the catch- He doesn't work there anymore!  I just happened to see him going to the ATM. 

Also today, I was thinking about watching a special of a comedian I enjoy.  That exact special was on the Laugh Radio channel.

I don't know if this is "psychic" behavior, but there are definitely more coincidences in my life than I can count.  They have been happening to me more and more recently, and I'm not sure who to talk to about it or to see if it should be looked into.  
I've always thought of higher beings (God) and spirits, and I don't know if this is one's way of trying to connect to me.  I have always felt that I have had someone or some force looking over me.

I am more spiritual than I am religious (Judaism).

What are your thoughts?  Any input is appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 01:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More close to $400, I got some of the data packages incorrect.  
Self-employed family, no employee discounts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 23:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> L1: UDP CED = 09/19/17
L2: UDP CED = 06/29/17
L3: 5GB CED = 12/06/16
L4: 5GB CED =09/19/17
L5: Basic flip phone.  09/13/2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 22:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our last upgrade was before the price hike.  Next upgrade we'll be hit with the $50 I presume.  Bill says $30 for unlimited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 22:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nationwide talk and text.  Unlimited texting, 1400 minutes.

I've been taking other's upgrades the past few years to keep my phone payment subsidized while keeping unlimited. Have I been getting a new contract each time?

5 lines total, two unlimited and two 5gb. I use the most data about 2-4gb/month, but I've had 7-8 gb months in the past. Wifi is so prevalent these days that I really don't use data as much as I used to.

Jailbreaks aren't available and I'm going to need a hotspot by next week that's bigger than 2GB.

Mom has 5gb/month.

If we switched to shared data, with the XXL package still, we're saving $10/month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 22:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been taking other's upgrades the past few years to keep my phone payment subsidized while keeping unlimited.  Have I been getting a new contract each time?

They both end in September of 2017.  5 lines total, 2 unlimited and 2 5gb.  I use the most data about 2-4gb/month, but I've had 7-8 gb months in the past.  Wifi is so prevalent these days that I really don't use data as much as I used to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worth keeping unlimited? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 21:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad and I both have unlimited data on our iPhones. Come the next time we upgrade, that $30/month for unlimited will jump to $50/month. Unlimited data is great and all, but I'm missing out on features like mobile hotspot, early upgrades etc.

If we get a shared data package, it will stay around the same price, but we will have that data cap now. Also will be sharing with my mother. I use the most data between everyone due to streaming and other things.
Is it really worth keeping unlimited at the current point in time? It's been great having it for 5 years but is it beneficial over shared data anymore?

Honestly, it mainly comes down for my need of a mobile hotspot, which I will need sometimes.  If I wanted to get the feature added, it costs $30 for 2gb of data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it worth it to keep unlimited data? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 21:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad and I both have unlimited data on our iPhones.  Come the next time we upgrade, that $30/month for unlimited will jump to $50/month.  Unlimited data is great and all, but I'm missing out on features like mobile hotspot, early upgrades etc.  

If we get a shared data package, it will stay around the same price, but we will have that data cap now.  Also will be sharing with my mother.  I use the most data between everyone due to streaming and other things.

Is it really worth keeping unlimited at the current point in time?  It's been great having it for 5 years but is it beneficial over shared data anymore?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 21:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JPM Coachworks has a selection of aftermarket parts with blue stitching available </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I too, keep adorable shit here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 18:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MacBook Pro constantly freezes after wake from sleep. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 03:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10.11.4, but have had this problem for a while now.  Mid 2012 MBP, 16GB + SSD.  Whenever I wake my Mac from sleep, it tries to connect to WiFi.  You see the wifi bars loading animation like it's trying to connect.

Any internet-related application will pinwheel and go into "not responding" mode.  It will do this for up to 3 minutes or so, but by then I just kill it and do a hard reboot (if it comes to that).  This happens daily.

Does anyone have this issue?  It seems like the computer is just confused when trying to reconnect to the network so then everything else goes with it as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 07:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually noticed the same thing a few days ago.  I think it just may be the gearbox in that case.  But don't worry, they're made to take a certain amount of roughhousing :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When anxiety strikes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 19:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever something big happens in my life, my body goes into full 100% anxiety mode. Mainly over the fear of the unknown. This is no exception, because right out of college I was offered a full-time job. Great! However, I will be moving into my own place without any roommates, and the thought of being alone like that honestly scares the hell out of me. For the first time in my life, I will be living alone. The only thing I will have in life is work, and no one will be there when I get home at the end of the day.

When anxiety strikes, my whole body is affected. I get depressed and lethargic, not to mention that I lose my appetite, get nauseous, and lose any motivation to make food or even eat. Has anyone else run into this issue? What can you do? Force feeding doesn't work, doing so just makes me gag and possibly throw up.

For those really intense panic/anxiety attacks, I use Xanax (prescribed) but I really only like using them for those purposes.

Do you guys have any advice? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 04:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try this. Get a fixed lens with a high aperture lens (i.e. f/1.4, f/1.8) and then shoot. You'll get awesome perspective shots with a great depth of field :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 16:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 04:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the STi aero kit, comes factory installed on the Series.Blue model BRZ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 04:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU'RE MY BOY BLUE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 00:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd be a rad name TBH...  should be illegal to NOT call your kid Rifle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 23:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean.  If it makes you feel so good about yourself then take it lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 22:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my BRZ in the NorthEast, your argument is invalid by default. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 21:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many houses do?  idk, I can't think of *not* seeing a driveway as such within a 100 mile radius.  NJ here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have no idea how this happened, but did I mention how much I love you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 21:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 20:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait.  How fast does it say you're going?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 20:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're just renters.  Previous tenants used it for a basketball hoop.  Motorcycle belongs to my roommate...  And we don't have a garage.  He covers it as needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you study for an exam as such?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 17:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 15:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a 1989 Honda Interceptor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 15:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I definitely passed it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well fuck. I didn't study. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 15:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My lawn looks like shit but that's not what this picture is about. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 15:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 02:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow, nice.  Looking to go early June with my roommate.  I'm at around 9500 or so miles...  Still a baby haha.  But at 4-5k miles later, kinda nervous of how the road will treat it.  Also gonna have to do an oil change somewhere along the trip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Road trip? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 01:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How has anyone faired on a road trip with your twin?  Looking to go cross country...  NY area to around CO and back.  I'm possibly looking into getting a bra for the car, for some additional paint protection (most likely one of the black ones that I can take on and off with ease)...  Has anyone gone on a road trip in this?  What should I expect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 18:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't repair permissions in El Capitan.  They took that away from disk utility </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 16:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only thing is, once you plant that money tree you spent thousands on, your ROI is only about 5%, they keep the other 95. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mac won't display images after El Capitan upgrade. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 16:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Working in a corporate environment and recently upgrades our Macs to El Capitan.  Last night's upgrade went fine, but the Mac will not display images properly (pictures show up as a little blue box with a question mark in the middle).  

We thought this was just an issue with Microsoft Outlook, but it's more widespread and affects other apps such as Safari and Mail.  The machine (rMBP 15") is on 10.11.4, and we're not updating to 10.11.5 until we test the build to be sure it is stable.  

Anyone else have this issue?  What would you do?  It's currently affecting 2 of some 25 users. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 16:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can repurpose it as a server in itself, or maybe set it up to be a VPN concentrator so you can access your home network while away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 14:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hate to be controversial and all... but the name isn't steve :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Siri for Macs Colorful Waveform Dock Icon Revealed Ahead of OS X 10.12 Unveiling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 18:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 20:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are these plug   play?  How hard was the install? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 19:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's tentative.  Still waiting on confirmation of a 2nd interview. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right...  A bit *too* right actually.  Yeah, I'm really not interested in being a POS tech.  It's a pretty big step in the wrong direction at the moment.  But, assuming a desktop position opens up, this is the best route to get there.  

But in financial terms...  I would probably be saving around $10k/year as opposed to saving upwards of $50k at home...  It's really not hard to tell that this isn't the best option for me.  Even if a desktop spot opened up, I'd be saving a similar amount to that of POS (but a little bit more).

Back at home, I pretty much have a desktop/help desk job lined up already.  Essentially, what it looks like it comes down to is that I'll be missing out on making an additional $40k just to *not* live with my parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 16:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True.  Honestly, if I were informed about this a few weeks ago, it would have been much easier to say yes.  Because if I take the job not, I have to find a place to live in a matter of 5 days..  It's not entirely feasible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 16:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry...  should have specified.  I concentrated in Information Systems.  But honestly, at 13.50/hour...  It's really not something I can live on.  But my other option is to go back home with mom and dad, and hope to find a job there..  which isn't ideal either lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Job opportunity... Opinions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 15:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there- I'm a recent college graduate, major in Computer Science   Info Systems, concentrating in Information Systems.  For the past year, I have been working a Desktop Support tech for a retail chain's corporate offices, as an intern, then a temp associate.  Due to my recent graduation, it looks as I'll be moving back home because they can't hire me full-time (at the moment).

Although the full-time desktop gig isn't available, my boss offered me a full-time job as a POS Support technician, which works on the store POS systems.  I'm considering it because in about half a years time, it is likely that there will be a full-time spot open on the Desktop Support team.  This is what my boss told me, as he is trying to keep me on.

Only thing is...  I feel that I would be selling myself short if I took this POS job.  Studying Computer Science for the past 4 years and really not apply it post-grad is not ideal for me.  But I could be wrong.  What would you recommend?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the stars we see in the night sky part of the Milky Way? Or other galaxies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graduated University yesterday, the commencement speaker said we are now Aluminum. How can I become a metal just like that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If my two cents were adjusted for inflation, does that mean my opinion becomes more valuable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 16:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 22:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong.  [see here](http://www.macofalltrades.com/ProductDetails.asp?ProductCode=MP-266-4C-E06B utm_source=googleshopping utm_medium=cpc_feed utm_campaign=comparison_shopping_feeds gclid=CNTHm82w2swCFYFahgodF_wIcw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 15:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup...  Or in storage waiting to be purged out really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 15:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a Mac Pro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 20:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Price of original purchase... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
