<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3355</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I've found myself telling the story of Andr Trocm in Le Chambron-sur-lingon during WWII lately. 

Trocm was the priest at the local church, and therefore a local leader. When the Gestapo came to his village and demanded a list of Jewish villagers, Trocm replied "we do not know of Jews, we only know of men." His leadership and compassion during the war led his entire village to form an Underground Railroad of sorts for fleeing Jews and it's estimated that 3500 innocent lives were saved by their efforts. 

All it takes is *one* person stepping forward and resisting to inspire hundreds more. Reminding ourselves of the most incredible examples of that, like Trocm, his nephew (who died in Majdanek concentration camp for his efforts), his flock, and other heroes like them doesn't trivialize the holocaust. It gives it more meaning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ICE *is* doing it both illegally and unethically, though, at the behest of the president. That was my point.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna just let you sit and think about what you said there. Because it didn't make sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has been encouraging these attacks. He's given white nationalists protection from being considered hate groups. 

His rhetoric is a means to an end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, right? But it is, somehow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean besides the ones who have been attacked physically in either successful or attempted murders in Trump's name?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no excuse for you besides willful blindness and the frightening ability to ignore the suffering of others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then what are you trying to say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I don't think it's a stretch. 

Trump is currently purging legal US residents from the country and banning others from entering. 

What do these two peoples have in common? 

They're brown.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad was a marine, that kind of talk would've gotten someone's ass kicked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell me what you think the definition of Gish gallop is. 

Edit: crickets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't call the type of guy to speak that way, "men." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I won't be taking questions or holding a town hall, ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure where you're getting "violent" from. And the Kaine family is incredibly down-to-earth, humble, and charitable. So basically, you're wrong on every level.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! Fuck those struggling families who pay taxes and just want to be left alone! /s

What's unethical is what Trump and ICE are doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Clean as a whistle caught on tape bragging about sexual assault.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're telling me, "I will literally die without this" is more reasonable than "Obama is a socialist!!" ? 

You'd be right to say that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be noshing and getting good and drunk during those hearings. Hopefully it'll be a good time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Now go back home to your golden palace in the sky." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  shorter is better.

Reminds me of the Samantha Bee bit where's she played Spicer saying "it's just so frustrating when nothing we do is good enough, it's not big enough..." And Sam comforts him, saying, "shh, honey, I know, I know."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. The concept of safe spaces came about during civil/women's/LGBT rights consciousness raising meetings. 

The meetings were a "safe space" to speak about your struggles and be yourself in a world which was hostile to who you were. 

Totalitarians don't get safe spaces. Saying they deserve them is insulting to those who *actually* needed them in history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can bet your ass Exxon is going to the arctic circle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 09:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you *seen* Michelle? 

He's just as lucky as she. They're a gorgeous couple.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 09:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, Obama is just hot. 

He, Michelle, and the girls are the only first family to rival the Kennedys in beauty and poise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even Snooki, who I once thought of as the epitome of reality TV idiots, is smart enough to see though Trump. 

I'm not sure if her tv persona is an act, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no set number. It's everyone who sees Putin for what he is: a cruel, corrupt, totalitarian, ethnosupremacist war criminal.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never forget that the problems with Obamacare exist mostly because Obama was forced to compromise with a do-nothing republican congress. 

Obama wanted to give us universal healthcare. 

Hillary did, too, and her attempt was shot down when she was First Lady.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans like to tout Reagan, but they never mention his granting amnesty to undocumented immigrants or passing gun control laws. 

Or Iran-Contra.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't perfect by any means, but he was good. 

He is one of the three men about whom, in *March,* Rep. John Lewis wrote "that was the last time I ever saw him alive."     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't seen it, I recommend *The Day Kennedy Died*, a documentary which outlines that tragic day moment by moment. It's on Netflix iirc. 

I've always felt a deep, personal sadness for Jackie, and that doc does a wonderful job of explaining what she did and felt and what was done for her. Her personal Secret Service bodyguard is one of the interviewees and his account is gut-wrenching. 

The most emotional part for me was when she said goodbye to get husband. His body was lying in the hospital room under a sheet, and, as she left the room, she noticed his foot was uncovered. She took his foot in her hand, kissed it, and covered it before being escorted out by her bodyguard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And don't forget, he was the president who got the ball rolling on Civil Rights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you kindly. I was hoping the NPR article would link to it, and was disappointed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's one of the most secure government agencies because the data they deal with is so sensitive. 

Although it's hardly as if the easily hacked State Dept. doesn't handle sensitive info.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 10:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like "one lump is benign and operable, but it'll take the best surgeons a long time to cure and there a lot of physical therapy you'll need to do, and the other lump is a fully formed malignancy whose side effects include devastating opportunistic infections. Oh and also lump 2 is contagious." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still, though. That's fucking stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that "work makes you free."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smooth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My response was always just "Hillary's campaign is the most progressive in history."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, but he was the illegitimate half-brother of the NK dictator and thus was murdered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I was addressing you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured it was because Harry had finally grown up enough to stop seeing Dumbledore as a perfect person, especially after he heard Dumbledore scream about his worst fears and memories in HBP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Nazi fuck Spencer is the most eloquent idiot I've ever heard speak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They anglicized the spelling. I have records from both before and after they immigrated.  But I was wrong about Ellis Island  they moved here during the Great Famine and came in elsewhere. It was the other side of my family  the French side  that came in through Ellis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Willful ignorance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't bother. This guy literally took part in the harassment and refuses to acknowledge it as harassment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, minorities attack whites at a higher rate than whites attacks minorities.   Stats are fun
 

Yeah, it's lots of fun to take statistics at face value and not bother examining the systemic social causes of phenomena. It makes it much easier when using them to push a narrative that they don't actually support.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family lives at the very end of the Colorado river. Like, follow it a few more miles and you hit the gulf. Good to know they're probably going to get poisoned and it's not Arizona's choice, for once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As do I.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.cnn.com/2017/03/05/us/washington-sikh-shooting/index.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only my sense of personal identity. *eyeroll*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Sikh man was told to "go back to (his) country" and then shot. That's not a coincidence. He's also not dead. 

The hanged boy's death is still under investigation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a Lebanese thing. It's a personal choice. The guy you knew chose to change his name, and the guy in the article did not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family name was changed ~~at Ellis Island~~ when they came to America because it was too confusing to spell in its original Irish. My family dealt with it because it became their legal name before they could do anything about it, but they did not choose to lose their name. 

Names are important. My first name is French, but I'll die before I change it to make someone else's day easier. It's my fucking name. In the end, it's all I have.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The man with the president's ear, folks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably part of president Bannon's plan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We already said that to the translators who have been denied entry. Fucking shameful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's precisely what got us into this mess - Islamic terrorism got wall to wall national coverage, but domestic white nationalist terrorism got local coverage at best much of the time (Dyann Roof being the only exception I can think of).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but they're mostly poor and nonwhite. So a disheartening portion of America doesn't care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure it's a submission thing, not a gay thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or need a public option for healthcare. 

Or need social security. 

Or like the environment. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to get off Mr Bones Wild Ride </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you misunderstand, that logic only applies to *women*. Duh. /s but that's def what this guy thinks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, just because you're a misogynist victim blamer. 

You're the kind of dude that, after his time as a marine mechanic, convinced my dad to ban me from dating servicemen. I should give him a call and thank him.  

I'd just like to point out the irony of my comment being removed, but your comments where you literally admitted to sexually harassing and doxing your fellow marines are all still around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking right? What is up with this guy, besides the fact that he's about to get a court martial? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never mind that, if someone reports this conversation to one of the investigators and the IP can be tabbed back to this guy, he's admitted to being involved and not being sorry, lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot about that one, holy shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a funny way to spell fascism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh fuck off, mate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Practical raptors, our national symbols are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Independent journalism isn't a bad thing mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then perhaps you shouldn't be posting about an ongoing legal matter you're involved with online, don't you think? 

All it's doing is putting proof out there that you're aware of the allegations, took part in the action, and don't feel bad about it. Lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking as a woman, it's obviously their fault because, by being women, we basically *beg* to be reduced to sexual objects and harassed! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, the report came from the Institute for Investigative Journalism, and investigative journalists tend not to publish without being sure of their sources. 

But it's more convenient to dismiss what is literally evidence by saying it's isn't, amirite?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When someone gets this defensive and uses that kind of inclusive language, it usually means they have either participated in that kind of behavior or think it's okay to do so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does a court-marital smell like? Cigarettes and starched collars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally none of what you said was accurate. Did you even read the article? Do you know anything about how consent works? What about revenge porn case law? Holy shit.  

Also: 

In one instance cited in the report, a woman corporal in uniform was followed at Camp Lejeune in North Carolina by a fellow Marine, who surreptitiously photographed her as she picked up her gear. The picture was posted to the Marines United private FB page, where dozens of obscene, sexually explicit comments were posted.     

Lastly, by claiming they're not victims and it's their fault for taking those photos, you're literally victim blaming lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm certain the women in the photos were very surprised.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh if Obama knows how to embroider I'll be fucking impressed.  That shit looks hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Scotland abhors President Dumpster Fire, is the Irish public similarly against him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't care if Quist is a musician. If we can make the rural Midwest liberal again, we're golden. Ffs, McGovern was a Dakotan, and he would've been the most progressive president since FDR. His defeat was what caused the democrats to race to the center.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubt the women consented to those photos being shared. 

But yeah, blame the victims. That'll show those evil victims not to get stalked and harassed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nonconsenting coworkers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never mind that, at age 69, Hillary is probably more hormonally stable than the average 45-year-old man.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's like saying "the sun's gonna come up in the morning" at this point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he's lucky, all this attention might keep him from "shooting himself" in the back of the head, twice.  

But it also makes him more of a target for such "suicides" orchestrated by the FSB.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you Catholic, by chance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I make 8.10/hr. I'd be okay with slightly higher prices if it meant I could breathe a little after paying rent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chordoma. 

It's a spinal tumor which has a low risk of metastasis, but will grow back if not eradicated completely. 

That's how fascism works, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no way of knowing for sure, but I feel like he is based solely on the fact that he is Mormon and unmarried. And he doesn't want to undo marriage equality based on "public opinion" being for it, but I'm not sure if that's still accurate.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus, no one will have access to reddit anymore because a) net neutrality is getting gutted, b) everything will be monitored, and c) who can afford internet when you can't even afford a better building material then cardboard boxes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't control the supreme court as of yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's... Actually better. It even sounds like a 30s slang term.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best part is that the police are so heavily militarized that they'll be able to raid GOPvilles (the new Hoovervilles) with incredible ease in order to cut down on the "undesirables."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He admires Kim Jong Un too much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it has to happen, I want it to be called this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're only due for a recession because the republicans have control of two of the three branches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thing is, we kinda *did*... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. It's a mutually important trade relationship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're a threat to our pacific allies, but one of our most important allies against Russia. That's why Russia wants to sow discord against them here. 

We were allied with the Soviets during WWII, even though they were obviously a threat. It's not a stable partnership, but it's a convenient one.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been Charlie Brown-ing a lot these days, too.  

Also "jeezy Petes," a la Cyril Figgis, has been getting a lot of use. 

I'm not allowed to swear at work and it's been bleeding into my daily life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad once fell down a flight of stone stairs and broke his knee. His leg was sticking up at an angle legs are not supposed to go. He started laughing hysterically. 

This is how America feels about Trump.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China would be pretty well fucked if we stopped trading with them. They're our most important trade partner. 

You obviously don't understand geopolitics or geoeconomics in the slightest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China certainly is, dude. And Russia is an ally in certain respects, although I agree that they've proved their hostility hasn't diminished since the fall of the USSR.  Geopolitical relations are more nuanced than one person's belief on a country.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure this conversation is pointless and you're just a trump troll. Peace out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, we were talking about Cheney. Fuck off with the misdirection.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure we were talking about Cheney, friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably a stance Stein holds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We spend more than the next dozen or so nations combined on military, all of which are our allies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Then let them eat cake."

Melania Antoinette </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
