<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1779</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/HarryPotter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that got a smirk out of me, congrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw it for the second time, and it was superb. Simply superb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never seen that one before, but I'll check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only form of punishment allowed is tickling.

I know there's some historical precedent for this sort of thing, but I remember Veggietales more than anything else.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RSpudzk3y2E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I recall, the Magistrate was actually known as The Foolish Magistrate in the story book. Tai-tai was grating, but eventually mellowed out--the episode where she lost a simple trinket her father had given her upon returning from a journey was very humanizing for her.

But those dogs were awful. They were just mean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the episode where the kittens learn about their names, but I didn't know that about the daughters. 

This is fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You remember correctly.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cOP7rkUrqNE

And I found your favorite too. Dimensions are a little off though:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6BAXoyrmAr4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/UExpectedANameHuh, would you like us to start a brand-new prompt, or continue one we've started already? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.fanfiction.net/s/7227719/1/Dinner-With-the-Weasleys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IP] Friends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://spotty-polka-dotty.deviantart.com/art/best-123073242 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Setting aside computers, with the number of times they've killed the suspect, I doubt any cop in any cop show would still be on the force.

And then there's the absolutely horrific abuse of the Fourth Amendment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, doctor, hospital?! Won't do any good?! Eleven times?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say a man should always dress for the job he wants.

So why am I dressed up like a pirate in this restaurant?

It's all because some hacker stole my identity.

Now I'm in here every evening serving chowder and iced tea.

Shoulda gone to Free Credit Report dot com.

**Yee-haw**

I could have seen this coming at me like an atom bomb

They monitor your credit and send you email alerts

So you don't end up selling fish to tourists in t-shirts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CALL JG WENTWORTH! 877-CASH-NOW!

THEY'VE HELPED THOUSANDS, THEY'LL HELP YOU TOO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deck the Halls or Santa Clause 3.

And I saw them on the same day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think publication is indicative of quality necessarily, but at the same time I don't think that excuses obvious cash-ins either.

Perhaps you are right--acknowledgment that my novel is the sort of thing people would buy is what I'd like. And I'd like to see it happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it unique to ladybugs or does this apply to other beetles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wolverine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, alligators are generally pretty docile. Crocodiles are far more aggressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably writing a novel. I've done it before--once in high school for fun, and then again in college.

Maybe I should amend this to writing a novel and getting it published. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember George Shrinks! It aired on Bookworm Bunch, with Elliot Moose and Timothy Goes to School!

It was actually pretty good, from what I recall. I liked all the little gadgets George made for himself, to make managing being four inches tall easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree with you but didn't Indiana Jones, who Nate is more or less an expo of, kill his fair share?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Splee! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know that the voice actor for Dongwa, her brother, was one of  D.W.'s voice actors?

Or that Baba Miao was voiced by Mr. Ratburn? Or that Mama Miao was voiced by Mrs. Read (which is actually isn't particularly surprising, comparatively speaking)?

I think my favorite episode was the one where Sagwa snuck food out to one of her friends, Finn, who didn't get enough at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember it existing, but I didn't watch it. Partly because I don't think my mom would have let me, and partly because it did look kind of stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of traditional 2-D animation, very few seem to remember *Adventures from the Book of Virtues* or *Rupert Bear.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great choice! That was a fantastic cartoon that needs a lot more love.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that may be because it stank, and Nickelodeon pulled it quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sagwa, you're my best friend... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fanfiction.net </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think this is a good question. 

First, let me say that I believe that all life is sacred. In addition to being pro-life, I am leery of the death penalty. 

Am I willing to kill somebody who will go on to do great evil?

My answer is no. 

It is a travesty of justice for the punishment to come before the crime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They grabbed me when I came back from checking the mail, and the first thing they did was tie my scarf around my eyes to use as a blindfold. 

I yelled and kicked and punched--one of them was wearing a sweatshirt and another was wearing flannel.

I could hear three voices...but they were speaking in a language I did not understand. Gibberish it sounded like. 

I was dragged away, my sneakers scraping against the asphalt of my family's driveway. Their grip was like iron, pressing into my arms. 

I hear the door to my house being opened. 

The one holding my left arm asked a question in that gibberish I don't understand. His voice is squeaky and then deeper and then squeaky again. A voice from above me answers but of course I can't understand it.

I'm lowered to the ground--my head bonks against the linoleum of the kitchen floor--and then my legs are lifted up. I try to protest, but my captors ignore me. I'm being dragged again, and I register the carpeting of the family room. The voices are arguing--though it doesn't sound overly combative.

I'm being dragged downstairs, my head scraping against the stairs, into my family's basement. It's much cooler here and it smells musty. And what little light I could register through the scarf is even more muted.

I'm forced to sit in a wooden chair. The three murmur to one another, still in that gibberish. Why can't they speak English?

*Skriitch* 

The sound of tearing? No, not quite tearing. At least not clothes. More like tape.... 

"Mmmmmph!"

The duct tape is pressed against my mouth, and then smaller pieces are placed on either end.

"Mmmmph!"

Something thin and scratching is wrapped around one of my wrists, and then my arm is yanked behind me. I struggle but my wrists are tied behind me. It's not particularly tight--the dress shoes I wear to church pinch more, truth be told--but the knots are tied in places my fingers can't reach.

I try to kick out but my foot is caught. There's some more gibberish and my sneakers are pulled off. And then my socks. The cement floor of the basement is freezing against my bare feet and then another rope is tied around my knees. It isn't tight either, but the knots is out of reach.

I'm completely trapped. And my nose itches.

I hear the sounds of shuffling and then I hear the television being turned on. And then the Playstation. And then the sounds of lasers and spaceships and explosions. And more yelling in gibberish.
****
And that's the story of how my brothers took me prisoner to stop me from tattling when they played some stupid Star Trek video game for six hours when they were supposed to be doing chores. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You assume that the people playing number large enough so that each piece gets picked.

You also assume that nobody swipes one of the pieces from a novelty box to avoid the wheelbarrow. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. Did anybody EVER pick the wheelbarrow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On birds:

You can have raptors--birds of prey. Eagles and hawks and falcons.

Seabirds: Pelicans and albatross and cormorants

Songbirds: Self-explanatory

Flightless birds: Ostriches have been bred for meat and people race them (yes really). The now extinct Moa was even larger.

Don't be afraid to diversify. Historically, falcons were raised by man to hunt. But what if, in addition to this, they were bred for color? Imagine falcons in vibrant shades of red and gold and blue.
*****
On cows:

Cattle are actually part of the bovid family, and this includes bison, water buffalo, cows, and sheep and goats.

But let's focus on cows, for the moment. Or at least, cows and other bovids that are large enough to squish humans.

Cattle are a fair bit more diverse than a lot of people realize. Just in America, you've got your Holsteins (the classic black and white), Texas Longhorns, Jersey cows, and more.

Cattle have occasionally been bred with bison, leading to hybrids called "beefalo." 

Bison are huge, mighty beasts. And then buffalo in Africa and water buffalo in India are similarly large.

And then there's yaks and muskox.
*****
Bears.

Well, what kinds of bears are we talking about? There are eight species of bear: the brown (includes grizzlies and Kodiaks) bear, the polar bear, the American black bear, the Asiatic black bear, the spectacled bear, the sloth bear, the sun bear, and the giant panda.

You could go a more mystical route here. There are many Native legends about the Kermode bear and glacier bear, which are American black bears with white and blue coats respectively. 
***
Dinosaurs. 

Okay, the first dinosaur that came to mind was an ankylosaurus.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ankylosaurus#/media/File:Ankylosaurus_magniventris_reconstruction.png

Call them "club-tails" or maybe "stone-backs." They could pull plows or maybe be used in military conflicts.

And though they're not technically dinosaurs, could plesiosaurs be used? They could be beasts of the ocean that your peoples have a semi-friendship with, not unlike man's relationship with dolphins.
****
Reptiles

Can't overlook turtles or crocodilians. Or monitor lizards like the Komodo dragon--though if you're sticking with dinosaurs, then I recommend Megalania. Think a Komodo dragon that was thirty feet long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IP] Simple Things </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://pascalcampion.deviantart.com/art/Simple-things-615970611 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in the same way that they did Jungle Book, with the extremely realistic animation.

The question is whether or not they will change the plot in a meaningful way. And in ways that **haven't** actually been done before. (The 2016 Jungle Book shares more than a few similarities with that live-action *Jungle Book: Mowgli's Story*) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> inFAMOUS and inFAMOUS 2 are quite simply the best superhero games ever made. Great visuals, fun and evolving powers, a above-average storyline, and character choices that make legitimate differences in gameplay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not quite sure what I can say that might be of help to you. I haven't seen anything quite like this.

But I can say that this was not your fault. This was not your fault. This was **not** your fault. 

You need to find someone, anyone, to talk to. You mentioned that you think therapists and counselors might have long waiting lists, and this is possible. But I would still suggest that you seek help, from somebody.

I don't know whether or not you're religious, but if you are, it may be a good idea to speak to your pastor. A lot of the time, they have counseling training. 

And u/imonewiththeschwartz is right. We're here for you if you need anybody to talk to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "On one otherwise normal Tuesday evening I had the chance to live the American dream. I was able to throw my incompetent jackass of a boss from a fourteenth-story window."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of authors, I hold Larry Correia in the highest of respect. He's the author of *Monster Hunter International,* *The Grimnoir Chronicles,* and *Son of the Black Sword.* 

In short, he's the man who made me love reading for fun again. There was something enormously gratifying in reading something that was well-written and **fun** when I was in college. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it hasn't been very fun in a while. 

That said, I've grown to appreciate CinemaWins. 

https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCL8h3ri2WN_-IbviBlWtUcQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will Friedle. 

Yes, the one who was Eric Matthews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taken as two parts of one whole, inFAMOUS and inFAMOUS 2.

Best superhero game ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nightmares of Future Past is over 400,000 words.

https://www.fanfiction.net/s/2636963/1/Harry-Potter-and-the-Nightmares-of-Futures-Past </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 11:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was really, really good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 11:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww, this was very sweet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, here's another story. *Mind's Eye, Soul's Reflection*

http://www.sugarquill.net/read.php?storyid=2023 chapno=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of Biblical, specifically Old Testament, history repeats itself in similar ways. Floods happen, a reverse tower of Babel, leading to the diaspora of most life. God always favors the humans specifically in my world, though there aren't any real non-human followers.

Personally, I drew some inspiration from the Judges in developing my heroes, though those ideas are largely on the back burner now.

There's a constant battle between gods and I have the Abrahamic God as the good guy, though his followers arent always too good. The world is constantly undersiege by demonic forces and physical manifestations of sin, so there's definite "evil" I guess.

There's nothing wrong with this. Some of the greatest heroes from the Bible were deeply flawed human beings. King David for one.

If you're curious, I base the justification of having other gods exist in my interpretation of "thou shalt not worship any other god before me" (paraphrased) to be admittance that other Gods exist; but you must solely place your faith in him.

I've given this some thought too, actually. Occasionally. The prophet Elijah confronted the prophets of Ba'al, after all. 

So you say these Shepherds had crusades and priests, Im assuming there was no precursor? No jewish-esque faith?

I should have clarified. The Shepherds are an off-shoot of the Crusaders from 1000 A.D. (I'll need to read up on the Crusades to get the specifics). They were one temple over from the knights that formed the Templars, and instead of treasure, they found a gateway to another world.

So the reason there wasn't much of a Jewish-esque faith is that Christians got there first, so to speak. Other people have travelled to the various realms throughout history, but the first people who were deliberately sent to the other world were these knights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, well in that case, I'll go and find you some more. 

You like longer fics:

Not From Others

https://www.fanfiction.net/s/11419408/1/Not-From-Others

Stages of Hope

https://www.fanfiction.net/s/6892925/1/Stages-of-Hope

The Butterfly Effect (YMMV on this one. It has a lot of the OP!Harry tropes. But it definitely has moments that are genuinely good. And it is quite long)

https://www.fanfiction.net/s/11254763/1/The-Butterfly-Effect

When in Doubt, Obliviate!

https://www.fanfiction.net/s/6635363/1/When-In-Doubt-Obliviate

Oh God, Not Again!

https://www.fanfiction.net/s/4536005/1/Oh-God-Not-Again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the Wolf Comes Home. I know it isn't terribly long, but it is good.

http://archiveofourown.org/works/6873916?view_full_work=true

Here's a 400,000 word fic. That should hold you over. Not sure if it can be downloaded though

https://www.fanfiction.net/s/2636963/1/Harry-Potter-and-the-Nightmares-of-Futures-Past </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Singing a very annoying jingle and waving your arms around

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f9dWld7EsqQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And to my knowledge, he's never admitted that he was wrong. But I disliked that video from the very beginning. There's just something really smug about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.

With all due respect to the OP, when I think of meteors, I cannot help but think:

SPACE SWORD!

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DITY1WzbLj8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they have some interesting statistics, like Florida has more people with concealed gum carry permits than any other state.

That's curious. I wasn't aware that chewing gum required a permit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this inspired by Calvin and his Duplicator?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh...Santa? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a name for this race of peoples yet, but they're powerful healers. They can absorb the injuries of the wounded and take on the pain for themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So are your Gods real?

In my world, only one God is real. Though many pagan idols exist.

Is there only one religion that's right?

The religion of the Shepherds is right--though there are some denominational differences. And there are many false religions. 

Are there multiple?

No, there is only one God. Though my villains fancy themselves gods. 

Is there one God that is misinterpreted as many?

No, though this does remind me a fair bit of "Tashlan" from *The Last Battle.* 

Furthermore, are they interventionists or do they keep to themselves?

The God of the Shepherds is loving and intervening in the lives of His followers. But it's often through the use of prophets. 

Are they like the [A]brahamic God or like the ancient Greek gods?

The God of the Shepherds *is* the Abrahamic God. The first knights who went on to form the Shepherds were participants in the Crusades. They set up a few tiny sanctuaries in the realms they were sworn to protect. And there were also a few chapels already existing.

Consider this: there are werewolf priests that can give communion to Minotaurs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, I've been waiting for something like this question.

My world started forming ten years ago. It was more or less Narnia--a forested world connected to ours by gateways. Denizens of the fantasy world included dragons and elves. Creatures that could travel between them were cryptids--Sasquatch, onza, shunka warakin, Loch Ness Monsters. Defending the gateways were a group I called the International League of Christian Cryptozoologists. (The name sucked, I know). I eventually renamed the ILCC the Cryptid Templar.

Ninth grade, I pushed myself (and my brother hogged the video games) and lo and behold, I was able to finish a rough draft, 39,500 words long. 

That was nine years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cortez was the Spaniard. Columbus was Italian, from the Republic of Genoa. He simply worked for the Spanish monarchs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sense#Non-traditional_senses

Balance? That's not really related to touch (like heat or pain would be). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] [IP] Two men amid the flames </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.deviantart.com/art/Meet-the-real-Fire-Lord-311146980 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent prompt for this week, and I have to say that I feel honored to be included in the look back to last week's top prompts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, here's a couple videos that compare the howls. Maybe that can help.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6qdUTRjvSVY

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=byMUVZ1yRp8

Where'd you say this was? Iowa? A lot of coyote populations in the Eastern United States have a fair bit of wolf blood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cougars have been known to take down moose on occasion, and in some regions, elk, which are no slouch, is their primary prey.

And there is also deer:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1CLqJCGNCjo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it took only one hit to kill your horse. And the ruckus usually attracted a pack of wolves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indian wolves, which may actually be their own species, are rather small as wild canids go--weighing only about 50 pounds, or 25 kilograms. Wolves in North America can weigh over a hundred pounds.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Indian_wolf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The term you are looking for is "Dragon"

http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/TheDragon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for pointing that out, I fixed it.

I'm really glad you enjoyed this.

Samuel and Elizabeth are actually my go-to characters when having to write about a chaste romance. I've used them in another love story prompt, and intend to do so again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmmm....do you read any other book series or are you looking for something to hold you over? Butcher's written a great epic fantasy series in *Codex Alera.*

Or if you want to stick with urban fantasy with protagonists that are smart-mouths, there's *Monster Hunter International.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They sat side by side, the boy and the girl.

His head in his arms, his knees to his chest, he stared down the bank.

She sprawled on the grass giggling, her bare toes amid the dandelions wiggling.

He was lost in thought; her head was in the clouds.

And they were happy.
****
His name was Samuel. His t-shirt stuck to the back of his neck, but the shade of the tree prevented discomfort. His bicycle, his transportation to anywhere his heart desired lay to the side. This place was where he desired to be. Samuel turned to his companion, and smiled. 

Her name was Elizabeth. Her arms, browned from the sun, stretched up, tucked behind her head, nestled under dark tresses. Her dress shoes lay discarded; blades of grass brushed against and tickled her bare feet. Elizabeth shifted her gaze to Samuel.
****
To stay here forever, that would be nice. Samuel liked being with Elizabeth. She was a dreamer, and always hoping to find the good. Sun beams peeked through the branches of the shady tree they sat under and kissed Elizabeth's arms.

Simplicity was blissful, mused Elizabeth. She liked sitting with Samuel. Sometimes they talked about things, things like the future, and sometimes she held his hand when he was upset. And sometimes, they just sat like this. Under the shade of a tree, while the brook flowed downstream.
****
Love is often considered the most complex of all emotions. We do things that we cannot explain for those we love. But this wasn't the case with the love Samuel and Elizabeth had.

It was uncomplicated. It was simple. It was good. It was right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah...I forgot that one.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not a bad idea at all. We've seen the kids as elementary schoolers and teenagers. Seeing them as young adults just trying to make it on their own is a very good idea indeed. And I second seeing Young Randall trying to woo Young Beth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~What about Hephaestus, of the forge?~~

It has come to my attention that Hephaestus was not a very nice person after all. So, instead, I present Hestia. Hestia's nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So do I. I started on them a year and a half ago, and am now on Book 16.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, Doctor Cox...I think I missed the punchline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er, did you mean to reply to me? I was just pointing out that Trump has held pro-life views for a relatively short amount of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which fandoms are we talking about for AO3? The best Harry Potter fics (with only a few exceptions) are all at Fanfiction.net. Same thing with Avatar: The Last Airbender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you're not entirely wrong--Trump has identified as pro-life for several years, and unlike most of his flip-flops, I'm less inclined to believe he's just playing it up for the base. People change their positions on that issue all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Kevorkian." That's fun to say! Funny random words--that's a great idea Coxy!

How does Schmoolod sound? Or maybe Teppellambo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, to my understanding, Donald Trump only relatively recently shifted to a more pro-life stance. He was advocating partial-birth abortion back in the 1990s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes some sense. The Cap trilogy is over (and it was an extremely solid offering), and now we're going into the Infinity War. 

Cap, more than any other established A-List Avenger in the MCU, has the opportunity to pass the torch. 

Bucky is enhanced with a Soviet-Serum, and has been shown to be adept at using Cap's shield himself. And Sam Wilson, the Falcon, is steadfastly loyal and holds near-identical views on liberty and righteousness to Steve Rogers. Either one of them would be an excellent candidate to be the new Captain America.

Also, with respect to the Infinity War, there is a classic scene where Captain America stares down Thanos, the Mad Titan.
https://goo.gl/images/68XivW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cox, if laughter is the best medicine, how 'bout we tell some jokes for the patients? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, don't misunderstand me. The story is fantastic. It's strange, yes, but in a good way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's bizarre, but also extremely faithful to the source material, so take that as you will.

The Dragon King's Temple crosses over Avatar: The Last Airbender and Stargate.

https://www.fanfiction.net/s/7679074/1/The-Dragon-King-s-Temple </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, you work for Disney?! Would you ever do an AMA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great line, and Eustace wound up being one of my favorite characters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The building was on fire, and it wasn't my fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever thought of posting one yourself? You seem to have a good sense of humor about this genre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book readers of Reddit, what was the first book you checked out from the library? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, a third option. Guess "Redvines vs. Twizzlers" doesn't qualify for "absolutely no in-between." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rory Gilmore getting pregnant at the end of Gilmore Girls: A Year in the Life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But don't Minnesotans tell Canada jokes a lot? Like how all Canadians are afraid of the dark? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There definitely does seem to be a difference between the older sibling being needlessly cruel, and stuff along these lines where they all laugh about it when they're old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the actual definition? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The greatest moment in any younger sibling's life is when he or she is bigger than the older sibling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I never put ketchup on anything. Not even fries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Redvines or Twizzlers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, then what about a sandwich wrap? Or a burrito for that matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did that work out? You said he was four years older--that's big enough to squish you both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what about open-faced sandwiches? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yikes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of me wants to say yes, but at the same time, a seven-year-old girl and a seven-year-old boy are about the same size.

So, you were the middle child, between two boys. Did your brothers ever team up to get you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about a meatball sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dr. Pepper is better than either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Third option, place the roll on its side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang.

For those of us Americans, a lizard that is one meter long is a little bit longer than a yard.

So u/maps_mandalas managed to track down a three-foot long lizard, drag it home, and hide it in her older brother's room.

Edit: u/maps_mandalas informed me that she is a girl, so I edited accordingly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were you afraid of heights in general? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never saw *Dante's Peak,* and now, never will see *Dante's Peak.* Not ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is very gross. What happened when you'd tell your folks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, blessed AO3; the land of well-developed and fleshed-out characters and what-might-have-beens.

You must have better luck than I. I have almost always had better luck on Fanfiction.net when it came to finding good fics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Colin Farrell, I thought he was a fantastic villain. I almost wish he was playing Grindelwald instead.

I would prefer him to be along the lines of Grindelwald's lieutenant. We know that Albus Dumbledore is the one who takes down Grindelwald once and for all (and we'll get to see that in Movie 5), but a lieutenant who believes in the cause could be a perfect adversary for Newt and friends to fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adding onto this, it's worth noting that very little of the Harry Potter books carries over elements of classical British folklore.

Jim Butcher (with his Sidhe courts, Foo dogs, Fallen and archangels), Rowling ain't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Younger siblings of Reddit, how did your older siblings tease or torment you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cory Matthews and Shawn Hunter from Boy Meets World. There is something extremely gratifying about a duo of opposites that don't even bother justifying it. Cory and Shawn are friends because they're friends, period.

Runner-up: Mr, Feeny and Eric Matthews
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost always put water on before the toothpaste. If I'm not careful with doing it the other way, then my toothpaste falls off my toothbrush and I have to start over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That the Red Sox are better than the Yankees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful! This one seems to have the hero and villain on the best terms thus far. I enjoyed it very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's "Swimmy." And I looked online and I couldn't find any criticism about it being socialist.

https://www.amazon.com/dp/B006N56YL0/ref=dp-kindle-redirect?_encoding=UTF8 btkr=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I like slice-of-life fanfics, especially those that focus on Ginny and Luna.

So, here's Fire and Air:

https://www.fanfiction.net/s/11152139/1/Fire-and-Air

And here's Dinner With the Weasleys--a fic I describe as the Sunday dinner you eat at your grandparents' after church. Most impressive about this one? Luna's point of view, first person, and it *works.*

https://www.fanfiction.net/s/7227719/1/Dinner-With-the-Weasleys

You can never have too much Luna. Here's one of the best Luna-fics of them all. *Mind's Eye, Soul's Reflection.*

http://www.sugarquill.net/read.php?storyid=2023 chapno=1

Finally, if you're looking for an AU story that will not scare her off...then the only one I can recommend is Stages of Hope.

https://www.fanfiction.net/s/6892925/1/Stages-of-Hope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Is Us--Season 2 Speculation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, what a season. What a season. Where do we go from here, guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then...what happens next season? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
