<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6129</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A year ago: http://www.upi.com/Defense-News/2016/02/04/Russian-company-proposes-production-of-T-90S-tanks-in-Iran/4261454593338/ 

A week before that the UN sanctions were lifted. And here we are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamas Ukrainian Coup Caused 2.5 Million Ukrainian Refugees into Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep. Dana Rohrabacher challenges former Estonian President Toomas Hendrik over nonexistent 'military threat' posed by Russia, warns of war. Respect! https://t.co/pzXjuTfIW6" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukrainian Soldiers Caught Planting Car Bombs in Donbass. Guess Who Trained Them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Od Ebra do Dunava (Live in Vilnius) - Barcelona Gipsy balKan Orchestra </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia's Sberbank's head office in Kiev suspended work for security reasons https://t.co/7U7lTFB7m3" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Church of the Savior on Spilled Blood in St. Petersburg was built on the spot where Alexander II was assassinated on March 13, 1881. https://t.co/oUARrgSGI3" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dutch PM Rutte says nationalist Wilders could win election | Reuters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New drinking game sweeping the nation! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 10:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps saving orca wales, and washed up comedians! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 10:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia Did It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 arrested in pro-Trump rally in Berkeley. LET THE FRONT PIC SINK! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In new book, MIT linguist expands the horizons of language analysis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the same Harry Reid who said in Dec 2016:

**In my communications with you and other top officials in the national security community, it has become clear that YOU POSSESS EXPLOSIVE INFORMATION about close ties and coordination between Donald Trump, his top advisers and the Russian government  a foreign interest openly hostile to the United States, which Trump praises at every opportunity**

So he pretty well knew from the horse's mouth that the Jared/Flynn talk with Amb. Kislyak in the Trump Tower were wiretapped and he knew about the transcript of the talk. Now ELI5 how they had a transcript of the talk if they didn't wiretapped it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JOHN McAFEE speaks the truth: If it looks like Russia did it, I can GUARANTEE you - It WASN'T Russia Memo to the Resistance https://t.co/hopE8Biaqk" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 06:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia in RSA on Twitter: "Russian MFA Spokesperson Maria Zakharova on @LisaMillar's question whether #Russia might 'return' #Crimea to Ukraine: NEVER, N-E-V-E-R https://t.co/vaHS82JfxN" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Eastern Outlook on Twitter: "The State Department didn't invite #Moscow representatives to #Washington to meet 68 states members of the anti-#ISIS coalition https://t.co/AfgZBV6bWy" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Police Union Head: "Integration has failed. Don't believe me? Come to Berlin" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German police union head: Integration has failed. Don't believe me? Come to Berlin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pamela Moore on Twitter: "Reagan was right. https://t.co/VrPYAbcY4F" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obsession </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Museum exhibits Russia's cold war secrets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaks and Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty simple if you look at the details. The EU sanctions don't block Russian trade, they block individuals and their assets mainly, make access to financing from EU banks more difficult and the ONLY trade affected directly is high tech in deep sea drilling and oil/gas extracting technologies (which by default will reflect on the EU gas/oil delivery prices - I hope you can see the absurd here). Russia OTOH directly blocked trade imports from the EU and the US. That causes loss of jobs and mainly of market (as that could be irrecoverable even if relations are restored), it gives the Russian economy an impetus to diversify from its mainly raw materials export dependence, develop its own economy and create jobs. Also the EU sanctions literally have no effect even in the areas they target as seen - the Norway company which had the contract for providing deep sea drilling tech, and fell under the EU sanctions, just registered an offshore company that served as a shell and thus avoided the sanctions. So let the sanctions stay and Russia develop its economy and I believe in the current situation Russia is NOT a partner which will be denied financing from other banking institutions outside the EU. Plain as that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  counter-sanctions are more disruptive to Russia than to the EU

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 09:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.ceps.eu/publications/economic-impact-sanctions-against-russia-much-ado-about-very-little </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China trying to rope India, Russia in cyber pact against the West </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia to Arm Nuclear Subs With New Supersonic Cruise Missile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll rather disregard your advice which, believe it or not, I didn't ask for. Now you can go and get informed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>     ,      " -     </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you're spreading the anti-american narrative more than anything.

You are def right about that and /u/Lucky13R and /u/Alpha100f are not right about giving you sweat. **Anyone CAN open the Google Search Home page and input 'Sally Ride' and CLEARLY see that this is NOT what comes up.** The OP is NOT using Google Search in his first example but some deviant search. Period. No Google Search result comes in this form as in his first screenshot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have a slightest idea about the foreign involvement in Chechnya, just saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, man, you are ruining the wishful thinking of the debased primitive russophobes with facts. We all know these US prospects were a result of "Russian hacking".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Budget deficit in Russia is no different than the one in the US as % from GDP, both around the 3% mark. That (RNWF) is ONLY one of the reserve funds, the other one increased and so did the FX reserves. Russia is out of the recession and heading forward, GDP is on the rise too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia doesn't mind and is happy to extend the sanctions on EU too. Haven't heard any Russian official even the ones the sanctions are directly against complain. Everyone is taking it in stride and  agree that even if sanctions against Russia are lifted the ones against the EU should remain as they are a push for the economy to diversify, seek better and cheaper alternatives and get self-sustainable as opposed to dependent on oil and oil products only.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, they'll enjoy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't call tossing the dead bodies in the *septic tank*, read the lavatory, a proper burial but maybe I'm old-fashioned guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>         :   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 09:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Catholic church is shocked at the hundreds of children buried at Tuam, Ireland. Really? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 09:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Russia... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Refugees Already Destroyed Swedish Police...Police Chief tells girls: Dont go out after sunset or youll be raped or worse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pamela Moore on Twitter: "CIA posed as Russian hackers to create all these false flags  everyone but Trump fell for it So Big Brother was not a myth after all #Vault7 https://t.co/Z3ZkmTosDb" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reuters Top News on Twitter: "LIVE: Panel to hold open public hearing in Russia probe on March 20 - House Intelligence Committee Chairman Nunes. https://t.co/4Yq9rOeSfu" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhhh, that's easy - an attempt to establish a No Fly Zone in Syria as she vouched e.g. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, starting a war against ISIS is one thing, starting a war against Russia **CAUSE THAT'S WHAT A No-Fly Zone OVER SYRIA MEANS** is totally a horse of a different color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
