<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3471</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A LITTLE HELP PLEASE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hell is What You Make of It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 11:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One week and three days after his wifes death was the worst day of Jake Millers life.

Its a survival mechanism that our minds cannot absorb shock all at once. The most poignant moments would be so great at their best that the rest of life would lose its luster; at the worst, fate would crush us in an instant.

Hypertrophic heart disease literally took her overnight. The next days were filled with wary friends and family staring wide-eyed at him as though he would explode at any moment. It wouldnt happen, though, at least not yet. Their surreal behavior around him kept her death in a far-off realm, one where everyday rules didnt apply, and where the normal order would be restored in due haste.

One week and three days later was the first night that no one brought over any food. The funeral had passed with all due solemnity, his wife lay in the ground, and there were no immediate plans to be made. Jake watched TV and ate dinner alone. 

This would be the new normal.

His head got suddenly hot, and the screaming began all at once. The unfairness of it all. He had been happy. Just last month (he longed for last month), he and his wife had returned a toaster to Target, because it didnt work, and that had to be fixed. 

Why was the toaster guaranteed when his world was not?

The screaming reached a fever pitch, and his head felt like it was going to explode. And then it was dark. 

Jake had no memory of waking up. He was just there. Same salmon-colored shirt, same jeans with the tiny ink stain, same cowlicked hair that had been a byproduct of decreased grooming standards over the past ten days. 

The man in front of him was new.

He was lean, nearly gaunt, and held the hint of a smirk without grinning. The sandy blonde hair was untamed but balanced. He wore a dark trench coat with the collar flipped up far too high. A lit cigarette was perched delicately between his thumb and forefinger, the smoke lazily enwreathing his head. 

Why am I here? Jake was surprised at his own question. He didnt ask where he was or how hed gotten there, but those queries seemed secondary at the moment. 

The mans hint of a grin grew into a genuine one. Well, Jake, why are you angry?

He blurted his answer before he had time to think. Because I didnt have a fucking choice! Once again, his own response surprised him, but it seemed to fit.

And thats why youre here, Jake. He pivoted his head and locked him in with his sky-blue eyes. Is it the worst thing possible? Not to have a choice? Isnt there comfort in resignation?

He struggled to answer. Jake finally decided to let the words come on their own. Who are you?

He gave half a chuckle. Oh, Ive had many names. He took a long drag from the cigarette. A name is nothing more than how other people see you. Its your choice to accept it or not. He looked down contemplatively at what he was smoking, and Jake noticed vaguely that it had not seemed to get any shorter. For the moment, you can call me Janus. Ive always liked that one.

Jake struggled to speak again, and realized that he couldnt because he was trying too hard. He relaxed again. It this real, or is it a dream?

Janus pinched the near end of the cigarette and pointed at Jake with spindly fingers. All dreams are real. Otherwise we wouldnt have them. His eyes were piercing. They happen. Whatever happens can never be undone. Thats the most important rule. He paused, took a drag, and let it slowly out his nostrils. The cigarette still did not shrink in size. But to answer your question  were in between. That will have to suffice for now. But! he nearly shouted. Never underestimate the consequences of what happens inside your head. Everything you will ever know happens inside your mind. He labored to punctuate these last few words.

He leapt down, and only then did Jake notice that he had been casually squatting on an unseen perch. It had somehow seemed to unimportant to notice before then.

Now, Janus went on, placing the cigarette back in his mouth, you couldnt live without a choice. It bobbed up and down as it dangled precariously from his lips. Lets see if you can live with one. He grabbed Jake by the collar with both hands.

Noise. Traffic, specifically, and rushing wind. It was twilight, and they were on the median of a busy thoroughfare. 

Listen carefully, Jake, Janus spoke above the din. Over there, he pointed over Jakes right shoulder, is a careless boy of about six. In a little under thirty seconds, hes going to get hit by a distracted driver from over there, he jerked his thumb over his own left shoulder. It will kill him instantly.

He put his arm around Jakes back and turned around to face the same direction. Over here, we have a meth head.

It was clear who Janus saw. Skeletal thin and ghostly pale, the man emitted wrongness. He was standing thirty feet away on the median, but apparently oblivious to their presence. He, Janus continued, is about to kill John Miller, aged thirty, walking to the gas station across the street after a long day at work. He will take nineteen dollars and thirteen cents from Mister Miller, who will die slowly of stab wounds.

And that car, he said, pointing to a white Mercedes weaving through traffic, will prevent you from saving both.

And Janus was gone.

Jake was completely frozen.

And then the spell was broken.

Jake turned away from where the boy was wandering carelessly toward traffic and sprinted toward the meth head. He looked up in paranoia, and withdrew a mean-looking Bowie knife from seemly nowhere.

Jake dove low and wrapped his arms around the mans waste. He was frail, almost fragile, and Jake spun him easily. 

Hed only have one shot at this.

Jake tiled toward the curb and hurled the meth head toward the street. The white Mercedes weaved from the far lane to the near one. 

It contacted him, and launched the man six feet into the air. 

The car fishtailed and drove up onto the median. 

It stopped well short of the boy. And John Miller, whose mind was on the Power Bar he was about to buy, had safely crossed the street before becoming vaguely aware of the commotion he had just bypassed.

Jake once again found himself alone with Janus, who was eyeing him with something between fear and admiration. So, he drawled, youre one of those people.

Jake was panting. I want, he gasped, to save my wife.

Janus regarded him for a long moment. Whatever happens can never be undone, he articulated slowly, thats the most important rule.

Jake winced in agony. So shes  gone? he whimpered. 

Gone? Janus blinked. No, shes not gone. Shes dead. Surely someone of your - predispositions - must realize that things are complicated.

Jake continued to pant, dropping his hands to his knees. I  I just want to be able to do something. Anything.

Jake, he explained slowly, you just killed a stranger. Do you really think you dont have the ability to change the world?

Jake looked up from the floor. I want to change my world. I dont want it anymore.

Janus looked strange. After a second, Jake realized that its because he was sad. 

Okay, Jake, he let out a forceful stream of smoke from his nostrils. Just remember the most important rule.

I will.

No. People never do. Now follow me.



[Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/61r6u8/hell_is_what_you_make_of_it_part_2/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
