<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7348</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 04:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, we had adoption sales (a garage sale with donated items from friends and family for the purpose of adoption) in order to help with the costs. But the supply and demand component has the benefit of giving more children families. There are couples who would insist on a white baby and pay more for that, and then there are couples who just want to love and raise a child, regardless of race. The fact that more "undesirable" (god, it makes me sick typing that) races are cheaper helps place more children in loving families than an across-the-board pricing scheme. I know of s couple who insisted on a white baby and gave up on the idea of children because they couldn't get a birth-mother to choose them. Their loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 04:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The adoption agency did a lot for the birth-mothers. Counseling, housing, childcare, etc for the last three months of their pregnancy. That plays a big role in the cost. The adoptive parents are responsible for the hospital costs too,  and since many women who choose to give up their children to adoption are not financially secure, they often don't have insurance. There is also a supply and demand component. The waiting period for white and Hispanic babies is often 5 years and twice the price of an African American baby. We were chosen for our first daughter in two weeks. The demand for AA babies is so low in the U.S. that many are adopted internationally by European and Canadian families. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who domestically adopted two babies from an adoption agency (the most accepted adoption process today) I have to say that the "human trafficking" problem is not so clear cut. Although we were chosen by the birth-mothers and have an open-adoption with them, we still bought babies with money, about the price of a mid-priced car (although that depends on the race of the child, but don't get me started on that). The birth-mothers never got a penny of that money. I would argue that the intent of the adoption is what dictates adoption vs human trafficking. Are you going to love the child as your own or are you looking for an indentured servant? Then again, are my children's weekly chores considered child labor? The rabbit hole of legitimized adoption vs child trafficking may never have a bottom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I complete disregard for your own life. Haven't got people seen the CGPGrey video on teleport?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
