<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4170</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 18:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One O too many, you mean. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 16:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple has abandoned Quicktime on *Windows*, and has no plans to patch it despite several known and serious security flaws.  AFAIK that's what the issue is over, and it has nothing to do with Macs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 14:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One owns possibly the best liquor and beer store in Grand Rapids, which is itself an amazing town for beer.  He's a freaking awesome guy. He still gets this shit, though, despite the fact that it doesn't occur to people that a *Muslim* would be any good at making beer pairing recommendations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 01:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By assholes, maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 01:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live 185 miles (~300 km) from Chicago, up Lake Michigan's west shore.  Chicago is absolutely our area's cultural locus even though Detroit is in-state and closer by ~30 miles (50 km).

EDIT: Except for pro sports, which is mixed but mostly Detroit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 03:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap! Haven't been to /r/creepy in forever, just now I click the link and the number three post is an albino owl...with BLACK EYES OMG RUN.  What the hell happened to that place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 07:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here in Michigan we have farm markets all over the place with an incredibly diverse amount of produce available if you hit them at the right time of year. Last summer my wife and I drove from Manitowoc to Sheboygan then around Lake Winnebago clockwise. Imagine how flabbergasted we were to visit market after market only to find them full of nothing but cheese and sausage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 03:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Westsider here.  I feel like that was reductionist and insulting.  

I know a lot of people who feel like the Detroit area has too much influence and people there are too dismissive of us and too happy to let GR/Kzoo/Muskegon be ignored and left out in the cold.  I also know a bunch who feel like (suburban) Detroiters are culturally very different and "weird" (i.e. selfish, materialistic, complicit in urban sprawl and inequality, willing zombies in "what's wrong with America," whatever that means), and blame Detroit and Flint for letting what happened to them slide (I'm talking about things like the white flight, corporate greed, and a relative lack of philanthropy) and taking us into the mud with them.

**I'm not saying all or any of this is correct,** (*I edited this just to bold it--I don't buy a lot of it, but I wrote it to illustrate things I hear that have nothing to do with the racism of the speaker*) but there is some smoke to support the idea of a fire.  EMU gets better funding than GVSU, for instance, and there's a lot of grumbling over how that shouldn't be so.  I also know people who question why the freeway to Saginaw is "nicer" than the one going through downtown GR.  Little things, yes, but they're there.  And yes, I myself feel like a Canadian having to explain he's not an American to outsiders sometimes--no I don't live near any urban ruins, no people don't randomly shoot others around here, stop asking.

Then there's the fact that people apparently think we're all racist/hick/bible thumpers/teapartiers whatever over here.  We know we have a rep. We know how people talk about us and we don't like it.

But how is this different than anywhere else? It's not uncommon for there to be stereotypes and animosity between the larger and not-so-larger parts of any state.

And for the record, I was shocked at the casual racism--directed towards Detroit, no less--I saw in Clinton Township the first time I visited. I'd never seen anything on that level in Grand Rapids.  Not saying racism isn't a problem here, just that I was shocked, and it happened there, not here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 22:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? Cats wag their tails when they're pissed. It's part of the reason they feel threatened by dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 00:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta love how they tried to blame it on a broken dishwasher AND a kitchen under construction.  Two excuses on one door, only to be outed by readily available public records.  S-M-R-T! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 00:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.wzzm13.com/news/local/kent-co-health-department-orders-xo-asian-cuisine-to-cease-operations-for-7-days/149798723

http://www.mlive.com/business/west-michigan/index.ssf/2016/04/repeated_health_code_violation.html

http://fox17online.com/2016/04/22/xo-asian-cuisine-closed-for-health-violations/

...Well, ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 22:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is Legend of Kay?  I need more 3d platforming in my life, and $3.74 for the PS3 version seems like a nice price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 18:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serpentine swan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 18:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not much of one to comment "this" or "/thread" but I kinda feel like this is the only thing that still needs to be said about these two scofflaws </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 18:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sandy's secret origin story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 18:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Northeast side/Plainfield Twp is great, but it kinda drops off soon after you get the other side of the river.  Ada proper is pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rowster Coffee partners with chef to open restaurant in former Kava House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 18:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 17:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't someone say the PSN ID was the key in their database, so it can never be changed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 13:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that and the proximity of Detroit to Canada meant that our car companies established a presence in Ontario just like they would in, say, Ohio, while the industry was still young. I was just thinking about how the Chrysler competitor to the above burning van has pretty much always been made in Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 02:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife is getting this for my 33rd birthday in a few weeks. I know because she's reeeally bad at not making it obvious (I.E. outta nowhere I'm forbidden to buy it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 13:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Income inequality? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 03:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a distant relative of mine.  And, yes, he's an asshat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 06:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap, what? It's "treatment, payment, operations," not "payment, payment, payment." The hemorrhoids are absolutely PHI. The hypothetical doc shouldn't be discussing anything even *acknowledging* the email recipient as a patient! Get thee to a privacy officer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 02:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Lego Marvel's Avengers Season Pass looks mighty tempting at $10...but I haven't bought it because I don't trust them to finish it after they announced they wouldn't be finishing The Hobbit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 15:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a straight up feminist but it happened to me four times across a year where I was a stay at home dad. Your anecdotal evidence doesn't cancel out that of others to the point of calling names. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today in "You might be a Michigander" headlines: Grand Rapids bar has license suspended after illegal euchre tournament </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 16:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 06:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, the story traditionally mentions the city where it was *filed*, which is usually the location of the news service's editorial desk or bureau. This is why it may seem like all of the news from, say, Egypt seems to come from Cairo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 05:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I was thinking it was GH and Ludington because of the Coast Guard presence. I was joking, mostly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 04:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say that like 2013 didn't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 04:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never mind that, what did Grand Haven do to deserve a direct hit and who moved Kalamazoo to Marshall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 01:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Tours at Disney World is a 3D ride on a gimbal but it isn't terribly far off from this idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 15:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan City, Indiana has one that's attached to a gas station. The gas station side is immaculate by comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 06:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just came back to this thread after being the first poster.  I submitted what I thought was a pretty good but not terrific answer.  I'm at negative five.  Y'all should be ashamed of yourselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 15:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always been Vivi.  Something about not knowing one's own strength has always been very appealing to me.  The whole "reluctant badass" thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 08:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just can't get past the bologna in their chorizo.  Anything specific you recommend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 07:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here we see the problem inherent in a two party system.  

Last time around, the Democrats had a golden opportunity to unseat him thanks to the whole circus around the primary challenge.  It seems like the party has written the district off, though, so Bob Goodrich barely got any support.  I don't expect that to change in the near future.

Just my two cents, feel free to disabuse me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 07:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been awhile and it turns out the storyboard artists get a lot more credit than I thought, but here's a few points:

* Po originally lived with his mom and had a mean boss who was a goose.
* Tigress was originally going to be the chosen one and Po was going to land on her causing a sitcom-y mistaken identity thingy.

* Po's original characterization was much more abrasive and less self-aware. The change was credited to Jack Black, though.
* Apparently I was wrong, because they actually  *do* state that the studio's notes made them go back and make Tai Lung scarier and more deserving of his imprisonment because the execs felt he was too sympathetic and Shifu looked like the bad guy.
* They frequently talk about scenes being reworked multiple times and changes "being better for the story." what this means is open to interpretation but I read it as there being outside influence.
* The scroll was originally a dragon sword, then something in a mysterious box. It took them awhile to come up with the idea of it just being a reflection.
* The final battle is full of really great callbacks to Po's journey and the things he learned.  Originally it was going to start in a volcano and "last for weeks" across mountains. They reworked it to actually tie into the rest of the movie.  In fact, a lot of the call backs magically came in late in the process.
* Instead of "Skidoosh!" we almost got Po belly-bouncing Tai Lung through 15 buildings until he landed in Po's bedroom, where he would look around and be confused by all of the memorabilia.  The Wuxi Finger Hold was in there, it just had had no payoff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 04:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you listen to the Kung Fu Panda directors' commentary, it's never stated but it's pretty dang clear *someone* outside the main creative team intervened and pulled them away from some very bad choices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 18:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. So Norway walks with the Prophets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 02:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EGR Grew out of "wants to be EGR." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 06:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to say I'm starting to doubt this stout79 person. They have a Gleam up for an Xbox, a PS4 and this at the same time?  And they've been randomly tweeting the links for them at people. Can anyone vouch for him/her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 21:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She canna' hold any more captin!

Seriously, though, I'm really glad to see that there doesn't appear to be much if any chain presence on this list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 05:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I...don't think that means what you think it means.  "No news is good news" means "a lack of new information to the contrary must mean everything is fine." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 02:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro, do you even Midwest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rumor: Trek may leave Prime, Netflix for CBS All Access </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 03:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 17:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wisdom tooth removal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 15:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They banned gore a few weeks back.  Jury's out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 07:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During the short time they had a presence here on the West side they had an oil change Groupon that I took advantage of. They told me they needed $250 to replace a corroded TPMS sensor (just one, mind you) and tried to convince me that it was too dangerous to let me drive it away. I did anyway, straight to Discount Tire, who had a good laugh over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Johnny Brann disappointed that all GRPD cruisers won't be getting rifles because "ISIS is real." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 06:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 06:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH Cherry would probably just make a referral to Network 180 in this case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 20:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have a second one, but it's not mine.  Someone in the IT department at one of the big three hospitals here in town apparently ran a script last weekend to delete all users who had been inactive for six months.  They didn't do it quite right.  It deleted everyone who'd been inactive for *six minutes*.  On a Saturday.  Next thing you know, they're going out buying reams of paper and clipboards because no one can get into EPIC and nobody at the hospital has used paper charts in years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 20:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am an AmeriCorps VISTA who redid my small nonprofit's website, picking up where some other volunteers (who didn't document *anything*) had left off two years earlier.  The site's hosting had since changed from the registrar to a new company, but no one updated the DNS, so I couldn't get in to add a new database before I uploaded my site.  

SOOO once i figured this out, I pointed the DNS to the current host and went home.

The next day I came into work and the Executive Director was on the line with Microsoft Support.  Our Office365 had gone toes-up some point in the middle of the night...right around when the DNS change propagated.  Neither she nor they had *any* clue what the problem was.  


The MX records hadn't been moved either.  


Look at my flair.  Why, yes; I'm the idiot who didn't even know what an MX record was at the time.

It's incredible the amount of havoc one can wreak by missing the transfer of one little value.

Several MVA courses later, I'm now in charge of our entire network infrastructure.  Keep in mind there's no one else available to do it.  What'll I break next? It keeps me up at night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 19:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have to access the host.  You can do it [through a plugin](https://codex.wordpress.org/Backing_Up_Your_Database#Using_WordPress_Database_Backup_Plugin).  I use [BackupWordPress](https://wordpress.org/plugins/backupwordpress/) myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 14:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basic user here. Pro is a bit expensive IMHO for what it does.  

Is there a reason you can't update to the current WP version? That's going to be a major source of hackage in and of itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 14:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's only in states that refused to expand Medicaid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 19:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1963 Corvette--the one with the split window.  I'm a Ford guy, but DAMN, that's a beautiful car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 18:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The city's two main founders, Campau and Lyon,[ feuded over how Grand Rapids and Kent County should be platted](http://www.mlive.com/news/grand-rapids/index.ssf/2012/12/feud_between_grand_rapids_foun.html). I believe the inner numbered streets ~~were on Campau's plan and the outer ones~~ were on Lyon's original plan for the city (edit:whoops, should have reread that article; it's been awhile).  At any rate, the outer ones start at the absolute southern border of GR from ~1925 until the last few outer regions of town got annexed starting in the fifties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 18:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leonard is actually a mile and a half north of Fulton.  The mile road system uses Michigan as a baseline.  I don't have a source handy for this, but I remember hearing it stems from Lyon and Campau having it out over the way the city and county would be platted (the same reason most of the outer streets are grids and downtown is a...well, it's special). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans Nostalgic Quest for the Christmas of Their Childhoods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 19:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 19:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just by checking my queue, eh? 

*Tries to check queue, gets server error*

Yup, it's a Steam sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 00:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mean to be a party pooper (cautiously optimistic here), but wasn't REI pulled from the plans for this site a long time ago? Where are you getting this version, OP?

EDIT: both the [latest planning commission minutes](http://grandrapidscitymi.iqm2.com/Citizens/Board/1007-Planning-Commission) and [Lormax Stern's site](http://lormaxstern.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/Knapps-Plan-10-5-15.pdf) (PDF warning) show a very different site plan than yours, with one 36000 sq ft building on the north side of the parcel and NO REI logo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 20:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends.  You need a newer Band 12 phone to take advantage of the new coverage.  

I just got one and haven't tried it yet, but my older LTE phone was still sipping data off AT T's towers in Ludington a week ago (well after the expansion).  Some phones will become Band 12 capable once they are updated to 6.0.1, if I'm not mistaken, but otherwise if your phone isn't [on this list](https://www.t-mobile.com/cell-phones.lte-band-twelve.html), you are probably out of luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 17:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're referring to what was possibly the worst episode of Trek ever, Voyager's *Threshold.*  It was so bad that the powers-that-be supposedly stripped it from canon.  It's now a running joke in the Trek community to act like the episode never happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 18:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. [South Haven](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/South_Haven,_Michigan)
2. [St. Joseph](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/St._Joseph,_Michigan) (inner) / Benton Harbor
3. [Manistee](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Manistee,_Michigan)? Yeah, pretty sure that's Manistee. 
4. Hard to say but I think that's the outer one at St. Joe.
5. Dunno (same as 4)
6. Manistee again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 17:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People *used* to live in the more remote ones, which are set back from the shore for this reason, but the ones in this gallery are all on piers in cities/villages. The keepers would've lived in town with everyone else back in the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 05:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manistee's light looks like it's the third and last ones, actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 02:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, accounting for the three prices he's revealed, the average price of the remaining games in the bundle is $7.33.
(107-19-15-6)/9= 7 1/3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 07:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robinette's is at 4 Mile and the Beltline, almost two-and-a-half miles from where you mention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 03:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It started that way with us too.  Now it's the case on our adult profiles as well.  Why, Netflix? Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 03:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In "In Theory," Data offers to rearrange Jenna D'Sora's wardrobe, so yes, there are closets of some kind aboard the Enterprise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 19:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant XKCD](https://xkcd.com/1053/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 18:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awright, so thanks to /u/SuperMoonky's advice I've pulled the trigger, but we've got some ungrateful wretches in this thread, so if you want a gift link for any of the following, you're going to have to be the first one to PM me with the name of the game you want.

* ~~Contagion~~ nope
* ~~Abyss Odyssey~~ gone
* ~~A Story About My Uncle~~ Taken, sorry

EDIT: OK, all gone, I hope you all enjoy your games!
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 17:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone tell me if the BTA is worth it if the only item on my wish list is ETS2 and I already own Teslagrad and A Story About My Uncle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 17:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some rude soul already took these, but thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 21:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check with [Psychology Associates](http://pagr.net/) to see if they are taking patients.  Brett May is especially great.  Dr. May mentored my brother when he was an undergrad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 16:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why'd it have to be Kurtzman? Whyyyyy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 16:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sequel, [Worlds Apart](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00PI1850S/), is also $1.99 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 18:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Irrespective of this deal,  I just wanted to  share this warning. 

A few months ago this same site had Batman Arkham Origins for the same price.   I pulled the trigger and had them do an in-store pickup at one of the stores near me in Grand Rapids,  Michigan.   The next day I got an email saying it was ready to pick up... in Fresno,  California.  I called the store near me and they didn't  have my reservation... But they did have one from Kentucky and another from Florida. 

I called customer support and at first they flat out refused to believe me or acknowledge there was any problem.   Once I finally got two or three supervisors up,  they said they couldn't  help and I needed to call their eBay department.  The eBay department sent me back to the first support  number. 

This went on for a few hours,  every  successive rep making me hate humanity just a bit more than the last,  until finally I found someone who could cancel my order. They then attempted to place another order,  and charged me twice in the process.   They did not acknowledge there was any issue with their systems the entire time, even after the manager of my local store got involved and confirmed what they were seeing on their end. 

TL;DR don't be surprised if you reassess your definition of incompetence when ordering through this site.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 15:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually where the idea came from that Shakespeare's works must have actually come from someone else.  I am on mobile so I can't find a source but there were academics that couldn't stomach the idea that something so brilliant came from somebody of such low birth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sandmann's, others suing Mercantile Bank alleging they set out to ruin black-owned businesses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 23:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 22:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap! I can't even imagine.  I'd moved on to the GameCube by then, and its port of 3 was superb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 22:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tony Hawk 1 and 2 were ported to N64.  IIRC there was hardly any music, the controls were horrendous, and OMG that pop-in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 21:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how solid of a source can be mustered for this one, but I did find [this quora post](https://www.quora.com/Why-does-France-have-a-reputation-for-surrendering).  As a person who was in his early twenties back then I can definitely tell you that it was nothing new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 21:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an odd mix of factors here.  They include:

* Genetics (this affects the mixture of skin secretions)
* Diet (yes, garlic affects BO)
* Lifestyle (do you shower often? Are your clothes from yesterday? What chemicals do you use to clean yourself? What's the climate like where you live? Is your home dirty? Do you have any pets?)
* Gender
* Medications (helloooo norepinephrine reuptake inhibitors!)

Overall it's really a question of what's on the skin (chemicals, secretions, microfauna/flora) and how long it's been there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 18:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Works great with my Vizio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 21:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC the site is rife with troll articles that were written for parodic purposes.  I can't find a concrete source on this but there was [This AMA awhile back](https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/i3oxm/iama_former_administrator_of_conservapedia_ama) by a person claiming to be a troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 19:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can choose "Game Bundles" under the View filter at the top of the page.  I agree, though, it's not quite the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
