<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2408</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember much about how this arc began in the manga but I remember it being different, so anyone who does remember, how faithful is it?

I like the additional scene with Eren and Mikasa but something about the direction in this episode felt off. I read here that Tetsuro Araki didn't direct this season, and if that's true, then it makes sense. It doesn't capture the scale of the terror that well when the titans appear, especially during the Beast Titan's appearance and the music playing during Mike's battle didn't feel right, the fight itself was kinda underwhelming and didn't really show his skill properly.

The OP was pretty disappointing sound-wise, but it has some cool visuals (what's up with the animals though) and the ED has some nice foreshadowing and it sounds kind of creepy but I still like both the EDs from the first season way more.

Some weird directing techniques though, not a fan of the whole rewind thing they did and they did this weird rapid cut thing while Mike was getting eaten that was similar to Eren's dream at the beginning of the first season. Didn't really like that either.

The visual quality of the show seems to have increased, there's less drawing errors this time around than there were in the first season and the thick outlines are toned back a bit.

Disappointing in some aspects, great in others. The first season was better than the manga so let's hope this one continues that trend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if it's anime original such as Flip Flappers, or if the pacing fits the show better as a 12 ep series? Not everything needs to be over 20+ eps, it can just feel bloated, just look at Attack on Titan, the second half is way too slow (mostly because the manga's pacing is bad but you get the point.) You need to pace your shows properly, some shows work better as 11-12 episode series, others do better as 20+ episodes. Tatami Galaxy and Ping Pong, for example, are paced perfectly as 11 ep series. The amount of source material released isn't and shouldn't be the only aspect to look into when figuring out the pacing for a show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember seeing much about art being underpaid on /ic/, just that it's hard to get into cause you need contacts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, different shows need different paces, some shows would be way too stretched out if they were 20+ episodes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In real life, most people would probably think she has some kind of mental issues, aside from the fact that she has no sense of personal space, she behaves pretty childishly throughout the show. Don't get me wrong, I like the show but if you saw anyone like her in real life you'd be pretty weirded out. Unrealistic characters aren't necessarily bad characters though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ACCA and Kuzu no Honkai have pretty great EDs, as for OPs the only one I really like is Kuzu no Honkai but Maid Dragon's grew on me over time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slice of life and iyashikei and the use of internal monologues. Also characters that aren't realistic in any way (eg: Chitanda from Hyouka) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not why animation is sparse. Character complexity was born out of people moving away from Tezuka-esque styles, anime has a low budget and animators are paid per drawing, so less drawings = less budget wasted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 13:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hyouka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 13:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kaiba

Hyouka

Natsume Yuujinchou

K-On!

Attack on Titan

There's other shows that were good at first but declined in quality and others that didn't get me all hyped at the beginning but got better later on but these are the ones I've enjoyed all the way through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 11:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like Natsume from Natsume Yuujinchou and to a lesser extent Wolfgang Grimmer from Monster, they've both had a shitty past (Grimmer especially) and I can relate to Natsume being an outcast but they're both pretty selfless people, even though Grimmer [Monster](/s "can't even feel emotions like sadness or guilt.")
While I do relate to Oreki in hiding insecurities through lying, I found his whole thing about his life motto and energy conservation to be kind of annoying, honestly. I like relatable characters, I liked Shinji from NGE (but not in EoE) but I don't like Oreki thaat much, especially toward the beginning, because I found him irritating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Hyouka's ending is great, but it's still possible to build it further and do it well. The novels are still going so maybe there might be a second season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she has been involved with all their best works. 

Doesn't she have some level of involvement in all of them though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao, I'm probably gonna drop a ton of those, to be fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kuzu no Honkai is massively overrated and a lot of the times the characters' actions seem to exist just for the sake of drama and plot progressino.
[Kuzu no Honkai](/s "Like when Ecchan makes fun of Mugi after she fucks Hanabi, why does she do that?") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to check it out, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
