<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7165</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what the health care bill was really all about, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should just turn it into a pissing contest and jack up their ad rates for this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think this statement will be widely reported in the Hollywood press? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love The 13th Warrior!  I saw this in the cinema in the summer of 1999; had to go by myself since none of my friends wanted to see it.  The word of mouth was particularly harsh for this film.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you feel about growing income/wealth inequality? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious.  I myself am against it and in favor of progressive income taxation, raising the income tax on the top bracket, raising the capital gains tax, estate tax, as well as eliminating the carried interest loophole.  

I'm not trying to antagonize you here (i'm new to this sub) but many folks on both the left and right are starting to think that neoliberals are indifferent to income and wealth inequality.  The percentage of voters who likewise think that neoliberals "are in the pocket of Wall Street" is also higher today than it was ten years ago.

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently this Page fellow replied to their request some some juvenile snippiness.  Not smart.

Why doesn't this joker just get an attorney to handle this stuff in a diplomatic and professional manner?  An attorney can stonewall as well without being inflammatory about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.  Holy moly what a narcissist.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amusing, but not particularly helpful or smart to antagonize a body that could really do some personal damage to ones self.  

Doesn't this joker have an attorney who could have answered that interrogatory in a more diplomatic manner? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize there are other places on the internet than /r/politics right?  This place is beyond redemption anyhow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can be a little more blunt about it and just say that foreign aid is sometimes a euphemism for bribing local strongmen to "serve U.S. interests" which itself is a euphemism for allowing corporations with U.S. shareholders to act with impunity, pillage resources, exploit local labor, and all that . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember, we can organize our own troll army to fight the right wing trolls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elections are a state and local affair.

Unless you are talking about the propaganda and disinformation camaign.  That's an international affair -- but its not the "election" per se, more the campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does anyone think today's House vote will energize Ossoff voters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Reviewing Trump's Executive Order On Religious Liberties, ACLU Declares It Meaningless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you'd support that too, regardless of the political motives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it true the President and House GOP jumped on a few "party coaches" and cruised up to NYC this afternoon?  Are they hanging out at Scores tonight with Howard Stern? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree.  It seems like a lot of the ranters shitposting on this sub happen to think they are part of "The Resistance" as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have an upvote, my friend!  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm pretty in agreement that this particular EO doesn't do much of anything. It's not like the president can give the IRS "discretion" to not enforce the Johnson amendment.

In fact, many of Trump's EO's have been practically meaningless.  The ones that actually do effect changes have gotten blocked in the courts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm pretty in agreement that this particular EO doesn't do much of anything.  It's not like the president can give the IRS "discretion" to not enforce the Johnson amendment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent news.  Some of my republican buddies in Texas swear up and down that Cruz is utterly despised in their part of Texas (Dallas-Ft Worth). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy appears professionally unstable.  What's the longest he's held a job for lately?  Like six weeks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best case scenario is the bill dies in the Senate and the Representatives who voted for this get a run for their money.  A real win win, eh Comrades? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a very well-written article.  Really puts the human cost in lives in perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for posting this article, but I must say the substance of it is total bollocks.

The article is merely a recounting of a few short-term legislative issues that have been well-documented in many other places.  There indeed is a compelling case to be made for the death of ideological (movement) conservatism -- but this article isn't it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right.  Damn liberal media strikes again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a completely, totally, outrageously misleading headline.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a fire hazard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very well said!  I think you hit the nail on the head.

One point of confusion is that the definition of "conservative" changes over time.  On the other hand, the specific, finite, ideology represented in NR (tax cuts, anti-Communism, states rights, etc.) actually has a specific name, namely "movement conservatism."  Movement conservatism is indeed dying or is already dead.

Meanwhile, the term "conservative" lives on, and shorn of even the feeblest ideological pretense, morphs into "drrr whatever Trump wants do to today . . . "   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Cold War was the glue that held it all together.  Once the USSR collapsed the game started to unravel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally?  Really?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
