<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7195</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AAAAAGGGGHHHHHHHHHHHH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 08:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I was originally going to post this picture to ask why this could be happening. They were at 7% liberty desire, and halfway through December they go straight to 100% and this message pops up without fail (weird, my game crashed multiple times!!) 

Turns out they had pretender rebels close to enforcing their demands, and there's no way for me to siege down that rebel province in time. Is there any way to tell how close PU nation rebels are to enforcing demands? Cuz now I've lost my PU with Lithuania amidst a war to stop the Teutons from achieving independence, right after a war where I spent all my manpower to park myself next to Vienna. I'm losing my mind here, and maybe I just need validation that this is, indeed, the worst case of obfuscated game transparency ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lithuania...but why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 08:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 23:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't think that's possible. Maybe it was a glitch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 22:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta check that military ledger book, young prince. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 22:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes Poland rivals you, but then maybe Austria can help. Allying the HRE usually lets you conquer provinces within the empire more easily then. If they rival you, too, then I don't know man, look for France or something. Brandenburg isn't the easiest start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 21:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they've tried balancing the game more so you can't straight up declare war without consideration now. With Sweden I know the best strategy is to building up a fleet really fast and trap the Danes once they send their entire army to take back Gottland. I haven't tried in myself, but it sounds like it would effectively cut off all land units in your independence war so long as your navy holds the blockage.

Brandenburg also isn't easy in the beginning; their provinces suck. You need to utilize alliances more in the early game to get you into a good spot. Poland is a pretty easy alliance to secure with them, since you both have a common enemy in the Teutonic Order.

Easiest nations I think are the Ottomans and probably Muscovy. You can do almost anything you want to the small nations around you with little penalty. Ottomans are more forgiving, but Muscovy is fairly braindead, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 21:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't quite know the answer to all of these, but here's what I got:

2.) A lot of things go into how a battle is decided. The composition of your army factors in, so pretty much make sure your infantry/cavalry/artillery numbers are proportioned appropriately (I don't have specifics, but EU4 tells you not to have more than half your infantry in cavalry. I see a ton of people with like 10-12 infantry and 3-4 cavalry, which works out well in many cases). 

Military tech discrepancy plays a huge role in battles, too. If you're behind 1 tech, they're going to be much more effective. Obviously, if you're lagging behind 2-3+ you'll be pretty useless. 

Military generals also have an impact, and they have a simple ranking system of 1, 2, or 3 stars, with each rank being (generally speaking) significantly better. Each general has individual blips that indicate his strength in one of four categories (Fire, charge, maneuver, and siege) which give a more detailed view of why a general is ranked 1, 2, or 3 stars. If you don't have a general leading an army fighting against an army that does, that's bad news. 

Finally, terrain and defensive bonuses have the potential to really wreck your morale and fighting power. If you're Venice moving into Savoy, odds are you're getting negative modifiers for crossing into mountains or over rivers. Northern Italy is a mountainous region and is a pain to fight offensively in (from my experience). You want to try and maneuver around so that you avoid being the one on the offensive. You can tell if you'll get a crossing penalty when you pause and click to move your army to the target army. It should show a red minus sign where the battle is to take place. 

Considering you're losing 33k to 11k, odds are you are experiencing more than one of these potentially harmful effects. 

4.) If I'm reading this correctly, the country you want to gain trust with is a rival, and therefore, it's pretty much impossible to do so. Rivals are designed to dislike you until the AI decides you aren't a rival anymore. Honestly, I'm not sure the specifics pertaining to when AI feels like unrival-ing, but it probably has part to do with provinces of strategic importance and size of nation. If that country has claims on you, they want your land and probably won't rest until they get them or die trying.

5.) The only way I know of is you can enforce peace with the target of your ally, only if your ally has +100 relations. Most times the computer only accepts when they're losing, so it kind of defeats the purpose of the diplomatic action in my eyes. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 17:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, for one, appreciate your lil' boot, and have never had Iberia and Great Britain and also the Maghreb and Jerusalem by that time. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 02:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #triggered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 15:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muscovy is getting wrecked by the Golden Horde and a not PU'd Lithuania and now me :]. Poland hates my guts though, but what can you do when you vassal-annex the Teutons out from under their noses! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 15:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you I love you.

I've been doing another run before listening to any feedback and I've vassal-annexing Teutonic order and Holstein, and have vacillated between taking coastal HRE states alongside wars with Novgorod, Lvonian Order, and the Teutons. This has allowed me to pay off 2 coalitions that spawned (including probably 70% of HRE states) with 500+gold and East Frisia, or 500+gold and Stettin. 

It's 1500 now and liberty desire is under check for now (I rejected the Scandinavian Constitution like you said), I'm finally back down to acceptable levels of AE after 2 massive coalition wars took next to nothing meaningful, and Muscovy lost Moskva to the Golden Horde so now I'm just patiently eating them up and recovering cores for my vassalized Novgobear. 

I'm definitely going to look into getting Prussian ideas, as Poland actually took Danzig in its first war and are my only tangible rivals. Luckily they chose to not grab the PU with Lithuania. Barring I don't fuck it all up, this could be a decent run for the Danes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 04:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting idea for releasing Novgorod after they are eaten up. I went for an immediate vassalization of them after Muscovy's first war, but then they rose up with Sweden for independence shortly thereafter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alright, How Do I Succeed with Denmark? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 23:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been trying to play Denmark recently and maybe I'm just horrible at managing PUs, but I can't for the life of me figure out what the best start would be. 

First, the beginning mission of "Danish Trade" (securing Danzig, Lubeck, and Neva) just seems completely unreasonable to do within any reasonable time frame. If I go for Novgorod, Muscovy rivals me. If I take Danzig, Poland hates me. If I somehow manage to take Lubeck, the entire HRE get upset. Should I just never take this mission, or do I need to employ some god-like level of patience in completing it? Pissing off three major powers around me while juggling with the liberty desire of Sweden is insane. 

And on the topic of Sweden, the minute any powerful nation rivals me, they tend to support Sweden's independence and the encroaching opportunistic war with Sweden bars me from trying to make any expansions. I've come to conclude that trying to keep Sweden under a PU is close to impossible, and I shouldn't bother trying to integrate them, so what's the best course of action regarding them?

Pretty much I integrate Holstein and Norway as soon as possible, and I can usually take quite a few Baltic Sea border territories by 1500 (Some of Novgorod, a lot of either the Lvonian or Teutonic Order, and sometimes a bit of Pomerania), but as I said before, usually Sweden or Muscovy or PLC decide it's time to reverse my advances. I have no idea how to create a strong start without it immediately crumbling and losing cores back to Sweden.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 23:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fairly certain the coalition won't trigger if you accept a call to arms and enter on behalf of an entirely separate war.

Though, that's not to say the coalition members won't declare on you while you're fighting that war. You'll be treading a fine line there, but if they don't declare and you don't take any land in that war, you'll at least prevent Florence from any future coalition war for as long as you have a truce with them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 23:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never let them blob. NEVER LET THEM BLOB.

Otherwise, the most effective strategy for a shit player like me is to wait it out. They tend to lag behind in tech eventually and become nearly as useless as Russia's millions of troops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 20:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I've learned is to drop allies before they start to bring you down. If you don't see Muscovy being able to fight back and put the PLC in check, then back out of the alliance. If you're strong enough to take on the PLC, though, either with Russia later or with other allies now, they could be a good target for you. The Baltic states would be great land to boost your trade in the Baltic node (ie. take the entire coast line away from whoever owns it.) 

Really, it's usually not simply "Who should I fight," but "How can I manipulate alliances to get me the land I want." If you're dropping Muscovy, try to find someone to take their place. If you want to keep them, understand they might try to call you into a war with the PLC in the future.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 20:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In regard to fabricating claims now, the difference is simply having to send a diplomat to establish a spy network and waiting for enough points to fabricate. It takes a few months, but once you get to 20+ points in the network, the "Fabricate Claim" option should be lit up in the Covert Actions tabs. Those 20 points then get consumed for the claim and viola! Back to your old conquering ways.

The only caveat is the cost to fabricate goes up for every action claim you have on a nation (20, 25, 30, and so on). I guess what also changed since the last time you played might be the default casus belli being humiliation wars if you're declaring on a rival. If you're not used to reading what casus belli you're using when you declare, now's the time to make sure you're not starting a humiliation war--these wars do NOT allow you to take provinces. (Humiliation wars are available for rival nations, almost as soon as you set them as such) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
