<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9664</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 23:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Considering that there are many people working very hard to make an honest living, many in very difficult conditions, do you think it is fair that someone who commits a violent crime is fast-tracked to a better life than these hard working people. 
2. For many people with difficult lives this will make committing a crime of personal gain a win-win situation. Either you get away with the crime and improve your life, or you go to prison and improve your life. Do you not see a problem with this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 12:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think The Babadook deserves to be lumped in with those other ones you mentioned. I think it's a much more thoughtful movie than that. Have you seen El Orfanato? It's not very recent (2007?) but one of the best modern horror films in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 10:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Louis CK has an interesting outlook on younger people who think they can do whatever they want while they're young and then they'll just explode at 40: "you don't die you idiot, you just have a shitty second half".

It is impossible to live life "perfectly" in terms of health. However if you live a very unhealthy first half, you are more likely to have a much more difficult second half. Health is a sliding scale, not a yes/no decision to make. Think about the future whilst not giving up everything you love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 15:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was my understanding that most scientists did believe that life on this planet did arise from non living material, so I think your premise is flawed. But even so, how did the extraterrestrial life arise? At some point, life has to either arise from non living material, or be created by a "creator" (which begs the question how did the creator come to be). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 11:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great picture. I love how the board breaks the horizon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 23:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend laughed when I said "porkiepine" instead of "porcupine". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 23:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs. The one that started them all! When I watched it as a kid in the cinema as a rerelease in the early 90s I thought it was a brand new film. Wasn't til years later that I learnt it was released in 1937. I found it scary as hell as a kid too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 16:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People can expect what they want out of a relationship as long as it is honest and mutually accepted. There are many things that I expect from a relationship that go beyond monogamy. I require my partner to not take heroin. I require my partner to want to travel to different countries with me. You don't get randomly placed with a partner and then start demanding things from them. You find someone who wants the same things as you. I have every respect for someone who doesn't want to travel ever, but I don't want to be in a relationship with them. I have every respect for someone who doesn't want to be monogamous, but I don't want to be in a relationship with them. It's nothing to do with controlling your partner, it's about choosing a partner that shares your values. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 17:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please can you clarify what you mean by a "non literal message"? If someone paints a literal representation of something to the best of their ability, and they are proud of the painting and they consider it art, does that meet your criteria? And if so, what is the "non literal message" in the painting. Let's say the painting is just of an apple, to use an arbitrary example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 17:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the one of the men between the two buildings looking out to sea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time to China (need some help please!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 12:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to China for the first time with my girlfriend next year. We have changed our itinerary around a lot and this is the plan we have currently:

Shanghai - March 24th
Zhangjiajie - March 28th
Fenghuang - March 31st
Guilin - April 3rd
Guangzhou - April 6th

Does this seem realistic for the timespan?

Guilin looks beautiful in the photos I've seen, but I read that it will be very rainy in April. Has anyone been there around that time of year? We can obviously deal with some rain, I just wondered if there was any reason that it might negatively impact the visit (visibility, mobility etc).

Is it generally quite easy to hire private cars from hotels in China? What sort of prices might they be? We would like to make a day trip to Qianyang from Fenghuang which would be about 2 hours drive each way. Is it realistic to do this in a private car?

Is there any general advice or comments that might help us with our trip regarding our first time to China and our itinerary. Any help would be really appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 16:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my first thought. One of my favourite NOFX songs of recent years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 12:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always put pineapple and bacon in a burger or a chicken sandwich. Sometimes pineapple in a stir fry too. Delish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 11:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to think that life can only be positive if you can experience pleasure by doing nothing. Boredom might be the default option if you sit alone in a room all day, but that's why people don't sit alone in a room all day. People have jobs and friends and hobbies, that provide constant stimulus. Having to put effort into life to get something back out isn't inherantly a bad thing as you seem to imply. You describe it like it's all a big chore to avoid boredom. That is a mindset that you have chosen to indulge in and not one that is shared by everyone. Life can be very difficult and not everyone has the same opportunities for happiness, but most people can work towards happiness in their life. I am very with my job, relationships, hobbies, and having worked for them makes them more satisfying, not a chore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 19:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, it's not one of my favourites at all. There are many great songs on there, but overall it doesn't feel like a 'complete' album, just a collection of songs that don't necessarily fit together. I appreciate that many enjoy the diversity of it, but I prefer the cohesion of some of their other albums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 17:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "To me" is already implied in the statement. You don't need to state that something is your opinion every time you state an opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 17:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think that people using "that's gay" so casually has been beneficial to the gay community? If I was gay I really wouldn't like the use of it. It has come from disrespectful origins and now that it's caught on, people are trying to dissociate the word from those. I can't see that any good has come of it. How will doing the same for other words make any positive impact? It doesn't take away the hurt of someone who wants to use words hurtfully, becuase the intent is still there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 11:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally looks pretty good to me, but have a look on it on iPad, some of the text and buttons are cut off on either side with no way to read it. Make sure it's compatible with mobile platforms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 17:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your argument seems to rely quite heavily on the idea that film can look more realistic than theatre and therefore it is easier for the audience to suspend their disbelief. I disagree that it is easier to suspend disbelief in film, and even if it is, I disagree that makes it superior to theatre.

When films are going for realism, it can be more distracting when something breaks that. For example there is a film called "let the right one in", (one of my favourite films) which is very naturalistically acted and shot, despite being about vampires, but I am always very distracted by a scene where the filmmakers have used CGI on the faces of some cats. Although as film further matures and technology improves, this issue may decrease, I still believe that the more realistic something tries to be, the easier it is for that realism to be broken.

With theatre, I am not distracted by those things as much, as i don't expect to see real blood, or real talking animals etc.

When I went to see the lion king musical (a long time ago now, forgive me if I forget the details), I remember being overwhelmed by the appearance of certain animals. The way the elephants were constructed and the way they moved. I was overwhelmed by the sheer artistry, creativity and beauty of it. It didn't look anything like a real elephant, nor did it need to, I never doubted it was an elephant. I realise that this is probably not the sort of theatre you had in mind with your argument but Ijust use it to illustrate my point. The argument also extends to non musical theatre.

Is photography a better medium than painting because it's more realistic? Theatre is more than just conveying a story, you can bask in the live spectacle of it. The creativity of it. The joy of seeing a one off performance that is just for you that night, that will never be repeated identically again. Seeing an actor give a emotive uninterrupted performance. These are things that can make theatre special.

I don't believe either medium is 'better'. They both have their own joys. It comes down to taste which one you enjoy more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waverley Abbey, Farnham, UK. Established 1123 [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 16:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 16:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That took me so long! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 17:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hanoi, Hoi An and Saigon are three of my favourite cities in the world. My main advice is, don't eat in the hotel, go out and eat the street food. Eat where the locals eat. Eat everything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
