<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3445</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saturn on the sunlit side of the rings from about 16 degrees above the ring plane [1041x1041] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 18:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada to end requirement that Mexicans need visas: Trudeau </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 18:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minnesota's Largest Health Insurer Will Drop Individual Plans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 18:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China on Schedule for Launch of Second Space Station </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 17:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinas long march to the Moon began with a bang this weekend The Asian country has embarked upon a long-term plan to colonize the Moon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 17:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton: All Americans must have broadband access by 2020 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 17:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chasma Boreale and North Polar Ice Cap of Mars [1041x521] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 17:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toy Falcon 9 Rocket landing on a mini SpaceX Droneship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 17:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL when Amy Schumer went to see "Hamilton," she left a $1,000 tip on a $77 bill for the bartenders who were aspiring actors. Having waited tables and worked as a bartender in New York City before her career took off, Ms. Schumer told the bartenders, "Ive been there, I get it." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 17:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men less likely to use a condom if woman is attractive, says study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 16:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men are less likely to use a condom if their partner is very attractive, study suggests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 16:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 16:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conclusions Male perceptions of attractiveness influence their condom use intentions; such risk biases could profitably be discussed during sex education sessions and in condom use promotion interventions.

http://bmjopen.bmj.com/content/6/6/e010883.full </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When a woman is more attractive, a man is less likely to intend to use a condom during sex with her, a new study finds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 16:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama opened up a new attack on Donald Trump Tuesday, saying in a radio interview that the presumptive GOP nominee is "hardly" the representative for "working-class people" he thinks he is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 16:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tough new hydrogel hybrid doesnt dry out Water-based material could be used to make artificial skin, longer-lasting contact lenses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 16:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DUI Suspect Drove a Mile With a Body Lodged in Her Car, Police Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 16:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study led by a South Australian university has found fast food outlets are ten times more likely to be built near disadvantaged schools in Adelaide than in higher socioeconomic areas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 15:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 15:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conclusions Disadvantaged schools were exposed to more fast food, with more than twice the number of disadvantaged schools exposed to fast food. The higher exposure to fast food near more disadvantaged schools may reflect lower commercial land cost in low-SES areas, potentially creating more financially desirable investments for fast-food developers.

http://journals.cambridge.org/action/displayAbstract?fromPage=online aid=10366665 fulltextType=RA fileId=S1368980016001385 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds Fast-food chains are more likely to be built near schools in Adelaide's poorer suburbs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 15:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raspberry PI-Powered AI Beats Human Pilot In Dogfight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 15:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps tariff proposal would gut US export jobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 15:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A former police officer and former court security officer accused of sexually assaulting a young woman will face no jail time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 14:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A former police officer and former court security officer accused of sexually assaulting a young woman will face no jail time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 14:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dad breaks daughter's ankles with sinister crossover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 14:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Benghazi report: Hillary Clinton should have realized risks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 14:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tulsa police officer arrested on allegations of pawning police-issued pistol, shotgun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 14:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boeing Co. has applied for a license from the Federal Communications Commission to launch and operate a network of thousands of satellites, joining companies such as SpaceX and OneWeb in the new race to build constellations for broadband Internet access. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 14:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Reeve presenting Robin Williams of "Mork   Mindy" with the Favorite Male Performer in a New TV Program at the 1979 People's Choice Awards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 02:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Beach tenant's rent increased from $1,800 to $8,000 a month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 02:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL to cope with being separated from his girlfriend, Rhea Perlman, Danny DeVito invented an imaginary friend to talk to at night during the filming of One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest (x-post r/movies) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 01:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burj Khalifa at Business Bay Canal, Dubai, UAE. [900x675] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 01:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bastei Fog in Saxon Switzerland National Park, Germany by Marek Kijevsk [1200x801] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 01:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadpool made after-trailer appearance in Japan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 01:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadpool made after-the-trailer appearance in Japan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 01:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana shops are more lucrative than Whole Foods, by at least one metric </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 01:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana Based Drug Effective in Treating Epilepsy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 01:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana extract proven again to treat rare forms of epilepsy, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 01:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cops: Bragging Burglars Get Arrested After Posting Video of Cash They Stole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 00:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogs may help detect hypoglycemia in diabetes patients, study suggests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 23:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 23:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hypoglycemia and/or fear of hypoglycemia are major challenges for many with type 1 diabetes (T1D), limiting ability to lower glycemia. Given anecdotal reports of domestic pets alerting owners to blood glucose changes, especially hypoglycemia (1), we hypothesized that volatile organic compounds (VOCs) in exhaled breath might change at low glucose.

http://care.diabetesjournals.org/content/39/7/e97 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogs can smell low blood sugar in people with diabetes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 23:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google and Viacom on Monday defeated an appeal in a nationwide class action lawsuit by parents who claimed the companies illegally tracked the online activity of children under the age of 13 who watched videos and played video games on Nickelodeon's website. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 23:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Threatens to Veto Bill to Combat Zika Virus Because It Doesnt Fund Planned Parenthood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 23:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cincinnati Police Body Camera Program Starts August 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 23:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philly Police Officer Arrested For Alleged Robbery In Bristol Township </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 23:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GW Pharmaceuticals announced positive results Monday from a second, pivotal clinical trial involving children with a severe form of epilepsy treated with its experimental marijuana-based drug. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 23:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now two security researchers have found a new way, using a vulnerability in the system Google uses to stream media through its Chrome browser. They say people could exploit the flaw to save illegal copies of movies they stream on Chrome using sites like Netflix or Amazon Prime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 17:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A now former Buffalo police officer pleaded guilty Monday to a federal civil rights violation in connection to the fatal incident at Molly's Pub in May 2014. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 17:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On-duty MPD officer arrested for DUI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 17:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boeing has applied for a license from the Federal Communications Commission to launch and operate a network of thousands of satellites, joining companies such as SpaceX and OneWeb in the new race to build constellations for broadband internet access. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 17:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana-Based Drug Helps Kids With Rare Forms Of Epilepsy In Studies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 17:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If put in place, the GOP health insurance plan would almost surely mean fewer people with health insurance, fewer people getting financial assistance for their premiums or out-of-pocket costs, and fewer consumer protections than the ACA provides. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 17:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DNC Adds Decriminalizing   Even Legalizing Marijuana To The Platform for November </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 17:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Hackers hacked into Uber to use promotion codes, find private emails using UUID, find users phone numbers, create fake driver accounts, validate them, find where you went, who your driver was, and who you are, date of the trip, driver name and picture, the ID and the cost of the trip. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 17:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP health insurance plan would make workers pay tax on benefits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 17:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Fiber could raise rents 11 percent, study suggests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 16:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robin Williams with his fifth-grade class at Gorton School in Lake Forest, Illinois. Williams is third from left in front row. 1960s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 16:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The bottom of a iceberg in Tasiilaq, the capital of East Greenland [962x1443] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 16:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BLUE HUNTER Blue Shark, Prionace glauca, with a close up of the eye. [1024x682] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 16:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> General Mills is voluntarily recalling four flavors of Nature Valley Protein Chewy Bars and Nature Valley Simple Nut Bars because the items may be contaminated with Listeria, a bacteria that can result in serious or life-threatening illness in consumers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 16:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> General Mills announced Friday a voluntary national recall of four flavors of Nature Valley Protein Chewy Bars and Nature Valley Simple Nut Bars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 16:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Hackers hacked into Uber to use promotion codes, find private emails using UUID, find users phone numbers, create fake driver accounts, validate them, find where you went, who your driver was, and who you are, date of the trip, driver name and picture, the ID and the cost of the trip. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 14:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three hackers have found eight holes in Uber that could allow fake drivers to be created and user email addresses reveal, and found more than 1000 of valid coupon codes including one giving drivers $100 extra in fare rides. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 14:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Body camera video shows fatal police shooting of Chaska man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 14:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House warns Congress not to kill net neutrality and cable box rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 14:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What If MICHAEL JORDAN Played In The Modern NBA? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 14:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House Warns GOP to Stop Sneak Attacks on Net Neutrality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 14:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garden City police officer arrested on domestic battery allegation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 14:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garden City Police Officer, Omar A. Mora, 37, was arrested at 3:30 a.m. Monday on an allegation of domestic battery after police responded to a report of a domestic violence incident involving Mora and a woman in the parking lot of a strip mall in the 2300 block of East Kansas Avenue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 14:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After 36 tries and a class of kindergarteners in recess rooting and cheering for me I got in my basketball first trick shot from half-court range. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 14:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: Netflix is going to let you download your favorite movies and shows this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 19:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new paper in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences demonstrates how the evidence in favor of brain training is likely just a placebo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 17:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 16:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Placebo effects pose problems for some intervention studies, particularly those with no clearly identified mechanism. Cognitive training falls into that category, and yet the role of placebos in cognitive interventions has not yet been critically evaluated. Here, we show clear evidence of placebo effects after a brief cognitive training routine that led to significant fluid intelligence gains. Our goal is to emphasize the importance of ruling out alternative explanations before attributing the effect to interventions. Based on our findings, we recommend that researchers account for placebo effects before claiming treatment effects.

http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/06/16/1601243113.abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research Shows That Brain Training Is Nothing But The Placebo Effect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 16:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Brunswick police officer accused of sending pictures of his genitals to an undercover federal agent posing as a 13-year-old girl was arrested Tuesday on a charge of attempting to transfer obscene material to a minor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 16:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Brunswick police officer accused of sending pictures of his genitals to an undercover federal agent posing as a 13-year-old girl was arrested Tuesday on a charge of attempting to transfer obscene material to a minor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 16:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jury: Former Rocky Ford police officer guilty of murder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 16:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A former Hancock County sheriff's deputy has been charged with use of excessive force. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 17:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A former Hancock County sheriff's deputy has been charged with use of excessive force. The same man is also the Republican candidate for sheriff. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 16:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowden allegedly used excessive force during an arrest in January of 2015, and then falsified a document in an attempt to justify his use of force, Ihlenfeld said. The indictment came after an FBI investigation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 14:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man tried to swallow wrench, not such a good idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 14:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] He is getting his PhD - and is homeless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 14:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He is getting his PhD - and is homeless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 14:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Dearborn police officer accused of groping a woman during a traffic stop has been suspended without pay and the Wayne County Prosecutors Office is weighing charges, according to media reports. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 18:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sources are telling 7 Action News a Dearborn officer has been suspended without pay, facing allegations of groping a woman during a traffic stop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 18:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recent accounts suggest that accountability pressures have trickled down into the early elementary grades and that kindergarten today is characterized by a heightened focus on academic skills and a reduction in opportunities for play. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 18:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clean broad aerial shot of Dubai Marina, Dubai, UAE. [1200x797] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 18:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC Chairman Tom Wheeler isn't afraid of the large telcos like AT T (NYSE: T) and CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) challenging the commission's net neutrality rules, which were upheld by a Washington federal appeals court last week. He says they also won't fall to a Supreme Court challenge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 18:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cable Industry: Our Shitty TV Apps Are Just As Good As Real Cable Box Competition, Right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 18:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix Price Hike Could Cost Company Almost 500,000 Users </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 18:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 18:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was already sore from working out; so I probably extended the pain with the stunt. Mainly my shoulder and elbow are feeling it. Thanks for watching! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In response to a question about presumptive Republican presidential nominee Donald Trump's proposal that he could renegotiate U.S. debt with foreign creditors, Yellen said the damage from that could be "very substantial." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 18:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This plant reportedly tastes like pulled pork. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 17:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fog in morning hours in Elbe Sandstone Mountains, Saxon Switzerland, by Jens Bhme [800x1000] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 17:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 17:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will give you a good idea: https://youtu.be/AdW7C_3HVjA?t=1m1s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 16:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know after all these years, I thought that movie would be too corny to watch (especially while hating Jordan for whoopin' my Knicks' asses so decisively back in the 90s). You just converted me; that's on  the weekend's playlist! Thanks for sharing. You need to pick up a royalty from Warner Bros. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 16:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recent accounts suggest that accountability pressures have trickled down into the early elementary grades and that kindergarten today is characterized by a heightened focus on academic skills and a reduction in opportunities for play. This paper compares public school kindergarten classrooms between 1998 and 2010 using two large, nationally representative data sets. We show substantial changes in each of the five dimensions considered: kindergarten teachers beliefs about school readiness, time spent on academic and nonacademic content, classroom organization, pedagogical approach, and use of standardized assessments. Kindergarten teachers in the later period held far higher academic expectations for children both prior to kindergarten entry and during the kindergarten year. They devoted more time to advanced literacy and math content, teacher-directed instruction, and assessment and substantially less time to art, music, science, and child-selected activities.

http://ero.sagepub.com/content/2/1/2332858415616358 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Testing, Less Play: Study Finds Higher Expectations For Kindergartners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 16:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 16:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for checking it out! Really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 16:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely repeat that a lot to the boys when their first reaction to something tough is that they can't do it. Thanks for checking it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 14:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conclusions Greater access to alcohol was associated with more atrial fibrillation and less myocardial infarction and congestive heart failure, although an increased risk of congestive heart failure was seen shortly after alcohol sales were liberalized.

http://www.bmj.com/content/353/bmj.i2714 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study links drinking alcohol with heart-rhythm disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 14:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1 in 10 Cal State students is homeless, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 14:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Southwest Virginia police officer is charged with nearly 50 counts of sex crimes against a child. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 14:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Big Stone Gap police officer accused of sexually assaulting a child younger than 13 for more than two years will be arraigned this morning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 14:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Unconscionable Difficulty of Getting Health Insurance for a Newborn - My own plan only covered my child as an extension of me for the first two days. After that, he was on his own. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 14:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] After about 93 tries I made my first basketball trick shot with my son coaching and rooting for me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 14:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After about 93 tries I made my first basketball trick shot with my son coaching and rooting for me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 14:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Trek: Beyond Cannes Event Canceled Following Anton Yelchin Death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 01:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cable Companies Tell FCC More Competition Will 'Harm Consumers' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 01:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As the weather gets hotter, pay TV customers could be shedding their television subscriptions  along with their long pants and sweaters  in greater numbers, according to Sanford Bernstein media analyst Todd Juenger. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 01:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 21:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed kissin' ain't easy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ghost of the arctic: Snowy owl by Thierry Gosselin [900x631] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 21:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poquoson Police officer charged with assault, abduction in Newport News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Poquoson police officer was arrested over the weekend and faces a slew of charges after he allegedly assaulted his partner at her Newport News home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taken on 4 July 2014. After 20 hours severe storm on 3 July, it was a peaceful morning at Mount Taranaki with a gentle breeze under moonlight by Yan Zhang [OS] [1100x734] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Drug Enforcement Administration will reclassify marijuana as a "Schedule Two" drug on August 1, 2016, essentially legalizing medicinal cannabis in all 50 states with a doctor's prescription, said a DEA lawyer with knowledge of the matter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to be your friend, friend! No offense in some overly-involved yet, I have to admit, thought stimulating discussion. Thanks for sharing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's a photo of a redditor's dad on his way to work posted on r/pics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 17:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They should get a room </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 17:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alabama police officer forced man to perform oral sex at gunpoint, warrant claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 17:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 16:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However, you want to put it, it is a **informality,** meaning unofficial http://www.dictionary.com/browse/informal?s=t

I could say *down packed* means an action is tightly packed which implies it's well organized. The term *high and tight* represents the skin fade haircut which is always heavily scrutinized to ensure perfect shape ups and hair length transition from bald to long hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. Drug Enforcement Administration will reclassify marijuana as a "Schedule Two" drug on August 1, 2016, essentially legalizing medicinal cannabis in all 50 states with a doctor's prescription, said a DEA lawyer with knowledge of the matter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 16:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 16:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well your source is citing the *The Dictionary of American Slang* https://www.amazon.com/Dictionary-American-Slang-Robert-Chapman/dp/006270107X

In your source slang is defined as informal and playful http://www.dictionary.com/browse/slang?s=t 
So if there is a slight variation to the term that is also widely used there's no credible body of the English language that is going to say which is the correct way. There is slang terminology that is put to use in the English language that are proper words in other languages in parts of New York City. Whose going to tell thousands of drug dealers, stick-up kids, and hoods that they're wrong? What institution is going to waste their time with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 16:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure how official this source is; but here's what I pulled after a quick query attempting to avoid corrections: http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=down%20packed

IMHO it's an informal expression regardless of either one you choose. *Down packed* seems like it can represent something that is perfected as it connotes an expression of security or tightly wound perhaps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Blue Origin "New Shepard" rocket launching three student payloads into suborbital space and landing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 16:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Challenge Aims to Grow Human Tissue to Aid in Deep Space Exploration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 16:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Electric Wind Strips Earth-like Planets of Oceans, Atmospheres </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 16:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] This skateboarder tries 67 times until he gets a 360 flip down packed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 16:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This skateboarder tries 67 times until he gets a 360 flip down packed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 16:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venus has an "electric wind" strong enough to remove the components of water from its upper atmosphere. This action may have played a significant role in stripping Earth's twin planet of its oceans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possibility of alien contact could be 1,500 years away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ExoMars Orbiter Beams Back Its First Image of Mars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two catalysts efficiently turn plastic trash into diesel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chemists Just Turned Plastic Into Liquid Fuel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From trash to treasure: Scientists turn plastic bottles and bags into liquid fuel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abstract

Polyethylene (PE) is the largest-volume synthetic polymer, and its chemical inertness makes its degradation by low-energy processes a challenging problem. We report a tandem catalytic cross alkane metathesis method for highly efficient degradation of polyethylenes under mild conditions. With the use of widely available, low-value, short alkanes (for example, petroleum ethers) as cross metathesis partners, different types of polyethylenes with various molecular weights undergo complete conversion into useful liquid fuels and waxes. This method shows excellent selectivity for linear alkane formation, and the degradation product distribution (liquid fuels versus waxes) can be controlled by the catalyst structure and reaction time. In addition, the catalysts are compatible with various polyolefin additives; therefore, common plastic wastes, such as postconsumer polyethylene bottles, bags, and films could be converted into valuable chemical feedstocks without any pretreatment.

http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/2/6/e1501591 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A combined team of researchers from the Chinese Academy of Sciences and University of California has found a way to degrade ordinary plastics in a way that allows for fuel to be created from plastic trash. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abstract

OBJECTIVE: The incidence of sports- and recreation-related concussions (SRRCs) in the United States is unknown. More than 44 million youth participate in sports annually, thus understanding the frequency of SRRCs in children is important on a population level. Our objective was to determine the number of SRRCs occurring annually among US youth 18 years old.

METHODS: We identified SRRCs using 3 national databases: MarketScan, National Electronic Injury Surveillance System, and National High School Sports Related Injury Surveillance System, Reporting Injury Online. We determined the number of SRRCs seen in health care settings (outpatient, inpatient, and emergency department) and SRRCs reported to certified high school athletic trainers (ATCs). We used these data and findings in recently published literature to generate a national estimate of SRRCs.

RESULTS: We estimate that between 1.1 and 1.9 million SRRCs occur annually in US children aged 18 years. Most children with SRRCs, 511590 to 1240972, were not seen in health care settings. Of children with SRRCs seen in health care settings, most were seen as outpatients with 377978 visits, compared with between 115479 and 166929 ED visits, and between 2886 and 4936 hospitalizations.

CONCLUSIONS: This study provides the most accurate and precise estimate to date of the number of concussions among US children annually. SRRCs are a common injury in children. Providers in all health care settings need to be trained in concussion care. There is a need for better surveillance to enhance our understanding of the epidemiology of concussions in youth.

http://pediatrics.aappublications.org/content/early/2016/06/16/peds.2015-4635 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Up to 2 million youngsters may get concussions every year, study says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three New York Police Department commanders, including a deputy chief, were arrested early Monday, along with a Brooklyn businessman, on federal corruption charges stemming from one of several continuing investigations into Mayor Bill de Blasios campaign fund-raising </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 04:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He recorded it to prove it. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mFCn5AJl8Ec </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since a couple of people said they hoped it wouldn't be fake, my son recorded himself making my card in his world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 21:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
