<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2315</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 08:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this /r/doggo real?!  I needs him in my life!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 07:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insha'Allah. May Allah forgive those who have had their lives taken and grant them Jannah. 

 Anas ibn Malik reported: The Messenger of Allah, peace and blessings be upon him, said: Beware of the supplication of the oppressed, even if he is an unbeliever, for there is no barrier between it and Allah. Source: Musnad Ahmad 12140, Grade: Sahih
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I missed him saying that. Will re listen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 04:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a non-TAL suggestion of an adorable and hysterical Moth podcast story told by Jay Martel! I was going through benzodiazepine addiction treatment (aka hell on earth) when I first heard it and really cheered me up on the particular day I listened to it! 

https://themoth.org/stories/head-of-clay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 18:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9/11 

Walahi, every single time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did we start controlling things? I thought the Jews still had control. Are we in cahoots with Jews?! Or did they just pass the ball to us? Subhanallah, I need to re-subscribe to the mawz-lim mailing list; right after I fix my HAJIB and do some stabbings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subhanallah! I can't breathe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol! Why is this even a thing that people think?! The kufr are weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [evidences here](https://islamqa.info/en/129446)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drawing anything with a ruh (soul) isn't permissible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soooo cuuute!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My condolences, love. May she rest easy and may you find peace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walaykum Salam Wa Rahmatullahi Wa Barakatuh, Akhi! 

Everyone has given you really good advice here, but no one has mentioned the fact that it is not permissible to be speaking to her directly. 

It's best for you to communicate strictly with her Wali and as someone else said, arrange to meet ASAP. With her Wali present, of course. And decide from there if you both want to have the Nikkah. 

Going about this any other way can lead to lots of haram. 

Speaking from experience! 

May Allah SWT make it easy for you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
