<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9880</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 13:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the old lady? Did you just leave her naked on the street? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 21:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can have a plus one, but I don't know why you're here ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 20:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it not just from the point of view of the monster in the closet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 20:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It says that the mom fell asleep smoking, setting the place on fire though.

Not the dad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 17:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The book about a can able tribe was totally faked, the whole thing was a complete fabrication. the meat he ate was human, but I think it was from a morgue in the us somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 16:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is his mental illness making him think that he was hurting someone else, but really he stabbed himself? He thought that she was being molested, but really he was doing it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 15:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pride, you can stay! I. Sure she is proud of her strength and of her son! Don't fade away, I like you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 15:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dad didn't do anything? I'm confused! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 15:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, doctors probably should have referred you to a mental health professional... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 21:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only part of this that I don't understand is the monster seemingly having this sole intention of making the writer suffer, but then randomly kills the neighbour with no warning. Or so it seems.

Maybe you should ask around about that incident op? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 20:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please let us know what happens.
I want to find out her deal! If she fakes it, people can't meet her surely? It would give it all away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 20:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real ghostbusters was the shit. I have them all on dvd. :p 

And at least you know the fear your child is going through, maybe you can do more for him now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 19:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True satanists, simply believe that you basically shouldn't be an ass and that sometimes sinning is permissible. If you want a very very simplified version of things. 

People who are in Satan worshipping cults are not satanists, they are just cult members who do awful things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 10:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Satanists are not nut cases who murder people.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 17:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sniggers, not snickers I think. I pictured the little sweets floating up in the air.

Amazing writing though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 20:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update please! What happened?.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 12:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your grandma knows what's up. 
I like her haha!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 10:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you put the horse shoe back?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 10:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Names and locations are meant to be changed on here, it's the rules I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 22:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please add more, there is so much I need to know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 21:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 19:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've written the story as if you are angie, but now you have broken character. Which breaks the rules x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 19:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try adding this to r/letsnotmeet :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 23:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a little confused op.. There was a bannister in the bedroom? And how long were you in the bathroom?

You didn't notice anything else out of the ordinary for the whole week?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 18:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well maybe not, like what if these actions are what causes his parents to meet in the first place. Time is a very confusing thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 00:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scouts... What age are scouts in the us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 16:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold on... Hoooold on. In the uk scouts are only between 11 and 15 years old. 

Please tell me that they are actually adults in the us? Because otherwise that scout master should be the next sacrifice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 00:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm, those clues aren't really that strong for your case.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 23:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So those gang guys didn't take the girl then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 11:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you found a brochure, but now your parents or family had one too you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 02:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like dr lee is the resident doctor with the authority on things that 'stay hidden'. I imagine that Daniel has been taken off to a government or specialist facility.... Now the lose ends are being tied up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 13:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 13:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Move Eric, move. _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 12:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weed induced paranoia, focused on spirits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 22:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having someone like jake in my life would be nice, unconditional love, protection...
I would choose him. 
I mean, nothing is really normal. Who cares about what other people think? Just do your own thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 18:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Men is black is aliens though. This is more similar to scp types dealies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 20:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Mark is just a misspelling of Mike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 01:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You left your one year old home alone so that you could go to the pub. The ant should have eaten you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 04:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, just the escalation I warned against.
Come and find me is an invitation to death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 08:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok.. so my comment got flagged. Even though I'm not breaking any rules. I'll just put it back.

So, when did the fake detectives come to hire you? Because you don't make any mention of it... Unless, you somehow forgot about it? Also, how did ops soul end up back in the original body? It was swapped into the patchwork body.
And if they did work on soul retrieval, why did they bother making a patchwork body at all? Because they didn't need it, when they planned on using another body that was freshly dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 04:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god. Ten minutes after reading this story I clicked that it was 'i see you' not 'icu' as in hospital ward. 
I'm such a moron... I couldn't make sense of it haha.

Stay safe op. I guess that you were just in the wrong place at the wrong time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 04:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you lived in the apartment and moved out? 
I think you need to edit this a bit, it's very hard to follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 04:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, when did the fake detectives come to hire you? Because don't make any mention of it... It doesn't clearly fit into the storyline. Unless, you somehow forgot about it?
Also, how did ops soul end up back in the original body? It was swapped into the patchwork body.

And if they did work on soul retrieval, why did they bother making a patchwork body at all? Because they didn't need it, when they planned on using another body that was freshly dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 05:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely thought that this story was going to go a different direction with the whole 'jack filmed us' angle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 04:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can telephone companies disconnect internal calls? I think they lied to you to make you happy when you called up.. the only way to disconnect internal calls would be to remove the phones etc from block A. 
But I would suggest trying to salt and bless the building. Any local religious person could do it. 

But I advise caution, because this being is clearly escalating it's behavior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 04:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That building is condemned.
But yeah, go and case the place in the dead of night.. just in case.

Also, I never get how ghosts seem to randomly show up. 
Like, after so many years of haunting one place they decide to move house and float into a new place. Must be nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 04:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't understand how the story got here.

You had the ordeal in the cave with the doctor and Terri. Then you met some cops, who weren't cops. But we still don't know anymore about them, or what the doctor was working on.
You were about to reveal something, then don't remember writing it. But that hasn't been addressed ever since. 

Now, you're all over the place.. but are you actually, or are you just losing it? 
It's gone way overboard now... You need help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 11:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What were you doing in the woods? 
I really want to know...

Is this a rapture story? Like, all the bad people got left behind or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 01:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the scales of the balance between good and evil.
Not like, actual scales on an animal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 01:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does the tag on this story mean? Removed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 01:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But at what point does the attempt begin? 
Grey areas all around.. and he could be about to graduate up to murder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 01:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But blood would not freeze properly to be an ice lolly... And it tastes like metal.
She must have added a lot of sugar, that's so unhealthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 01:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it just got tired of you guys messing around on the road, especially as you said it was a pretty dangerous road already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 04:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont really understand, she was running from something or what she refers to as "them".. while wearing a necklace that's meant to grant protection. 
Then she gets drowned or killed in a hottub, which then leaves behind the little gems.

Now she herself is killing people too, leaving the same marks that she had upon death.

So did she kill herself? I wish there was more info available haha.

But I'm sorry about your friend, especially.as you were trying to help that lost soul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 04:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that wouldn't explain why everyone else can see the grandma again.

Maybe, op died and came back too. I don't know. It's very weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 04:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think that it would be Tara... Why wait like 20 years? 

I guess that he really did care, and he realized that his joke or test about Tara pushed him over the edge. Maybe he thought that he was testing your love for him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 03:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I dont see why they would need to kill op. I mean, he killed a guy for this job security. They could just make the extras, and keep him on his old job haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 03:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, he doesnt seem to be as eloquent as I'd have expected someone from high up to be.
Was he really from the company? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 03:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The circle with the x through it just screams slenderman story...

But none of the other tropes match that theme, and we all know that it can't be slender because that's basically a creepypasta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 03:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that maybe he was making the movies, and showing his 'girlfriends' before killing them. That's all I could get from this. 
He is talking to a doctor, so I guess that he has a serious mental condition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 02:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does a night light not keep him away?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 08:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're supposed to stay in character! :O  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 08:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just saying that the author makes comments about this girl being odd and making her feel uneasy. 17 is not legally adult age, so she could have been punished by letting this child loiter there. What if her parents hadn't actually been abusive? Calling social services is meant to be about help, not just taking kids away lol.

I stand by my comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 04:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is beyond creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 04:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did she have dead girls brought home, but a live one in the cupboard?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 04:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, maybe someone is taking your pictures and editing them? 
Then your mind is interpreting it as being real, creating the feelings and tastes.

Who runs that site? Find out what they know, or maybe they can point you to the model or photographer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 01:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't see the end coming, and it was very unexpected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 08:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that you can.. my friend was adopted twice, and had her name changed twice. (maiden and surname) 
I know that in the UK at least you can change an adopted child's name, otherwise a lot of babies would still have numbers rather than actual names. 

They do keep track of the names though, so there would be a record to look back through.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 05:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an odd thing to say. But it just sounds like baby has finally reached a stage of healing, a while after the physical healing.
I agree with the person above :) her mind might now be processing the trauma. You've helped her so much :)

Poor baby has just made you a bit paranoid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 05:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you had more, you should have posted some more. Just to make this longer, and more interesting to read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
