<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1320</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 10:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! People who lived through Poltergeist or demonic hauntings esp one that lasts as long as this one has lasted know even your worst even doesn't deserve this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 01:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will email you. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 23:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tacoma.  What organization? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 23:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many thanks. 
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=APO5088EAJM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 23:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, its been a steep learning curve. not all paranormal teams have been perfect. The Catholic Church didn't respond right away and do some degree came kicking and screaming. Fr. Brian never doubted our story but the environment the world is in right everybody is timid. Everybody is afraid of being led down a path of hoaxes.  Its not hoaxes. Its not fake. This situation is cookie cut and easy to describe and explain.  A couple: GF and I move into a house. On day one weird stuff started happening. Logically we ruled it out as most people would. Its easy to shrug off the early stuff.  Whats hard or near impossible to shrug are the objects being thrown. There is no rational explanation for objects to rise by themselves and go flying across a hall or room.  That event doesn't make our experience unique. Suffice what the skeptics say these events are happening all-over the world in all typed of homes. 99% never get reported.  I personally feel its my responsibility to report it and I'm reporting it because I believe it deserves to be shared among alike minds. I have to believe there's someone out their be they a person, or organization suitable for handling this sort of information. Be it TABS, SEC, GhostBusters "R: or who ever. Someone needs to be made aware of this stuff in addition to the paranormal community.  I was referred here. I'm glad I'm here. I'm sharing a true story. A true experience.  Thanks for understanding.  Be safe knowing there are a few people, few out of many that are helping. To them I am forever grateful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 20:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much. Fr Roy of the Episcopal church near Seattle. Reached out to us and did the 1st full exorcism on the house. He's over 80yrs old, retired. He has documented 7 previous demonic cases and assisted us in July of last year.  He openly admitted he's never seen a entity this active and this extreme. 
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=APO5088EAJM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 20:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> email me privately. The east coast team led by Karissa Fleck and Nikki will be spending days and weeks at the house soon to do a thorough investigation. We are looking at LIVE feed and 24/5 LIVE monitoring. In addition to them a UK team traveling from England will arrive Jan 21st.  This is not fake. That I can vouch and promise. Its weird. The activity has subsided for now (Knock on Wood) so right now we're sort of in a holding period. The events that happen now are minuscule and far few in between. Two weeks ago our garage door went up and down by itself.  Woke up and discovered it open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 20:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friends have witnessed it.  Individuals from two Paranormal Teams. Jennifer founder of No Bull Paranormal and her team were the 1st to respond Spring of 2014.  They witnessed the house humming.  Her Sage stick self lit when she tried to perform a cleanse ritual. BUMPS paranormal co-founder Kyle and team witnessed a step ladder teleport. A cast iron candle stick holder slid across the floor before everyone. Kyle saw a sliding closet door on its own and heard a growl.  Our friends Tina and mine have heard the loud bangs, foot steps and seen objects thrown.  When we tried the cameras aimed at cameras all that would happen is equipment malfunction. Camera goes missing or camera gets thrown.

LOUD BANG
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Us0Ss66R9Zg

Candles Thrown
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PFBtpo9OOU8

Loud Noise and Constant foot steps is heard by Husband and Wife Medium
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ufix69pMwyY

Dennis and Alice from messagesfrombeyond.com visit Keith and Tina . Topic: whats been going on. Both arrive at 11:18, 27:44 1st noise is heard. 29:15 2nd noise is heard Alice admits to it "Its not house settling noises. The noises there are referring to that me and GF are accustomed to are the foot steps and walking around. To learn more about them or even contact them see there web site above. August 23rd House Visit by Husband/Wife Medium team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 09:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I stated B4, video cams and motion cameras where installed and kept on 24/7 monitoring.  Cameras would go missing. Let me back up. 1st cameras would be unplugged. We plug them back in.  2nd Then cameras went missing. We'd buy new one's.  The new cameras would then go missing and get destroyed.  So your idea is valid. It has merit. But its been tried over and over and over and each time a camera gets destroyed or goes missing or better yet the power cut to that camera the activity in the home escalates ten fold.  I'm all ears for a solution that mitigates that should the activity spike again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 09:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue shirt. Back is turned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 09:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue shirt back is turned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 09:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I be curious to see verbiage of that opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 05:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U can't see my face. It's burnt off. Pic is my brothers graduation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NEVER NEVER EVER DO THIS: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 03:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the biggest mistake I've made in dealing with this is the mistake I'm about to share with you. One of the biggest annoyances a malevolent entity can do to you is deprive you of sleep.  We all know sleep deprivation leads to aggravation,irritation, frustration - the pillars if you will of making a mistake.  That mistake being OPENLY CHALLENGING A POLTERGEIST.  And thats exactly what I did.  It was a week night. The house was active. Active while we were sleeping.  After 2am or 3am door knocking, tapping, foot steps and stomping sounds coming from the ceiling. Some times right above our heads.  I'm sad and some what embarrassed to say (but try to understand us as being the one's being tormented, the victim) we hear this daily, and by 8 months plus of this particular nuisance u get or try to become numb to it.  But you have bad nights and this night was bad. So bad little sleep was gotten and once the 5am alarm clock run which means get up, shower and shave. Join your peers in an 1hour+ travel commute where 99.99999% of people in cars and van pools next you had anything similar to the kind of night my GF and I had.

BUT before I leave for work I must leave the Poltergeist a piece of my mind.  Its almost too humorous to admit. Idiocy. 

I walk into my office. Yank two blank sheets of paper out of the printer and write and after writing tape the paper unto the TV and walls of my office. The same office where two fires took place. The most active room in the house. I write these notes (see below) and head out the house.

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140703_065027366.jpg

and

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140703_065015843.jpg

Prior to doing this the activity was centered around the house. Meaning GF and I both would witness stuff or be at odds places of the house-something erupts and we rush to it and witness it together. Those are un-easy things to experience.  But at least you have each other to depend on.  Stuff happening to you both albeit fearful still provides you a benefit of not being alone.

And there have been times where stuff happened where one of us experienced and the other person didnt. But those events are far few and between. I call those instances residual presence still being felt.

Meaning the stuff she and I experienced while the other was away happened within minutes of the other person leaving the home.

Once I took it upon myself to post notes. Notes directly aimed at the Poltergeist. Calling it out if you will.  The house stopped being attacked.  I started being attacked.  Examples below are real

1. Sitting in my office and objects are now being thrown inside my office. Missing me by inches. At first objects got thrown in the hallway. Objects like beer bottles, wine bottles, candles, cologne bottle. All glass.  
2. Taking a shower and while showering the bathroom door slams.  GF is gone. Just me there
3. Taking a shower and minutes later when I step written on the wall is a upside down cross. Lotion or soap used.
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140624_222004768.jpg
4.  Like some when I get ready for work I go into my closet and grab the clothes I'm going to wear and lay them on the bed. When I get out of the shower  and gran my shirt I see every button is gone.
5. Have gotten dressed. Usually after I get dressed within 10 minutes I'm out the door. I wear button downs shirts.  By time I get down stairs and reach for the door knob every button on my shirt is gone. This has happened 4 times. 
6.  How about sitting on the toilet, using the bathroom.  The bathroom door slams, before slamming something clicks the light switch off, slams the door shut
7. Light goes off and door slams while taking a shower
8. Loud bang from the wall inside the shower stall
9. Cleaning the kitchen back is turned and Pottery goes flying.
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20141213_140635397.jpg
10. Taking a shower and coming out the shower and discovering the shirt you placed on the bed is hanging on the wall.
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20141207_202920597_1.jpg
11.  Objects with holy water go flying in the house
a) Dish in tact
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/Oct16th_BedroomD.jpg
b) Same dish thrown through the air like a frisbe. Come crashing in my office. My back was turned.
c) http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20141022_204301825_HDR.jpg
12. Pages in Bible ripped to shredds
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140601_155025158.jpg

13. Chair
The chair I sit in in the kitchen is most manipulated chair in the house. Has even been placed in my office a few times
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140630_180222917_HDR_1.jpg
14. Watch goes missing.  watch is missing for a few days. Tina finds it in my sink and texts me
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/watch_missing.jpg
15.Light fixture(disk shaped) goes missing. Is launched into my room and leaves a dent.
Missed be by inches.  Totally unexpected.
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20141225_160012836.jpg
16. Every non digital photo i.e. tangible photo of me, even its with other people. My face is burned off.
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/Pic1KeithC.jpg

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/Pic1KeithB.jpg

http://s299.photobucket.com/user/subject1320/media/Stafford%20Way/Pic1Keith.jpg.html?sort=3 o=254

Pictures that were tucked away in boxes that I forgot even existed. began appearing in the office and hallway book shelf with my face burned off.

I mentioned previously the "Die KL" wall markings
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/KL_Die1.jpg

Head Board bed scratches
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/20150703_115511.jpg

Lastly!

there are tons more.  The mental component darkens and deepens.

2nd pair of car keys go missing. I keep these buy my side or in a safe. $500 to replace.

The bed shakes. The poking of the rib cage while sleeping. The biting down on your feet. The yanking of the sheets while sleeping. The yanking of the sheets while sleeping in a Hotel room away from home.

The instance at work one day, while working at my desk I get spun around total 360 by an invisible shoulder check.  Something bumps me on my shoulder and spins me around. 

Leaving a friends goodbye party down town Seattle and get to my car. every door is wide open. Nothings missing.

Door bell rings 5am in the morning on a weekday. Its my next door neighbor. Every car door is wide open(my car).

It got so bad with me, and me only being attacked or messed with that my GF and I would leave the same time for work.  It just got to be too dangerous with me in the house and her leaving.

House black out as she's pulling out the drive way. Iron or Iron Board being thrown as she's backing out the drive way.

The activity spiked and centered 99% around me once I left those notes on the wall.

There's an old proverb that says "never go to war with someone who buys their ink by the bulk"

I see these shows were the ghost hunter openly challenges the spirit to a dual or worse and the ghost hunter leaves unscathed.

Maybe there are. Maybe they aren't messed with

I can tell from my experience you will be.  Doing so plays right into the hands of the entity.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 02:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they have been instrumental and helpful.  They and a UK team will be here in 2 weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 01:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Paranormal Teams Below will be arriving to the house end of January. There will be a LIVE webcam feed setup.  http://www.nikiparanormal.com/

and

She(Nikki) and others have been monitoring the house since Aug of last year. Keep in mind the activity I'm sharing now took place 2012, and 2014. 2013, and 2015 by in large were quiet years.

a lull period every other year.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_rlldSmE5T4

It should also be known Poltergeist and demons for that matter can leap. Those observing a web feed must not fool themselves and ignore the risks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2nd and 3rd Bible Burning / WHY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 00:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Ashalon understands and shares my sentiment. [ "Now the Bible was taken because I put emphasis on it." It could have been any book or object, but you thinking about it probably puts some kind of energy around it.]  

The items that began missing at the very beginning were items common to Poltergeist haunting. Car keys, silverware, cups, jewelry, etc.  Items that took us days to miss. After we started displaying our religious beliefs openly - a tide if you will switched. The items being displayed began to go missing that includes cameras to record events.  Activity so many here want to see and worse than that the crosses and Bibles we put out to warn off demonic entity's.  Since there's no way to be sure what is our thinking and the urging of others was leave no stone un-turned.

Keep in mind by this time frame.  Churches be they from the Baptists, Episcopal, and Catholics houses of God were paying house visits. The house was blessed. The house was cleansed. room by room. Upstairs and downstairs. The local parish, (The Priest seen the pic here, is being kept up to date).  Visits by the local Parish have now become weekly after Aug 2014.

Catholic Communion and Mass was held summer 2014
same time frame when the 2nd and 3rd Bibles took place.
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/Symbols_Stafford_way/Mass%20August%2013th%202014/2014-08-15_9-30-41.jpg

The items being taken now are the items we are in fact putting energy behind. We're not wrong for praying, we're not wrong for reciting Proverbs, and Psalms and drilling into our belief symptom but on the flip side of all that is a Poltergeists that observes us 24/7. Observes who ever comes in that house 24/7 and by taking items, religious items we display its telling us cliche methods don't work on me.

The first Bible that got burned. Woke us up in the middle of the night. There were actual flames. I could feel the heat on my face when I opened the bedroom door. That same level of heat that set off the fire alarms

The 2nd Bible burn - also happened while we were home but no alarm went off.  If you look at the pages. There crispy, folded in. its almost as if the Bible was opened and the pages purposely sat under a heat lamp. A very hot heat lamp that would burn the pages slowly.  When I found this Bible sitting on the Kitchen Island there was no smoke smell. The Bible at most was missing maybe 11 hrs. We went to bed it was still on the shelf. We woke up it was gone.  We weren't even up an hour before it returned. 

Look at the 3rd Bible burning. This one was burned while we were at work. The house was attacked, camera alerts went off and shot off emails to me. I come home and find this.  The pages burned on this Bible is more darker. The ashes are jet black. Might have something to do with both the paper and the ink itself.  There's noway of knowing if it set off the fire alarm which i must add it very close by.

But the 3rd Bible is significant and should raise the eye brow to anyone investigating Poltergeist and Demonic infestations.

3 Bibles were burned in this house. The 3rd Bible would be the first Bible ever burned while we are away.
2nd Bible Burning
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uVZVtcjZzgo

We came home and found the 3rd Bible on the shelf, all Bibles are kept and the page and passages incinerated . Mind you its sitting on a wooden book shelf. Two shelves.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CjkYw2kleBU

Which gives evidence to the argument that Poltergeists, or malevolent entities for that matter have the ability to burn a house down. But CHOOSE not to do so.

3rd Bible Burning
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CjkYw2kleBU

Also the entity is doing activity when both occupants are gone. No agent as some theorists like to cling to.

This would be last Bible to burn in the house. It would not be last Bible to be attacked i.e. go missing, or get thrown or even soaked in water.  Three more fires would take place. One cross will be burned on Halloween 2014/Nov 1st.

Wooden cross
Bought it at Goodwill and hung it in the Living Room
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20141109_125735320.jpg

religious items missing in the house

1. 2 Bibles are missing
2. Virgin Mary statue
3. Holy Water is missing
4. Michael the Archangel statue is missing
5. 2-3 wooden crosses are missing.
6. Sage and sage tray are missing

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 09:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No the last wall writing was Dec 2014.

Before and after that it was lawn, and personnal car writingsAfter the exorcism and other counter measures it began to tapper of. Poltergeist cases come in waves though. So we'll see. A stellar team is investigating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 06:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  armoire  Ooops  Thanks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 06:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats the stuff we can't explain.  Its not paint. That much we know.  The 666, upside down cross and upside down man "Native American" symbol means death. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q3meCW-YznM

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20150224_053642956_HDR.jpg

Ill-attempts to paint over it with several types of primer.  

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20141219_112235347_HDR.jpg

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20141123_135805770.jpg

http://www.warpaths2peacepipes.com/native-american-symbols/man-symbol.htm

https://theghostvictimexperiment.wordpress.com/2015/07/14/native-american-symbol-upside-down-man-as-shown-briefly-on-ghost-adventures-demonsinseattle/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 05:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-F9K0bvVa2s

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J6mFKLLVKwc


Its ok to be afraid. This is some really outlandish stuff. But no matter how outlandish it seems to your eyes and ears. Its 100% true and it happened 2012 - 2015.  And the investigation continues.

https://app.box.com/s/lmero13u8x58h27rphc6i3rl8uimj6vy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 05:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things happen when she's around.  When I'm alone and when she was alone. Most of the events happened when both of us are at work. 60% that is. 30% happens while we're home together. 5% with just me and 5% with just here. Around Oct 2014 till February 2015 the attacks began to center on me. It got so bad my GF who normally leaves for work before I do, had to hang around an extra hour in the  morning or some mornings we'd just leave at the same time. because if we didn't that attacks would start solely on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 05:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello I just emailed you.  subject1320. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 05:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  The belief now among several people investigating the house including the Priest who did the exorcism was we're dealing with a Poltergeists.  The doings, workings, and attacks just point to a clever, elusive Poltergeists that when provoked unleashes crazy attacks as most Poltergeists do.  I try to stand clear of the word demon, even though I believe in demons. I believe in God. Therefore I believe in Satan and the Devil. Is that what occupies this house?  I dare not say.  What I will say is the events be they past events and what transpires now does fit the profile of a Poltergeist.  Ironically Poltergeists are the hardest cases to solve let alone ascertain.  

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-F9K0bvVa2s

and

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_rlldSmE5T4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 03:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yes Paranormal Teams are assisting or have assisted. The investigation continues during the lull period of what is believed to be Poltergeist activity.  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_rlldSmE5T4

and https://app.box.com/s/lmero13u8x58h27rphc6i3rl8uimj6vy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 03:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually most of the activity happens while we're away. Keep in mind this was 2012, and 2014/15.  

Examples of us being away: Aug 2014
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sAjIRemgbZk

and Halloween 2014

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pow8xFUDWW4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 03:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great idea. Thanks. I know there all encrypted to prevent hacking from outside and etc.  Updated with the latest firmware. But good suggestion non-the-less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 03:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is 200% genuine occurrence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Throwing of Heavy Objects </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 09:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things start off subtle with Poltergeist haunting. Objects being thrown is no exception.  The first things to go flying (even with friends present) were flower pots. A 4 foot Ivory plant - this plant here ( https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gbWXXnjfB9E ) rose up while GF and I were watching TV. Summer 2012. It seems LIKE once something happens - events of a similar nature happen more frequently. It's like a seal has been broken. A Pandora's box if you will. Pretty soon plants began flying daily.


1. I was doing dishes(loading the dish washer) back turned to the kitchen and living room - when I heard a loud noise. Turned around plant was that sits by the wall was laying on the floor. July 2012. Remember we moved in May 2012.
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/Flower8.jpg

2. This is the plant that flew one night during Monday night football. Sits in the den. This plant flew or was thrown so many times it finally died. We couldn't salvage it anymore. I was thrown from one side of the room to the other no less than 5 times. Twice when company was over. Its significant because after it was thrown the LOUD bangs began and other paranormal activity. Lights Off and On. Pacing, Thuds, and door slams. Prior to it being thrown objects were coming up missing and objects neither of us owned began appearing. Esp kid toys.

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/Flower5.jpg


3. This event has to be interesting to somebody. By this stage of the game Aug/Sept 2012. LOUD Bangs were pretty much every night. I think I saw the female apparition before this plant got thrown either give or take a week or two.  The night this plant got thrown GF and I were trying out an idea friends had told us. Friends recommended we attempt to make communication with the entity.  With kid toys popping up everywhere we were still of this mindset this thing could be friendly. Lost but friendly. After this night we stopped thinking that. Sitting at the kitchen table with the voice recorder my sister mailed me. She's a Dr, so she mailed me the voice recorder she used while in school.  GF and I are sitting at the table asking questions we found online. Very mundane. Questions like why are you here?  what do you want? whats your name?  Please go into the light?  After a few questions the bar stool behind us got thrown and the plant sitting on the wine rack few feet behind us got thrown, well actually it got slammed to the ground. Both bar stool and plant were just a few inches from us. After that night we stopped trying to talk to the spirit. This was summer 2012.  You should know the voice recorder my sister gave me- the one she used while in med school that she parted with because she knew of our problem. That voice recorder went missing a few days later after that plant got thrown down to the floor.  Its still missing. 
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/Flower3.jpg

4. I saved the best for last. This is the 300+ lb Amour that when we moved in it took 3 of us to carry this thing upstairs.  Its a B* tch to move. I hate this thing. It doesn't lend itself for grabbing. The edges are bulk and sharp.  When we got it upstairs we planted it never hoping to move it again. I'm 6"5 1/2 . This Amour is about 6"3.  After a 1 1/2 of no activity the Amour was sitting in the hallway. It would be the 1st thing thrown when the Poltergeist left and came back i.e. became active again.  This 300+ was resting on a wall and when thrown was thrown from side of the hallway to the other. IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.

After being tossed in the hallway two more times we moved it painstakingly into one of the guest bedrooms. Not to prevent it from ever being thrown again. But to save the walls in the hallway. This was spring 2014 mind you. Hence came the cameras months later

After the cameras were erected the activity got worse and this same Amour would be tossed a few more times inside the guest bedroom.

Video is a video of the Amour erect in the bedroom.  Yeah weird light action to.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R4R_32gpK64
It doesn't look no where near like this now.

if needed I can provide a pic of how it looks now.  Right now its a poor imitation of what an Amour should be. You child could probably bring it down stairs now if needed.

This is the Amour laying on its face.
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/House_Home_Chair/Kitchen%20LivingRoom%20and%20Office/bedroom_2014_august.jpg

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140519_212424658.jpg


I wish to God I could relate or paint a perfect picture to you of what its like to see let alone hear an object this big being thrown. Its not so much the size thats haunting vs the sound.  These things happen abruptly. Totally unexpected.

You're chilling with your girl or are in your house just living your life. I'm watching TV upstairs. GF might be watching TV down stairs or on the phone with a friend or family member. Or we might be having dinner when all of a sudden a LOUD CRASH. A loud thud, or BANG. There is no precursor for when objects get thrown especially the BIG items.  After it happens you're running trying to find your partner before anything else.  a noise that loud could only mean someone just got hurt. Once you reconvene and meet in the hallway or the bottom of the stairs you look at each other almost pale white.  You then go looking for the noise.  When you find the root cause or after math your mouth drops wide open.

I have to give it everything I've got to raise this Amour back up. Everything I've got. I'm 6"5 1/2 250 lbs.

I'm a tall, big guy.  When it goes flying its flying ladies and gentlemen. You dont want to be in the path of it and its final resting place.

This is what I want people to understand about Poltergeist and Demons.

2-3 yrs a go I was stupid and naive. I was running around erecting cameras without a clue as to what I was facing.

I dont think people who suggest try this, try that totally understand the repercussions of such actions.

TV personalities make it look funny and silly. Its not.

The next time you're having dinner with your wife, or GF try to think of a plane crashing through your ceiling some part of the house where you can't see.  Better yet try to imagine that when you're asleep.

If you can imagine that you might be able to understand the term Malevolent Haunting.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 00:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h45QMuICA-8 2nd Bible burning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 00:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just me and my girlfriend live in the house. I would say no.  Having done thorough research of the house I was able to get in contact with the previous tenants. Both wife and son suffered major emotional issues.  Son developed meningitis and became very ill-8 odd yrs a go.  Wife fell into alcoholism and deep physical and emotional abuse from her Ex husband.  That in addition to the land being on old controversial Native American ground its one theory out of several currently being looked at. 

2nd Bible burning
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h45QMuICA-8  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 00:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Several house cleansing and one house-exorcism or house cleanse I should say by both Catholic and Episcopal Priests. Last house cleanse was July 2014.  https://youtu.be/APO5088EAJM

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/Symbols_Stafford_way/Mass%20August%2013th%202014/2014-08-15_9-36-08.jpg

that was Bible #1.  Two more Bibles burned summer/fall 2014. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1st Bible Burning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 06:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the title is correct 1st Bible. I have to distinguish it because we had 3 Bibles burn in our house. And please its not what you think it is. 

The 1st Bible to burn went missing in summer/fall 2012.  That Bible would return March 2014. Missing for over a year and a half before returning.  The question is why did it go missing in the 1st place?

Like I said before we began experiencing LOUD bangs, cabinet doors open, flying plants, raising plants, foot steps, thuds, lights going off and on at will.   After about 4-6 weeks of that I began informing friends, clergy and family for assistance. One of the recommends was Sagging and displaying our religious beliefs out openly.

The night the Bible went missing my GF was out of town.  A co-worker recommended I sage the house. To cleanse.  I got home with sage in hand and began sagging.  As I was sagging the masterbedroom I heard the sound of running.  By time I got to the door and to the hallway landing - I could see from the 2nd floor landing with a clear view of the front door. The front door opened and slammed shut. Something invisible obviously darted passed me. I saw the front door open. ADT Alarm even said "Front Door Open" and the door slammed shut.

I took that as a sign as of the sagging actually working. After all it appeared something just ran out of the house.

Hours later I was on the phone with my best friend he urged that I leave a Bible out in the open and chapter open to Psalms. I placed the Bible out on one of the lamp tables and went to bed. 

The next morning I woke up house still heavy with sage.  From my landing you can see the down stairs. When u step out of my bedroom you step into the hallway landing. When I looked over the rail I immediately notice the Bible was gone.  Now the Bible was taken because I put emphasis on it.   Its not like we were one day having dinner and all of a sudden out comes a flaming Bible. Now GF was in Vegas on business.  I was home alone.

By this stage of the game friends of ourse have seen objects fly. Objects get thrown and have heard the loud bangs. The recommends coming from friends, co-workers, and clergy is display your religious belief openly. I'm not criticizing their advise. I'm calling out a Poltergeists reaction to it. 

Exorcisms where Poltergeists are concerned can at times be a means of provoking the entity. Challenging the angry spirit. Remember the sole purpose for objects being thrown, and bangs is to get attention.  Placing a Bible on a coffee table, or lamp table is no exception.  

FastForward: For the most part 2013 was quiet. By Nov-December the activity was subsiding. Of course Bible was still missing. As was other objects.

 But something about 2013 just didnt sit right with me. occasional, about every other month weird things would still happen.  TV channels would change by themselves. Fire alarm one night rang by itself but there was no fire. The thing that felt weird the most was the feeling of being watched.  2013 would soon end minus any major activity-minus any violent activity.

By March that would change. A Sunday night, nothing usual about it.  Typical Sunday night. We went to bed. 2 months after my knee surgery.  We heard a loud bang in the hallway. It woke us up.  Nothing found so we went back to bed. 30 minutes later a loud thud and crash. The Amour in the hallway had been thrown from wall to the other leaving a major dent in the wall it was resting on.  After that day. Events happened daily. 2012 all over again.

This time we called Paranormal Team. A team came over about a week or so later. Did an 1 hour investigation. 

When they left we went to bed.   Hours later we were awaken by the house fire alarm.  When I opened up the bedroom double doors there on the floor was a book on fire. Looked like a small camp fire.

I think i used my foot or hands to close the book to put out the fire. I then after closing it realized it was the Bible. The missing Bible taken summer/fall 2012.

Inside it was burned wooden cross. That cross was hanging above our heads. Over the bed.  Pages all burnt and ash everywhere.

We tried calling the Paranormal Team that came over just hours prior.  No answer. It would be midday Monday before they got my voice mail.

Equally shocked as we were.

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140331_021633407.jpg

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140331_021627889.jpg

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140331_021642887.jpg


Pics below are events that motivated us reaching out to friends and family.

exploding light fixtures

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140330_124345947.jpg

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140329_233000205.jpg

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140729_221430945.jpg

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20140729_221423383_HDR.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 03:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't see this earlier. Once again great mind think alike. I laid out talcum powder to try to catch our culprit. Zero success. One upside down cross was drawn on the restroom mirror. Aside from that all the other writings always took place in my office.  Where these writings done while you were home?  Away? Or sleep? Ours was always while we were away. No writings ever took place while we were home.  Do you have photo's of the Poltergeist workings, shenanigans, and after math attacks?  I'm learning so much from your account. The similarities are astounding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 16:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the puddle of water only happened once. That was Halloween Oct 31st. I learned puddles of water is a strong indicator of Poltergeist activity.  Came home to that and this burnt cross on the wall.  Cross was always there but it was scorched around the edges.

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20141109_125735320.jpg

I know all to well about the cabinets being open. Like I said the 1st time that happened we had company over. And you're right zero sound. We sat a few away in the next room. Heard nothing.  Bar stools and chairs got relocated all the time

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20141101_024941079.jpg

You above anyone else might appreciate this video. The video is made from the mail alert emails I got while at work on movement in the house i.e. kitchen and office.  watch the chairs and left side of couch area. snap shot pics taken by my camera in the time frame shown.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fwhyfd8A3EQ

My occupation?  I'm a IT project manager for a IT hardware manufacturer company.  I would say my GF keeps her feelings more inside than me. It was hard to tell where her mind was at most times. Or get her to share her feelings. Not so much about me just the other things going on in her world, her life be it work or family related.  I can tell our Poltergeists seized on disagreements, and arguments. It caused a few and some it failed in causing. These things do instigate and ours did all the time. I started noticing how it instigated and pretty soon we started have deep conversations away from the home. We'd go to the neighborhood starbucks if we thought a conversation was going to lead to a debate.  Having said that I also want to reiterate some of the most crazy level of activity stemmed from light hearted moments to.   I had LOUD bangs and objects thrown during Monday Night football with the eyes. Light fixtures exploded when Tina was in the house by herself.  My office caught fire when only I was there.  I have enough data for every scenario.

One thing is for sure from Fall 2014 to February 2015. major activity like candled being thrown also came after subtle activity like lights going off and on.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PFBtpo9OOU8



s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 05:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello.  Did you ever find puddles of water?  On the floor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 17:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi NASA_ .,  thats been the upmost unsolved mystery to me and to us. And by us I mean clergy, paranormal teams, researchers, and myself. There are documented cases of a Poltergeist jumping. There are documented cases of a Poltergeists following its victims from home to work even. Those cases are 1 out of a 100. Extremely rare. A lot of things about this case change the paradigm or understanding I should say about what we "think" we know about Poltergeists. Keep in mind we think its a Poltergeists because of some of the actions its done that fit what previous Poltergeists cases.  But there are things its done that haven't been seen much before. As it is with most cases. All cases be they demon, Poltergeist or Ghost related offer its own uniqueness. What makes this case compelling is the length of time its been around. 3 families in a 10 year time frame is unheard of. Poltergeist attached to land or building have happened before. There occurrence is extremely rare. And by being are means we have less to go on-study wise and information wise. 90% of Poltergeists that are real cases we think lend themselves to people. People are the root cause albeit through some mental component. 10% or less are tied to some physical elements like land or property.

the number could be higher. Might be higher. We just don't know. People could be running into this issue and simply moving.As someone posted the Eddie Murphy video earlier. Simply move and be done with it. So the case and experience goes un-reported. The people who move don't have attachments because they weren't in the house long.  Others move in after them and experienced nothing because there DNA persona doesn't trigger or activate the Poltergeist.  Its just interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 17:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello thanks for answering. So when you tell me about the TV and demand channels and stuff being of predestined, predetermined channels "Ghostly Movies" I'm right there with you. Your history and recount is doing volumes for me. Providing me great info because we've had something similar. You'll see in my time line in 2014 we had a incident I labeled the "Katie Perry" incident. Yes Katie Perry the singer.  It was a Friday about the time when the activity was kicking back up Spring 2014. The TV in our master bedroom kept coming on and when it came on the TV screen was black but blasting from it was the Katie Perry song titled: Black Horse . And the lyrics playing was [ So you wanna play with magic
Boy, you should know whatcha falling for
Baby do you dare to do this
'Cause I'm coming atcha like a dark horse
Are you ready for, ready for
A perfect storm, a perfect storm
'Cause once you're mine, once you're mine
There's no going back]

GF and I would run into the room look a blank TV screen blasting. Screen was blank but the channel was One Sixty Something, i forgot exactly.  We'd look at each other and say "WTF" I then would turn the TV off. Manually. We'd leave. 5-10 minutes later TV would blast again same volume level. Same black screen and same lyrics above.  I then un-plugged the TV and we left the room.

Minutes later the TV came screaming again with that same song, same lyrics. Now the overall length of this ordeal was 10+ minutes. Maybe even 15 minutes. The song is nowhere near that long. I an see a TV coming on a new song be playing every time. After all time moves forward not backward.  But for 15 minutes or less the TV kept coming on and that song was playing and just those lyrics.  Ladies and gentlemen I swear to God this happened. You can't make this stuff up. Truth is stranger than fiction and Poltergeists are no exception. So I know how you feel sharing that part of your story. But trust me you don't have to worry. It all makes sense. There's stories I've yet to tell because even though they happened last year or the year before I'm still mentally coming to terms with them. My whole reason for coming to a site like this and sharing my ordeal. our ordeal is I have to believe others, as in modern people have experienced something very similar to what we experienced. My 2nd reason for coming here is years from now when someone has their own Poltergeists experience that they leap to the internet like I did. Like we did and share there story. I hope there doing there own research. This info helps. Your info helps me. Helps us.  People can laugh and shrug, giggle, scream hoax all the want.  When the "devil" bites your ass and comes to your house to play with you and your loved one's we'll see who's screaming hoax then.  These things can avoid detection. Avoid the being captured by the most skilled Paranormal Investigator. if something can make a TV play by itself minus being plugged in a wall or control a TV like you mentioned in your story - do people seriously think hiding cams around a house to catch something is going to work? Doesn't means we shouldn't try.  But the fact that it doesn't has no bearing on the house occupant making stuff up.  Thats my rhetorical question and soap box for today.  You Christoforever has lived and witnessed something 99% of the worlds population has yet to see or ever experience.  Your story offers a begin date that seems to correspond with your girlfriend?  Stress and strife and etc does play a major role in some of these cases. Not all. But some. I have more to share and seen. PS. So days after the Katie Perry sorry the activity sky rocked and became relentless. It was like the verse to that song was a omen i.e. prediction as to what was about to come.  After that song played-we had activity everyday. Each day got out did by the next.   Continue to share anything you might recollect.  I will as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 03:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I can put the items being thrown or missing in two categories. Common items, items we gave little thought about but would be missed within 30-60 days. Ex. 2nd set of car keys-never used them. Moved them from point A to point B. Old Apartment(A) to the new house(B). I noticed the keys gone after moving into the new house, days later. Never used the keys they were spares. Ex. Music CD's I ordered online of Amazon. Hard to find CD on the net but I had them for months. There gone now. Sat on my office desk.

The other items moved or thrown were objects the clergy, the church, friends and family say display to warn of negative entities.  Ex. Sage sticks, Bibles(3) burned. 2 other Bibles ripped in half. One Bible is still missing. Other objects thrown or missing are cameras obviously, white candles, wooden crosses, Michael the Archangel statue and a wooden Virgin Mary given to us by the local Priest.

So its not so much objects we focused on except the one's we were advised to display. Interesting enough a St. Benedict cross that hangs over the entry door has yet to be touched.  

My GF has her own stories of house attacks. Later in 2014 when I'm out of town on business her BFF would spend the night and they both would be attacked in my absence.  I once got emails from my monitoring cams that mass motion and sound is being detected why she was en route to the house from work. I've had delay entry. Meet me at starbucks and we go into the house together.  She's found the house upside down a few times.  I have to. 

The first fire I was in the house alone. The 2nd fire we both were sleeping and got awoken to it.

Us and others don't think the entity is tied to us. We based that on two key facts. Two previous families (tenants) came forth and spoke of similar activity.

The land, city, and county has rich Native American history.  We think the rich native american history might be a reason why it attacks Christian symbols. But that might be a false positive because Poltergeist by definition respond negatively to removal tactics.  The violence we get is like its telling us these counter measures are an insult to it.

We also think the reason why it attacks me more vs. my GF is I'm the one who's most active in trying to rid it. I'm the most active doing research about it. One night after 0 sleep due to the loud bangs and shaking of the bed I got up and challenged it. Bad move.


It took the gloves off and began attacking me 24/7. Home, work, and abroad.

Questions:

How big was the 1st house?  How old was that house?
Who's in the house now? Have you followed up with them to see if they are having activity?
From start to finish how long would you say the activity was?
What type of electrical issues took place? TV's? Radios?  Cell phone?

Did you ever feel like it was creating animosity between you two. Stirring up dissension?

Might sound weird me saying this but I like the fact that Paranormal teams came in and got little evidence with gadgets. The techniques applied by Paranormal Teams. 90% of it doesn't work.

5 teams have been to my house. 4 have seen with their own eye's. All their equipment died. At most they left with high EMF and weird temp signatures upstairs.

Most of their experience has been with their naked eyes.
One actually was kicked. The other heard a growl.

A Shaman came in and saw the cabinet door close on its own.

This Bible is missing:
http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/IMG_20141002_055918761.jpg

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 23:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its believed these spirits can't cross major bodies of water. Permanently. meaning if you take up new residence. I've been bombarded a few times in my Hotel room while traveling on business.  I'll be in Hawaii next week so it should be very interesting what happens.  House I'm in is a rental.  Lease is up in May. The follow you elsewhere and the fact we don't have kids or pets are the reasons for not yet moving. The synopsis for activity for us goes like this. We moved in May 1st 2012, Day one in the empty house we heard a kid cough come from upstairs. Owner had just minutes prior.  After a few weeks we began waking up finding as you mentioned all doors down stairs open. Including the front door and all kitchen cabinets. That was odd but we shrugged it off. Then it kept happening around the time the 1st plant flew and when the 1st plant rose up by the TV and did a 360 spin and keeled over. After that we knew something was up. Days later ADT came and installed the security system. We were just getting to many doors open while sleeping. activity spiked during house parties. Then the LOUD bangs began. Thunderous. Unable to locate the source. Missing items. Teleport. Finding stuff neither of us owned pretty much went from Summer to Winter of 2012.  Then in 2013 for the most part got quiet. The bangs stopped. Objects stopped flying and etc. The Bible, the 1st Bible I should say that went missing summer/fall 2012 never came back.  Then on January 2nd 2014 I took a bad mysterious fall. Tore my knee cap clean off. Patella tear. Was laid up for 2 1/2 months.  Thats when the noise and movement began. By time March rolled around on Sunday we were sleeping and was awaken to a loud BANG. We heard this bang before.  Minutes later we went back to sleep and thats when the first Amour got thrown.  This was March 2014.  After that night the activity spiked and remained spiking, escalating till February 2015. Everyday was an event.  Oh and that Bible that went missing in 2012. It came back April of 2014. Fire alarm woke us up one night while sleeping. There in the hallway was the missing Bible on fire, ablaze. This was about 1:34am.  A local Paranormal team had just left the house two hours prior. When they walked in they say our house was humming. All their equipment died.  the dangerous activity has now subsided.  No one knows for sure. Poltergeist are known for this lull.  I'm thinking with the lull the time might be ripe to finally move.  But there goes that follow me to my new home fear factor.  Question- have you and your girlfriend ever had a caught in spiders web feeling?  If so please explain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 21:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You see that's how I'm able to determine and spot a truth person vs. a hoaxer. It takes one to know one as the saying goes. As I'm reading your words I'm linking it mentally to my experience. My GF and my own experience. And you're correct. We've been dealing with this for the last 3 years. Last year was insane.  You're right about the large objects missing. We had a 3 foot step ladder disappear and re-appear between 3-4 people. It just vanished and re-appeared. We have giant Amours tossed like confetti.

From about Oct to February of last year I was poked in my rib cage while sleeping. Like someone's fore finger was literally jabbing me. We've had bar stools thrown and knocked over. One day my GF was in my office listening to some of the sounds I caught on handicam and the stereo kept coming on and the volume put on high.  

What proceeded the bad activity was lights going off and on. Sometimes a total black out of the house, 2nd floor or the exact room I was in.  We've had fires. 2 fires in my office. 1st fire we had I called the fire dept.  Poster caught fire.  GF was at home alone one night and every light bulb in the hallway and stairway exploded. Light bulb and the porcelain case that the bulb was in. We've come homeor have been awaken in the middle of the night by that dense feeling you speak of. Its like the house is alive or is watching you. As the torment increases you both get irritable mood swings. We began questioning and fighting each other. Blaming each other and each time the activity spiked higher.

It was total catch 22 situation. House party's, levity , and fun moments activity still spiked. But when we got angry or frustrated a different sort of activity would happen.  A few paranormal teams aka thrill seekers made matters worse by what they recommended. Our local Parish(local as in the one in our suburb) dragged his feet in helping us. 

Did you ever hear the sounds of furniture being dragged around?
Did you ever see movement or shadows out the corner of your eye?


My GF hair got pulled a few times. Something would whisper to her while she slept or was napping.

I've seen a female , torso apparition 3 times
I've seen the shadowy figures about 1-2 ft tall.

When sleeping was your toes ever messed with? Like pins or needles poking you. Like a vise or needles sandwiching your feet while sleeping?

How many miles would you say you had to move before the activity subsided?

Are u and your girlfriend still together?

I know thinking and answering these questions conjures up deep, dark emotions. I feel you. We're that way now.

There's really no support system. No support group for people like us. people who lived this stuff. Friends and family those that sincerely believe you really are ill-equipped on how to assist mentally.

I'm clinging to my belief system. Thats what we got me through thus far. I'm no saint by any stretch of the imagination. But I'm no bad person either. I work a 9 to 5 and when done just want my couch or love seat and TV or Xbox.

This Poltergeist had other plans and hit us hard on day one.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 19:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Christoforever?  I think you just became my new best friend.  I will be in contact with you soon to pick your brain for info.  Questions I have for you worth sharing here include:  Did you or your GF ever experiencing LOUD bangs, wall tapping? Objects being thrown and objects missing?  You mentioned something about the taps on the forehead while sleeping. Yikes.  Was there any other movement while sleeping like bed shakes, mattress indention's, hovering. Your case and mine mimic a lot.  http://s299.photobucket.com/user/subject1320/slideshow/  GF was scratched to. 3 times.  I know about the warm sensation feeling. I get it or use to get it on my arm and thigh. when the activity was heightened. Never any scratches on me though.  I've been pushed though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 17:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they follow you. 3 yrs in. Attachment is almost certain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 17:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes good people have helped us. Fr. Roy a Priest. Several paranormal groups. Some have been good, others have been horrible. The last team to come on board has been SEP. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TeHTpVqGn-g
House Cleansing / July 2014 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 09:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thought is being entertained as we speak by Paranormal teams local and abroad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 09:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Error372 I like and appreciate your idea. Its thinking outside the box and I agree with it.  It has been attempted at least the part about the  portable power supply.  Back up battery. But please understand me when I say this. Back up batteries offer the same problem as a wall outlet, matter of fact they bring about more problems.  Their heavy, expensive --- and pose a threat as being  anew projectile object. When I had 3 hour to 4 hour length back up battery the battery would mysteriously drain, mysteriously be turned off. Remember I said I had camera watching cameras. If an entity can unplug a camera from a wall or from a AC port it can equally turn a battery off. And guess what it did. A portable battery does not eliminate the object being teleported away.

There's a saying nothing can defeat a determined mind. That proverb holds true with Poltergeists as it does with humans. A Poltergeist that doesn't want to be captured on film or digital video guess what is not going to allow itself to be captured on video. Now that doesn't make the story less true.  I can use editing and movie making software and make a  video and posted here. What then? I'm believable all of a sudden. It becomes cool then.  All of a sudden I'm believable.

I've searched online and I cannot find one Poltergeist related video where the activity that is caught is still subject to 50% believers and 50% skeptics.  Will someone please provide me a video where the consensus is 100% that the video is real. 

The evidence is not the video or the gadgets used to capture an entity writing on a wall. The evidence is witnesses, tenant statement, credibility of the one experiencing the event, the one witnessing the event and the numerous amount of people involved in the project. Would you like the previous tenant to post here?  How about BUMPS. the paranormal team that saw objects levitate themselves.  I could post there reports but guess what there reports are equally man made, equally hand written just like any video I post here.  The definition of insanity is " trying the same thing over and over again hoping for different results. Myself and those helping us thought about embedding cameras into the dry wall of the wall but that poses significant risk to house and property.  I've seen this Poltergeist throw a 300+ Amour across a room like it was paper. If I leave a camera embedded in my wall while I'm at work for 8 hrs.  The only thing I'm going to come home to is the same thing we came home to last year except now I got  a huge hole in my wall and for what. To satisfy skeptics and scenics online who are in no position to help or offer substantial advice. I'm not even seeking advice. Everything I'm reporting happened last year. I'm just recounting events we experienced last year and sharing it.  People can believe or not believe.   I like your advice. Its been tried and the results have been the same.   The best thing a skeptic can do is take my account and compare it to previous Poltergeist related events in the past and look for similarities.  Trust me you'll find plenty. That's the best advice I can offer a skeptic. I don't even want to waste my time on scenic's.   Scenic(s) are just here to run interference on topics worthy of being advanced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 05:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
