<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8864</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 03:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, doing something still feels better than doing nothing.  Today I was too busy with chores and work to dwell on my self-pity.  It's something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 19:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> excercise, workout.  When I do it, I start telling myself I'm going to fail, and then I just stop.  I get so self conscious after looking at myself in a mirror that I just give up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm just miserable, and I can't even take the first step to start changing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 18:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone.  I know, I should sound like a whiny bitch.  I've talked to some people already, and I know what I need to do, but I feel so low that I can't seem to get myself to take the first step.  This lingering ache of self doubt is hanging over my head.  Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 3 of NoPorn: Fapping too much </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 17:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For day 2, I masturbated twice today without porn. Once in the morning when I woke up, and once at noon. Without porn, I had to rely on mental fantasies. But even then it was draining, and my body didn't react to my stimulation. Instead, my body felt tired, but the mental stress was pushing me to orgasm. It drained all the energy out of me, and I went to sleep at skipped lunch. I have a midterm two days from now, and I feel stressed. Before and after each session, there was this lingering dull ache throughout my body. I've been staying indoors studying without any movement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 2: Withdrawal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 17:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Monday morning.  I feel stressed, and I feel tempted to watch porn.  Do you guys have tips, or activities you do what the urges come? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you hype yourself up before sparring/fight? How do you build your ego? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 00:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you hype yourself up before a fight?  That extra kick in mental energy to think you can win the fight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 23:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've found it difficult to find tips on mental training.  I youtube a guy on practicing meditation and visualization techniques, but I'm not sure if it works?  Like he said something about imagining yourself in a fight.  Have you tried meditation or visualization exercises? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 23:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good effort, do you spar often? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 01:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right?  Lady's man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are boxers attractive? Does boxing help you get dates? Any love stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 07:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How old can someone do amateur boxing for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 21:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there age groups a brackets as boxers get older?  Or are older people afraid of getting hurt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 04:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, no one cares, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 02:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you're right and I might be over analyzing.  Come to think of it I just don't fit into group settings in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 00:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I wonder if there were boxers who happened to be LGBT who came out of the closet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LGBT in boxing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 18:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how many LGBT there are in boxing, or came out?  I identify as bi, and sometimes I feel out of place.  Boxing has mostly been a hetero, male dominated sport.  I think all the guys at my gym are straight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 05:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends, what part of LA are you?  I looked everywhere near where I lived.  I'm near Pasadena. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 04:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel better guys, thanks for the tips! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 07:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the stress from finals and being surrounded by sick students. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 17:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always felt that I had a weak, effeminate body.  I wish I was stronger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
