<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7254</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 19:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely right. I love fighting, but I save it for competition. Street fights are the dumbest things ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 19:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://youtu.be/Gw4EoWi5QSM

Check this out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 17:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take out the knee. YouTube search the front kick. It can be angled at the knees, body, or face. However, without proper training, body kicks or head kicks aren't a good idea. However, if you take out the knees, you disable their movement. From there, you can run away, or you can jump on them and attack the face. 

If you're anticipating a fight, I suggest training martial arts. Taekwondo is a fantastic striking art and Judo and Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu are great arts for throwing and submission holds. If you can find a Sambo school, even better. Sambo incorporates both. It's like Russian MMA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 17:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although they also can do many things we can't. Part of the reason why they can't do what we do is because of skeletal structure, not muscle strength. They have fantastic strength ratios, but skeletal design keeps them from doing things like running as effectively as humans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stories about playing with friends? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 03:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured I'd share some of our stories. Big wall of text ahead. 

1. First time we got together to play, I never saw any of the movies, so I asked my friends to give me info on what we're up against. They told me what they knew about the Xenomorph anatomy and the owner of the game explained that it's impossible to kill the alien. You can only hide and pray. 

I decide to watch my friends first, each falling (in survival mode) to the Xeno. Keep in mind I just watched my friends die before my very eyes. And I realized: I was next. I was going to die. Like everyone does in this game. 

I start my turn. I hear the Xeno's cry in my headphones. I freeze. I say quietly, "Oh God." It heard through the mic. I heard footsteps. "Oh God." Closer. "Oh God." Closer. "OH GOD!!!"

It looked like the scene from the first movie where the tail dangles down then you see it's face. I saw it's tail in my peripheral vision and turned in time to see it's little mouth. We all promptly screamed then laughed. 

2. My friend was playing. He hid in a locker. He used the motion tracker and saw the alien was nearby. Then we see it walk in front of the locker, and we could see from it's waist up to its head. My friend forgot to hold the "Hold Breath" button. 

It stops straight in front of the locker, turns slowly, and looks directly at it. Our hearts stop. It rips off the door and guts my friend. 

3. Keep in mind this shape of the vents. 

0--|
     |
     |
     |--0     0=vent entrance. 

My friend uses the motion tracker and sees it's nearby, so he jumps in the vent here: 

0--|
     |
     |
     |--0 x     X=friend

And makes his way here:

0-x-|
      |
      |
      |--0 

And uses the motion tracker and realizes the Xeno is patrolling the outside near his current location. He backs up to here:

0--|
     |
     X
     |--0 

And uses the tracker periodically to keep track of the Xeno. Clearly the alien heard the beeping because we immediately see this:

0--A
     |
     X
     |--0       A=Xenomorph

Cue the pause button and us shouting and saying, "Oh, God, God, God!" My friend said, "I'm so dead guys." We spend ten minutes on pause. Five freaking out, five formulating a game plan. The plan was to bring out the flamethrower as soon as it was unpaused, shoot, and GET THE FUCK OUT! Here:

0--A
     |
     X
     |--0  lt;----- GTFO Spot

Then we spent the next 2 minutes reviewing the exact combination of buttons to press. It works, he hides in a locker, for 20 minutes, saying, "I really don't want to move."

4. Last story: I was playing, I hid behind some boxes near the door because the tracker said the Xeno was near. Seconds later, it walks in the room, completely ignoring me, back almost turned to me. I pause. All of our faces look like:
O_o and :O and a combination of the two. 

We come up with my game plan. Very similar to before. Bring out flamethrower, shoot, run to the nearest locker. 

Everyone counts down, "5! 4! 3! 2! 1!"

"I don't wanna!"

Everyone counts down, "5! 4! 3! 2! 1!"

I unpaused, shot, and through the flames, the Xeno's face appears. We all scream as the little mouth takes a bite out of me. 

Funny thing was, I don't think he would've noticed me if I hadn't brought out the flamethrower. When I brought it out, his face appeared like, "GOTCHA!"

Those are my stories with friends. What about you guys?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 04:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd probably use pepperspay as a topping. I like things spicy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If weapons were tasty treats, what would you eat and what would it taste like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 03:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 21:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called the glans on a male. Does the same thing, you just have to clean up afterwards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 21:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes a guy. With a penis. And I prefer to not have my penis contaminated by porta potty air </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 21:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was referring more to the constant discomfort of blue balls and the possibility of changes in personality. When I get blue balls, I get very irritable and frustrated. My testosterone fueled mind constantly thinks of sex and how I can get it. 

I'm not one of those guys that will sleep with any girl for recreation. I only want to have sex with someone I'm in love with. That is a big personality change for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 20:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is, in fact, the male equilvalent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 20:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a guy, I never go to porta potties. I hold it till I get home. The only places I use restrooms are hotels and my home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 20:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comes at a price. Pissing with a boner is the worst </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What part of the opposite gender's anatomy are you envious of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 20:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 17:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instructions unclear: Raped iPhone

Edit: so apparently Reddit doesn't like iPhone rape jokes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 17:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's never too late to spontaneously grow a penis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 15:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever notice how white people are trying to be black? Like, high schoolers and douchebags are sagging, wearing gold chains, and calling each other "Nigga!"

There's this one very white girl at my school that keeps saying "Nigga please" to me. I have to constantly remind her that she's white, and I'm so white I'm almost translucent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 15:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C'mon man. Stop being so Week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 15:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what happens when you cum in your socks too many times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The UFC has organized a "Celebrity Fight Night." Who is on the fight card? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 15:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are six fights on the main card. Who is the Main Event, Co-Main Event, and the other four fights? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 14:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering WWE is choreographed, I'd probably use my Striking and Judo/Jiu-Jitsu experience. I'm a much better striker than grappler, I'm much lighter. Use my evasive footwork to stay out of his range and counterattack. Shots to the liver would be devastating. Once downed by a good liver shot, I'd either throw as many punches to his face as I could, or if he gave up back control, try to sink in a rear naked choke. 

If he tried to go for the double leg takedown, I'd do one of two things: either knee him in the face, or sprawl and sink in a Guillotine choke. 

If he managed to take me down, I'd close up my guard and attempt a submission. I'd say that armbars, kimuras, and omoplatas might not be as effective because he's much stronger, so a Guillotine or triangle choke might do it. 

I'd do my best to keep it off the ground, but if he took me down, I'm confident in my submission skills

Edit: Also leg kicks. Kick the shit out of his legs to reduce mobility </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 04:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I just died a little inside.

Wut

Da

Faq </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 04:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then just FUCK HER RIGHT IN THE PUSSY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 02:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, they're all Comicon Geeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 22:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuthulu? Do tell please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 22:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask what a zauberbiest is? Is it a religion? If so, please tell more. I LOVE learning about new religions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 21:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Xenomorphs from the *Alien* franchise scare the living shit out of me. 

They're essentially unkillable. They can adapt to nearly any environment. They aren't dependent on food, water, or air like us. How the FUCK do they sense their prey?? Everything about Xenomorphs is designed to kill. They use humans as an incubator for reproduction, after the facehuggers rape you down the throat. 

These things terrify me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What fictional creature are you downright terrified of even though you know they can't exist? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 21:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 18:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in mind all the people who care about those people. The kids might get kidnapped. If they survive, they have the opportunity to grow. If they die, more than likely they're going to Heaven. Either way, their parents, family, and friends also have the opportunity to grow. 

Those born mentally retarded... Have you ever met people like that? They're usually some of the nicest people. They're suspended in childlike innocence forever. Like a really young child. Young children that only seem to know Love. Their families and friends struggle with their disabilities. They also have the opportunity to grow. 

My parents were probably just as miserable as me while we dealt with my depression and Aspergers and ADHD. Now that I'm no longer depressed, and my Aspergers is under control, they're filled with such relief. They're the best parents I could ask for. They've grown from the experience as well. Considering I'm their first child, they weren't expecting any of this at all. It's been a positive experience in the end. 

God doesn't create misery. Love provides opportunities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 16:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember hearing about a theory about parallel universes. I believe it applies to this concept as well. The parallel universes are shaped like planes, and every now and then... *boop!* 

The planes touch for a very brief time, therefore allowing interaction. I'm sure something like that does occur. Just enough for God to influence an event and set a chain of events into motion. 

I also think of the Old Norse view of the cosmos. There are nine realms. Midgard is earth, possibly the rest of our universe. Helheim is Hell. Asgard is the realm of the gods (or God). And there are other realms like Alfheim, Vanaheim, Jotunheim, and I believe Svartalfheim. They're linked together through the branches of Yggdrasil, the World Tree. These worlds are separate, but connected. Because they're linked, our souls may move on, possibly not physically, to these other realms. 

Asgard means our souls are enveloped in God's Love. Helheim means we rejected his love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 14:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really use Jesus and God as synonyms. Jesus is Love incarnate. 

I've noticed when you discuss religion with some people, they're more willing to talk about God than Jesus. They might shut down when you talk about Jesus because, historically, he was just a man. So the fact people worship a "regular guy" makes it sound like a cult. 

So I prefer talking to people when they ask about Christianity about God. And really, if I mention Jesus, I'll just summarize the bulk of his teachings, "Do your best. Do your best to be a good person. If at times you fail (and often you will) that's fine. Just never stop trying." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 14:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There isn't any evidence. It's impossible to use evidence from our plane of existence to prove or disprove something from another plane of existence. Which is why science will never prove or disprove God. It's a matter of faith. 

People choose to believe for comfort reasons. That there is someone out there that loves you unconditionally. That you don't really die. 

If people choose not to believe, that's fine. As long as you live a life of Love, you're going to Heaven anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 14:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horrible things happen in life. This is true. Example: very young in life, I dealt with horrible bullying, as well as ADHD, Aspergers, depression, and anxiety. I was miserable. I tried to kill myself. 

But I wouldn't change anything about it. I believe those horrible experiences helped to shape who I am today. God doesn't just make you an awesome person. He lets you choose to be one. He gives you crap to deal with because he wants to see you succeed by yourself. And that is Love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 14:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated before, God doesn't send anyone to Hell. Psychopaths and other mental illnesses I assume must do the best they can. Just like everyone else. We all must do our best and that's all Love asks of us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 14:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you've sinned, you can be forgiven. Doesn't matter how awful the sin, God will forgive, but first you must ask for it. He wants to forgive, but man must make the first move in their relationship with Love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 05:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are people from long ago that we still talk about today. On one end of the spectrum: Buddha, who was supposed to be a really chill dude. On the other: Emperor Caligula of Rome who was Batshit crazy. Two different kinds of immortality, though I think I'd prefer the first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 05:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer to believe because it gives me hope. If you've lived a good life and there's an afterlife, you get to hang in Heaven forever. If you've lived a good life and there is no afterlife, you've still lived an awesome life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 04:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just Kim Jong Un right? They believe he's God over there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 04:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, in Heaven, you're not really praising some old guy. God has no definite form. He's pure spirit. Most Christian denominations teach that God is Love in it's purest form. So when someone is worshipping God, they're worshipping Love. If someone is living a life of Love, then they're living the life God wants them to. 

Heaven is that connection you have with God (Love) at death. If you've accepted Love by the end of your life, you're at peace. You're in Heaven. You're rejoicing in God's Love with everyone else who has accepted it. You're seeing your deceased relatives and friends you've missed so much. Making new friends. And just happy. It's like a new relationship. Super exciting and makes you feel all warm and fuzzy inside. That's my understanding of Heaven. 

Hell, on the other hand, is when someone rejects Love. They choose to hold on to anger, and hate, and hard feelings. Their soul stays that way after death. God doesn't send people to Hell. They send themselves. He wants nothing more than for everyone to make it to Heaven and enjoy Love, but people have to make that choice. Yes, he could make everyone accept Love, but then it wouldn't be real. It's like your mom telling you to love this girl because "she's nice," and yeah, she may be, but your mom forcing you to date her makes the feelings false. God needs us to choose his Love for it to be real. 

As for what Hell is... If you've ever experienced depression, that's a good analogy. It's like depression on steroids. Your soul has rejected Love, and now lives in hate, wrath, and sadness. 

The afterlife is a reflection on how you choose to live your life, and whether you decide to do your best to choose Love. It's a state of the soul, not necessarily physical places. I've always viewed Christianity more as a way of life than a religion. The major thing they teach is Love. Do that, and you'll be fine. Doesn't matter if you've never set foot in a Church. Doesn't even matter if you killed 1000 people and are about to be executed. If right before they zap you, you feel true remorse for what you've done, try to put yourself right with Love, you're gonna be in Heaven. 

TL;DR: I'm a philosophical 18 year old who should be asleep and who studies many different religions and the philosophies of Christianity and have described my beliefs on the Christian afterlife, taking much from Catholic doctrines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 04:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's a hole or can pull, it can be full </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 03:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shrek is love. Shrek is life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 03:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grow them myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 03:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject7254 here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 03:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, 21 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 03:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But did you get it?

And my real question is where do you put Peruvian sex jelly? There are three orifices I can think of </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 03:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cupcakes... And porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 03:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You better take me on a dinner date if you're gonna show me your banana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 02:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be properly warmed up to use a dildo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 01:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That reminds me of the Greek myth of Tantalus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 21:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. I'm gonna broaden the question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 20:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black is cool. I usually wear some kind of black, but I mix it in with other colors. Personally, I wouldn't care what you wore, but other guys might think differently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the craziest thing you know of that a psychopath did? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 20:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: I'm broadening the question. We will include insane things cult leaders have done, insane things people you know have done, and insane things you have done. None of the people have to be legally psychopaths (though it's preferred), just did something considered psychotic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 17:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Copied from a previous post

Figured it was time to share this story on the Internet. Back in the summer before my Freshman year of High School, I loved watching funny YouTube videos. Sanity Not Included was one of my favorites. Being an immature and dumb almost-freshman, the series appealed to all of my comedy interests: vulgarity, sexuality, awkwardness, and things that I didn't really get, but laughed anyway because I felt I was supposed to. 

There was one episode where the dialogue goes:

"What's that sound?"

*shows another character* "Well it wasn't me drawing Hentai and vigorously masturbating... Just saying."

Hentai? What's Hentai?

I was fresh out of Catholic School mind you. Still very naive to the ways of the world. So I turn to my old friend Google. He has all the answers a young pubescent moron could want. Ranging from: "How do I ask out a girl?" To "Funniest cat video ever."

I type in Hentai, and up comes cartoon porn. 

"DAFUQ!!!" I shouted. 

I had never seen porn before. Believe it or not, I just didn't see the big thing about it (at the time). 

First porn I ever see are gifs of Danny Phantom getting it on with his sister, and some weird Japanese chick rubbing her penis. 

I exit out, run to the shower, sit down in the running water, and cry, "Not clean. Not clean."

TL;DR: Was stabbed in the back by my close friend Google and my Catholic upbringing. TIL that Google is Judas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 15:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girls do get crazy on their first period </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 15:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... I think that's me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 19:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello. Thanks for doing this! Big fan here. 

My friend was wanting to know if you were in any relationships at any point with your fellow cast mates. 

My question: since you were a star in one of the world's biggest franchises during most people's most phase of life (age 10-21), what things did you do either during filming or behind the scenes that makes you cringe to this day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have started a tournament to find your perfect SO called the Horny Games. What does the tournament entail and how does someone win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 17:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 13:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone please elaborate on what this is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 05:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To sex or not to sex. That is the question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 05:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not anymore. DUMPED! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 04:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta put yourself *in her*

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 04:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told him. Dump that bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 04:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love can be a poison </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 04:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not cute! I'm manly as hell! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 04:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... Not sure if you're really Tom... On account of username... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 04:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We may have places to go, not necessarily people to see. We're single, remember? :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 04:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can't be that bad man. Right? I mean, if Tom is your bud, you owe it to him to tell him. And if he finds out you knew but didn't tell him, he might hold it against you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 04:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of my Senior class are being senior citizens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 03:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom, whoever and wherever you are, dump that bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 03:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That may also depend on if you had something special with someone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Single people of Reddit, what message do you have for Redditors in relationships? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 03:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 00:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will never look that up again *shiver*

It wasn't a video. It was a gif on the home page </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 00:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and my friends have a fantastic memory of playing that together. We turned the lights out, and played it around 10:00 PM. I went last. I saw each of my friends die before me. The thing about the game is that you know you're gonna die. You don't know when. You don't know how. But it's gonna happen. 

Watching my friends die and knowing what was coming made my heart pound against my chest. I heard the Alien. I say "Oh God. Oh God. Oh God. OH GOD!"

It hears me through the mic. You see a tail swing in my peripheral vision. Next thing I know, I'm impaled by that tail and me and all my friends are screaming and laughing. 

It really looked like something from a horror movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 05:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The twin children of Hermes, being the god of traveling and communication

Wifidite-Goddess of Fast Wifi

Neoteles-God of Slow Wifi and Thrown Phones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what is the best revenge story you have for getting back at your bully? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 05:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 05:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been a while since I've seen a "Shit myself" post on this subreddit. 

Ah, memories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were a Greek God, what would you have your priests sacrifice to you to freak them out the most? [possibly NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 05:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 05:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/TIFU

It went through a couple of phases however. It had a "TIFU (Today I Fucked Up) by shitting myself" phase at one point. Then a "TIFU by having sex" phase. Now it's still kind of in the sex phase. But overall the stories are pretty good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 05:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! Harry Potter. Always </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 04:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *I love everyone, even people I hate*

Wut? 

Hate is the absence of love. Like, that's textbook definition. Hate is a state of mind where the person has no love for a person, object, or idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by not knowing what Hentai was... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 03:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Figured it was time to share this story on the Internet. Back in the summer before my Freshman year of High School, I loved watching funny YouTube videos. Sanity Not Included was one of my favorites. Being an immature and dumb almost-freshman, the series appealed to all of my comedy interests: vulgarity, sexuality, awkwardness, and things that I didn't really get, but laughed anyway because I felt I was supposed to. 

There was one episode where the dialogue goes:

"What's that sound?"

*shows another character* "Well it wasn't me drawing Hentai and vigorously masturbating... Just saying."

Hentai? What's Hentai?

I was fresh out of Catholic School mind you. Still very naive to the ways of the world. So I turn to my old friend Google. He has all the answers a young pubescent moron could want. Ranging from: "How do I ask out a girl?" To "Funniest cat video ever."

I type in Hentai, and up comes cartoon porn. 

"DAFUQ!!!" I shouted. 

I had never seen porn before. Believe it or not, I just didn't see the big thing about it (at the time). 

First porn I ever see are gifs of Danny Phantom getting it on with his sister, and some weird Japanese chick rubbing her penis. 

I exit out, run to the shower, sit down in the running water, and cry, "Not clean. Not clean."

TL;DR: Was stabbed in the back by my close friend Google and my Catholic upbringing. TIL that Google is Judas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what is your drive? What drives you to do your best every day? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 03:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the greatest birthday gift you ever gave/received? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 19:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can be anything from something you've kept to this day or something hilarious that made everyone laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 05:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit is the only place where Jesus can be compared to Voldemort.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 04:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awkward boners. 

"Is that a wand in your pocket or are you just happy to see me?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MMA at Hogwarts! As both an MMA and Harry Potter fan, I'm absolutely in love with this! :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 04:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 23:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel constantly pissed off and depressed. Not quite at the level I used to, but I'm not used to it and I don't know why I feel this way. 

http://www.reddit.com/r/AMA/comments/2dcld3/when_i_was_younger_i_was_diagnosed_with/

This is a link to an AMA I did a while back for adults wanting to know about my previous experience with depression. I haven't felt like this in years. Yes I've asked myself why I feel this way. Nothing. Zippo. Zippidy-doo-da. No idea. Constantly bored with life. Not to the point where I'm considering suicide, but I just don't feel good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for a Harry Potter inspired yearbook quote. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 16:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily a quote from the books, but something funny inspired by the books. Saw one online: "Master has given Megan a diploma! Megan is free!"

Anything that would get a chuckle from people reading it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 05:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOVE those movies! Not really sad though. I'm curious, why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 04:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kill all the humans you want, just DON'T FUCKING TOUCH THE DOG!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 04:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally for me, it's The Fault in Our Stars. I cried in front of my gf at the time when we saw it in theaters. We both cried. So sad... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie besides The Notebook makes you cry every time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 04:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 03:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say THAT bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 22:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He paints a picture that the evil thing he wants you to do will turn out absolutely fantastic. In a way, that is a hallucination </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 16:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of the inspiration also came from the Greeks Tartarus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 16:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superdevilnado </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 16:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes demonic entities can possess the human body. However, I don't think it's that they are controlling you. The three stages of possession are 

1) infestation 
2) oppression
3) possession

Infestation means the demon becomes attached to you. Oppression is when they wear you down emotionally and spiritually. Possession is when you do what they want. However, I don't think they are forcing you to do anything. You still have your free will. It's just because of the Oppression stage wearing you down so, that you give in to the temptations of Satan and his demons more easily. If you've ever heard accounts of possession and Oppression, you'll notice they're depressed severely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 05:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superdevil. Sounds like a bad Syfy movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 05:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Satan's a deity. He's a fallen angel, therefore immortal. However, he has no powers that a deity possesses. He doesn't manipulate any part of nature. He doesn't even have the power to make humans do evil things. He just whispers in your ear, "You should get back at Phil. He keyed your car. What are you waiting for?"

Edit: This is from my comment later in the thread regarding possession

Yes demonic entities can possess the human body. However, I don't think it's that they are controlling you. The three stages of possession are 

1) infestation 
2) oppression
3) possession

Infestation means the demon becomes attached to you. Oppression is when they wear you down emotionally and spiritually. Possession is when you do what they want. However, I don't think they are forcing you to do anything. You still have your free will. It's just because of the Oppression stage wearing you down so, that you give in to the temptations of Satan and his demons more easily. If you've ever heard accounts of possession and Oppression, you'll notice they're depressed severely

I would add to this that people who are depressed (which I have experienced) are somewhat more prone to misbehavior. Worn down spiritually and emotionally to the point wear you give up on what's right and wrong. There have been cases where someone possessed had told the demon to leave and, in the ensuing spiritual battle, the demon does leave, defeated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 05:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bitch! 

... I wanted to feel like I contributed... Bitch... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 05:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So says the God of NSA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 05:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You right. Cheeto fingers suck. Dorito fingers are God's gift to humanity however </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 05:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cocaine, hookers, and Ebola for all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 21:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no. I love talking. I just don't talk about my personal life. I don't think you'd really want to answer questions regarding your sexual orientation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 16:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If having a dick shoved up your ass tickles, then something's up... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 16:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disappointment if they have their own USB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 16:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spongebob? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 16:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sound of the woman who cuts my hair's voice. For some reason, everyone who cuts hair insists on talking nonstop. 

Don't get me wrong. She's a family friend. She's so nice. I just hate the sound of her voice. She sounds like Female Squidward. 

She asks me very personal questions too. Things I just don't want to talk about. So normally I give one word responses and she just drones on constantly. 

ATTENTION BARBERS/HAIR SALON PEOPLE OF REDDIT: I speak for most men when I say I'm perfectly comfortable sitting in silence while you do your thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you do when you don't know what to do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 04:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 18:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I currently train Youn Wha. Thing is, Grandmaster Han's Organization quickly became a McDojo. He started taking most of the money for himself. So, several Masters, some I trained with personally, each started their own organizations. They split off from Grandmaster Han and called themselves different Organizations. Traditional Youn Wha, Youn Wha Ryu Federation, etc. I'm with Traditional Youn Wha. All the sister organizations still get together for tournaments and stuff though. 

As for the training, it can be very effective. I'd say the training is roughly 75 % Taekwondo, 24 % Judo, and the other 1% is split between Hapkido, Jiu Jitsu, Kung Fu, Aikido, and Karate. It's certainly a mixed martial art, but it's not MMA training if that makes sense. 

The sparring is point based. Kicks to side of the head and body, hand techniques to the body only. You wear gear like you see in Taekwondo in the Olympics. 

Going with Grandmaster Han's Organization would mean your school isn't as well funded. The sister organizations provide better funding and overall better teachers I'd say. The Masters in charge of Traditional Youn Wha draw experience from training with other schools too, then come back and teach their students what they learned. Like, 4 times a year, Royce Gracie comes to the St. Louis area and teaches BJJ. The masters go and any student is welcome to learn as well. These masters went to Las Vegas earlier in the summer for the martial arts expo and trained with all sorts of people from the UFC. 

You must learn forms to advance in rank, but, even though most people say forms are useless, and they are not my favorite part of classes, they do help you learn control. Help you put that punch or kick exactly where you want it. 

It's a great style, as long as you pick the right Organization. Been training for 3 years. I mostly refer to it as Taekwondo, since that's what most of the classes consist of. However, the higher in rank you get, the more grappling is involved. Also, just like any other martial art, the only way to get good at it is to keep it up and do your best.  

TL;DR: I've trained Youn Wha for 3 years, I love my specific organization, a lot of people, especially the instructors, can really kick ass, but be careful about joining Grandmaster Han's Organization. Stick to the ones that split off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 04:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he liked it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 04:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While going through puberty, you are constantly horny and want sex, but nature's cruel enough to make you so ugly you can't get sex. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 04:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 04:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freaking middle schoolers/freshmen. 

For the most part, they're rude, obnoxious, immature, bullies, and think that doing all those things makes you cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 21:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technique really is the biggest thing I'd say. The better technique you have, the more efficient you are with your movements. Strength training helps build up the strength, but using it in a technique requires training. 

I remember reading an article (don't have the link) where Georges St-Pierre said his Muay Thai coach was overweight, smoked like a chimney, had a poor diet, etc. His coach could still kick the crap out of him and all the other students. It was because he was efficient in all his movements </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 21:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use compound weight training exercises. I try to hit as many muscle groups as I can so my body works great as a whole, and not just the individual muscles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 21:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lesnar is a freak of nature. He cut weight to make the 264 lb division and still moved like a jackrabbit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 17:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need it warm for a turd burger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 17:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feeling *him* intensifies. 

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 15:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a family story, but a town one. It involves a black Nazi. 

First off, yes he's black. Yes, he's a Nazi. And yes, the dude's psycho. He's a legit black Nazi. He wears swastikas. He has the uniform. He even has a Hitler stach. He thinks he's Hitler reincarnated. He lived in the trailer park. He was also a bodybuilder, so the dude was ripped. 

One of my classmates worked at the local Walmart. She was a cashier. One day, the Nazi was in Walmart wearing a large coat. She thinks, "Oh no. It's him." He comes up to her at the register and whispers, "Hey! Psst. Wanna buy a VCR? I got VCR's in my truck." She politely declines. 

He reaches into his coat and she thinks, "Oh no, he's got a gun."

He takes out a bar of soap and throws it at her. "Fine! I don't want your soap then!" (To be honest, I'm not sure if it was soap or not. It's been a while since I heard her tell the story. It might have been gum or something, but I do remember it was a ridiculous object.)

He runs off. Security runs after him. He beats the crap out of them. The cops show up, he beats up two cops while being tased. The taser doesn't even faze him. 

He's eventually subdued and I believe he's currently in prison

TL;DR: crazy black Nazi tried to sell VCR's, threw soap, beat up security and two cops, taser energized him, Hulk Smash, is currently in prison </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 14:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impressive!

Edit: thought of another

Can you feel it Mr. Krabs!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, can we discuss your theories on the biology of Xenomorphs? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 14:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, Xenomorphs from the *Alien* franchise are weird creatures. I'd like to discuss biological aspects of their existence. Such as: if they never eat their prey, how do they acquire energy to metabolize? Why do they kill just to kill? 

Any questions you've asked yourself about the Aliens but never thought of an answer would also contribute to the thread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What, from your experience, should you never Google? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 20:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 19:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been getting into Judo for the last 6-8 months. I have a training partner at my TKD school who had some experience in Judo before. Mostly what we do is we get to class an hour early and have our own "class". Just us, practicing Judo takedowns and ground game. Something awesome that he did (that I get a kick out of) is he made me a *syllabus*. He found this video (http://youtu.be/J6xiq-RKhCg) that has all the most common takedowns and went through it and wrote the Japanese name of the technique and the English translation, as well as a short description. He also marked what time in the video each technique is at. It's a fantastic video. Check it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 19:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really does depend on the school. But also depends on yourself. 

My TKD school has some younger kids. But it also has a bunch of teens. Kids 14-18 years old. Also this one guy whose 39 who has the HARDEST elbows out there. 

Most of the time, we spar people our age/height. You'll see these kids who are 7-11 years old really going at it. The teens (myself included, as well as the 39 year old most of the time) push each other VERY hard. We all have our own styles of fighting that we developed sparring each other. 

One girl always blocks and counters. A guy is a pressure fighter. Always comes at you and rarely takes a step back, and utilizes punches more than kicks. Another girl fights similar to the guy: applies pressure (while throwing in spinning elbows). The 39 year old is very calculating. Then there's me who circles opponents, constantly switches between orthodox and southpaw, applies pressure and a fast pace, and uses flashy unorthodox techniques to catch people off guard. 

We don't spar soft. We don't pull punches because we realize that we're taking away from each other's training when we do. I can't remember the last time I left a sparring night without an injury of some kind. 

TKD is a fantastic striking art. The problem you faced is finding training partners to push you to your limit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 06:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the sequel. "The Second One" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 06:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love YouTube.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 06:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 05:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ma'am, allow me to make it up to you with our... *Premium Package*

*Bow-Chicka-Bow-Wow* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 02:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a fist can fit, your duckdick will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 02:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a fist can fit, your duckdick will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 01:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the added info of your username, I assume a rubber ducky is what you use as condoms, correct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 01:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While masturbating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 01:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like... Off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 01:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go on... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, have you ever injured yourself masturbating? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 01:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 17:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst kind of boner (or best, depending on how you look at it) is the kind that ache. Like it's almost painful so much blood fills the penis. It throbs, your mind is full of testosterone. The testosterone fills you with so much passion that you feel you will die if you don't release. You start looking at every girl you see. It doesn't matter if you're absolutely in love with someone. The lust doesn't mean that you love them any less. It just means you have a hunger that needs to be filled. 

Something that I read somewhere on Reddit described men and women's views of sex/orgasm pretty well. For men, it's like eating a big steak. For women, it's like enjoying a chocolate Sundae </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 17:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will not lie, that was probably the worst time of my life. I was very suicidal then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you see posted on Facebook that made you cringe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-10 02:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
