<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6292</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 16:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, you know... Went home, called parents, called lawyer, started trying to sort it out. Took almost a month to get in front of a judge, and they gave me the time back. Of course, with young children, there is no real making up for missed time, but... It was still nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 17:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A tube of tinfoil from which was squeezed a shit-brown substance interspersed with what looked to be a vaguely yellowish-brown runny fluid. Made me gag at the sight of it.

Turned out it was a wad of chocolate fudge loosely mixed with caramel. He let me try some, it was delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 17:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When being confronted by a ranting, raving, screaming man threatening me and my livelihood in a public place, I managed to stay calm, logical, and not react negatively to his spitting anger. I don't care that it's not exciting, it takes a real badass to stay level-headed in that situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 14:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem! And hey, if you try that out and decide you like it, the author has another series out called the Codex Alera. Haven't read it yet, but I hear good things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 14:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a series of novels, about 15 books long right now, with the next one coming out in may. It's also a TV show, only aired for one season in 2010, though. Definitely worth your time, but I'll warn you now: if you don't like the pacing of the first few books, it picks up significantly after the 4th/5th novels. That's about when Jim Butcher (the author) got established enough to risk writing in his own style - which I think is significantly better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 14:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kung Pao: Enter the Fist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 14:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay a while, you'll love it here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 14:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Dresden Files series has a lot of breaks like this, and I love 'em all. I wish I could think of any to quote specifically, but they always get me laughing.

There's one part where Dresden does something that gets pointed out as pretty stupid, and he "turns" to the reader and says "What? It's been a long day, and I'm not making great decisions after all that. I'd like to see you do better in this situation."

Or, you know, something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> _hick-Fil-A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Float On by Modest Mouse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being the only sober person at my bachelor party, having to try and control a rowdy drunk because nobody else is able to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chili cheese fries and beer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and that's when I decided to buy the horse a hooker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A smaller statue of liberty. Holding a smaller statue of liberty. ^holding ^a ^smaller ^statue ^of ^liberty ^^holding ^^a ^^smaller ^^statue ^^of ^^liberty^holding ^^^a ^^^smaller ^^^statue ^^^of ^^^liberty^holding ^^^^a ^^^^smaller ^^^^statue ^^^^of ^^^^liberty^holding ^^^^^a ^^^^^smaller ^^^^^statue ^^^^^of ^^^^^liberty^holding ^^^^^^a ^^^^^^smaller ^^^^^^statue ^^^^^^of ^^^^^^liberty^holding ^^^^^^^a ^^^^^^^smaller ^^^^^^^statue ^^^^^^^of ^^^^^^^liberty^I ^^^^^^^^think ^^^^^^^^you ^^^^^^^^know ^^^^^^^^where ^^^^^^^^I'm ^^^^^^^^going ^^^^^^^^with ^^^^^^^^this ^^^^^^^^by ^^^^^^^^now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Answer dozens of silly questions on AskReddit from people who have nothing better to do with their time than I do right now.

Also, porn. There is lots of it being viewed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former WalMart employee here.

I was the cart wrangler for a WalMart in San Antonio. Not "a" cart wrangler, mind. "The" cart wrangler. The only other person hired to do my job was mentally challenged, and never actually did anything on his shift. I know, because I had to clean up his mess, and got heat from management when I tried to get the man to actually work.

Aside from that, though, my biggest complaint about WalMart is the cashiers. Everyone - EVERYONE - in the store is cashier trained so that long lines can be taken down as needed. Thing is, they never use people that way. The cashiers are cashiers, everyone else works where they're assigned. 

Although, if you spot a manager and mention this tidbit of knowledge, you'd be surprised just how quickly they'll get another lane or two open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope and tenacity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would have been easy to give up, but I didn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try not to worry about things you can't control; but, if you can take control, do so without hesitation, for the biggest regrets you will ever have in life will always stem from the things you wish you had done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emotional: Going to pick up my daughter from daycare, to find that my ex wife had un-enrolled her without telling me, told the workers there (who knew me and knew better) that I was abusive and untrustworthy around my child. Worse, when I called to try and talk to her about it, she called the cops. Never even told me why she wasn't letting me see my kid.

I actually collapsed onto the floor from the sudden heart-stopping grief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totes. As in "OMG, Julie, this dress it totes fabs, found it at a cray sale."

...also, most of that sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ice Breakers wintergreen mints.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serious answer here. Instead of wadding up the paper and prodding at the problem area, just take a few sheets and fold them over each other. 3-4 sheets, tops. Then, use your fingers to press the paper against yourself, effectively scraping loose all the accumulation. 

I used to have the same problem you're describing before I started using this technique. Now a roll will last me a week or two, rather than a few days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any size container.

1/2 orange/pineapple/apple juice (Welch's makes this mix... I think.)
Split the rest with vodka and triple sec
Dash of grenadine, for color.

Liquor burn vanishes, and it f*cks you up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remake: The Princess Bride (closer to the book)

Never remake: The Fifth Element </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 13:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally, from what I've seen, it's the audience's own preconceived notions of how the storytelling should be handled. These days, a video game is usually a cinematic experience in its own right. Because of this, fans of the game (who would make up the core audience of the movie based on said game) go into the film expecting more of the EXACT SAME STORY THEY ALREADY KNOW. When they find that the director took the good story and ran with it in a different direction, they tend to react poorly, feeling personally betrayed that the director allowed such a "travesty" to happen.

This is why I always try to go into any new movie with as few expectations as I can. If you can convince yourself not to expect any specific thing, you'll often be surprised how enjoyable many things can become. For example, I knew nothing of Resident Evil when I first saw the movies. They weren't great movies, but pretty decent shoot-em-ups after the first one. I liked the Super Mario Bros movie, even though it was only vaguely related to the games. 

Hell, I liked World War Z. The book *and* the movie. I just treated them as separate entities, and found a lot of good in both.

I should make a puffin from this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 12:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost all animals eat other animals. Why should we be any different? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 12:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about anyone else, but I cringed at your unnecessary usage of quotation marks. Using them the way you did implies that you mean the term "phrase" hypothetically, or perhaps sarcastically, which is honestly a concept I can't really make sense of. 

Seriously, what happened to the grammar Nazis on this site? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 17:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She took it in stride. It's my sister, remember; mostly she was just upset that someone had done that at *her* base.

Made myself feel like a dick, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 17:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look at where I-35 crosses into Mexico (Texas map), the border crossing looks like a huge sad face. What makes it funnier is the crowd of cars south of the border, and the empty roads north of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keyboard shortcuts!

Ctrl+f = find text

Ctrl+c = copy 

Ctrl+x = cut 

Ctrl+v = paste 

Ctrl+b = bold text

Ctrl+u = underline text

Ctrl+i = italicize text

Ctrl+del = delete word/character string

Ctrl+backspace = same as above

Shift+arrow keys = highlight text

LESS KNOWN

"Windows" key+arrow keys = shifts current window to fit either the whole screen, left half, or right half, or minimize.

Ctrl+shift+esc = open task manager

Ctrl+shift+t = reopen closed tab

Ctrl+w = close current tab/window


There are probably more, but I can't remember them right now. These ones are extremely useful to me, though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I choose B.

Pitfalls of A: It doesn't say all at once, meaning it's likely that many of those multiple deep, intimate, loving, romantic relationships will end with tragedy and heartbreak. I've had quite enough of that, thank you.

B says, flat out, one person for the rest of my life. That's the plan for my wife and I.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Day after the recent shooting at fort hood, talking to my sister who works there.

"So, how's the weather down there? I heard you guys had an unexpected lead shower yesterday."

...I am not a smart man. Please don't hate, you asked for inappropriate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found $117 floating in a swimming pool once when I was a kid. Two ones, a five, a ten, and a hundred.

My mom didn't let me keep it, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not wrong, you're just wasting your time. This is an opinion thread, and you're not likely to change what OP likes/dislikes with your explanation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can slip my arms behind by back while holding my hands together.

Sounds easy, but try it. Go on, hold you hands above your head, then move them to your butt without letting them go.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> acquired taste is more what I was going for. Unpleasant at first, improves as you go on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in high school, girl was ragging. Didn't care, we went after it anyway. She was on top. When we finished, she lifted herself up off of me, and our intermingling juices slipped out of her and plopped into my belly button. It looked like raspberry jam. We called it belly-button-jelly. It was singly the most disgusting thing I've ever experienced in the bedroom. I have a deep belly button, so I was picking dried mense and spoo out of there for a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit.

Redditors can't stop talking about Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a spoon, a palm-and-a-half folding knife, nail clippers, a large incense burner, forty-pound barbell, and a steel coffee mug with a spill-proof locking lid. I'd say I'm pretty set.

Also, I need to clean up next to my chair. Geez. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I heard that cows' tongues are, like, really sticky? And if they lick you, they'll swallow you."

Girl I used to work with. I have no idea how she survived this long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to get used to. I wish I could give you a useful technique for controlling that anxiety, but to be perfectly honest, it's just something that get's easier the more you do it. Like drinking beer, or coffee, it just isn't great at first, but the more you have, the easier it gets, until eventually you realize that it doesn't even bother you anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me, my dick, and Irene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine a place where a few people put things on display, thousands more judge those people for it, and anything original gets ignored until people have already seen it a few times, at which point it is first bathed in flaming hatred, and then heralded as a brilliant work; also, cats and porn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody will ever judge you as harshly as you judge yourself. Just remember, in their minds, they're probably worried about the same things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 16:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Introvert here, Jedi4Hire is telling the truth. Six years ago I hated talking on the phone, would put it off as long as I could, and could never figure out what to say. Always felt like I was somehow intruding on the person I had to call. 

They forced me to take/make calls at work. Important calls. Time-sensitive, too. It sucked.

Anyway, long story short, now I can make calls with little to no problem... but sometimes I still put it off. I don't like it any better, it's just become a matter of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 15:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not me personally, but it directly affected me when this *sshole broke the bro code.

I met a guy at work who was having some pretty significant troubles. I won't go into detail about what they were, but it was clear that the guy could use a friend. So, I started talking to him, figuring stuff out, giving advice, etc. It seemed to be helping a lot, and so my bosses decided to let me be his "de-facto" supervisor, given that we'd already established a decent rapport. No big deal, nothing really changed. For a while.

See, around that time I was going through a divorce and custody battle. My ex-wife had just split up with the guy she'd been with since I'd filed for divorce, and I made the mistake of asking this other guy to help me pick up my stuff from the pre-divorce house. I didn't think anything of it, really, until a few weeks later.

I noticed the guy seemed extremely conflicted, holding back explainations where he would have shared them before. I couldn't figure out what the problem was, though, so I went to some other coworkers to ask if they knew anything about what was going on.

The guy was dating my ex wife. During a custody battle. And they were engaged.

They got married in less than eight months.

During a custody battle for my three year old daughter.

Yeah. Bro code=shattered.

On the plus side, I won custody. So I've got that going for me. Which is nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 15:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shower-bath. I combine them.

Comforting warm-water embrace of a bath, *and* the soothing sound and feel of the shower water. Also, this pretty much eliminates the cold air problem for any body part outside of the bath water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 15:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two parter:
"What does 'burial at sea' mean?"

answered: It's where they bury you at sea.

"You mean, like, in the water?"
****facepalm**** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 09:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having just finished writing for 1.5 hours after my brain got me up at 1 AM with a way forward in my story, I can honestly say I feel at least a portion of your pain. But, at least it's friday.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 06:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Randomly screaming "I'm a douchebag!"

Jerks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 17:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went through this a few years ago. I recall the day I recognized the signs of depression in myself, and that very recognition made everything substantially worse, nuking my motivation and sense of self worth. I somehow managed to get myself to call my supervisor, just said right off "I think I'm depressed, I need to see someone." 

Next morning, I was sitting in a confidential mental health session, left it with a new bottle of antidepressants and a faint gleam of hope I didn't dare look at yet.

Of course, after all that drama, I learned that you can self-refer to mental health with no middle man. At my base, they said if you walk in and say you're experiencing depression symptoms and ask to be seen, they have to get you in as soon as possible, especially on the first visit.

Do what you've got to do, man, but step one is just getting the nerve up to tell someone. I know it doesn't make sense, but you'll be more highly regarded for self-identifying than for toughing it out in silence.

EDIT: Forgot to mention, by self-referring to Mental Health, there are no negative consequences (Air Force, anyway). The only negatives that will happen are if you are referred by Leadership, or if you display significant tendencies toward violence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 15:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yawned just before clicking this link, now I feel like I made the prerecorded internet sloth yawn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 15:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Johnny Depp and Bruce Willis.

Might've made a better Die Hard than the latest one, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 14:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would take my wife out often, stock the house with healthy food, work on writing a novel, play video games till my eyes bleed, and devote all remaining time to doing my absolute best to raise my daughter as well as I possibly can.

You know, in a nutshell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 14:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sudden realization, through a fog of anti depressants, that we had agreed to sleep with other people, and had both done so, and it didn't really matter. This realization was following a phone call in which she described having one of my coworkers inside her, and I didn't care.

A marriage is pretty much dead at that point. And I'm glad. 

Believe it or not, though, it only got worse from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 02:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With this comment, you kept me from disappointment. Thank you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 15:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ICO

8 hours in, came across a puzzle where there was a rope on one side of a gap. I knew I needed to swing across, but I had no idea how to swing on a rope. Tried every button, to no avail. Used copy, so no user manual to help me. 5 minutes of frustration and 20 seconds of googling later, I learned that I needed to hold the circle button to swing. HOLD the damn button. And no in-game tutorial to even give a clue.

Other than that, I made it to the last stage of a shooter once before I realized that I could aim down the sights. Can't recall which one. 

Also, got 3/4 the way through Uncharted 3 before discovering the reload button. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-29 16:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My last playthrough, I got arrested outside of whiterun. Came up in the prison, completely bypassed the gate guard. Worth a shot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 18:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, fruit. No prep, no waiting.

Probably grapes. Or apples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 17:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fond of subtle evilness. Got anything like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 16:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carry a small amount of BBs and a tube of super glue all the time

Encounter douchey parker 

*JUSTICE MODE ENGAGE*

Remove tire caps

place drop of super glue into cap, followed by BB

Replace cap

Repeat for each tire

Laugh evilly to self </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 03:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but that's why I'm a little more hopeful now. Him giving updates means he's ready for the work to be seen. Maybe an update will happen soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 06:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed what I really hope to be a real trend, in which Wollay doesn't post things until he has something to show, and usually that's right before it goes live. Case in point, shortly after he posted that he was making his own site for Cubeworld, said site went live. Within a few weeks of that site appearing, the game itself went live. So, hopefully this is a real trend, and these screenshots/updates mean that the new version will be posting soon.

Fingers crossed! (hopes low.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 01:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every other comment I see on here seems a bit jaded, so I'm gonna try for an unbiased answer for you.

If you like exploring for hours on end through any number of endless worlds, following your own ends, then this game will likely be enjoyable for you.

However, it is currently lacking in content and polish. That said, it has many more features than most games that provide access at this point in development. It's fluid, though not without bugs/flaws. It can handily occupy most of your day if you let it, but it is definitely unbalanced no matter how far you progress.

As far as content updates, they are few and far between. It looks like Wollay is averaging 1-2 a year, optimistically speaking. So, if you want something that will grow rapidly, stick with Starbound or Terraria, and come back to this later. 

Just pointing out here, though: Alpha buy in price is normally smaller than finished price. I, for one, saw the promise of the game and threw down the $20 buy in just so I can get the finished version for less - much like I did for minecraft. 

So, there's the facts. Make your choice. I would like to request, though, that if you do decide to buy in, please don't be the guy who grumps about the lack of updates. It's basically one person building the game (Pixxie is really only building the voxel sprites, from what I understand, though I am likely mistaken), so you can't expect much in terms of speed. So far, quality is their aim, and their only failing so far has been communication... though they seem to be getting better about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 03:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I've ever upvoted harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 00:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dog is a cat. Seriously. Looks like a dog. Acts like a cat.

Except for coming when called. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 00:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair point. In any case, OP calling someone ignorant because they won't maintain eye contact is, itself, an act of ignorance.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 19:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it has. Let's see you do what Wollay's done, by yourself, in less time, huh? Or perhaps move on to another game, one with more frequent updates. I hear Terraria just updated again, go there for your instant gratification. Meanwhile, I'll continue waiting for quality content here. Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 19:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually, hunting for excuses to label others as ignorant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 19:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say this necessarily says ignorance. Duplicitousness, perhaps. People tend to avoid eye contact while fabricating lies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 19:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game being developed by many people, using small scale 2-d sprites, where the average world size is many times larger than the actual game files, doesn't take nearly as much effort to create an update as a game being created by 2 people, in a full 3-d environment that must flow naturally. Coding one character, made of blocks, in a 3-d realm takes much more time and effort than coding one character made of several pixels in a 2-d realm. Wollay's also adding a number of different enemies, creatures, and biomes, as well as modifying AI and quest generation. For ONE PERSON, I'm not surprised it takes 20x longer than Starbound's entire workforce.

Perspective. Seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 03:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Creating successful comments on Reddit threads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 03:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mini-usb charging cable for owners of Apple devices.

Ipod charging cable for everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 14:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We both spent the whole night (first date) saying no sex. Keep it simple, get to know each other, no sex. That night: Sex. 

Caught me COMPLETELY off guard.

And was amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 04:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would not say this man was a terrible actor, but...

The Lone Ranger: Johnny Depp as Tonto.

Or should I say, The Tonto Movie: Jack Sparrow tries to sound like an indian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 15:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why, yes! Yes I am! Thank you for noticing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 13:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. I have no experience with drugs. Don't judge me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 02:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL things said to perfectly sober kids sound an awful lot like things that may need to be said to people on acid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 02:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else find it odd that this feline's namesake is a creature his species eats? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 01:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for pointing that out. Re-math'd it, and looking at what I actually spend it's closer to $2000, but that's still pretty significant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 15:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pack a lunch. Here's why:

Cost of lunch: $8-$15, depending on where you go. Call it midrange, $10.
5 days a week - $50
52 weeks a year - $2700.
My personal lunch budget runs around $10 a week, times 52 is still approx. $2180 savings

Just over $2 thousand saved by packing a sandwich.

Not to mention gas saved not driving to the restaurant.

EDIT: Quick-math betrayed me, there's 52 weeks to account for, not 48. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 15:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard Candy.

Trying for spoiler free here...

I know the kid is supposed to be the "good" one, but her twisted methodology made me forget what the "bad guy" did. I actually wanted her to lose, especially after the surgery scene.

If you haven't seen it, think "to catch a predator" only change out Chris Hansen for a preteen girl with extremely fucked up methods to get the bad guy to confess   atone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 23:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact not many people consider: 10 cents less per gallon only save $1.00 if you get 10 gallons. My car has a 12 gallon tank. Gas prices locally tend to vary only 4-8 cents. I don't even care what gas station I go to anymore since I realized that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 06:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been near where you are now. Not as bad, but pretty near in a different way. I can share what helped me through, if you care to listen.

I know it sounds contrived, but try to focus on the good, the positive. Start as small as you like and try and look bigger.

A small example, based on your post and starting with the simplest things I see: You woke up (still alive) you're healthy, you have a job. Your family is still there, and it looks like they're going to stay around. You're all healthy. 

There's lots of good to be found in any bad situation, and if you can take a moment when you're overwhelmed to find the good, it can often help you through the worst times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 06:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The term "YOLO" and everything associated with it since it's conception.

NOTE: Leave "You only live once" alone. That was fine before SOMEbody messed with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 06:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TD/DR Up top: I changed, she didn't.

Married high school sweetheart. She refused to work. Could not hold a job. Couldn't complete anything she began, be it looking for work, getting her GED/diploma (scheduled test once, didn't go 'cause she didn't feel like it, never bothered rescheduling) or even simple household chores (when I moved out in the end, found several shirts on the bottom of the laundry pile I hadn't seen in months, one of which had been missing since before we moved into that house the year prior - that's right, the dirty laundry got so backed up it migrated houses) and would get mad at me when I tried to do housework and pick up the slack because that's "her" job. Selfish, self righteous, incapable of mistakes or being wrong in any capacity whatsoever. Frequent arguments would occur in which we both identify things about the other person that are frustrating/irritating and need to be worked on, and she would make 1 day's effort to display corrective action before reverting. 

Tried for years to make it work. I changed, she didn't. I grew up, she stayed 16. We divorced. And it only got worse from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 05:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're unhappy, but don't change anything, the only thing that will change is that you'll slowly become more unhappy.

--Myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 13:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [www.supercook.com](www.supercook.com)

Thanks, Actual Advice Mallard!

Seriously, since that meme posted a couple days ago I've had three delicious meals I didn't know I had the ingredients for, which took less than twenty minutes to prep, cook, and serve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 00:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not cute. You're stupid. 

Or:

Trying to talk "street" makes you sound more douchey than cool.

Or, my big one:

Saggin' your pants was a trend started in prison. It showed the other inmates that you were "open for business." In other words, those pants around your knees would mean you're ready to be raped by Douglas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 14:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1: Wasn't nicely. Reddit got the cliff notes version.

2: Decade ago, been married a while now to someone who doesn't play games. 



Don't think you know me, random redditor. You don't know me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
