<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1966</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not an asshole, you're a troll getting its kicks. If you aren't a troll, you're just an idiot with a keyboard and too much free time. You can argue about it to your heart's content, but if you were just some asshole, you wouldn't care enough to argue.

Go jill off some place else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, future people* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry your gf's dog dumped you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Chemical Romance's first album, "I brought you my bullets, you brought me your love," otherwise known as the Bullets era, and a few of the songs therein, especially "Demolition Lovers".

Excerpts from the song dealing with bullets

"Hand in mine into your icy blues,
and then i say to you,
We can take to the highway 
With this trunk of ammunition, too
I'd end my days with you
In a hail of bullets"

"All we are, all we are, is bullets I mean this
All we are, all we are, is bullets I mean this
All we are, all we are, is bullets I mean this
All we are, all we are, is bullets I mean this,
 
As lead rains, will pass on through our phantoms
Forever, forever
Like scarecrows that fuel this flame we're burning
Forever, and ever
Know how much I want to show you you're the only one
Like a bed of roses there's a dozen reasons in this gun

And as we're falling down, and in this pool of blood
And as we're touching hands, and as we're falling down
And in this pool of blood, and as we're falling down
I'll see your eyes, and in this pool of blood
I'll meet your eyes, I mean this forever"



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beerus and Champa are probably based on anubis,  an Egyptian god that was sort of a guardian of the dead similar to Charon, at least in design. They're probably also based on the eastern religion in some way, but im not really educated on that, so..

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 02:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im new too. On basilisk, currently trainng marksman and scout skills. Ill be off work in a few hours if you want to meet up. Started on tattooine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
