<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1260</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which version is the definitive version? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 10:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which version of the game will be the best one? Are there any differences between any? I imagine the Wii U onehaving gamepad functionality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MFW someone else snags a reaction pic I was going to use </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who changed their name in adulthood, what did you change it to and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 15:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dan Avidaniel Avidan Helped me with depress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 11:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arien Die In SoopEr Mahrio. Make me sad. Windwake 19 help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What console do you play on and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 20:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do more people play on ps4 or xbone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 12:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the GTA series and this is a pivotal question about which console I should get </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Against all odds I really enjoy the GTA steam train series </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 12:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I avoided it like the plague originally but it's a really funny series. Do you think they'll continue? None of the videos have had many views? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A sub where I can talk about and describe my experiences as I lose my faith </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 22:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just brought a packet of inverted Custard Cremes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 16:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dont sell to the man below me! I am also buying Habbo accounts! Rare names please! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 12:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am willing to pay /$$$ for these rare names. I really am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things you wouldnt want to hear in a comic book shop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 11:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things you wouldnt want to hear the Avengers say. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 15:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 [M4R] full time lonely geek! Just got diagnosed with depression and losing my religion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 19:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kik is specialunitt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [m4r] 20! UK full time nerd, looking for friendships! Just been diagnosed with depression and losing my religion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 19:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyway to read "The death of Captain America"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 14:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just read Civil War #1-7 and I want to read the aftermath of it but can't find Captain America (vol. 5) #25-#42. Is there a collection of these comics or am I screwed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Want] Kimberley Marvel [Have] Plump Princess acc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 19:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I chose to be a 60s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 12:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt read what this was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently tried to get into Marvel and comic books in general. Just read Civil War #1-7. What now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 10:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this on my newsfeed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think the TV show's will tie in to the movies at some point? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 10:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example will we one day see The Defenders in an Avengers movie. Will the events of Agent Carter change things directly in the movies? I am pondering whether to watch them, it's alot of content that I dont have time for... I really enjoyed Daredevil however! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 foot long subways, 5 sausage rolls and 4 chocolate [m]uffins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 17:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I pray for what I write before I write? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 10:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other day I posted a [poem] (http://www.reddit.com/r/TrueChristian/comments/33gh2i/i_wrote_my_first_poem_because_of_its_subject/) on here, and got some great feedback but feel a little guilty as I didnt actually pray about what the Lord wanted me to write. Before writing should I have an inclination from the spirit or can I just write? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wrote my first poem; because of it's subject matter I didnt think /r/OCPoetry would like it. Could someone give me feedback? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 11:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever waited for the next big thing?

The next big movie, the next big car?

The next big concert, or the next big song to sing?

Advertisers have make it quite clear

You need this product to live; the future is here!



And time, and time again we fall for it

We buy things we do not need

And fall into the dreaded consumer pit

We buy and we store 

Until are egos are swollen; and our wallets are sore



The anticipation then begins to start

Waiting for the next big thing

In that time we give that thing our heart

Counting down to the next big thing

Waiting eagerly for the next big thing



Friends let me take you back a few thousand years

To around 30 BC

Where we see Jesus there with his following peers

The messiah had come; to take on our plight

The Jews werent convinced; they wanted a warrior knight



He spouted things they just couldnt believe

Blasphemer! They called him

A crucifixion he was to receive

They stood before the King of Kings

And tore apart their next big thing.



Thank God the story didnt end there

We would be in trouble,

None of us would be heirs

Hes coming back though; let our hearts sing

For the coming of the next big thing.
___________________________________________________________________________________

Apologies if this is not welcome here!

Edit: I cant seem to format it properly on reddit :(, it's also more a performance than written so keep that in mind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your baby is dead! [Scream!] That's what you'd hear if your baby fell victim to the thousands of deathtraps lurking in the average American home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 16:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody remember Butt Ugly Martians? What a terrible show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 13:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lack of content being explained swood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 13:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twitter.

Sorry for no vide0s. L3t u no s00n! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh, so mother nature needs a favor? Well, maybe she should have thought of that when she was besetting us with droughts and floods and poison monkeys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 23:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I get dk64 for Wii u or N64? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 22:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a n64 a few months ago, one of the major contributors to this decision was playing DK64 for the first time in 10+ years but now it's on the eshop , should I just go for that? It's probably cheaper and I could have the game *now*. I also don't have a n64 expansion. What do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the room with electricity. But it has too much electricity. So, I don't know, you might want to wear a hat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 00:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I opened two gifts this morning... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 10:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats wrong with me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 09:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I decided to get up earlier (6:30) twice a week to have some quiet time with God, this morning however I just didnt feel motivated to do it and hit snooze. This wouldnt be so bad if I didnt get up twice a week also to go to the gym, however then I am excited and get up immediately. I feel so bad, whats wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conversation I saw when my little sister was playing Habbo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 14:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting a Surface RT right now, shall I? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend is selling his original Surface to me for 100 which is great, should I go for it? I only need it for typing, and internet browsing really. I have a Nexus 7 to for Netflix stuff but the fact there is no keyboard to that makes typing and browsing harder! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm putting Jake and Amir on a Tuesday Afternoon Blast! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 15:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sun is out and so is my dick! Where the bitch is the latest Jake and Amir flick? The night is old and so is my heart, where else can I let out his ghastly fart? I want the office scene that I love so, I also what a girl to me blow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where the stitch is the new episode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 11:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the episode where these spinthrifts announce that they never will end the webshow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Because of a mentally disabled man kidnapping me, typing me up and threatening to kill me I am now irrationally scared of the mentally disabled. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 17:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note: I will only be able to answer questions for half hour today but will be back tomorrow!

Edit: I am really confused as to why I'm downvoted.

2nd edit: I came back and answered some questions right now I really need to get to sleep I'm up in 4 hours. If you want to ask questions ask away! I will answer tommorow!

3rd edit: British Time Zone isnt it! Back to answer more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Gospel : A Haiku </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 15:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man died to be God.

Man craved control of themselves.

God died to save man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The brief gospel as Haiku </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 11:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man died to be God.

Man craved control of themselves.

God died to save man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been texting a girl for the last 4 weeks or so and she doesnt think I'm boring enough to stop talking yet! AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 16:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a noteworthy event because I havent tried to 'court' someone in over 2 years! This is the longest time Ive spent actually talking to a girl! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's spinning the ball on his finger! Just take it! Take the ball! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 14:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are people here who tried to get a 60s... all I did was not read what /r/thebutton was about. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 11:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 10 things to do now the series has ended... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 12:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Number 10: Meet Quan Chen. A Chinese Man with a Chinese hand makes a nice boy band. Play music through the night to forget about this sad plight.

Number 9: Soak in brine. The scars hurt now I can see, so get in a tub of hotdog pee! The saltiness will help with the hurt and the smell will help with her squirt.

Number 8: Just wait. These coy boys are coming back one day soon, TBS wont have them and neither should you...n.

Number 7: Collect money from Kevin. Kevins my friend and he said he's pay you when J A came to an end. Spend the money on anything you please, a logging company cut down trees!

Number 6: Suck my dicks. It's a toe now though and thats a shame maybe I could with it get my 15 minutes of fame.

Number 5: Hit a beehive. Why are you still alive? No J A your life is pointless, kill your body, make it jointless.

Number 4: Fall to the floor, wait there until theres a knock on the door. Its your mom knock her out, she doesnt know how you feel that grout scout.

Number 3: Climb a tree, take in the world around you, and then maybe you can do a crusty poo. Jump when you've had enough, because we've had enough... of you.

Number 2: Congratulate the crew, they did a good job and they're all golden rods. Tell them you want it back or else they will get a smack.

Number 1: Get over it it's done. Both Jake and Amir wont be here again, the deeds theyve done have unbalanced their zen. Wait for the TV show if it ever happens, but overall my mood... it dampens.


You coy boys did good. Todah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a split personality disorder AMA. I dont have a split personality disorder AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 16:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My uncle would describe himself as a gay male. However he thoroughly believes that he chose his sexuality. AHM! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 13:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the title suggests. My Uncle has a husband and two adopted children and is very happy. We had a discussion and he agreed to do this after asking him for a while. He's not that into computers so I'll transcribe all his answers for him. To make that point clear all answers will be in speechmarks (")!

Edit: He's here for a few days but we'll be away from the internet in about an hour until tomorrow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most casual conversation you've ever had? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 12:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right I'll try again... Who wants to play Cards Against HUmanity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 11:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://pyx-1.pretendyoure.xyz/zy/game.jsp#game=59

The password is CasualCards. If you're unaware of the game the rules can be found [here] (http://s3.amazonaws.com/cah/CAH_Rules.pdf)

Edit: The game is in progress however I believe y'all can still join! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird charging problem... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 11:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My iPhone wont charge. I've tried it in different sockets, from a laptop and everything it just wont charge. There's no debris in the charging hole, however when I plug the iPhone in when it's off it turns on, it still doesnt charge but it boots up so its obviouslly reacting to the cable, is this a problem that anyone else has had etc?

I've only had the phone since November and Im on a two year contract! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do I always shout first? Just gives them a chance to run away. Well, I'm an idiot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 10:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once again I have hit a lull in my faith... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 10:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However I know that God still loves me and His name is worthy. However I'd appreciate prayer from y'all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, you're certainly doing your job, Mr. Sun. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 14:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you have an enemy? If so what did they do to you? Could you ever forgive them? [Serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 13:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last Jake and Amir? Nah Last Cake and I'm clear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 11:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clear of Heroin that is. After this Web Series ends I'm going to start injection again until you call me luck number slevin. Down this D-bag with D-votes if you agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mr. Scorpio says productivity is up 2%, and it's all because of my motivational techniques, like donuts and the possibility of more donuts to come. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 10:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worst things to read on a cereal box </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 09:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What a Bank Holiday Monday! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 15:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I will answer all your questions in an unnecessarily harsh way and because you're a pussy you won't be able to take it. Ama. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 15:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why am I not excited today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 19:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to Church today (Easter Sunday) and Good Friday and I didn't emote. I felt nothing today or Friday.

Is there something wrong with me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You've changed man, it used to be about the music. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 16:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Nintendo consoles so far.. (Games not pictured) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 16:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am not a cook, Ive only ever cooked for myself. In two months I am cooking for 10 people, what do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 10:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, so in 2 months I am cooking for 10 people, it doesnt have to be anything special but because of my cash flow and skill it should be cheap, healthy and easy.

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> and now I give you... The Eternal Struggle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 14:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was voted sexiest virgin of 2005, ten years on. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 12:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prove them wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 11:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parappa the Rapper vs Jon Jafari </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 16:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1 : Fisticuffs
Round 2 : Some sort of Musical Contest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am the Deliver that OP's. AMTDA. Ask me to do anything. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 16:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am in a well of Lust and Debauchery. I have no idea what to do... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 16:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am addicted to Masturbation. I dont think there is another word for it. Addicted. I simply cannot function without masturbating it's planned into my day. Wake. Masturbate. Just hit 12 at work? Masturbate? About to go to sleep? Masturbate. I have tried again and again to stop using things like God Over Porn and /r/NoFapChristians. But again and again daily I fail and fall over.

Recently I got bored of the stuff I was fantasizing to so experimented with some more... bisexual in nature fantasies. And they felt better than before! My routing had new breath poured into it and I cannot get enough. Does this make me Bi? I no longer know who I am.

I still love Jesus, go to Church, have meals with fellow believers and teach the youth etc. I am not ashamed of myself... yet. I dont want to be a damp and wet Christian, but I know that this cannot go on. I'm confused about myself and want to repent but everytime I have done in the past I come (no pun) to this point again.

Pray /r/TrueChristian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the absolute worst game the Grumps could play? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 15:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many many many different threads of people discussing what game the Grumps should play? But what games do people think should never be played on the channel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mmmm... fattening </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 13:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those are supposed to be baggy pants! Baggy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 13:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello, Simpson. I'm riding the bus today because Mother hid my car keys to punish me for talking to a woman on the phone. She was right to do it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best way to listen to The Ricky Gervais show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 16:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heya guys Id love to listen through the podcast again. I watched the series when it was on Channel 4 but Id love to listen to the podcast during my commute to and from work. Where could I listen to it on my iPhone? Preferably downloaded to it, I cannot find it on iTunes.

Thanks y'all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marge :Homer, I really appreciate you making dinner, but this food tastes a little strange. Lisa: It hurts my teeth. Homer: That's because I've loaded it with sugar! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 15:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "We want Chilly Willy! We want Chilly Willy!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 12:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix video quality constantly changing.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 15:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heya all! When I go to watch Netflix on my Chromecast the video quality always changes. The Chromecast and my phone is the only thing connected to the WiFi so I don't get it. Only had this problem today... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relaxing on a Sunday [M] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 14:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend [20] is struggling with his faith, full story inside. Prayers appreciated. [UPDATE-ish] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 15:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys thanks for reading my predicament [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/TrueChristian/comments/30djri/my_friend_20_is_struggling_with_his_faith_full/)

Well we've prayed and me and my friend are going to be meeting him tommorow at a pub. My other friend goes to Bible college and is coming back for Easter so its going to be social however we're going to ask him if hes okay etc and try and understand and talk through some of his things. We prayed over Skype and felt this was right to do.

Thanks y'all! Will update again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stuggyvines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 13:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of slime would I marry? Hmm, I dont understand. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 12:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend [20] is struggling with his faith, full story inside. Prayers appreciated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 15:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heya all. As the title suggests I have a friend who is struggling with God and Jesus and the like. I thought I would come here to explain whats up and hopefully get some prayer and things I can do to encourage him.

Basically I've lived next door to him my whole life. In fact he's the one that got me to church etc. However recently he's been a bit distant. From September - January he attended Bible college, but left because he was enjoying it/homesick etc. However before that he got engaged. Since his return form Bible college, he hasnt attended church come to anything etc. I know its not about attendance at all, but anytime we try and talk about Jesus he changes the subject. Recently I asked how his relationship with Christ was and he just said "Not good, I dont want him". Recently his fiance (who lives away) came back for Easter and they havent been apart since, she just bought an Xbox One for him and thats all they do together. I'm worried about him, I love my brother and want him to be content and full of peace through the Lord.

Thanks for reading! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today I grabbed my belly for the first time in ages and got immensly turned on. Gym memberships been cancelled... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 15:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you really want something in this life, you have to work for it --Now quiet, they're about to announce the lottery numbers! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 13:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blub, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 10:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't give up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 10:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 12,400 mile road to link UK and USA proposed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 14:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was watching Eggheads (A British Quiz show) and one of the multiple-choice answers looked familiar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 13:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I give DanAvidanDanDan a Danouttadan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 12:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everytime Shreks head on the left moves and wiggles a little bit James Franco ejaculates a little more. Make it happen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 12:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American jerks are going home, now we sleep for a thousand years. When we wake the world will end! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 11:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi, class! Hi Bart...over here, sweetie. It's me, Mom. Hi! Hey! Hello? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 11:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What you all think about the film Her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 19:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently watched the film Her, a few people from my church disliked it because of its sexual nature and profanity. I loved it however. What does r/Christianity think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Lets Go To the City good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 17:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard that it's the worst AC? Is this true I saw a really cheap copy today so wondering if its worth it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a reason that Donkey Kong is only playable in one of the original DKC games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 16:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing through these masterful games once again and thought it's a bit weird that DK is only in one of the DKC games. Diddy and Dixie are in 2, meaning in the original DKC line of games Diddy and Dixie appear more than DK. Was there a reason for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey I'm Chup! I'm not so Chup! And we're the... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 15:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Franco is getting raped by a mysterious green being. Could it be Shrek? Or a dank meme? Hit upvote to expose the culprit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 12:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have recently made the decision to start collecting Nintendo games. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 12:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I gave my kidney a wife, AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 12:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There still isnt a full sized Creme Egg Easter Egg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 12:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Criminally underrated games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 10:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought a little Wii game named Zack and Wiki: Quest for Barbaros Treasure. I bought it because it was cheap and looked stupid enough for me to laugh at it. What I got was a surprisingly deep and fantastic point and click adventure game with fantastic and funny writing. Why is no one talking about it?!

Then I got thinking about games that no one has heard of that are hidden gems. Do you have any?

Edit: As somebody pointed out technically I mean underappreciated and not underrated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a society we Brits seem to not understand that if there's no room on the train then you probably shouldn't get on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 09:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have bruises I didn't have when I got on the train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Friday afternoon. I have 2 hours left at work and my boss and other employee have gone home. I'm bored out my tits, ama. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 16:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me get into Monster Hunter... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 12:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heya all. I bought Monster Hunter 4 Ultimate about 3 weeks ago and unfortunately I am not enjoying it as much as I thought. Dont get me wrong it's an impressive feat and am impressed they can cram such a game into such a small cartridge.

It just seems to me that it's a game that you're meant to know what you're doing going in... and I dont. Killing Monsters gets a bit boring and the combat does seem to be a button masher, even though I've been told time and time again that it isnt.

What am I doing wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm watchin' the road, sweetie. You Jiiiiive turkey. See, you've got to sass it. Quit Jiiiiiiivin' me turkey. You've got to sass it! A turkey is a bad person. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 11:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game Grumps' Arin and Ross are tackling DKC 3. Good conversation and view points. Thought you'd all be interested. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 11:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just bought a Gamecube for 15, so this question inevitably comes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 11:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course I'm going to be getting Sunshine, WW, Pikmin, Paper Mario etc. But what other games should I get that I wouldnt really think about? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh! She won't hold! She's breaking up! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 10:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A sub for people who post things they found on roads, at tips etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 12:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... what shirts are still available? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 11:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all! 

I was one of the lucky few to have got a Tennouttatenn shirt and I love it dearly after all these years. Thinking about getting a new Game Grumps shirt but the range is spread over so many stores (Maker, 1 Shirt, Redbubble, Shark Robot) etc I dont really know which shirts are available or not because where ever I look one just pops up somewhere. Anybody got a list of which are still available and which were just limited?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I warm my Wheetabix up and everybody in the office looks at me in pure disgust. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 10:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait for it Simba... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 09:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love how squidgy I look. Want to get softer and softer. Can't wait for Gravity to pull my belly more and [m]ore downwards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 14:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> List of differences between Netflix regions? [Meta] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 14:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently used the Hola unblocker on my tablet and am adoring using the US netflix. Man you guys have such great stuff! However it'd be better if there was a comprehensive list of differences in content between the regions so I could find what i was looking for easier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I'm too drunk for this!" - Ross O Donovan moments after he destroys space and time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 13:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, thanks, everybody. You know, I'm here today as Luke Skywalker, but I'm also here ... to talk about Sprint. As you can see, you stand to save up to seventeen cents a month over the more dependable providers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 12:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody else just sing the Game Grumps theme in public? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 12:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since the "Hey I'm Dan" remix on the shirt promo, I've been singing "Hey I'm Tom" to myself near enough everyday. Today I was making porridge and without thinking was singing "Hey I'm Por, I'm not so Ridge!"

This needs to stop and I am scared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Picked up what I thought was a Custard Cream in the Biscuit Tin at work, turns out it was a Strawberry cream. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 13:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only difference being the colour of the Cream which no one looks at and the writing on top which no one reads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Introducing 'men in red shorts hanging off buildings with guns pointed at them' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 11:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most pedantic thing someone has corrected you over? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 17:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this technically stealing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my friend has been out of a job recently, and has wanted to get Netflix. On the plan I am on I can use Netflix on two devices, now because I only use one device I made an account for him on mine and gave him the password? Is he technically stealing as he isnt paying for it?

Blessings! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kwyjibo: K-W-Y-J-I-B-O. Twenty-two points. Plus, triple-word score, plus fifty points for using all my letters... Game's over, I'm outta here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 12:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop looking at Poo, I'm a Willy Music video. [Slightly NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 14:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most controversial opinion you have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 15:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what are these good works then? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 10:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy yall, a couple of days ago I was wrestling with a bit of scripture [here] (http://www.reddit.com/r/TrueChristian/comments/2y4ewo/help_me_understand_matthew_72123/)

And someone in the comments very helpfully put this

"Remember, it is not faith + works - salvation, nor is it faith + nothing - salvation, but rather faith + salvation - works."

So now I ask, what are these works? Does attening a prayer time or bible study constitute as works? What exactly are works?

Thank you all for joining with me on my journey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit: What's your favourite letter, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 15:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm allergic to questions, AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 13:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost passed out on train on the way to work this morning, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 11:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was standing up on the train to work today and I suddenly got very very hot. The train was packed as it normally is I was listening to a Podcast and all I could hear was a buzzing noise eventually my eyesight went to. I pulled the chair down from behind me and sat down. I think I was dazed and confused for about a minute before I sat down, no idea what happened in that minute but I can hands down say it was terrifying. Suffering from social anxiety I really didnt want to pass out in front of everyone on the train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NO, no, Dig UP Stupid!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 10:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me understand Matthew 7:21-23 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 10:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 21 Not everyone who says to me, Lord, Lord, will enter the kingdom of heaven, but only the one who does the will of my Father who is in heaven. 22 Many will say to me on that day, Lord, Lord, did we not prophesy in your name and in your name drive out demons and in your name perform many miracles? 23 Then I will tell them plainly, I never knew you. Away from me, you evildoers!

Does this not go against what Romans 10:13 says? "Everyone who calls on the name of the Lord will be saved."

Is doing the will of the Lord merely Salvation through works? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I dont like any fruit. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 17:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every single piece of fruit I have tried has made me very ill or vomit on the spot. I'm 20. AMA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should I do for dinner tonight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 16:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 500 calories left for today and am willing to spend up to 10 ($15) what kind of cool things could I make? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 3 weeks I am cooking for 10 people, I have never cooked in my life and thought Ramen would be easy enough. What should I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 16:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just became Admin on the Facebook page "World Famous Pugilist Tommy Ray Handley" to try and bring new life into the community. Please come and check it out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 14:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want a Daim bar and dont know how to pronounce Daim. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 12:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw the first Christmas is only x number of days away post on Facebook. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 12:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Give my friend who is away in America some encouragement! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 10:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all! I'm in the UK and my friend has gone to America for a year to be a Nanny for a family over there. Before she left I told her that I would post an encouragement on her Facebook wall. This month marks 6 months of her being there and me doing this and have got a bit stuck. I wanted to make an image with encouragement so thought I'd ask you guys what you would say to her. I'd appreciate swift replies as I am 3 days too late.

Thanks y'all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are lets plays so popular? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 10:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Oh great Dads dead" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 08:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putting Jake and Amir on a UK Tuesday Afternoon Blast! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 17:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you two coy coy jews? Release the whole series blu-ray? I need thiz.. I want thiz. I will pay a bad amount of money for it. I can see your greedy jew eyes glow at the sound of that. Put some behind the scenes and fired on there and release it inside a full scale Jake or Amir Puppet. Cmon you ass. Daddys Thirsty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Show Confirmed: Grump Paid! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 12:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Proof] (http://24.media.tumblr.com/01eed5a6c510c5f6b63b7a3ee0c08b51/tumblr_mg86amhuZu1rrbvmgo1_250.jpg)

Hey guys. Aren here. Just wanted to confirm our new show [Grump Paid] (http://i.ytimg.com/vi/l1kgA3eDKKM/maxresdefault.jpg)

This is a show where me and Danny talk about things and play money. Hope you guys enjoy it.

Love Arina. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once the series ends how're you faggoty jews going to react to fan scripts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 12:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nick Clegg: having faith must be the most wonderful thing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 10:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can only type 8 words at a time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 15:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> are blue pants and jon still frends? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 17:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This has turned into the one thing that Jirard asked for it to not to turn into. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 15:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not a battle of good vs evil. This isnt a mystery that *needs* to be solved. It's a conflict between two friends. No sides. No theories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My N64 collection so far... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 18:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have ADD and struggle to concentrate on reading the bible or praying, what could I do to help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 11:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why we love video games : Nintendo 64 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 11:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously everybody here loves the N64 and with good reason. It's a fantastic console. I wanted to create a space where people can discuss their love for the console and **why** they love it so much.

As a kid I never owned a N64 and was instead bought a Playstation for my 6th birthday. Obviously back then I didnt care and loved (and still do) the console. My best friend who lived next door to me  however owned both. As we were both boys who were born 4 months apart we of course were best friends and I went over his house every so often to play his N64. I dont know what it was but those memories of Super Mario 64 and OOT are so crystal clear. The N64 (from what I played of it) was more adventurous. While I waiting for disks to load on the PS the cartridges loaded up the games in seconds. Everything was faster and (what I thought) bigger. I had Rayman, Toy Story 2 and Lego Racers to name a few games on PS1 but Mario 64, OOt, Mario Party and Dk 64 felt more alive. I spent years gushing over my friends N64 and him never really understanding why as he went on to get Xbox 360s and the like. But I now know that when I played the N64 it was the first time in a video game that I felt like I was bang middle of a great adventure. 

I went on to buy my Pikachu N64 a couple months ago, and coupled with the Wii U the only consoles I own. I would have it no other way.


TLDR: What are some of your N64 memories? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your favourite Banjo Kazooie song? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 10:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is no news to anybody that the B-K series has some kick ass music.  [So much so that Blake Robinson did an amazing orchestrated version of the whole games soundtrack!] (http://www.banjosymphony.com/)

So I was wondering what is everybodys favourite song from the games and why?

For me it's [Gruntys Industries] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=shrzrH3F0z0). I love factory and industrial levels in games and the music caught that monotonous working environment to a T but still added enough to make the level fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love the rolls I have gained. I love being stuffed fatter and fatter. I need [M]ore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 15:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Really really nooby question... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 14:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heyall picked up MH4U the other day and adoring it! However wanted to ask do I have to have the materials I want to craft with on my person or can i keep them in the item box and craft from there? When going to "The Man" not all the materials I gathered are there.

thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few weeks ago the company on the 3rd floor of our office block just went, no one knows why. Today the boss isnt in so a few of us are going to snoop around for a few hours to see what we find. AUA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 11:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legit plot device from FinaleLegit plot device from Finale Part 8: Mickey is Amirs Hands. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 17:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear this is true, those micey micey bastards. Uptoke me to karma... seven! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any of yall ever actually used pocket sand? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 15:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ate a whole jar of Nutella for breakfast. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 12:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I regret nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had a 3ds for ages finally bought games for it. Pokemon and Munster Hunter 4 Ultimate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 18:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The names Tank. The codes 5386-9773-1483 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What games could I play if I got a 13" Macbook Pro? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 12:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specs: Processor	Intel Core i5 (2.6 GHz, 3.1 GHz with TurboBoost, 3 MB cache)
RAM	8 GB DDR3
Graphics card	Intel Iris
Storage	256 GB SSD

Waffle: Howdy Y'all, looking into getting a Macbook today! Hooray! I was just wondering if I could play low end games such as Minecraft, Civ5 and the Sims 3 on it? Those kind things. I'm not using it for gaming primarily but would be nice to play with friends on Minecraft and Civ. If not will the 15 inch with an 17 Processor do it?

Thanks!

Edit: I'm also worried about the portability of the 15" so any opinions on that. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am the social media dude at TBS Very Funny. AMA about this this this silent treatment we are giving y'all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 10:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Proof] (https://twitter.com/tbsveryfunny) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Who needs the Kwik E Mart? I doooooooo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 10:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hi, this is erin dog richard. I liekd jons bulls so he left. AMa. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 15:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will this MacBook play Minecraft? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 14:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy yall! I know I know I am off my rocker trying to "game" on a Mac. But I Minecraft is the only game I will be playing. Will the Mid 2014 Macbook Pro Retina 13" be suitable? [Linky to specs] (http://www.currys.co.uk/gbuk/computing/laptops/apple-laptops/apple-macbook-pro-13-with-retina-display-21962973-pdt.html)

It will literally be the only game I play when I'm not working on the Mac so no need for a gaming pc!

Thanks yall! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of Fear, Loathing and Las Vegas I shat my khakis today. Ask me anytime, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 14:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please justify me getting a Mac </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 19:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heya all! I've lurked around a bit today and decided I want a Mac. However when I go to Asda they're selling the same size laptop (Hp) with more memory and same processor  for a grand less! Is there a reason to waste my money other than just buying the brand? Really struggling with this and don't want to feel as if I've wasted money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buy now, Pay later stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 15:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all! I am going to be making the leap from Windows to Mac in three days. am very excited. However I will be adopting a buy now pay later payment scheme. Wondering if anyone here has ever done the same thing and had bad/good experiences? Love to hear peoples stories! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mac noob here, looking into getting a Macbook Pro with Retina display. The question is 13 inch or 15 inch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 11:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I havent had a laptop in about a year. I want to have one for continuing to write a book I put on hold, Graphics design and Video editing. Would the Macbook Pro be capable of all this? And which screen size is better?

Also I want this laptop for at least a couple of years. Will these laptops be replaced soon I dont mind being behind the times but was just wondering.

Edit. [A little linky to what I am thinking] (http://www.currys.co.uk/gbuk/computing/laptops/apple-laptops/apple-macbook-pro-13-with-retina-display-21962972-pdt.html#cat-0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These coy Jews did it... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 19:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here I am eating my evening meal and no episode. Looks like we've been thomas crown affaires by the big man himself giving us the good old how do you do?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imagine a scenario where everyday at the exact same time somebody you know vomits on you. How many days would it take until you got angry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 16:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something you should know about the announcement video? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 15:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did some researching into the Last 8 episodes and found out that it was put up by a Mr Jon Wolf. In fact [this is a picture of him doing it] (https://pbs.twimg.com/profile_images/516981491192954880/MKbzMN5P.jpeg)

I swear, so subtle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey I'm a Grump, Hey I'm not such Grumpy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 15:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And we're the doodle dangs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello I am a Game Grumps fan. I'm still hurt about Jon and think Suzy is the worst thing ever. Also I have loads of pictures of Arin from 2008 and like looking at them. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 15:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a big boy today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 13:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She didn't reckon with the awesome power of the Chief of Police. Now where did I put my badge?... Hey, that duck's got it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 10:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Jesus go to hell to defeat Satan and was he still God on the cross? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 10:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard a friend describe Jesus going to hell to "take the keys of death off Satan". This sounded very nice and part of me agrees with it as Satan is no longer in control of death, but is this biblical and what do we think of that here? also I've heard people say that to attone for our sins Christ must become FULLY human meaning he was no longer God.

I can Google and have but this is all part of my research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Pancake day! What are you having in your pancakes today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 08:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a fussy so and so, so Nutella is on the cards for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> we let the gays get their way and now we have 50 shades of grey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 17:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder what life would be like if I robbed the Kwik E Mart? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 13:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are "Lets Plays" so popular on Youtube? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 12:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why wasnt Road Trip Part 7 the end? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 10:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong I adore the episodes after Road Trip and dont feel that the show has declined in quality. But the whole series had a massive build up. Even at the beginning of the episode when the open screen was just Jake and Amir saying Thank You. The build up with the odds and ends. It seemed like a perfect ending. 

I just wonder why they continued when they only had a year left...

todah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm going to bed now but I want to wake up with something to do as soon as so... AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 23:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to access the Breaking Bad insider podcast in the UK? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 10:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently rewatching again and wanted to listen to the podcast alongside it. However it's not available in the UK iTunes Store.

Is there anyway?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Decided to take matters into my own hands... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 17:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm posting here because being let down over and over again by people, I've decided to build my own gaming PC. Right now I am feeling very overwhelmed and nervous. Not here for advice but the nervousness is mixed with excitement! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So Project Ukele comes out... what do you think Playtonics next port of call should be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 10:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playtonic are in the business of making games like Rare used to make it seems. They seem to have a clear vision, what do you think is in the future for Playtonic? An FPS, A vulgar platformer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are these specs good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 19:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Jantran is making a new series called Dame Crumps. It is about the titular Dame Crumps and her Crumpy shenanigans. Arin is Dame and Danny is Crumps. AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 14:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 40 acts of kindness: If you want to do Lent abit differently. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 14:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tried to lose weight, but I cannot overco[M]e the want to be bigger... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 13:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A UK idiot wants to build a gaming PC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 17:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What will you be doing with this PC? Be as specific as possible, and include specific games or programs you will be using.

I want to play games such as Fallout 3, Skyrim those kind of things. I have no idea how intensive those games are but would also like to play GTA V when that comes out.


**What is your maximum budget before rebates/shipping/taxes?** 

At the end of the day I am still a student, and found a gaming laptop that could do what I wanted for just under 1000. So preferably below that because I heard building one would be cheaper.

**When do you plan on building/buying the PC? Note: beyond a week or two from today means any build you receive will be out of date when you want to buy.** 

The next month or two.


**What, exactly, do you need included in the budget? 
Everything really. Tower, Monitor, and all componants.

**Which country (and state/province) will you be purchasing the parts in? I

Bloody Ol' England 


**If reusing any parts (including monitor(s)/keyboard/mouse/etc), what parts will you be reusing? Brands and models are appreciated.** 

None

**Do you need a copy of Windows 7 or 8.1 included in the budget? If you do need one included, do you have a preference for one or the other?**

Any Windows 8. Dont have a prefrence.

Honestly I just want a PC to play games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting a gaming desktop is out of the question. Looking into a gaming laptop. Are these specs good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 14:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chassis   Display
SkyFire: 14" Matte HD+ LED Widescreen (1600x900)

Processor (CPU)
Intel Corei5 Dual Core Mobile Processor i5-4210M (2.60GHz) 3MB

Memory (RAM)
8GB KINGSTON SODIMM DDR3 1600MHz (1 x 8GB)

Graphics Card
NVIDIA GeForce GTX 850M - 2.0GB DDR5 Video RAM - DirectX 11

1st Hard Disk
120GB KINGSTON V300 SSD, SATA 6 Gb (450MB/R, 450MB/W)

2nd Hard Disk
750GB WD SCORPIO BLACK WD7500BPKX, SATA 6 Gb/s, 16MB CACHE (7200 rpm)

Memory Card Reader
Integrated 2 in 1 Memory Card Reader (SD, MMC)

Thermal Paste
STANDARD THERMAL PASTE FOR SUFFICIENT COOLING

Sound Card
Intel 2 Channel High Definition Audio + MIC/Headphone Jack

Wireless/Wired Networking
GIGABIT LAN   WIRELESS 802.11N CARD INC. BLUETOOTH 3.0

USB Options
2 x USB 3.0 PORTS + 1 x USB 2.0 PORT AS STANDARD

Battery
SkyFire 14" Series 6 Cell Lithium Ion Battery

Power Cable
1 x UK Power Lead   90W AC Adaptor

Keyboard Language
INTEGRATED 11.6"/14" MSI UK KEYBOARD

Operating System
Genuine Windows 8.1 64 Bit - inc DVD   Licence 


Thanks yall!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting scared of heretics, pray please. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 11:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all. My church gifted me a Smith Wigglesworth book and many folks at r/Christianity say he is a heretic and false teacher. I am scared that if I read the book I will be enticed with what he has to say. I am really bad at discerning. Please pray. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 10 reasons the series is ending. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 11:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 - We're not friends. Jake and Amir come together like two peas in a pod and then yes one of them is a Golden Rod. A falling out, a boxing bout is the only thing to save these trouts.

9 - We're looking fine. We hit our peak, take your seat, tickets please you dirty sleaze. It's the end for us, the finale of the line, it took long enough, yes our sweet time.

8 - We want to masturbate. A webseries is fun to be sure, but I'd rather spend my time not being pure. A porno mag for this fine stag takes up my time, it's a steep uphill climb.

7 - It's time for heaven. A mass suicide is what we bargained for. Shoot ourselves in the head, blood pouring everywhere and guess what? I am bread.

6 - We're collecting sticks. Sticks has become more than a hobby, in fact I got in trouble with a British Bobby. Bit his ear off, and he had the year off. Hit the stick around his head and guess what? He is bread!

5 - We took a career skydive. People complained the quality wasnt on par, like a round of golf. Get in the golf car.

4 - They locked the door. We are stuck in this room with no way of escape. I will save the day put on my cape. No way out of here and no camera. Means no web series you panderer.

3 - Introducing Jake and Amir: The Movie. A feature length short is the perfect retort. On the big screen we take it and we dont even fake it. A hour and half short film is perfect and our own stage we will build!

2 - Gone for a P U. Poo being the operative term, we're a long way from sperm. Keep pushing and pushing and there is a lot of flushing. it's a mother lover and I have health cover.

1 - It was fun. 8 years of coy jews, doing coyish things like trust fall and sing. After my poo I will but fart. These diva roaches will forever be in my heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the consensus on Smith Wigglesworth here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 09:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was recently gifted a book full of Smith Wigglesworths sermons by my church. Of course before I read it I want to discern, pray about it and gather people's opinions. What do people think about him here? Great man of God or false prophet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best tweet you have ever wrote? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 15:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohhh... why did I get this Lego shirt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 15:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about calorie deficient... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 09:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So today I worked out in the gym and burned 400 calories which was fantastic and was really happy. How when I do this My Fitness Pal (Great app btw) adds to the amount of calories I can have a day. I'm on a 1860 diet but My fitness pal says I can still have 2172. Should I heed the apps advice or still eat 1860 regardless if I've worked it off. Thanks all!

Edit: Stupidity- I'm 5ft 9 and 17st 9lbs (247lbs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog Chicken </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 14:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a Big Cutie Jae membership, if you have a Plump Princess membership and dont mind sharing we can trade. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 14:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the point in Blu Ray and DVD double packs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 13:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean when you get both a copy of the DVD and a copy of the Blu Ray. [Relevant Example](http://www.amazon.co.uk/Ashens-Quest-Gamechild-Double-Blu-ray/dp/B00KAXSQAI)

Who is the target market for these things? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now, this technology is new to me, but I'm pretty sure that's Homer Simpson in the oven, rotating slowly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 13:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
