<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4909</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UPDATE: 24 1/2 Years Old Female: No job living with parents in squatters' condition   depressed VENT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 06:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 09:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU FOR ALL THE COMMENTS/ADVICE/OPINIONS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Letting go of resentment is easier said than done. I am not sure if I can let go of my resentment. I hold onto to things forever.

To be honest I am not sure if she understands depression. She's been in denial for such a long time, it's gonna take a long time for her to understand it/come to terms with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Title: My best friend got diagnosed with depression, when almost 5 years ago; she dismissed/shamed   didn't believe me when I told her about my depression. Mixed feelings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title: My best friend got diagnosed with depression, when almost 5 years ago; she dismissed/shamed   didn't believe me when I told her about my depression. Mixed feelings.

Another one of my vents/rants. Anyway as the title explains my best friend told me she got diagnosed with depression. The thing about all of this is I have mixed feelings about this revelation. I say this because about 5 years ago I told her about my depression and pretty much she dismissed/shamed/didn't believe me. I remember this particular conversation from 5 years ago because it hurt me so much and it made me look at her a bit differently since then.

5 years ago

I have un-diagnosed depression for about 6 years. Info: I saw a licensed professional for a couple of years and she told me she thought I had clinical/major depression. She suggested drugs and I declined without being officially tested/diagnosed. It took me over a year and a half to really talk about it. The people in my closest circle knew a bit about it; but I didn't really talked about it. Anyway I guess one day/night I snapped and told my best friend online. I don't remember all the details but I do remember reading her telling me that 
"I don't believe you have depression"
"It's just sadness"

Long story short she pretty much dismissed me, told me that she didn't believe me; and pretty much to get over it. She also gave me the impression that she didn't believe depression was real. After that experience I started to see her differently and shared/confined with her less and less. I also started to trust her less and questioned her loyalty. Whatever the case I chose to forgive her and move on (She is my best friend after-all).

A bit about my   her personality contrasts/relationship dynamic.
Not sure if these apply for me   her anymore****
She is day. I am night. (maybe not so much anymore)
She's definitely quieter, shyer one of us (but not quiet or shy if you what I mean)
She's presented herself as a strong, optimist, look on the bright side, turn the other cheek kind of person.

Present day
The funny thing about all this is when she told me I wasn't surprised. I knew she was hiding things from me. I know she wasn't being honest to me about her true feelings. Her telling me about her depression bought me back to all those years where I felt like a freak to her. This is where my mixed feelings come in. 

Mixed Feelings
The lower part of me is thinking: Ha, I knew it. Isn't it ironic that almost 5 years ago I told you about my depression and you didn't believe me/dismiss me and now look at you. I feel she was being a hypocritical, and a fraud. A part of me wants to rub this in her face. Of course I am not going to do that. But there is a bit of anger and I told you so in my mind.

I am hurt that she didn't trust me enough to confine in me when I gave her plenty of opportunities to do so. I always feel I am more open then she is with me. BTW me being open/vulnerable isn't easy for me at all. I am not an open, trusting person. Whatever the case I felt it was more important to be open/honest than feel trapped/feel fake. She has told me about some of her deepest darkest secrets/experiences (so I know she trusts me). But I feel she didn't trust me enough. I feel she has been fake/in denial for so long that I feel betrayed/lied to. All those times when I tried to talk to her about my feelings she shut me down. She made me feel stupid, ashamed and weak. 

Of course I am going to support her as best I can (I won't turn away from her if she asks for help), but apart of me lost respect for her and has resentment. I am venting on here because I know I can't honestly talk to her about this.

One thing I realized is that she can be really arrogant. She doesn't admit when she is wrong, or acknowledge her part in anything. She's an agree to disagree kind of person. When I told her how hurt I was she shut me down and pretty much left me with the impression that I am wrong, I am starting problems and that's all on me/aka she has nothing to do with it.

To note: I don't hate her or dislike her (if I did I would've cut her off a long time ago). She is a good friend. Anyway this is my vent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
