<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6752</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [News] HideMeX update for iOS 10 coming later this month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 01:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Introducing WhatsApp Status </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Introducing WhatsApp Status </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IDEA] GTAO 1.5 DLC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^^Please ^^^Youtubers ^^^Don't ^^^Steal ^^^this. ^^^thx

I know there have been rumors of R* slowing DLC for the game, but this is just an idea, because why not? 

If you guys didnt know this, GTAO is set in a time thats before the Trevor-Michael-Franklin trio. You can confirm this by going to Franklins new house and if you take a peek inside, there is nothing related to Franklin. I also believe Trevor and/or Lester make references to this by saying that they know someone but they haven't heard from them in long time. 

Due to this, I was thinking that 1.5 could make us go forward in time, matching the time where SP mode starts. Specifically when the trio meets for the first time. 

Once you boot up the updated game, you will enter a solo session. You get an unavoidable call from Ron. 

R: Hey, I need you to come here. We have a pretty big situation with Trevor here. Help us.

No context. Nada. The game prompts you to go to TPI. As with Prison Break  Plane there will be no NPC traffic so that you can get there faster and get back to gaming. 

Once you get there, Ron will prompt you to enter Trevors house, where you will find Franklin screaming at Michael and Trevor saying Stop fighting bitches. Trevor sees you, goes to you and presents you to the gang. From here and forward, a small talk happens, but the TL;DW/DR is that Trevor offers you to help the rest of the gang. 

With this new DLC we now have Michael missions. Some I can think in top of my head are: 
	2 player mission to spy on Amanda to see if she is cheating with another one of her teachers. We find out that they are and we are required to kill this rich teachers guards (about 10 of them) while he escapes in a top-range car. 

	2+ player mission to take revenge of various members of a gang that have been molesting the family. Sort of like a survival mode.
 
	Rescue Tracey from a place in Paleto Bay and bring her back a la Slasher style. You enter a place up there (I dont know much about PB) and play through a Maze, with no Flashlight, only with a Pistol, no pickups, no mini map, to rescue Tracey. You got a regular Kuruma waiting in the back of said place to escape. No Pegasus vehicles allowed. 

	Jimmy just bought a VR for his system. However he is trapped in it by a hacker (hallucination) who is controlling him. Lester enters with a box and suggests that we enter the game. We have to brute force into the system to find the hackers IP. Once we get that, Lester will look up the IP leading us to a house in Murrieta Heights (near Lesters house) and we are going to beat the kid up and his friends.

With Franklin, there isnt much I can think about, but it can be stealing cars, and/or killing gang members.

Some of the mission in SP could also be ported to support 2+ players in GTAO.

We also have new Heists. All the Heists from SP are ported to Online. Setups can be accommodated to support 4 players. In these Heist and setups, instead of the gang doing the work, they will be in the walkie talkie talking to us and we do the work. 

Some QoL changes for this DLC are:

	Voice pre-sets for our characters: Im seriously upset that we cant talk to the characters in the game. What could be done is that we choose a voice, out of 5 that will say the lines assigned to that role. I dont see how hard could this be. 

	Voice assistant: Saint Rows has this. I wish I could say GTA Pegasus Buzzard and I can hear the Thank you message and my $200 being deduced. Or I can say GTA Request Vehicle. 

	Sell properties. 

	New phones. Instead of using an iPhone, I wish I could switch to a Windows Phone or an Android. 

	Enter properties you own and instead of going to your apartment directly, when you enter, you will have a lobby and you can use the stairs or elevator to go to your apartment.   There can be activities like Dart and etc to play with other players.

	Changing brightness in Online rather than going to SP to change it. 

	More Yacht activities. 

	Having workers in the warehouse. When you reach the warehouse, instead of you going in to place the product in the shelf, someone does it for you. This is mainly useful for those solo players that do crate runs and cant carry more than 1 crate. 

	The assistant can stand up and do various stuff in the office. For example, calling her while you are outside your office, gives you the option to source a car, or buy crates. Of course, the crates will be in a place not close to you. 

	LJT stops fucking calling every half a second. 

I would gladly pay full price of the game again if R* makes this a thing. 

Edit: Formatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Idea] GTA 1.5 DLC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^^Please ^^^Youtubers ^^^Don't ^^^Steal ^^^this. ^^^thx

I know there have been rumors of R* slowing DLC for the game, but this is just an idea, because why not? 

If you guys didnt know this, GTAO is set in a time thats before the Trevor-Michael-Franklin trio. You can confirm this by going to Franklins new house and if you take a peek inside, there is nothing related to Franklin. I also believe Trevor and/or Lester make references to this by saying that they know someone but they haven't heard from them in long time. 

Due to this, I was thinking that 1.5 could make us go forward in time, matching the time where SP mode starts. Specifically when the trio meets for the first time. 

Once you boot up the updated game, you will enter a solo session. You get an unavoidable call from Ron. 

R: Hey, I need you to come here. We have a pretty big situation with Trevor here. Help us.

No context. Nada. The game prompts you to go to TPI. As with Prison Break  Plane there will be no NPC traffic so that you can get there faster and get back to gaming. 

Once you get there, Ron will prompt you to enter Trevors house, where you will find Franklin screaming at Michael and Trevor saying Stop fighting bitches. Trevor sees you, goes to you and presents you to the gang. From here and forward, a small talk happens, but the TL;DW/DR is that Trevor offers you to help the rest of the gang. 

With this new DLC we now have Michael missions. Some I can think in top of my head are: 
	2 player mission to spy on Amanda to see if she is cheating with another one of her teachers. We find out that they are and we are required to kill this rich teachers guards (about 10 of them) while he escapes in a top-range car. 

	2+ player mission to take revenge of various members of a gang that have been molesting the family. Sort of like a survival mode.
 
	Rescue Tracey from a place in Paleto Bay and bring her back a la Slasher style. You enter a place up there (I dont know much about PB) and play through a Maze, with no Flashlight, only with a Pistol, no pickups, no mini map, to rescue Tracey. You got a regular Kuruma waiting in the back of said place to escape. No Pegasus vehicles allowed. 

	Jimmy just bought a VR for his system. However he is trapped in it by a hacker (hallucination) who is controlling him. Lester enters with a box and suggests that we enter the game. We have to brute force into the system to find the hackers IP. Once we get that, Lester will look up the IP leading us to a house in Murrieta Heights (near Lesters house) and we are going to beat the kid up and his friends.

With Franklin, there isnt much I can think about, but it can be stealing cars, and/or killing gang members.

Some of the mission in SP could also be ported to support 2+ players in GTAO.

We also have new Heists. All the Heists from SP are ported to Online. Setups can be accommodated to support 4 players. In these Heist and setups, instead of the gang doing the work, they will be in the walkie talkie talking to us and we do the work. 

Some QoL changes for this DLC are:

	Voice pre-sets for our characters: Im seriously upset that we cant talk to the characters in the game. What could be done is that we choose a voice, out of 5 that will say the lines assigned to that role. I dont see how hard could this be. 

	Voice assistant: Saint Rows has this. I wish I could say GTA Pegasus Buzzard and I can hear the Thank you message and my $200 being deduced. Or I can say GTA Request Vehicle. 

	Sell properties. 

	New phones. Instead of using an iPhone, I wish I could switch to a Windows Phone or an Android. 

	Enter properties you own and instead of going to your apartment directly, when you enter, you will have a lobby and you can use the stairs or elevator to go to your apartment.   There can be activities like Dart and etc to play with other players.

	Changing brightness in Online rather than going to SP to change it. 

	More Yacht activities. 

	Having workers in the warehouse. When you reach the warehouse, instead of you going in to place the product in the shelf, someone does it for you. This is mainly useful for those solo players that do crate runs and cant carry more than 1 crate. 

	The assistant can stand up and do various stuff in the office. For example, calling her while you are outside your office, gives you the option to source a car, or buy crates. Of course, the crates will be in a place not close to you. 

	LJT stops fucking calling every half a second. 

I would gladly pay full price of the game again if R* makes this a thing. 

Edit: Formatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys, can we get serious about kicking randoms? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in a session yesterday as usual doing CEO work, when a couple of randoms entered. 

I first noticed a Lvl 70 came in. I set a bounty on them and proceeded to vote to kick them. 

I already saw the boot, so I was glad someone else got the bounty heads up. 

However, the random stayed in the session for about 7 minutes with the boot and no one else doing anything. 

Thankfully, a member decided to spam kill him to create pressure and leave. Be advised that this random also denied to do my request to leave via a text message in-game. 

Same thing happened with a lvl 20. 

Few hours later, a random came in, and invited his friend. 

No one was voting to kick him (the first random, not the friend) even tho I set the heads up with a bounty. 

I sent various messages to both randoms and they proceeded to bad mouth me via their mics as "they aren't doing nothing wrong".

They both ended up leaving the session. Though. 

Can we get serious about it? Not only that these randoms will join and invite their friends, but the game will make other randoms, enter the session with them. 

Special thanks to some of out members like JasonBlue_, as he made sure everyone voted to kick. There was someone else, whose name I can't remember at the moment, who also tried to message everyone and asking for a reply back to confirm whether they voted or not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New PS4 gamers, YSK that you can buy the Playstation Protection Plan within 1 (one) year of your PS4 system purchase. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read from the last couple of months conflicting info whether you can buy warranty after X amount of days. Some say 30, some say a year, but the way I did it, and how the PS customer service advised me to do it, gets you a warranty extension within 1 year of purchase. 

All you simply have to do is head over to the PS Store, on the PS4 itself and look up Protection Plan. 

**Note: I was told this by a PS Customer Service: "If you buy it from a phone or a computer, in the long run it can affect you because when you buy it from a PS system, they get the serial number from where the purchase comes from, and the plan is attached to that same serial. If you don't, the plan may or many not be applied to the serial number of your system"**

Then, you will have two options: [Protection Plan *with* Accidental Damage](https://store.playstation.com/#!/en-us/games/playstation-protection-plan-ps4-accidental-damage-36-months/cid=UP9007-CUSA00289_00-PS4ADH0000000000) or [Protection Plan *without* Accidental Damage](https://store.playstation.com/#!/en-us/games/playstation-protection-plan-ps4-non-accidental-damage-36-months/cid=UP9007-CUSA00290_00-PS4NAD0000000000)

Both plans are at a 10% discount for PS+ Members.

After you purchase the item, you will get an email confirming the purchase. From the day of purchase, up to 15 days, you will receive an email, welcoming you the plan. One day later, you will receive the plan's number, in case you need it in the long run. 

Once you get the second info email, call PS and just ask if your Protection Plan is active. They will help you out. 

In my case, I bought my system on 11/23/15. Bought plan on 11/22/16 with one repair case in the middle (July 19th). Called in today before making the post to make sure everything is good and not spread misinformation and PS support did confirmed that my Plan is active, until July 19th of 2019. 

Good luck!

Edit: Forgot to mention:

The Plan requires you to have Proof Of Purchase (POP). If you lost it, many retailers, like Gamestop can print it to you, email it to you, and even send the receipt themselves to Sony </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is my application being denied, even though I meet all requirements? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I requested to join twice and my request keeps being denied. Am I missing something? 

SC: ErickR13 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple stops signing iOS 5.1.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone feels like the 1sec deploy for the Pekka is actually a good thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Pekka is now a 'somewhat' viable solution for the RG, and Elite Barbs (both with negative trades). 

The 1sec deploy also helps you as it can overwhelm your opponent in 2x time. She works like a Giant now. 

The only thing that annoys me of her deploy change is the sound. You can hear when she activates and like 2 seconds later "Ergh destroy".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REDDIT_TITLE_SOFTWAREGORE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone noticed how close is Android Wear 2.0 to WatchOS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From [Google's Blog](https://blog.google/products/android-wear/android-wear-20-make-most-every-minute/): 

 "The Google Assistant on your wrist

 Android Wear 2.0 brings the Google Assistant to your wrist, so you can find answers and get things donehands free. Ask your Google Assistant about the weather or remind yourself to bring an umbrella. Make a restaurant reservation or navigate to work. You can even update your shopping list right from your wrist. To ask for help, just hold down the power button on your watch or say Ok Google." The Google Assistant is available in English and German on Android Wear and will be available in other languages in the coming months."

Siri on the Watch. Although, Google Assistant is better, but the execution is similar to Apple's. 

 "More personalized, helpful watch faces

 You can now personalize your Android Wear always-on watch face with information and actions from your favorite apps. Simply glance at your wrist to check your next appointment, stock performance, progress on fitness goals, or whatever is important to you. A quick tap on your watch face lets you instantly order an Uber ride, start a workout, or get in touch with your significant other. Interested in different info throughout the day? Just swipe to switch your watch face as you go from the office to the gym to dinner with friends and home again."

Possible since WatchOS 3. It isn't clear enough, but it looks like complications are a new thing now. 

 "Better ways to work out

 Google Fit, the pre-installed fitness app on most Android Wear watches, now lets you track your pace, distance, calories burned and heart rate* as youre walking, running or cycling. You can also measure weight-lifting reps, in addition to push-ups, sit-ups and squats. When you work out with a cellular-connected Android Wear watch, you can stay in touch with calls and messages, stream tunes from Google Play Music and still use your favorite apps right on your watch."

Activities and Workout apps. 

 "More ways to respond to messages

 "Now its easier than ever to read and respond to a message right from your watch. When you receive a message, you can expand the notification and tap to respond by dictating, typing or handwriting your answer, or drawing an emoji. Try it out on apps like Facebook Messenger, Glide, Google Messenger, Hangouts, Telegram or WhatsApp. Need to respond quickly and discreetly? Use Smart Reply, which instantly and intelligently suggests different responses based on the message you received."

Dictation, Smart replies are thing since WOS 1 (?),  and Sketches are a thing since WOS 3. Only new is typing. 


My intention isn't to circlejerk. But, is interesting to see how Google bases an update on Apple (I know it can go the other way around). Don't get me wrong, competition is good, and I hope to see an actual and real race on smartwatches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Galaxy Note 7 battery factory catches fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] Cydia seems to have a downloaded a package and is corrupted. Any way to delete it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is what happened:

Veexillium had an update, and tried to upgrade it. I was met with this error: http://imgur.com/a/UjC9s

I tried other packages just to see, and they installed just fine. I uninstalled and tried to install the theme again, same issue

I cleaned the device in iCleaner (I checked the options that are related to Cydia), and nothing.

My theory is that Cydia is trying to continue downloading the .deb from where it failed, so it will keep doing this until I delete the downloaded file. Anyone know the path to the tweaks in Filza? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] Biolockdown by R. Petrich updated with iOS 10 support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] Limneos submitted Bioprotect 2.0 with iOS 10 support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REDDIT_SOFTWAREGORE_TITLE (x-post from /r/iPhone) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yet another good experience from Apple's customer service. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last week, when copying and pasting a code, I noticed my "V" and "C" buttons were a little, down. Like they had something stuck under the keys. 

I looked up what should I do, and the recommendations where to get a compressed air spray [to clean my keyboard](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT205662).

I figured Apple would have that on their stores, and just paid a visit just to double check and see what they could do. 

[The Genius, took my TB MBP in, did an MRI, and everything was fine. However, she did a "physical" test and only saw the "C" key was "depressed".](https://imgur.com/a/JmyJ8). 

The Genius told me "Hold on, I am coming back". Got that email and I saw that "Estimated Turn Around Time" and I was getting ready to know what should I do, while my computer was in repair. 

The Genius comes back, and tells me, "Well subject6752, hold on a few minutes, I am getting the replacement papers ready."

The what? But isn't my computer being repaired? 

5 minutes later, she comes in with a brand new computer. Sealed box, everything new. Opens it, takes the new computer out, gives it to me, takes the old one and puts it back in the box. "You are all set subject6752".

I'm still lost, I didn't understand what happened for a second. 

She told me "I noticed you are going to college, and as a programmer, you need your computer right away, so I convinced my manager to just replace you the computer with a new one on the spot."

So, Mr. Manager and Ms. Genius from the 5th Ave store in NYC. Thank you. I still can't believe I got a brand new computer for just one key being "depressed".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] Limneos submitted AnsweringMachine with iOS 10 support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [News] Springtomize is getting updated for iOS 10 support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] Callbar updated to version 1.3-124. Adds iOS 10 support and fixes minor issues (Bigboss - $3.99) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] ClassicSwitcher 3 updated for iOS 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Submitted CallBar v1.3-124 with iOS 10.x support! - Elias L. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iOS 10.3 beta 32-bit alert suggests Apple may drop legacy app support in iOS 11 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NEWS] Apple stops signing iOS 10.2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the dark times my friends.... Initiate Survival Mode!

Source: https://mobile.twitter.com/TSSstatus/status/826222607003312128 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Release] Yalu102 B2 is released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Beta 3 is also out:

Changelog: fixed apple watch shit and added nonceenabler as default patch

Same steps as below to update 

--------


https://yalu.qwertyoruiop.com


To update:

1-) Reboot device
2-) Download .ipa
3-) Delete installed app
4-) Sideload the new beta
5-) Jailbreak


Changelog: yalu102 for 6s/SE/6/5s, iPod Touch 6 and iPad Pro and a bunch of other iPad Minis (all 64 bit minus i7) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Experimental 4x device support has been added to Yalu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] MKBHD - iPhone 7 review: 4 months later </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/srj-NLj4Kt0


TLDW:

* Best vibration in any smartphone. Period.

* Apple is "future thinking" the wireless life? Yes. Are they agresive about it? Yes. Is the lack of a jack a pain in the ass? Yes. 

* Best camcorder. Period.

* Camera is on par with Samsung's but photo processing is top-notch. 

* If you are on videography or photography and you want a phone, iPhone is the best choice. Especially the 7+.

* A10 is lit. It is considered the best responsive phone for Marques. No phone is as smooth and responsive to that. The Pixel and the OPO 3T are there, but not there. 

* Battery Life is about the same as last year, okay, but not great. The 7+ is really good on battery.

* "Apple, you made the phone the same dimension, and increased the battery. Keep doing that"

* Biggest complains: No jack, and no USB C.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple Developer Services are back online, you should be able to install Yalu and any other jailbreak apps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://developer.apple.com/system-status/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple inexplicably removes iCloud Activation Lock status page, which helped people avoid buying stolen iPhones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The iOS 10.3 update will allow devs have an option to change app icon on the go with user consent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: https://twitter.com/jakemarsh/status/823978792989249538

https://twitter.com/stroughtonsmith/status/823988446108774400 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple's iOS 10.3 beta hits with cricket scores, 'find my AirPods' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Seeds First Beta of iOS 10.3 to Developers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [News] iOS 10.3 Beta 1 is out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else not being able to reach fra.dot.gov on T-Mobile's network? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 16:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link for the lazy: http://www.fra.dot.gov </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC][Bug] YSK that there is only 9 arenas as of 1/24, not 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 16:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone 21 years old go into a Tesla Store and just ride a Tesla? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not looking to have a test drive, but rather a walkthrough and just a ride to experience it. Is it possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Watch Restore Cable pops up at a store for $500 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.vipprogrammer.com/apple-watch-restore-cable-rebooting-cable-update-recovery-watchos-system-programmer-3446

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vine officially becomes Vine Camera [App download link] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for leAngrySquirrel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Any one care to help me create a Jailbreak "hub" for all info, news, and etc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 22:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I have in mind:

* Create a website with jailbreak info, news, tutorials and etc. Maybe name can be jailbreak.me (.com is taken). Content can be curated by posts from this sub, submitted via email, or just from the team members. 

* Twitter handle for support and news (Facebook too). 

* Email support too. 

* Youtube for tweaks showcase, and how-to (HT Jailbreak, HT fix cellular/data bugs in iOS 10 are examples).


Mainly I am looking to make a No-BS project (no clickbait, no fake JB news/info). I feel this could help the whole JB community (not just the Reddit part of the community), and could actually ease tensions of devs asking for help/info

PM me!

Edit: We need 1-2 Youtubers! Apply here: https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/5o97f6/discussion_we_are_looking_for_12_people_to_become/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consumer Reports just changed its mind and now recommends the new MacBook Pro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 01:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] iOS 10.2.1 B4 is out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IF ELIF statements not working as expected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for shitty title. I didn't know how to word my problem in just one sentence. 

Here is the problem I am having:

I am using IF ELIF statements to take "different routes" in my program. 

Here is a snippet: 

http://pastebin.com/GcWN8r9T

Whenever I try to choose the second, third or fourth route, my program outputs the first route. 

Here is an example:

I chose route 2: "T"

My program goes the "C" route.

If I choose "T" - "Area", it will go "C" - "Area". 

What am I doing wrong? I can't figure out what the actual issue is                                     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple releases iOS 10.2.1 Beta 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/iosreleases/status/818516683417649153

This means that iOS 10.2 will see a few more days alive. Don't rush to update until the jailbreak comes out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Dev 3 of 10.2.1 is out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this Model 3 in the Facebook group. Thought you guys might appreciate it as well! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 04:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Strategy][Deck] Elite Barbs and 3 Musk deck that got me to my PB (3822) from High A8, low A10. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 21:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, first Strategy/Deck post, so if I am doing something wrong, please tell me! 

I know he Elite Barbs (referred as EB henceforth) are pretty disliked in the community, so they will get a nerf soon. However, during this time, I tried to use them until they get nerfed. To my surprise, they shot me to almost 4k, from 2900-3020. If they helped me, they can help you. 

My deck is based on both, the EB, and the 3 Musketeers (3M henceforth). They are both my win condition cards, and they both are also my defenses. 

My deck is composed from the 3B (lvl 11 [lvl 10 works fine here as well]), 3M (lvl 7), 3 minions (lvl 10), Musk (lvl 7), Elixir Collector (lvl 7), Zap (lvl 10), Archers (lvl 10), and The Log (lvl 2 [will provide alternatives in its section])

#Why do you use those cards?

EB: Win condition card. They are fast, strong, and can support most spells. They almost never go alone, unless I know my opponent has no elixir. They are also my main defenses. Golem can't kill them (death damage), Giant Skeleton can't (Death Damage), Pekka takes 3 shots to kill them. Overall, they have no direct counters. Now, one thing I hate to have the EB go against with, is the Ice Wizard. They become slow and attack like the reg barbs. If you have an IW, and you go against me, I would hate you and love you too (I love all my opponents..... I need some friends). So a IW, and a Sk Army will do great against the EB. Just keep it in mind (and is also an equal trade). 

3M: I hate them tbh. They are weak to every spell (you know what I mean), are weak against death damages (Golem, Giant Sk). If you leave them alone, they can rekt you however. I use them for the simple reason that some people will fireball, or Lightning the Barbs, and when they do, I use the 3M as they won't have a spell to kill them. In the replays below, you can see that. 

Elixir Collector: Pretty straightforward. You have a 9 elixir and a 6 elixir card. You need to have elixir to have a chance to use them and cycle. 

Minions: Support and defense. They only go with the barbs as support. No much to say.

Musk: Instead of having 3 musks, why don't you have 4? No, I don't use them like that, but like the Minions, she is Support, Defense **and bait**. She is the one to let you know if the opponent has fireball and etc. 

Archers: Support and defense. Not much to say. 

Zap: Sparky reset, inferno tower reset, everything reset, and helps with Sk Army. I also use them so that my EBs have an advantage against other EBs (think reset). 

Log: The positive elixir trade king. Kills princesses, Sk Army if Zap isn't available, gets rid of tombstones and the skeletons that get out when it breaks and pushed back troops. What else can you ask? Now, if you don't have it, you can use a Fire Spirit, Ice, or Spear Gobs. They aren't great alternatives, but is something.

#How do you play them?

Here is two wins (two battles in one video): https://youtu.be/QuxiZ4DkHJI

Here is two loses (2 battles in one video): https://youtu.be/O_Ue2JChmNM

I hope I have helped you, and use the EB while it isn't nerfed! It can help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] Anyone else have an IW in their army and will try to not place him in a field? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 02:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of 10 that I planned to keep I wasted 6. I guess I won't be attacking at all (MM War)this year... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview for Bakirfatah99 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 01:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Double Elixir Challenge is coming back! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CES 2017: Faraday Future Shows Off 'FF 91' Connected Electric Car for 2018 Release </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 04:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FF's Live Stream Reveal at CES 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any Tesla fans watching the Faraday   Future flagship car unveil today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supposedly, it should be the "direct" competitor to Tesla. Which is a good thing as I feel that Tesla has no actual 'direct' competition, and a direct one should motivate Tesla to do better. Like Apple and Google. 

It is even said that the prototype won against a S100D. 

Link to stream's page here: https://www.ff.com/en/

Edit: It has started. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple - Best of 2016 (Music, Apps, Movies, Podcasts, TV Shows and Book) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 22:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8lspg7nMpdc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla -- "If you couldn't order by 12/31, you can still order by 1/15 to receive unlimited SuperCharging" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 20:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/TeslaMotors/status/815633800403308545 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to add a code to my program that identifies the first letter of the word entered. How do I go about this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, Happy New Years!

Based on a Codecademy lesson, I made my own version of [Pyg Translator](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pig_Latin#Rules).

I was looking to add more features, and one of them was to detect whether the user entered a word starting with a consonant, or a vowel. 

I tried using the .startswith(vowel) function, after I defined vowel in an array, but a syntax error comes up and I can't figure out what actually is the error. 

How do I go about this? If possible, I would like to set up an if function to check for this. 

For those interested, the code is here: http://erickjreyes.me/PygTranslator/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] App Admin updated with iOS 10 support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 03:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tweak is at beta.unlimapps.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows, my what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 02:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Luca has a modified version of Yalu B3 with TSMC support. Release anytime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 01:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] CPDD got Slide to Unlock "semi-working" on iOS 10! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 01:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Release] Yalu B4 released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 03:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Release] First release of CoolBooter released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 02:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BUG] When the status bar has an active alert (In-Call, Hostpot, GPS, Recording), Narwhal bugs out and won't let me do any action </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] There is someone going around telling people to install AppSync. Please don't. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 04:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't fall for it.

Mods, please ban them: /u/WhenETASon

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Holidays /r/PS4! Are you (or your family member) new to the PS4 ? Then this is for you! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 04:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greetings!

As Christmas approaches, I wanted to make a friendly welcome and guide to those who are expecting a PS4 on Christmas, or will give one away and should know a few things about it. 

My guide is in a Google Drive folder, separated into different documents to make it as friendly as possible. 

Direct link is here: https://drive.google.com/open?id=0B_PlSBWevx_JZ2N1ZlVEc1JIQzg

Happy holidays! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steps to activate Model X performance Holiday - Elon Musk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 02:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/812463378270588928

Step 1 - Park in an open space

Step 2 - Tap and Hold Tesla T on Center Display

Step 3 - Type holidays or ModelXmas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it advisable to open a checking account to use as savings account? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 23:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello PF!

I currently have a checking account with BofA (student account). I planned to open a Savings account with them, however, to avoid fees I need a $300 (or 2.5k) or link an interest checking account (which I don't have). 

Is it advisable to open a checking account (for students), to avoid paying monthly fees and start saving up? I plan to go with a Capital One 360, or a Chase Student Account.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a new Adversary Mode, Juggernaut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 05:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/rockstargames/status/812145236394778624 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a new Adversary Mode, Juggernaut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 05:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/rockstargames/status/812145236394778624 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple lauched Mac-like UI for iCloud's photos app </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.icloud.com/#photos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple stops signing iOS 10.1.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple stops signing iOS 10.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Watch S1/S2 now available in Apple's refurbished store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla Model S Problems: My Experience! || MKBHD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 00:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Misc] After a battle ends, you can see how many crowns you got for your clan chest (if the crown chest do count to your clan chest or not) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 06:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MKBHD's car had an issue where his steering wheel locked twice while driving. Is it a hardware issue or a software one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 21:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incident 1: http://i.imgur.com/ZW3aJSB.jpg 

Incident 2: http://i.imgur.com/ScSLJuc.jpg 

Is it something having to do with hardware or software? 

https://twitter.com/MKBHD/status/810578253836648449 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone I meet is blown away when they see my Rocket Voltic (x-post /r/GrandTheftAutoV) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 01:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Third post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 04:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP Harambe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GTAV Title Update 1.37 (PS4/Xbox One/PC) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With today's update, you can chage the type of glow in your "Tron" clothing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interaction Menu - Style - Up - Illuminated Clothing

You have 4 options: Off, On, Pulse, and Flash

Video: https://youtu.be/JB6g_Lah3sw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With today's update, you can change the type of glow of your "Tron" clothing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interaction Menu - Style - Up - Illuminated Clothing

You have 4 options: Off, On, Pulse, and Flash

Video: https://youtu.be/JB6g_Lah3sw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sneak Peek 1 - New Arena </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 00:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple releases iOS 10.2 with new TV app, new emojis and changes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 18:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For some reason Spotify doesn't want to close </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] iOS 10.2 Beta 7 released! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/iosreleases/status/806556682771959814 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Jailbreak Awards 2016 - Setup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 06:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are a longtime lurker and poster, you might notice that ever since 2012, we have our own Jailbreak awards to recognize the works of fellow devs and members of the community. 

Why should this year be the exception?

Let's get it together! PM your email address if you would like to form part of the JBA 2016 team!

Updates about the awards coming in the next few days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] iOS 10.2 Beta 6 released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/iosreleases/status/805834339074375680 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Youtuber has stolen content from somebody and is using it to promote his channel and get money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 21:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple releases iOS 10.2 Beta 5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple seeds 10.2 Beta 5 || Macrumors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  http://www.macrumors.com/2016/12/02/apple-seeds-ios-10-2-beta-5/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS Community app out today on iOS and Android </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 18:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] iOS 10.2 B4 available as OTA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 21:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple releases 4th beta of iOS 10.2 || Macrumors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.macrumors.com/2016/11/28/apple-seeds-ios-10-2-beta-4-to-developers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any way to flash the ASUS TM-AC1900 Router to stock firmware? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My router is at 3.0.0.4.376_3169 , is there anything I can do to flash this router to stock firmware? I have looked around this sub and I see things for old SW.

My main interest to flash a stock firmware is to use the ASUS router app in my phone to enable parental control and disable it, without me needing to go to a computer to enable/disable it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [bug] Editing a comment via your user page hides the title of the post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 17:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *What's the problem?*
 Editing a comment in your user page will hide the title of the post you commented on. 


*What other browser extensions are installed?*
ADB+ 

*Did you read the known issues and search /r/RESissues?*
Yes, I didn't find anything matching the bug

Video here: https://youtu.be/MxDVdN1oQ3c



- Night mode: false
- RES Version: 5.0.3
- Browser: Chrome
- Browser Version: 54
- Cookies Enabled: true
- Reddit beta: false </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any Tesla owners have the T-Mobile Sync Drive UP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case you don't know what it is, is a device that attaches to your car, that gives you diagnostic about the car, and also gives you data to share as a Wi-Fi hotspot in the car. 

If you have a 6GB plan, you get BingeON, which means that video will not count against your data. 


https://explore.t-mobile.com/t-mobile-sync-up-drive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ASK] Doesn't the game balance cards based on what you have and what not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 05:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever a common is released, I can easily get it to tournament levels. Rares take a little bit of challenge, but is easy to get it to tournament levels. 

Now Epics and Legendary cards seems to not follow this pattern.

2 weeks after the tornado release, I have been opening Gold chests, Magical chests, and etc, but no Tornado was given to me. I also noticed this behavior when I reached new arenas. For example, when I reached A8, I got the Bowler 3 weeks after. 

For legendary, I believe we should have a higher chance to get other legendary cards we don't have, as a opposed to getting the same ones. Some people in my clan, including me, have found the same legendary cards again and again. 

In my case, I have opened/purchased 4 legendary chests. I got 3 logs and one Princess from it. I mean, I like the log, but I would very much prefer not getting it if it means that I have a higher chance of finding the others. 

Am I just going crazy, or is this how the game works? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As per FDNY, Pedestrian struck and pinned by a train in 3rd Ave and 149th Street in the Bronx. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 02:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will I lose my two free lines if I cancel a line now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 02:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I activated a line within the last 90 days before the free lines promotion started. However, I would like to cancel that line as the person using it is just being obnoxious and won't pay up. Can I cancel that line and still keep the two free lines?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Mom's S0 died when she was running it under tap water. A few days later it came back to life. What might have happened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As my mom was doing the dishes, she ran the AW under water to clean it (nothing spilled on it though) and it died. It wouldn't reset, it wasn't connected to the phone, it was dead. I put it on the charger and it wouldn't react to anythig and left it there until I can send it to repair on the A-Store.

One day ago, it came back to life. Like nothing happened. It didn't know what time and date it was as it didn't connect to the phone however. 

I tested everything, vibration, sound, and everything was fine. What could have happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fusion! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 02:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS Vue out for ATV today! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question, in order to buy the new clothes part of the Deadline add-on, do I need to buy the bike first? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] iOS 10.2 B3 is out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 18:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Binge On, 1 year after, how has it changed the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today is the one year anniversary of Binge On! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple starts selling 16GB iPhone 6S in their refurbished store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone 6S, 16GB available in Apple's refurbished store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> King's Cup ended! How did you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My max wins was 10, what was yours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iOS 10.2 Beta 2 brought a new app, TV. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 19:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screenshots: 

http://i.imgur.com/PwaEVGn.png 

http://i.imgur.com/dVWhUYB.png 


Short description coming soon after I test it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iOS 10.2 B2 available for testing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Half an hour for the King's Cup to start, are you guys ready? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you can't use your cards/deck, what tactics do you plan to use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Musk: In addition, we reinforced the surrounding body structure for improved safety (was already 5 star in all categories). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cubs are up 4-1 in the 5th inning... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 02:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Title.Reddit.Software] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 01:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silver DS4, available late December. Gold DS4 to be released later this month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 23:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All right we get it, Inferno Dragon was moved to A8, now stop posting it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maintance Over! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Update is live! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple stops signing 10.0.2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple has released iOS 10.1.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/iosreleases/status/793105193151897600 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first link of this post makes 2.7 crash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sneak Peek 3: Special Event Chalenges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/clashroyale/status/793075743102230529

SNEAK PEEK #3 - Special Event Challenges!

- Introducing the first special event challenge: King's Cup!
- Play the King's Cup on Nov 4th

Edit: 

Extra info: Thanks /u/Julz72!

Blind deck! If gives you and your opponent random decks with 6 defined cards and 2 completely random cards!

https://youtu.be/Eca03QykWS8

Chief Pats informative vid ^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sneak Peek 2: 4 new cards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 13:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sneak Peeks coming! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 05:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Hotz cancels his Tesla Autopilot-like comma one after request from NHTSA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 16:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  Title </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 04:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else disappointed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's official. No new iMac or Mac Pro. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bring your Pixel to T-Mobile and Cut its Cost in Half! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 15:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 hours and a half before the Keynote, what are you expecting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 13:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Speculation] G-Pixel to be available on T-Mobile soon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 02:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Truecaller has been updated to support PhoneKit in iOS10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 02:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Changelog: http://i.imgur.com/uSJtozC.png 

New option under Settings - Phone - Call Blocking http://i.imgur.com/LYBKBlD.png  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What episode does Stewie say this line? (See page) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 03:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> tvOS 10.0.1 software update for Apple TV is now available for everyone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 19:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple has released iOS 10.1! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 19:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MKBHD || Google Assistant Vs. Siri </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 04:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/JFiu5rfnhzo

Actually, Siri held up her ground. I'm surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sony isn't at fault for their downtime today. But I pay them so they need to fix it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 01:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meme] me_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 23:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] iOS 10.1 Beta 5 is available for testing! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk says first 12 months of Tesla Model 3 production are sold out, what does it mean for the federal tax credit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple stops signing iOS 9.3.5 and iOS 10.0.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 01:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only softwares you can restore to are 10.0.2 and 10.1! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple stops signing iOS 9.3.5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 01:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple stops signing iOS 10.0.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 01:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] iOS 10 Beta 4 is out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 21:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/iOSReleases/status/788106051673612289 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iOS 10.0.3 out for iPhone 7 and 7 plus! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 19:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does Multiplayer/Splitscreen work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 15:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you need like 2 VR to play together with VR games?

Also, can Splitscreen games have the ability to keep one screen on the TV and the other on the VR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Direct hit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 02:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else being kicked out of lobbies when trying to do MC business by other players? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since we can't do our MC business nor CEO business is Private and/or Invite only, we have to resort in having to play in Public lobbies.

But the thing is that doing it in a full lobby will bring clusterfuck and loss of money. So that's why I resort in finding "semi-empty" lobbies to do my business.

But I'm always getting kicked out of these lobbies so I never can do my MC Business. I don't shoot unless I am shot first. I don't go and hunt crates to destroy. I just do me and if you need help I'm in.
Anyone else experiencing this?

Here is a video so you guys can see that I'm not hostile to anyone and I'm getting kicked.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SyeeiOhlBbs https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RVZXp9vRNmk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else being kicked out of lobbies when trying to do MC business by other players? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since we can't do our MC business nor CEO business is Private and/or Invite only, we have to resort in having to play in Public lobbies. 

But the thing is that doing it in a full lobby will bring clusterfuck and loss of money. So that's why I resort in finding "semi-empty" lobbies to do my business.

But I'm always getting kicked out of these lobbies so I never can do my MC Business. I don't shoot unless I am shot first. I don't go and hunt crates to destroy. I just do me and if you need help I'm in. 

Anyone else experiencing this?

Here is a video so you guys can see that I'm not hostile to anyone and I'm getting kicked.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SyeeiOhlBbs
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RVZXp9vRNmk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Apple Maps on the Mac can send addresses to your iOS devices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 03:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as in iMessage/SMS, not as Airdrop, but as push notifications. 

Google Maps has this feature for a while now, but I like that Apple has it stock. Is the little things I didn't know I needed.

Gif of the action: http://imgur.com/a/aTfSX </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [News] Ice Golem Sneak Peak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (x-post from /r/Apple) Here is a way to try Apple Pay on Safari for free </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This website](https://stripe.com/apple-pay) has a code to test Apple Pay via Safari on Sierra and iOS 10. Apple Pay will say is 0.01 is the total due, but they charge won't go trough on the website, thus you won't be charged.

I just tried it and it is a seamless experience and I'm happy that Apple added this in iOS 10 and Sierra.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biker DLC one week later, how did you waste your money? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 03:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What clubhouse and business did you get? Any bikes you bought?

Fill this out :) 

https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScD0xVci_VCzQhOgSzyJtioD4HaDTod67SbabQg1xk_hFRgJw/viewform

I can post the results if requested. I just want to know what are the popular choices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biker DLC one week later, how did you spend your money? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 03:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What clubhouse and business did you get? Any bikes you bought?

Answer this: https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScD0xVci_VCzQhOgSzyJtioD4HaDTod67SbabQg1xk_hFRgJw/viewform

I can post the results if requested. I just want to know what are the popular choices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] iOS 10 Beta 3 is out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/iosreleases/status/785523504871538688 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-Mobile halting sales of Note 7 || John Legere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 01:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
