<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1178</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 17:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Masturbating. Now I have hourly breaks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 14:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.drunkard.com/issues/10_06/10_06_andre_giant.html
Said article  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 22:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> recipe in comments pleeeeeeaaaaaaaassssseeeeeeeeeee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 16:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 15:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Silly old bum!](http://youtu.be/qrBj3u5dPgM)

Edit:Link + possibly NSFW
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 14:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 00:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm gonna advise against drinking that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 18:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop. It sucks but stop for at least 2 weeks, go swimming or cycling, just not running for a while. I gave myself a shin fracture by running through my shin splints and trust me, t's not worth it :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 13:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't make it to the Falko in Gullen, they have one at Bruntsfield!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 20:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Copyright is mine mofo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 19:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bit of Joss Acklands spunky backpack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 19:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No! I sell something better! Cake. Dangerous dangerous Cake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 18:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a sad truth but I actually have... I also used to watch the kids TV show that was filmed on the set. The sticky sticky set...
 :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 15:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We told my friend that there is a brand of foot long cigarettes called "Keith Chegwins". Keith Chegwin was a cheesy British TV presenter for those that don't know. He believes this for nearly a year and would go into shops and ask for them - with very confused shop staff saying "uh... No...." And looking at him like he was crazy. Dude was pissed when he found out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 16:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bin that shit - Vermouth is good for a month maximum and only if refrigerated. It's wine! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 17:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have! That was my first port of call - I tried it with bulleit and it was good - it really accentuated the toffee in it. I think that it would work better with something like rittenhouse - it needs more of a rye kick to be balanced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Porter syrup uses? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 16:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently made a porter syrup (recipe below) and have been experimenting with it and I was wondering what you guys would use it for? It has a pleasant maltiness with a sweetness similar to maple syrup.

1 Bottle porter (I used Tap Out smoked porter)
Sugar

1)Bring to just below the boil then turn to a gentle simmer for 30-40 minutes until 1/3rd of the original volume.
2) at this point it helps to have scales, weigh the porter and add 3/4 of the weight in sugar (does that make sense?) and stir until the sugar is dissolved.
3) chill. TADA! Porter syrup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 01:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I be the rat king?!? 
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rat_king_(folklore)
On second thought... Maybe not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 19:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boodles is absolutely fantastic - the lack of citrus in the botanicals makes for a very interesting Negroni, really brings out the sweetness in the Campari for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 12:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tuuuuunnnneeee!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 00:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scales work fine! (In a pinch) 1g of water was originally defined as the mass of 1ml of water and booze really isn't that much thicker what with it being mostly water and all. Sure for cream of something maybe it's not right, but es-335's ratios all work out fine :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 11:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I challenge anyone to not read this in Neil Oliver's voice. I am now considerably more relaxed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 02:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you means smells like bacon.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 02:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do orphans play tennis?

It's the only way they can get love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 17:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah your bob on. It can also be called a Diamond Fizz and is just a variation of a Gin Fizz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 15:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 35ml spiced orange gin
25ml lemon juice
25ml simple syrup
Champagne

1. Shake lemon juice, gin and simple 
2. Strain into a glass full of crushed ice (apparently my parents house has no highballs, thus the red wine glass)
3. Top with champagne </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merry Christmas! Spiced Orange Champagne Fizz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 15:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 11:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You slap the bag you drink the bag! Chief chief chief! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 00:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmmm crystalised piss... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 12:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kenny Anderson and the Fence Collective on New Years Day. Sorted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 19:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drinkmonger at bruntsfield has an awesome selection as well! Mighty me spoilt for choice eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 13:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I woke to sucking
Better than alarm clock
I am satisfied </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 14:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Newsroom runs one at 9 I think. It's the same guy who does the one at the Cellar Monkey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 14:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off - we are mostly just drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 17:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really missed a trick - it should have been a bunch of banana facts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 17:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the most important point on my Mandelbrot set in the Y axis so consequently - Numberwang! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 17:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lager and cream in a shooter. A really terrible idea, but it was fun at 5am </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 23:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tagged as "its all pointless" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 20:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat means no ice... I think you want an unchilled cocktail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 16:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best band on Tru Thoughts and genuinely the best live show I have had the pleasure of seeing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 15:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't. Whatever you do. Don't.

That shit is so sweet - bitters would be wasted. Get yourself some bulleit or some dark rum then give it a go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 15:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whiskey sours are a shaken drink most def - if it has juice it's shaken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 14:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was deemed to be in seine (if he drowned) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 21:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captains is a frickin awesome wee pub! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 12:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is one of my worst fears - having a mental disorder and no one has told me :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 19:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Numberwang! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 00:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your choice of words is um... poor... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 20:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my favourite movie duo ever, such amazing chemistry. They always had the best lines.
"Bacall: You go too far, Marlowe.
Bogart: Those are harsh words to throw at a man, especially when he's walking out of your bedroom." for example </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 16:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this not the Redeker plan mentioned in World War Z? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 14:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 21:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really weird, i just got given one of these today... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 14:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem - I didn't know about him either! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A quick look at an under appreciated Edinburgh artist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 11:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 16:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The human anus is almost nightmarishly elastic -But moving on swiftly, this is how I got away with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 16:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lion King the musical behind the scenes exhibition at the city art centre on market street is free and from 12:30 till 2:30 there is a free workshop on the ground floor making necklaces :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 20:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second Canny Mans :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 17:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sort of... I't doesn't come with the black outs just a big dose of rowdy but whether thats just the scottish thing or the caffeine i dont know. A bucky bomb is a beautiful thing though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 16:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You lickspittle ninnyhammer!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 00:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As i said not a believer. When I worked there just after mopping the floor one evening after close, pouring the bucket down the toilet I hear "JOHNNYDONTDOIT COME INTO THE OFFICE!!!" thinking its my boss I run into the office. No one there. Just a little weirded out I leave the office and go into the cellar to put the bucket away, coming out the cellar it happens again so back into the office. Again no one there. When I go to push the door open I find its jammed, no biggy just give it a push. Nothing. Try again. Nothing. I end up having to slam my full weight against the door to open it which had never happened to me before or anyone since (as far as i'm aware). When I go upstairs my boss is standing with the one other member of bar staff and i instantly ask them whether they were messing with me. They say they hadn't been and with me more than a lot weirded out I make my boss show me the CCTV - neither of them had left the upstairs part of the bar for the 20 minutes over which this had happened. This was when they told me about the ghost. I still dont believe but they certainly did and I can see why - ask most of the long term staff there and they will have a story to tell, all with logical explanations but god damn a lot of weird shit has happened in that pub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 00:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That place is spooky as all hell, no ghosts to speak of but creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
