<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6749</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Bank error in your favor, collect $50" -monopoly chance card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 04:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my third grade class, my teacher was so into sign language that she "forced" it on us. Some days just to show us how hard it is for some, we weren't allowed to talk and could only sign. I really wish I would have kept more of that knowledge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 07:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also if you are feeling extra adventurous and want to save all that money that you have, check out the seasonal life of working in the national parks. It changed my life and whenever I think that I'm at a low point or near there, I know that they provide modest housing and will help feed me until the first paycheck with them. The website is called coolworks.com and it's totally worth looking into, especially somebody so young still. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 03:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To know that whatever is making you upset will pass in due time. Also that karma is a bitch and you hope they die or something when they leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This park bench has its own Ecosystem growing underneath it.[OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 20:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 06:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One does not pick the cat, the cat picks you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 08:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my home state and love that anybody goes there to see these stupid things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Northern Oregon coast. [OC] [6494 X 3118] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 04:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 16:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really difficult! But I keep trying to master it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My roommate's continuing attempts at sourdough bread, resulted in these pull-apart rolls.[OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 08:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
