<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4489</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Your Choice to Believe it Or Not; part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Your Choice to Believe it or Not... Part 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's your choice. Believe it or not. No, I'm not talking about that book that was published with all those wacky pictures, no, I'm talking about an event that I myself encountered. if you're reading this at night, beware, you are going to be paranoid of your surroundings from now on. This event happened awhile back...
Here we go.....

I'm sitting on my bed, spring break just started(sorry for you guys who still have school), and I'm looking at my phone laughing to myself. I'm not a weirdo. Just looking at iFunny because I had nothing else to do. It was dawn outside. Let me make one thing clear, I'm all alone. My parents had to go somewhere for reasons, and I was left at home. Don't worry, I'm old enough to stay at home by myself. 

So I'm sitting here and I start to here sounds above my head. I figured since my bed is in front of window with a curtain, I thought the sound was coming from somewhere outside. I ignore it, and I go back to looking on my phone. An hour or two later, it was starting to get dark outside and I was starting to get hungry too. I'm about to exit my room and I hear the sound again. the weird thing is that it started to rain outside just as I heard it. I go to look outside the window and I see this tall figure standing next to the tree outside my house. I'm not joking, that thing was creepy as heck and it creeped the hell out of me. 

I was starting to get scared. It was raining, my parents weren't home yet, and I'm starting to see things. Just like in the movies, I ignored it, Just Kidding, I started to get a little panicked. I run downstairs to my kitchen because my hunger was drawing me there. I remembered we had hot dogs. I heated one up and put one on a bun. I don't know how you eat hot dogs, but I don't put mustard or ketchup on my hot dogs. I like to put hot sauce and pepper flakes. Anyways I bring my hot dogs(I made a couple) on my plate and I go to sit at the kitchen table. I like to watch videos on my tablet, so I put on some headphones, plugged them in, and I watched my tablet as I eat. 

As I was watching, out of the corner of my eye, I saw something dash away. I quickly looked but I saw nothing. I usually sit on the chair of the kitchen table that was farthest to the kitchen door that led outside. The chair faced away from the door. And the blinds that covered the kitchen door had a semi-big tear so that someone could stalk me from the outside and I wouldn't know. That thought scared me, so I sat at a different seat. Every so often, I would glance up to make sure that no one was peering in through that opening. As I finished up eating, I went to my kitchen sink and washed my plate. I glanced back at the little opening for one last look(yah I think I was paranoid now) and I saw something. More like a face. I almost dropped my plate. 

(Edited) HERE IS PART 2: Well, welcome back to part 2. 

Let's get back to where we last left off. First of all, thx for tuning back in, I appreciate it. Now onwards with the story: We have a motion sensored light outside my house, and my house is fitted with an alarm system because my neigborhood isn't that great. The motion sensored light was just turned on after I saw the person standing outside. I started to freak out and I quickly washed my plate. I quickly started to think that I was in danger. I started to think back to the figure I saw earlier in the indie. Maybe "it" was stalking me. I quickly grabbed my phone and called my parents. In a rush, I told them that I may have seen someone outside the house. My parents started to sound distressed. They quickly told me   to get to a safe place in the house because they were rushing back to the house just as I called. I asked them, "why are you guys rushing back before I called?" My parents told me to stay calm, because there were some disturbing news on the news channel. The news people said that there was a storm out, (that explained why it was raining) but not only that... they said that prior to the storm, there was a watch for a lost, uncontrolled individual who escaped from a mental prison. He had previously escaped the security premises, and could be found anywhere, at anytime. 

They said he was wearing mostly dark clothes and could be around these counties: my parents told me a list of neighborhoods especially the name of my area in that list. I think I was having a panic attack or something but I couldn't think straight. My hands and my whole body started to tremble as I heard the news. I had a thousand questions running through my head. Was the dark figure I saw the crazy guy on the news? I started running around my house making sure everything was locked. I grabbed my electronics, and I ran upstairs to my room. I quickly grabbed the remote that tells my alarm to ring in case the crazy guy outside decides to come in. I waited silently. I tried not to make noise. I tried not to lose my courage. I kept telling myself: I ain't going to die tonight. It was started to hail a little bit outside just to make it worse. Then I heard the noises again, this time it was coming from downstairs. It was like as if something was trying to tear the outside of my house down. It kept getting louder and louder until I heard a loud crash.

There were sounds coming from all directions. It was like moaning or screaming mixed in with the sounds of the hail. I started to pray. After a few minutes, everything became silent. I waited anxiously. As I was starting to calm down, the sound of my alarm going off sent shivers through my whole body. I think the person downstairs destroyed my alarm. i heard footsteps running around downstairs. I didn't think twice, I hit the panic button on my alarm remote hoping that would do something. Miraculously, the alarm sent the entire house in loud noise!
I heard the footsteps run towards the stairs and then back towards the kitchen area. It was like hard boots on the wooden floor. After a few minutes, I never heard them again. A few moments later, I could hear the sound of cars coming in the direction of my house. It was my parents who had arrived. Behind them the police arrived. I heard their voices calling out my name and I ran downstairs as fast a I could. Dang, I was so glad to see them!

The police came in and inspected the house as well. I looked at what had happened too. The kitchen table had been flipped to its side, the kitchen door was wide open because its hinges were destroyed, there were plates broken on the floor, and everything was a mess. I thought to myself, if I had been in that kitchen longer than when I had actually been in there, I probably wouldn't be alive today. I explained everything to my parents and the authorities. They couldn't believe it at all. I was just glad that I had survived this madness. To this day, I still don't know why the maniac targeted my house out of all the other houses. The days that followed, I was paranoid. I made sure that everything was safe when I went to sleep. I made sure that everything was locked when I went to bed. I still see glimpses of something that dashes away every time i look at it in the middle of the night. It happens mostly at my bedroom door. I don't know for sure, but I think the maniac that attacked my house hasn't been caught either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your Choice; Believe It Or Not;Part 1... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your Choice; Believe it or not; part 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
