<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2951</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a thoroughly terrible human being he is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She deserves better. You need to get over yourself and accept she needs a lot of time to heal, and stop making this about your paranoia. If you don't stop, she will end up walking away possibly feeling like her only value is sex. Deeply unpleasant for a rape victim to feel that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAPPER SIR  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He does know how to use his charm, that's for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He really knows how to pull the best puppy eyes with those too. He gets really wide eyed when I ask him if he wants any noms. The eyebrows go up and everything. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His lion impressions sound like he's trying to take a particularly stubborn dump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WAT. Oh dear god.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sex addiction (chronic masturbation is just one aspect of it) is a very real phenomenon, but it'll take more than a video to work through it. Folks can genuinely lose everything because of it, unfortunately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Errrr...

Wow. Well I suppose after 40-odd minutes of THAT, you'd be so turned off it would shrivel up and fall OFF.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EEEEEEEEEEEE!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have to be to put up with that shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking hell what a monumental wankchariot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would totally happen to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There goes my childhood! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 07:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOPE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 07:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor woman. :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 07:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 07:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not allowed to talk anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 07:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scarfolk is eerily accurate in today's political climate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 06:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah that's staged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOPE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says 'wait' in morse code. 

Info says 'we are not starting just yet wait.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cthulhu fhtagn!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck had you been eating to produce that horror?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shitcano.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh dear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> S H A T T E R </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She could have sworn she turned off the television set before she'd gone to bed the night before. Her brow furrowed as she stood in front of it, stooping down, moving closer. Something definitely didn't seem right. Her mother wasn't up yet, so it couldn't have been her--and she definitely remembered switching it off.


She felt drawn in, her breath swirling out to meet the static. It left a steamy circle behind, the static prickling back against her lips with a tingling sensation. She dragged her teeth over her lips to stop the tickle, blinking softly and straightening herself up again. Her gaze changed to a gradual stare as she looked at the screen for a full five minutes.


That's when it happened.


The screen looked fluid. Screwing her eyes shut and blinking rapidly, she tried to clear her sight thinking her eyes were playing tricks with her. She'd been staring for so long, it had to be the same sensation she felt as a kid when she sat too close to the set. She tried to look away, but felt a flash of pain behind her eyes in her attempt.


A single soft ripple moved outward from the centre, moving slowly toward the edges, only to disappear.


She leaned in again, raising her right hand slowly, reaching out to the screen, her fingertips feeling the static millimetres away. Her hair, as yet un-brushed and a little fluffed up, reached toward the static like fine tendrils twisting to wrap around something.


It grabbed her, beginning with a sharp pinching sensation in her hand, trickling its way up her arm. It was viciously cold, and she panicked, her breath quickening, turning into a strangled whimper. It crept painfully up over her shoulder, her skin tightening, draining of all colour. It moved up toward her face, oozing across her jawline, and up to her lips. She was completely rigid with fear, unable to move or make a sound for help. Her lips parted and cracked in a silent scream, the teeth in her mouth shattering like tiny crystals, each feeling like burning needles driven deep inside her. Blood built and seeped over her greying lips, trickling down her chin and onto her nightdress. The blood vessels in her nose exploded, pissing down over her feet and onto the carpet. She tried to look down, but her eyes were frozen in their sockets.


Reaching up for her eyes, the irises turned a stark white, sucking the life from her pupils to leave nothing but a glassy stare. More blood spilled over her face as the capillaries broke, leaving bloody tears running over her seemingly lifeless skin. She stood completely motionless; a stiffening statue with every molecule in her form freezing and twisting. It continued to move down the other side of her body, pinching and biting all over, the static ripping more of her into its field.


It finally took control of her completely, pulling her into its void. She could hear thousands of screaming voices, old and young alike, all clawing at her mind relentlessly.


Her eardrums ruptured, and joined the other streams of blood coursing over her body. The pain was horrific, and it only seemed to build. From the other side of the screen, she could see her blood from the carpet pool together, lose its colour and seep upwards into the screen to join her.


It was as if she was never there; she was completely gone to the world, part of the white noise on-screen. Something shifted in her throat, and she let out a piercing scream. It sounded like someone tearing nails down a blackboard, and with every scream came a splatter of blood, draining of colour and settling on-screen.


Feeling an overwhelming presence behind her, she turned around and saw thousands of bodies in the same state, reaching out with their cracked skin and shrieking voices. She screamed again, turning back to the screen, pounding her fists against it.


The creak of a door upstairs signalled the arrival of her mother, who padded softly down to the living room. Frustrated and terrified she banged harder, desperately trying to scream for help. All that came was blood and that sickening shrieking. She watched in horror as her mother picked up the remote, shook her head and turned off the set.


She obviously didn't hear her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh dear god.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 15:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't breathe ROFL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 19:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SHINY! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 16:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. That seems like moderate depressive behaviour.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 16:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 20:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep this. He should be able to make his own food choices without fear of reprisals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 20:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ROFL  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 18:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What has he had to say about the situation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 13:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Nex would pull shit like this all the time, and bully me until I was sobbing on the floor; and THEN tell me I was hard to love. He was horrible and selfish and didn't give a shit about the pain his words caused. 

Dump him. They never ever change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 00:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I HAVE THE SAME PROBLEM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 13:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Difficulty with left and right, and difficulty with directions etc, are also associated with dyscalculia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 20:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's being a total prick. Dump him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 19:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thiiiis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 19:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly he should be 1000% on your side and blanking them until they grow the fuck up. You don't owe them a thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 16:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh bloody hell mate, that's horrible. I'm so sorry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 03:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DUMP HIM.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 03:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's more important to you? Helping your sister or pandering to your mother's bizarre attitude? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 03:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're just going to have to be honest about how you feel. She's pushing her fetish on you, and that's not okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 03:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe if you threw his stuff out he might finally understand YOUR frustration rather than being a dick about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 23:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah if that's the case, it's entirely possible someone might have intentionally messed with her drink. I'm not saying it excuses her, but if she was in the company of people who would DO that, it might mean she actually really needs help to deal with that aside from the issue you have with her. That's HER responsibility though. You still have your own feelings to consider of course.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 22:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAHAHAHAHAHAHA

that expression is GOLD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 22:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But such a bootiful derp! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 22:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to smoosh the face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 22:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 22:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww his little face  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 22:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dogs are easier to feed!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 22:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you accidentally switch to front facing camera  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 22:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is he? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 22:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SQUEE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 21:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't owe them a single thing. Your husband shouldn't be asking you to write any letter, you shouldn't have to smooth anything over since they sound like utterly awful people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 21:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted her to use her fingers and just push it all up and out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 21:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, are you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 20:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah she needs to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 20:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an idea - be more careful and don't do stuff that pisses her off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 20:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been on the wrong side of dead naming enough to know the difference between mistake and absolutely intentional. One of my friends (who I now no longer talk to) asked me if he could still use my dead name because it sounded cuter to him. I was speechless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 19:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 19:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it could double as a bottle opener!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 19:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loooooove Dr Lee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 19:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope you're not overreacting. She's being pretty aloof and detached and really your son is way more important.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 19:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she was blackout drunk, how would she know she had sex, and when did the guy she had sex with, get her consent?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 01:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was fucking EPIC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 17:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oddly hypnotic.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 16:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't access the article. Anyone else getting that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 13:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite possibly, but it depends on how good a kennel can be found in their area. Some are truly awful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 11:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/relationships/comments/4i1ifc/comment/d2uxidv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 11:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, that might be okay if you have a dog that normal, but I don't. My dog is special needs and so was the one before him. However, I take full responsibility for him and I don't expect anyone to take care of him but me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 23:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dead naming is cruel and spiteful. My response to being dead named is to blank the person doing it until they use the right name. People know exactly what they're doing when they do it too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 23:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you're living with a manchild. They don't tend to change. You might want to reevaluate your relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 22:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The stuff you've posted here is really not at all good stuff. It's hard when you love someone to try and be objective, but these are some really heavy rocks you're dealing with here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 22:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you're here on Reddit asking for advice which of course is totally up to you, but how good are things really if you have to come here to do that? This stuff is really clearly stewing inside you, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 21:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a dog and the idea of putting him in a kennel for even a DAY, makes my stomach turn. I couldn't do it. The thing is, unless your parents are going to stop being difficult over this, really you're going to have to make a choice between going to Africa, or staying home with your dog. Which one of those things is more important to you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 21:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These aren't things you can just let go. This is the kind of stuff that ends marriages, and to be honest it seems like you'd be best off away from him, for your sake and his. Marriage counselling maybe but really? I'd be walking away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 21:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think perhaps the best way to get the message through to her, is via restraining order, for her and your stepfather, because both of them are toxic as all fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 21:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sounds like a really unpleasant shit. The sooner you can move out, the better. You can't pick your family sadly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 21:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dump him and never look back. He sounds like a complete twat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 20:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not your fault. 

The problem with being sexualised early on, is that the body learns to zone out and just wait for it to be over. If you're not naturally assertive, standing up for yourself can be difficult. The moment you don't tell men who are touching you to stop, the more they will keep doing it if they are the handsy type. 

I think telling your boyfriend would be good for support, but it seems like you're worried about his reaction. Are you worried that he will think you've instigated anything?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 20:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For FUCK'S sake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 18:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops here I was thinking they were Akitas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
