<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4287</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 16:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 15:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened in Canada, in Alberta, where there are these standardized final exams in high school called "diploma exams" that count towards 50% of your final grade.  Apart from just being expelled, the rumor was that he wasn't allowed to write his (maybe because he was expelled?).  Basically fucked up his chance of going to university for a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 07:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At my highschool, all the classrooms had these heavy CRT televisions suspended up high and every day there were these scheduled "video announcements".  There were also like thirty of these televisions in the cafeteria, but more of that anon. 

Normally, the vice-principal would get on the PA and let the teachers know to turn on their televisions for the daily video announcement.  This was grade 11 for me (one year before graduation), and it was near the end of the school year, so as was customary there were a fair number of pranks from the graduating class going on.  I don't even know if half of them actually happened, but I remember hearing they released three pigs in the school at one point, with the numbers "1", "2" and "4" painted on them, so that the administrators would be running around looking for a non-existent #3 pig.  

Anyway, on this particular day, the vice-principal gets on the PA and says "**Teachers, DO NOT turn on your televisions**".  My bio teacher was this young hip lady, who upon hearing this went straight to the television saying "Well now I *have* to turn it on".  So she hits the power button and sure enough it's some super-hardcore pornography that one of the graduating students had put on the daily announcements after locking himself in the audio-visual room.  You could see everything, it was **GRAPHIC** and my teacher was so shocked it took her a good 5 seconds to hit the power-button again and turn it off.  It was a very Sir Patrick Stewart moment (i.e. "I've seen everything"). 

My best friend got into class late that day nearly pissing his pants laughing.  He had just come from the cafeteria where a bunch of teachers had been desperately jumping up to turn off the thirty odd TVs, suspended high up all over the big room, including the vice principal who must have been barely over 5' tall.

Pretty funny, I remember some of the more religious kids who presumably had never witnessed sex before all having little freak-outs; it was quite the 'to do' for a long time after, though the kid who did it got in deep crap.  

**TL;DR: Kid pranks highschool daily video announcements with hardcore porn, hilarity ensues.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 00:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were in his robe, I'd probably want to get out of it before summer too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 22:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yikes, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oilsands environmental data to be released for Earth Day, Tories will open long-awaited public information portal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 21:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 09:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patents are unfortunately the cart preceding the regulatory horse.  Pharma products, particularly biopharma can take upwards of 15 years *after* a patent is approved before they can typically receive FDA approval.  It's a ton of really expensive testing and trials.  However, lot of it can be supplanted with computer models today though.  This will likely be the basis for regulatory reform in this industry eventually, allowing more rapid innovation and less expensive drugs.

Technically, you could separate patent-protection into two stages, first being development stage, followed after by a temporary market monopoly stage.  

This would be a nice adjustment to avoid patent trolls, because if an organization failed to commercialize their product they would have no claims against a company actively selling a product on their alleged IP after the expired term.  It would also be a good incentive for companies to actively seek to commercialize their patented technologies, rather than simply patenting them and letting the technology languish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 05:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't think patents should exist for products that take 15 years to pass regulatory approval and enter the market? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 03:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, maybe an extension for products bearing little resemblance to any established product.  I mean, if someone develops a really innovative augmented reality product, or industrial automation product (i.e. not just another phone, camera, etc.), they ought to enjoy increased licensing benefits for a reasonable period of time after.  

A full decade might be too long, especially if the rate of innovation continues to increase.  So perhaps patent-legislation should be devised with flexible metrics to determine their length with respect to the pace of innovation in the industry to which they apply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 03:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compromise:  4 years for software patents.  10 years for hardware.

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston bombing suspect lies in hospital, U.S. begins search for 'root causes' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 03:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 02:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See my comment [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/CanadaPolitics/comments/1cr5m1/your_thoughts_on_copyright_changes/c9jco6m) and tell me what you think. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 02:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With respect to copyright, I think it's pretty well out of control the length of time a work remains outside the public domain.  At this point I feel like they should just give Disney an exemption already and stop punishing the public at large to satisfy them.  If an author is dead, I don't feel like I should be paying their grandchildren for the intellectual property.  [The Happy Birthday](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Happy_Birthday_to_You#Copyright_status) song is a pretty good example of this.  (written in the mid 19th century, copyrighted in 1935, current copyright still active and held by Time Warner, hence why they don't sing it in restaurants anymore...)

In terms of competition and innovation, there are areas of intellectual property law and patent law that could definitely be changed to help spur growth.  One big problem area in patent laws is there's no distinction between different industries; the same patent-lengths hold for the tech-industry (rapid cycle from product to market) as well as the biotech industry (slow cycle from product to market).  

Biotech, particularly pharmaceuticals, is a nightmare to try and have a start-up in.  If you discover something with awesome therapeutic potential and manage to patent it, it will take on average 10-15 years before you can clear regulatory hurdles and bring your product to market.  Then by the time you have people buying it at an exorbitant cost to pay back all the cost of development, suddenly the patent expires and generics (or for bio-drugs 'subsequent entry biologics') hit the market and undercut you.  Currently, most venture capital in North America goes to [bigger companies doing biotech](http://www.ey.com/GL/en/Industries/Life-Sciences/Beyond-borders--global-biotechnology-report-2011), because smaller companies just can't sustain themselves.  

Tech-sector products on the other hand, even hardware, can go from inception to market much more rapidly, and patents on these products extend to the point of being obselete, as evidenced by the glut of lawsuits between tech-companies, all owning thousands of overlapping patents.

Tech-sector patents should be shortened to 10 years, and biotech patents should either be extended or the regulatory process should be overhauled (or both).  Similar adjustments should be made on a per-industry basis with flexibility in the legislation to account for rapidity of innovation in the particular sector. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 02:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding your point#2, I'm not completely in favor of making downloading legal without introducing some means restitution fee for artists and content-creators.  

While I think that downloading is really more of a service/convenience problem than a "free-stuff" problem, I'd like to see Canada introduce a levy to redistribute funds back to artists and content creators.  I'm not a fan of the [blank media levy](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Private_copying_levy#Canada) introduced in 1997, I'd like to see it charged from internet service providers (w/o raising rates on consumers), since they're already gouging Canadians as it is.

Also, highly recommend reading stuff from [Michael Geist](http://www.michaelgeist.ca/content/view/6692/125/) if you're not already familiar with him.  And, rather than starting your own petition, you could consider volunteering to help [Open Media](http://openmedia.ca/) as they're pretty well in line with your copyright convictions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 01:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a semantic clarification, I think also you mean that intellectual property laws need to be loosened, including copyright (i.e. patents etc.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 21:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  I've been there before, but haven't seen a picture in a while. Makes me wonder what would be done with the Red Chamber if they ever did dissolve the Senate... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 21:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would name this armor "Greased Lightning" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 17:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Trudeau should actually come back at Harper now that the 'crisis' is at an end and draw parallels between this recent event and the Canadians that were at the Algerian gas plant.  

Young people becoming isolated and then 'radicalized' is something that should realistically be examined and discussed as a matter of policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 19:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is commenting less a new resolution?  (I hope it isn't!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 19:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically a Bourbon, but it's all whisky really.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 18:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This poll lost all legitimacy for me because of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MP Mark Warawa to replace abortion motion with new bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 21:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 21:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious whether despite what this article says, if a reemergence of the BlocQ could undercut the NDP's gains in Quebec and allow the liberals a chance to win-out in some ridings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leadership votes show Quebec still unenthralled with Trudeau </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 19:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Owner of bike shop used as Flaherty backdrop feels deceived </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 19:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MP Warawa to unveil decision on abortion motion appeal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 01:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long-awaited election reform legislation coming Thursday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 01:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 17:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like they must have better ads already prepared, but were concerned what the reaction might be.  So they released this one to 'test the waters'.  

That or this is just the best they could come up with, which is surprising really, since as Trudeau said himself said, he's had a mic in front of him from a very early age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 17:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to say the timing is also off, since there's no election on hand, but did they wait for an election to hit Ignatieff?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 17:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HitchKing: "Married Monarch, Modest-Minded Moderate" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 16:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with senate reform, and a few others.  If it came down to keeping a promise and losing power versus scraping a promise and keeping power, the latter will more likely win out.  Harper is a pragmatist, he would only need to establish a convenient reason for calling an early election.

It might be considered a pretty good argument that the conservatives may be expecting a stronger economy by 2015 and would still want to wait until then.  However, I think it would be more cunning to hold the election before the economy has fully recovered.  As long as the economy is on the minds of Canadians before various other concerns, the conservatives will hold a political advantage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 16:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Trudeau Takes Tory Attacks, Untroubled."

Writing headlines must be a super-fun job. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 15:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's interesting too, because on one hand Harper wants to keep them in line, at least leading through to the next election, but if they don't hold on to their majority there's no way they could ever pass controversial legislation regarding the abortion issues (or anything else for that matter), which could make the backbenchers more antsy for action now.

If I was Harper, I might seriously consider calling an early election in 2014.  Long enough to let the buzz about Justin simmer, but not so long for him to lose his 'inexperienced' image.  And, soon enough to quiet down the backbenchers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Negative ad strategy holds risks for Conservatives, experts say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 14:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trudeau takes Tory attack ads in stride </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 14:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 04:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the sentiment is correct, but the language just leaves me feeling flat...  Is it more of an Ontario or Eastern Canada thing to relate to the 'middle class'?  I remember when I first moved out here and had no idea why people kept referring to things as being 'sketchy'.  

When I hear rhetoric about the middle class, it just sounds like an abstract concept, there must be a better expression encapsulating people neither wealthy, nor below the poverty line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 03:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think he's pissed off, I think he's more just dedicated to pointing out any elephants in the room in case anyone was pretending they weren't there.  

However, I think his aim is off in saying that Justin's brand extends wholly from his father.  I think most Canadians were introduced to him by the [awesome eulogy](http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=z_jiFO3uBTw#t=63s) he gave to his father in 2000, and since then he's been a household name.  If he'd simply come out of the woodwork at the last election, just being a "Trudeau" wouldn't garner him the support he has, or give him an established image with protection from attack ads that seek to redefine him.  

On a slightly different note, I couldn't help imagining Andrew Coyne's article through this [scene in the IT Crowd ](http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=rsriu6a_ukw#t=2s) FATHER!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 03:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a sense I can agree with your sentiment, when the race first started out, I was more of a Garneau supporter.  

However, I think a lot of people weren't necessarily voting for Trudeau as he is *today* (though he seems to have come a long way over the course of the campaign), but rather for the leader he has the potential to become over the next few years.

I think the sentiment is an optimistic, "Let's see what he can do". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 00:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the LPC should really consider retiring the term 'middle class' in its communications. It's just too blas and arbitrary; not evocative of anything when you hear it. I suppose I'm middle-class but I don't *feel* anything when I hear it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 18:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More than that, buy anything made of plastic, and you're also buying a petroleum product.  

Even if we drove electric cars, the 'power' would still probably come from coal plant.  Even hydro-electricity, I was watching an old video from the ELA about how the artificial lakes that are created from hydro dams actually release more greenhouse gas than a coal plant because of the decomposing plant matter from flooded areas.

Sometimes I wonder if sustainability actually exists... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 17:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, I think most people accept that he's not 'brilliant'.  If we wanted the astronaut PhD, he'd be the leader right now.  The ad doesn't defeat his perceived strengths, which are that he's likable and can bring people together to build good consensus policy.  

That or I'm just doing my best to drink the Kool-aid now that the leadership selection is all over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 17:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His comment is a quote from Adolf Hitler.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 05:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it might be humanity in general.  We're at the peak of our intelligence and the peak of our stupidity right now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 04:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first time I flew up to Fort Mac and toured the facilities, it was like heading into a nightmare.  Pillars of fire and smoke heading up into the sky, the air stinking like sulphur.  I'm not kidding, it was like being on the set of a Tolkien movie or something...

Frankly, I'm not against developing the resources out there, but I am totally against giving companies a free pass on developing their engineering and processes to be cleaner and more efficient, and just accountable for the damage they cause.  Stricter regulation, as long as it doesn't defy economic realities is good for innovation.  

One of the biggest problems with the oil and gas industry, is that it favours robust 'working' solutions over innovative technology that's unproven.  Too much is accepted practice and a hundred little things add up to make for really dirty not-particularly-sustainable processes.  If these companies were really forced to tighten their processes, there would be a lot of fat available to trim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 20:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fetch?

Edit: ^ Comments that make me realize I'm getting old... :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 19:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to know for the sake of irony, did the separatist mod leave the subreddit, or just reevaluate their position? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 16:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The success of non-centerist parties notwithstanding, what kind of conflict and dialogue of political ideas will occur if each major party attempts to occupy the middle?

If it's all about perception and nothing to do with policy, I think Coyne is correct in saying the only distinguishing feature becomes party-leaders, and then parliament as it was designed and individual MPs become obselete.

I think parliament to remain effective in the future needs to retire geographical ridings, and elect all members on the basis of national popular vote with respect to issues.  Then you could elect a member who really cares about copyright reform, or one that insists on free trade, or a climate-change skeptic, or one that insists on tighter carbon emission controls. Parties would probably still exist somehow (they always survive) but there would be a return to electing individuals on the basis of an individual platform instead of a party platform.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 14:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the initial premise of the article correct at least? How many trade agreements have been successfully negotiated? (This was the main agenda item by Harper that I was a big fan of, I'm disappointed to learn that it might be faltering...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 23:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  2) Kinda in love what Whitehouse.gov does - the NDP should steal it

I know, right!  Being able to focus-group thousands of voters, especially the ones that disagree with a platform, and then target-advertising to them.  I hope all the parties steal it, frankly, just because it will make voters more engaged and a better political system overall.  Though hopefully the Liberals first... :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 22:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Ian, thanks for being here today!

I'm curious what you think of the Liberals' leadership selection process allowing outside 'supporters'.  Specifically, what do you think the value/influence is for the Liberals in having email access to that group of voters, even the ones that haven't registered to actually vote?

As a follow-up question, while it's related to American politics, what do you think of the Whitehouse.gov using their petition system to more systematically target groups of voters on particular issues, and do you think one of the federal Canadian parties will try to implement a similar system for better sculpting their platforms?

Thanks a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 22:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's underground sequestration (though I'm not a fan of acid-gas injection).  I'd like to see some innovation in scaling bioprocesses for these kinds of applications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservative MPs object to new Saskatchewan ridings, but is it too late? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 20:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberal leadership voter turnout at over 40% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 20:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 18:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that the prospect of having a carbon tax is being discussed more as a 'selling feature'.  Adds an important perspective to this debate.  Also, it's important to note that a system like this will drive a lot of research and innovation into carbon capture, such that it won't likely remain as expensive in the long term as it is projected to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Revenue Canada cuts undermine tax haven crackdown, NDP says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 18:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 18:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the NDP maintain their seats in Quebec and the Liberals take back enough seats in Ontario, there could be a situation where all three parties are on relatively equal footing seating-wise.  Could make for a very interesting parliament... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alberta, industry face wide gap on carbon tax </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 17:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 17:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title is misleading, but the numbers on registered voters per province is interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberals disappointed by Quebecs disinterest in leadership race despite Montreals Justin Trudeau </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 17:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 21:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, likewise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 21:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also **didn't** receive my PIN in the mail.  I called the 1-800 support number earlier today that they emailed out yesterday, and admittedly was on hold for about 10min (I was redditing though, so it could've been 2-3hrs.. o_O).  Nice lady called me 'dear', then apologized and called me 'sir', gave me an ID   PIN after confirming my voting details.  My ballot is cast! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 03:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen the speech yet, but I think a distinction can and should be drawn between an attack (which serves to harm and undermine a political brand) and a criticism, which serves as a contribution to political discourse.

Suggesting the current government's policy  isn't ambitious isn't the same as "just visiting". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 20:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds inappropriate, I agree; however, if it's an effective rehabilitation method for violent criminals I'd be more willing to accept the practice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 19:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It comes down to how verifiable and auditable the process is. There's a [good TED talk by a researcher named David Bismark](http://www.ted.com/talks/david_bismark_e_voting_without_fraud.html) on hypothetical methods that safe e-voting can be implemented.

Really, traditional elections have vulnerabilities too, the sooner we do the research and develop e-voting, the better the final practice of it will be (and it is coming...). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 14:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is wrong with *telling* people to be more active and thoughtful in an electoral process? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 14:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is unfortunate, (security reservations aside) electronic voting would ultimately make elections far less expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 14:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Eighteen of those contractors provided services to Muslim, Jewish, Sikh and other non-Christian prisoners.
 
 The part-time chaplains were to be replaced with a mix of volunteers, 71 full-time Christian chaplains and two full-time Muslim chaplains.

It would be curious to see if they increased the proportion of Christian chaplains with respect to the faiths of the inmate populations, or whether this was some kind of political decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 14:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What is wrong with asking people to be more active and thoughtful in an electoral process?

This could also be said for compulsory voting.  Plus, as /u/Aquanker noted, it's a $10 fine if you don't vote.  Would be a nice little bit of extra revenue for the state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 14:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Hefty fine of a bout $10 there

Sounds like an excellent new source of revenue, far better than raising tariffs on imports. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 03:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  compelling citizens by force of law to engage in an activity they normally wouldn't engage in 

The law compels you to do all sorts of things you wouldn't normally engage in, like pay your taxes, or buy insurance for your car... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 02:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the vote is compulsory, then a declined ballot becomes a more meaningful action on the part of the electorate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 02:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could just obligate everyone to vote, I believe they successfully implemented compulsory elections in Australia... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 23:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree, managed reforms would be the ideal for most institutions over time, but often reforms seem to follow stagnation and subsequent budget cuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 23:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding social infrastructure, I mean this very loosely to be how people and their information is managed and organized. So say a ministry of transportation, or medical information at a hospital, or prisoners in the justice system.  The way we organize people through our social institutions has a lot of room for overhaul to reduce overhead costs as technology improves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 20:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly, I think the cuts are important.  Bureaucracy and organizational infrastructure tend to be designed for robustness, not efficiency, and don't age well.  Cuts like those proposed by the CPC provide opportunity to redesign the delivery of government services.

Unfortunately, you can't make changes like this without political blow-back... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 20:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to think of it more in terms of social and organizational infrastructure.  

The inefficiency of any bureaucracy tends to increase over time leading to stagnation.  This is true for more than just governments, look at inefficiency and overhead of some older companies compared to newer ones and the differences can be pretty dramatic.

All these budget-cuts by the current administration, while having a negative direct effect to services will ultimately spur the creation and development of new and more efficient social infrastructure for delivering services.

/u/ROBOTINATOR I think is correct in surmising that our political institutions are mutually correcting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 19:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  he calls the decision "completely unfair"

I listened to the interview, while he's definitely expressing an opinion, he offers very good points and evidence, so once again I wouldn't say his communication in inaccurate, simply unflattering. 

There's a bit of an ethical paradox here, because on one hand as a government employee it's not appropriate to go on the news and criticize government policy (of which you're technically a representative).  However, it's also not appropriate to remain silent to policy changes that will be harmful to the public and essential services like legal-aid, since ultimately the duty of a public servant is to the public.  It's essential that that information reach the electorate, and even though it's not the role of a government employee to perform this communication, it is the role of a public servant to do so.

In the first of these circumstances (gov't employee criticizing gov't), frankly it's healthy for a government to suffer criticism - whether from media, ordinary citizens, even its own employees - despite its political inconvenience.  It may seem inappropriate, but there's no other realistic way for a gov't employee on the ground, independent of party affiliation, to affect policy up the chain.

In the second of these circumstances (gov't employee withholding 'sensitive' information from the public), it's not healthy to the public to wait for ordinary citizens to be in danger of hypothetically bad policy, when knowledgeable public servants could offer warning against those policies.  

If the reality is that that communication has to be done through the media, rather than less-sensitive back-channels, it ought to be accepted, because the greater harm to the public is in withholding information, and the greater robustness of the political system is in receiving genuine criticism, even from gov't employees (which is probably even more valuable since it's less politically motivated than something coming from the opposition in question period). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ottawa needs to reassure Canadians about food safety </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 17:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 17:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That doesn't mean that they can't give an accurate assessment of the situation. But they need to stick to "just the facts, ma'am"

I read the [first article](http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/newfoundland-labrador/story/2013/04/02/nl-legal-aid-justice-cuts.html) where the lawyer's views are first quoted.  I would hazard that the points he makes aren't inaccurate, simply unflattering.


 they still have a duty to support the decisions of the duly elected government.

Is this in fact the case?  Isn't the duty towards the public?  While these are government employees, if policy changes affect their ability to perform essential services to the public, communicating those facts to the public should be protected under whistle-blowing rules.

I would suggest this situation is not unlike closing a hospital for a rural population and then having a doctor suspended for telling the CBC there won't be enough equipment or personnel to treat the general population. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 16:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been considering this problem, because I recognize that when gov't employees (scientists or in this case a legal-aid lawyer) communicate to the media and the public, they become in a way de facto representatives of the government. This is problematic when the government wants to manage its communication and messaging (which it understandably wants to do), and someone seen as representing the gov't 'goes rogue' and starts criticizing policy.

However, these are servants for the public, not the governing administration, and if there's a legitimate concern to the public well-being from policy decisions, I'm tempted to suggest the speech and criticism by public employees should be protected under whistle-blower rules.

The problem seems to be that there aren't clear guidelines for gov't employees to represent their personal opinions and criticisms as separate from the governing administration.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada loses 54,500 jobs in March </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 16:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CP oil spill in northern Ontario larger than first reported </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 00:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 03:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pfft, best edit goes to [Bacon Pancakes](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MNXmeA-IMuI) all the way.

Jake the Dog from Adventure Time featuring Jay-Z and Alicia Keys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 01:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually not an official member, I should consider doing that too now that I think about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 00:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you mean, I just spent 15 minutes looking and it's all abandoned pages... :S  Now that I think about it, I don't think I've ever seen an ad on campus even.

Feel free to PM me when the next event is, I'll try and make it. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 00:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but I'm tempted to look them up now. It never occurred to me to get involved through the school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 23:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, stuck at a wedding shower all wkd, though sounds like I'm just down the street (UW), congrats on the election win! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 20:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [Metrolinx shortlist](http://www.cbc.ca/hamilton/news/story/2013/04/02/hamilton-metrolinx-lrt-funding.html):

 * Development Charges
* Employer Payroll Tax
* Fuel Tax
* High Occupancy Tolls (HOT)
* Highway Tolls
* Land Value Capture
* Parking Space Levy, including pay-for-parking at transit stations
* Property Tax
* Sales Tax
* Transit Fare Increase
* Vehicle Kilometers Travelled (VKT) Fee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 19:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The political fallout comes at the next election, when you as part of the electorate make an informed decision based on the actions of the previous administration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Information commissioner right to investigate muzzling of scientists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 15:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 02:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crash Override  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 00:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think /u/adaminc has correctly surmised that this decision has little to do with money or rejecting the UN bureaucracy, but is actually a strategic move to undercut domestic environmental/climate research by the NRC, which perhaps has come to be regarded as a political economic liability.

Tracking the policy moves by this administration, you would probably observe a systematic dismantling of environmental research and regulatory infrastructure, that this most recent decision falls in line with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 20:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not crazy about fully proportional, but I could get behind semi-proportional, i.e. 20 seats awarded by national popular vote. The PM and other party leaders as well as major cabinet/critics could fill these seats instead of pretending they have time to represent a riding on top of cabinet duties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 21:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just thinking on the downvote problem on the subreddit.  It's likely possible to script a few 'upvote bots' that just null all downvotes... though it might be a violation of reddit terms of service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 04:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you are my brother: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jL09C-IBWQU

They seem to get into it around [3:20] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 23:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You haven't really lived, unless you've got a lot to regret"
- Alan Rickman as Dr. Blalock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 03:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They received Simons go ahead to use the song for a nominal fee -- **about the price of nice dinner out,** said spokesperson Andrew Frank

I don't know, it's not such a bad video.  Though in the current political environment, I don't see the northern-gateway winning out.  

Really, though, it will be important to get Canadian oil to Asia and its developing economies, especially with the shale-oil boom in the states showing that they won't need to rely on our production.

The perceived risk means a political cost, which added to the monetary ones could make the whole thing nonviable though.  It's sort of like nuclear power, no matter how great the benefits, or how far the technology has come, when you have recent events like Fukushima, or bringing it back to coastal oil-spills, Deep Water Horizon (less than 3 years ago), winning people over becomes a pretty bleak affair.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 23:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about that, only just got the email from their campaign and thought it was new.

Cheers, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 16:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or at least the ones with big environmental science programs... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 05:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same way you followed your heart in choosing a degree, you need to follow your heart to find a pursuit in society.  

With my program there were plenty of jobs available, but they were unfulfilling in many instances.  While I chose the program based on interest, I hadn't stopped to consider what I might want to do with it.

You should find a problem in society, or service, or organization that you're genuinely interested in being a part of, and consider novel ways you can make contributions.  Don't rely on some arbitrary company, career, or paycheque to fulfill you, there's too much creative awesomeness out there...plus you'll be far less likely to be replaced by software or a robot that way.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 03:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of me wishes that some savvy media types could have started a kickstarter project to get the money to keep them going longer till a permanent steward could be found...  I'd love to see some videos of the ELA and just discussion of the ongoing projects that are going to be abandoned.

Schindler:
I really don't think Fisheries and Oceans has been negotiating in good faith [1:00]

This would be assuming it would be allowed to stay open, rather than the more uncomfortable narrative that there's a political will behind shutting it down... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 16:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really should pull a Preston Manning and found a new political movement. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 03:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just out of curiosity, what underlying assumptions of the party system do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 03:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  even the geologists

Geologists are definitely an outrageous group of people. :)

Those links in my previous comment suggest that the standard to which gov't scientists are being held isn't the norm.  Rather that researchers are just expected to follow certain guidelines when communicating publicly.  

Even taking the whole muzzling thing as a complete fiction though, I have to wonder how much overhead and personnel are being devoted to media and communications bureaucracy to 'manage' all public communications.  Is it more than before these new rules came into place in 2006?  Is it worth avoiding a few embarrassing quotes and sound-bites here and there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unlocking the gridlock - Toronto Traffic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 02:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 02:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I like the 'existence' of the idea, just because it forces the Liberals to re-establish a unique identity and brand apart from the other opposition parties.

It's a real opportunity for the LPC to say "we are a separate ideology that is not arbitrarily interchangeable with some other party and we will not abandon our convictions for the sake of an easy win!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 02:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be inclined to believe the issue to be exaggerated and just a few bruised egos, but with journals like [Nature releasing official editorials on the issue](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v483/n7387/full/483006a.html), and [non-Canadian scientists pushing back on collaborative projects with Canadian researchers](http://www.cbc.ca/news/technology/story/2013/02/15/science-audio-munchow-scientist-muzzling.html), it begins to take on an appearance less of a few isolated incidents and more a systemic concern... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sparks fly over co-operation with other parties in Liberal leadership debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 00:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 23:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been considering this problem, because I recognize that when gov't scientists communicate directly to the public, they become *de facto* representatives of that government.  This is problematic if you want to exert control on government communication and messaging (which the gov't understandably wants to do).

However, I think if we're going to employ scientists directly (as opposed to research at a university for instance, where researchers are still funded by the gov't typically, but not directly employed by them) they shouldn't be more restricted than non-gov't researchers in their communications, i.e. peer review, unless it's classified military research (i.e. defence and weapons, etc.).  Otherwise, there's an ethical hazard not unlike the state possessing it's own news-media that only reports news that reflects positively on the government or party in power, symptomatic of dictatorships...

Therefore, I think research directly sponsored by the gov't should be carried out by an independent body from the bureaucracy and parliament, subject to oversight and audit, but representing neither.

IMHO: the independence of scientific research should be protected the same as the independence of the Bank of Canada or the judicial branch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 20:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually an excellent point.  Disregarding political implications of certain legislation over others, in a lot of ways you could say that policy is ultimately an experiment based on a hypothesis.  The results will reward certain reports and experts and discredit others until consensus on the best policy is eventually reached (ideally). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 18:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Worse, it implies that government policy (ought statements) are ultimately able to be based on scientific evidence (is statements). This is a favorite trick of the left, to assume their ideological premises so strongly that they genuinely begin to believe that they aren't in fact ideological.

I would think historically, a fair amount of government policy is based in facts and evidence, which should circumvent any left-leaning or right-leaning ideology.  As an example, free trade agreements removing tariffs, while initially rejected at the time by left-leaning ideologies, was supported by economists and ultimately helped spur new economic growth.  Hence why PM Harper in his tenure has really put a lot of effort into getting Canada at the table for new agreements to open trade markets in Asia and Europe and diversify our economy from just the US, whose market we depend on too heavily.

Evidence is objective, and a good foundation for policy.  

That being said, I'll agree, this motion is more an opposition stunt, less about protecting scientific evidence than criticizing the government:

* Part (a) isn't really binding, anyone could agree to that.  
* Part (b) is problematic, because controlling communication and messaging so well has been a very politically profitable maneuver for the CPC and the PMO, you can hardly blame them for controlling their message, this is politics after all...  However, it is an important question how much control is appropriate for the ruling party to exert over the state bureaucracy.  Realistically, there should be some independence of the bureaucracy (incl. gov't scientists) from the politics of the day...
* Part (c) is really just an attention-grabber, since the ELA project has gotten a lot of media attention.  Realistically, the project could be totally bloated and not a realistic approach to the research they set out to conduct, and not worth continuing, no matter how expensive the initial cost of clean-up in the short-term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 17:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just out of curiosity, how are its implications offensive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-15 21:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having an awesome rsum, but failing on the charisma and how you're projected in media seems like pit-fall that occurred with Ignatieff. I think you're dead-on in your assessment of Garneau.

I think it's interesting that Trudeau, based on his background, has a lot of soft-skills that help him win out, despite in no way being a wonk himself. I'm hoping that since people acknowledge that he's likable, but not brilliant, in a way the liberals really aren't just putting all the burden on a new leader to make a comeback.  Rather, acknowledging that politics is rarely just about having the best policies, and that the Liberals have a lot of smart people, they can be brought to bear on the 'real problems'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 03:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it by accident?  I vaguely remember the volcano thing being on orders from his boss to "bring back clouds", because the father worked for a logging company that cut down all the trees.  So the extinction incident was more a comment on reckless industrial development leading ultimately to uninhabitable climate change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 02:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all related to any discussion points we're having here, but just little things that drive me nuts: the actor playing Jack, while holding the cane in the correct hand, is actually favouring the wrong leg in this biopic.  Jack Layton fractured his [left hip](http://www.theglobeandmail.com/news/politics/ottawa-notebook/jack-layton-on-the-mend-and-fully-engaged-after-hip-surgery/article612358/).

This clip of him stepping down from the NDP leadership begins with him [walking with the cane](http://youtu.be/3g0QMDHjjKY) and correctly keeping weight off of his left side by leaning on the cane.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 23:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rhetoric is a bit sensational, but then they are advertising a book they want people to buy...

Ibbitson has been discussing "the fall of the Laurentian Consensus" a lot in the past few years, [here originally](http://youtu.be/g8K3bFpXxjI) and more recently [here](http://youtu.be/xrIVRX4cp94).

I don't know if I buy-in to this narrative of obsolete Laurentian Elites incapable of understanding the new electoral reality...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 18:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I can't even imagine how something that big stay oxygenated... not to mention the rest of the whale. o_O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stanford builds first complex computer chip out of carbon nanotubes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 22:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 06:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm tempted to send your comment to Doctorow, he's a pretty responsive author, he might make yet another correction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stag Hunts: fascinating and useful game theory model for collective action problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 03:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 02:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a genuinely trippy film.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 16:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you'd be hard-pressed to find a manus more dexterous and efficient than the existing [human hand](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hand#Evolution).  

Extra arms would require some structural adjustments to the torso, but might be interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 16:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would be a better design?  Two hearts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 16:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speculation:

Too bad crocodiles lay eggs, otherwise, there would probably be fetal crocodile haemoglobin as well.  Still, there's probably a range of O2 affinity based on adjustments to the active sites on haemoglobin, such that this problem could be taken into account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good example I recall is human haemoglobin compared to [crocodile haemoglobin](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/7816138) as a means for human beings to live in atmospheres with toxic levels of CO2.  

(I was reminded of this from the [Mars Trilogy](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mars_trilogy) by Kim Stanley Robinson) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine that experience to be something like [this](http://youtu.be/h6rjmxoakRE).  I'd probably do it, for science. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crosspost from /r/askscience : "What are some ways human biology could be better? If someone were to engineer improved human physiology by examples in other living things today, what are some design features that might be adopted?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a pretty excellent example.  I'm no endocrinologist, but thinking about the monthly hormone shifts women have to cope with is alarming.

I suppose action of [hormonal contraception (i.e. the birth control pill)](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hormonal_contraception) is to temporarily halt these hormone shifts.  I wonder if there are any animals in nature that have a once-in-a-lifetime (or at least once-a-year) mating cycle, the best example I can think of now is salmon.

Though, if sexual reproduction in humans became a once-in-a-year thing, it would probably have a lot of sociological implications, unless the same sex-drive in individuals was maintained.

Altogether, it would be a complex issue to address.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some ways human biology could be better? If someone were to engineer improved human physiology by examples in other living things today, what are some design features that might be adopted? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 04:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget that if you can bring yourself to love someone again after, the depth of trust that you'll feel knowing how badly they could demolish you really is something special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 17:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a time when we made more contributions to the UN missions than any other country (in the 90s).  After Sept 11, though, we were more attached to NATO missions than UN peacekeeping operations.  

All of the peacekeeping operations would have had to be sold to the Canadian public, since the expense was likely significant, and it was at a time when Canada's national debt was a concern (hence a hypothetical mythology).  However, there must have been some foreign policy positives to our investing so heavily in peace-keeping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 16:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, it would be very difficult to say objectively whether the rest of the world noticed or cared about how much peace-keeping we did at one time. I'd have to look up some stats to see if those missions were even very effective towards Canada's image internationally (i.e. such that the people of those countries were left with a persistent positive impression of Canada).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 00:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on how you qualify "power" I suppose.  There was that period after WWII where we had pretty [significant air and naval assets](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canadian_Forces#Origins_and_establishment).  This qualified us as a middle-power at the time in terms of military capability. 

 At the end of the Second World War, Canada possessed the third-largest navy and fourth-largest air force in the world, as well as the largest volunteer army ever fielded. Conscription for overseas service was introduced only near the end of the war, and only 2,400 conscripts actually made it into battle

During the early part of the cold war, we also [possessed nuclear armaments](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canada_and_weapons_of_mass_destruction#Inventory_of_Canada.E2.80.99s_nuclear_armaments). 

With respect to international diplomacy and influence, when Canada was synonymous with [peace-keeping](http://www.cbc.ca/news/background/cdnmilitary/peacekeeping.html), we could have been considered a middle-power in this respect.  However, our military assets would have been much diminished from their earlier levels.

Today, economically we're still a middle-power; members of the [G8](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/G8), despite its exclusion of Brazil and China, such as it is... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writing in PNAS, a University of Manchester physicist has discovered that some games are simply impossible to fully learn, or too complex for the human mind to understand. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 22:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 16:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you're interested in aerospace, you could try doing something related to rocket design.  There's a company that's been getting some attention lately called [Orbitec](http://www.orbitec.com/propulsion.html) that designed a more efficient rocket engine that uses a [cooling vortex](http://www.bbc.com/future/story/20121219-a-novel-twist-on-space-launches/1).

Here's a [video](http://youtu.be/mEOoWWlUYhc) of their Oct 20, 2012 launch. 

I don't know if you could build anything like this, but some heat-transfer modeling could make for an interesting project.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 19:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there some significance to having the GG there apart from him being the official representative of the Crown? I'm just curious if there's some weird article in the treaty legislation that by having the GG there places a greater impact on this meeting... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Wrong'Official Trailer #1 (2013) - "visionary filmmaker Quentin Dupieux (the guy who brought us the homicidal tire thriller "Rubber") to turn a simple story about a man looking for his lost dog into an off-the-wall mind trip" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 04:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 01:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never underestimate the power of a negative brand to prejudice... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 01:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that she's currently unemployed notwithstanding, social work is actually a pretty broad field as I understand it.  

Going by Sen Segal's points in the video, if you instituted a reform like this lifting people out of poverty and it did lead to a cost savings on the provincial end with respect to its burden of programs, healthcare, crime, etc., such that you can afford to fund other things like early childhood education, band in school, and community social workers, which some provinces can't currently afford... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
