<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4647</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump administration is ill-prepared for a global pandemic, experts warn: High-level health vacancies and budget cuts could leave the United States extra susceptible to the threat of infectious disease which will likely lead to the deaths of Millions of Americans all from Trump's incompetence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump administration is ill-prepared for a global pandemic, experts warn: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Altright Nazi snowflake Spencer driven out of DC by anti-fascist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Jeff Sessions wants to bring back the war on drugs: is rhetoric against weed seems to get stronger with each speech. In Richmond, he cast doubt on the use of medical marijuana and said it has been hyped, maybe too much. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeff Sessions wants to bring back the war on drugs: He wants to increase arrest of non-violent drug invaders with long prison sentences, even those who use legal and medical Marijuana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeff Sessions wants to bring back the war on drugs: He wants to increase arrest of non-violent drug invaders with long prison sentences, even those who use legal and medical Marijuana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they wont probably out of respect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you are the one who doesnt know much about them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive heard assange a lot, at this point he just says what Russia wants. He could have been something better but he chose to be a shill. Its unfortunate. Although now that Russia no longer likes Trump he may be just going to support Trump. I cant tell who Assange is working for anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wikileaks likes to claim they dont know who the leakers are, and for months they claimed they had no clue who leaked this info to them. Suddenly at a time when Trump's approval is plummeting they suddenly know and offer a shady looking email that is easy to fake as *evidence*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt it. 

He will get a sugar high and it will crash. This isnt enough to boost them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wagging the dog works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said this as soon as he did this but I was downvoted and attacked on all subs I brought this theory too. I said warning the Russians beforehand and the minimal damage done from so many missiles did not make any sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should have just paid Syria half that and just bought all their planes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump could have bought the planes for far less money. For $100 million he probably could buy the  whole Syrian air force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assad did the chemical attack and there was a lot of benefits to doing it, but im with you that this is kneejerk. 

How is 200 people killed by chemical attack any worse than the 200k Assad has killed with bullets and bombs? Trump suddenly grew a conscious and cares after years of not caring when far more people were dying?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually a lot of schools dropped F. I know schools that stop at E, since it is failing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not quite what I wanted but you know what fuck it, I dont care anymore this is too hard and you arent going to figure this out. So here you go anyway

http://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-38966846 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> depends on the game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they also take pills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> examples of your anger? Every post you make is one of them... 

Your last one included... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay then do that and make the statement, jesus fucking christ. How hard is it to make a statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> only narrative is from you. You are clearly mad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never wanted you not to refute it. I want you to try and refute it. You wont deny the truth unless you you can refute it with a reliable and valid source, not your opinion, briebart, your own personal analysis, /r/t_d, infowars, etc. If you can find a source that clearly refutes it that we both agree is a valid source I encourage you to do so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Yes.* isnt a statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make the statement first that you promise once the proof is given you will accept it unless you can disprove it by a valid and reliable source, and if you do dispute it without a valid and reliable source you acknowledge you are wrong and are just being salty. 

All I require is a small statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not at all. While I am full of love I will still tell the truth, even if upsets and causes people like you to be full of anger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unlike you and Trump I am not full of hate but love. That doesnt mean I will reject reality like you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you want proof about Russiagate? Can we agree you wont make weak excuses once I present it because I can get it in 20 seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone with an IQ over 70 knew Trump was lying from the beginning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, funny how people like you blame democrats for what a GOP president is doing. Its the democrats fault Trump has so many people in his cabinet with ties to Russia that he tries to hide and that he bombed Syria.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yet it is. Not only did Trump do no real damage but he couldnt even stop it from being used. 

He just wasted close to $100 million on his ego. 

Regardless of how you feel about Trump you seem to be embracing alternate facts. Your choice but it is poor choice IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I believe is irrelevant, all that matters is reality and that is he is  a puppet and tool of many bad people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He always caved in. He never cared for his base it was obvious he was lying but people still bought it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wall is symbolic and nothing more. It will never get built too many legal battles and it won't stop anyone. It was and will always be rhetoric </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We tried to warn you he was exploiting you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I don't know either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol just now you realize trump lied to you and never cared about his base? You are guilible people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is too stupid to be a spy. More like a puppet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't even get the airfield closed for 1 day. It is just theater  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since they moved everything out of value either trump lied about the time they had warning or those Syrians are lightening fast. Accept the truth or choose alternate facts. What's really sad is 59 missiles couldn't even out the runway out of commission for a few hours. Truly pathetic of trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turns out the runway isn't even that badly damaged. Assad was using it today to bomb civilians. Kek

90 million well spent trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like trump sent assad a strong message  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monitor: Syrian warplanes take off from airbase hit by US cruise missiles- so trump wasted tens of millions of dollars to do what again? Too much winning for me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monitor: Syrian warplanes take off from airbase hit by US cruise missiles- so trump wasted tens of millions of dollars to do what again? Too much winning for me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monitor: Syrian warplanes take off from airbase hit by US cruise missiles- so trump wasted tens of millions of dollars to do what again? Too much winning for me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monitor: Syrian warplanes take off from airbase hit by US cruise missiles- so trump wasted tens of millions of dollars to do what again? Too much winning for me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monitor: Syrian warplanes take off from airbase hit by US cruise missiles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monitor: Syrian warplanes take off from airbase hit by US cruise missiles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7 expendable assad troops died likely left by assad. He throws away his troops life all the time. Probably sunnis who are treated like cannon fodder. Any alawhite would have been removed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's OK I am sure you didn't know these sites misled you. Now you know. Basically regardless of language avoid fake news, especially Russian propaganda.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jared Kushner hid dozens of meetings with Russians from his application for top-secret security clearance: the extent of Trump's season keeps getting bigger and bigger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jared Kushner hid dozens of meetings with Russians from his application for top-secret security clearance: the extent of Trump's season keeps getting bigger and bigger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jared Kushner hid dozens of meetings with Russians from his application for top-secret security clearance: the extent of Trump's season keeps getting bigger and bigger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jared Kushner hid dozens of meetings with Russians from his application for top-secret security clearance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **ground 6** being Russian spy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump just learned the quickest way to seem presidential to the GOP is to lob a bunch of bombs on brown skinned people, especially Muslim ones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump just learned the quickest way to seem presidential to the GOP is to lob a bunch of bombs on brown skinned people, especially Muslim ones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump just learned the quickest way to seem presidential to the GOP is to lob a bunch of bombs on brown skinned people, especially Muslim ones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump just learned the quickest way to seem presidential to the GOP is to lob a bunch of bombs on brown skinned people, especially Muslim ones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe read something else other than briebart, infowars, or rt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trolls jump off the Trump train, as the alt-right expresses anger over Syria actions: paid russian shills and organizations like briebart and infowars which are under investigation for potential ties to Russia  also denounced the airstrikes for going against the fascist international led by russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trolls jump off the Trump train, as the alt-right expresses anger over Syria actions: paid russian shills and organizations like briebart and infowars which are under investigation for potential ties to Russia  also denounced the airstrikes for going against the fascist international led by russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trolls jump off the Trump train, as the alt-right expresses anger over Syria actions: paid russian shills and organizations like briebart and infowars which are under investigation for potential ties to Russia  also denounced the airstrikes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trolls jump off the Trump train, as the alt-right expresses anger over Syria actions: paid russian shills and organizations like briebart and infowars which are under investigation for potential ties to Russia  also denounced the airstrikes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The story itself has the link. Read it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol operating procedure is not *we will do this so move everything out*. I guess when you don't want to cause damage it is though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So trump is clearly lying then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't the same thing as Trump is worse. But if you are OK with it whatever floats your boat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did move it all away and it was witnessed. So either the Trump admin is lying or Syria is really good at moving lots of stuff very fast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you read the article or any news report you would have known they moved everything off the base prior long before the attack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Trump is going to do nothing then do nothing. Don't waste tens of millions in theater. Nobody expects or trust him to act so this little show between Russia and us is not needed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for that. He was invaded because supposedly he had all these supposed secret programs and was going to arm AQ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spending tens of millions on theater to distract from treason is not impeachable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert Reich: There are at least four grounds to impeach Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert Reich: There are at least four grounds to impeach Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert Reich: There are at least four grounds to impeach Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump, whos totally not Vladimir Putins puppet, warned Russia before airstrikes on Syria: eyewitnesses observed personnel and equipment being moved from the Shayrat airbase in advance of the attack making this a useless $50 million firework display </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump, whos totally not Vladimir Putins puppet, warned Russia before airstrikes on Syria: eyewitnesses observed personnel and equipment being moved from the Shayrat airbase in advance of the attack making this a useless $50 million firework display </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Second attack on Syrian town hit by chemical weapons reported after Trump strikes in Idlib: Assad gasses another town after laughing off Trump's little firework display </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Second attack on Syrian town hit by chemical weapons reported after Trump strikes in Idlib: Assad gasses another town after laughing off Trump's little firework display </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Second attack on Syrian town hit by chemical weapons reported after Trump strikes in Idlib: Assad gasses another town after laughing off Trump's little firework display </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's senseless Syria strikes accomplish nothing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's senseless Syria strikes accomplish nothing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's senseless Syria strikes accomplish nothing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's senseless Syria strikes accomplish nothing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forget Troll Factories. A Journalist Unmasks Russia's Grief Factory. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorta it went down like 

*look im in big trouble from the aid and money you gave me and might expose my treason so tomorrow I am going to pretend to be independent.  Let Assad know too I dont want to hurt him, im just about to get impeached and need to do something.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, samething, he knew this would happen and he went ahead. He is even proud of it. Trump doesnt care about them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, well played out by doing nothing? Trump's little distraction failed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, im sure Assad rolled out some 60s migs for the occassion after moving out the good planes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, more like an empty runway, they are easy to fix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> making good posts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok list the numbers of cruise missiles this system is shot down in operational conditions and why is it 0? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, im sure that is what trump is telling people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what actions. he bombed an empty airforce base after giving them warning. So I cant take either seriously, nor does anyone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see you have never been to a air force base before. 

If there was anyone on it it is impressive that even one of these would not cause a casualty much less 59.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the fact remains he told them to fuck off and die which they did and then Trump pretends to be outraged. You cue the bullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He pretty much did, to their face, and then they were gassed by Sarin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldnt take anything trump does seriously </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too many to count. Here is a recent example

http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/donald-trump-syrian-refugee-children_us_56b8e1d4e4b01d80b24743ea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the same children he told to fuck off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See you have a strange creepy fetish with him and Putin. I mean whatever turns you on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant say for sure, who knows what a senile old man thinks. Most likely this is for domestic reasons. 

* try to show he isnt a puppet of Putin
* try to appear tough while contrasting himself to a *weak obama*
* distract from his recent failures in Trumpcare, trumpeconomics, and tax reform </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently you are as you feel the need to defend Trump's little show while getting angry at the facts. What is it with you and constantly bringing up Trump and Putin in sexually situations? It is getting kinda cringy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not if all the airplanes are gone, not really. I dont expect civilians who never served to know, but you can throw together an airfield and hangars real quick. An empty base is as important as an empty anything. With 10 Tomahawks he could have wrecked real havoc on the Assad regime if he wanted.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has plenty of airbases, and can quickly get this operational again. This is a minor inconvenience for him. Like if I murdered 500 people and had to do 6 hours of community service.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe some brooms and some screws in those buildings. 

No fucks are given by anyone except chest thumping Trumpets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol you are the one who seems upset. Is reality interfering with your alternative facts? Does that trigger you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, they were probably warned a day ago, if this whole thing wasnt planned earlier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the real ones yes, not Russian bots. I have a pulse on them too, but they can only support him on twitter they cant vote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He warned them beforehand. If there were any planes they were moved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who warned the syrians. This whole thing is fake. I mean it happened in that Trump warned them to get anything of value out and spend millions destroying nothing. It was probably Putin's idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it will end with Putin and Assad pretending to be sorry in this scripted show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assad lost nothing, except some empty buildings he will rebuild in 2 weeks. Maybe a few thousand dollars worth of common equipment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump supporting Russian bots are pretending to be pissed. his supporters love bombing Muslims. It fits into the whole *Obama was weak and US not respected but Trump stornk and restore America* narrative </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol 

*Trump blew up a little bit of oil in the ME when it is cheap and some screws.* 

$50 million well spent. I am sure Assad is so upset right now he cant stop laughing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the Russians did learn from it by focusing on disinformation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putin doesnt control America, I never said that. Like anyone could control Trump. He can just manipulate Trump like most people do. And Assad clearly was warned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they didnt kill anyone or damage anything of value. Trump warned them far in advance he needed a distraction and to get everything of value out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and not one casualty. In a airforce base being struck. It was empty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What karma? You really believe 50 Tomahawks would not cause a single casualty at a air force base? This whole thing is put together by Trump and Russia, who warned Russia and Assad far in advance. Assad has no harm done to him, and Trump can claim he is no puppet and did something.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they fire back, they are in on this. Russia needs to save Trump and in a way that doesnt hurt Russia or their interest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, it tells them Trump will spent millions launching pointless airstrikes to make himself look good while not hurting them. It does send a message, just not the one you and Trump want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pentagon knows they cant shoot any day which is why they shot them right over russian air bases and air defenses. This whole *pentagon is terrified of invincible Russia* is just something Russian shills parrot. It has no basis in reality. Why would the Pentagon need me to tell them what is common knowledge? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see you were never military and have no clue how bases work. Anything of value was moved from these buildings like the people. I am sure trump destroyed some cheap stuff lying around, I dont know how Assad will ever recover. 

If Trump wanted to do something with half as many missiles he actually could have done real damage to Assad. 

You are the joke for buying such an obvious staged attack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, NK got the message, the US can fire dozens of tomohawks and do nothing. *god forbid they may warn us they are going to blow up some empty buildings to make Trump look good.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, bullshit. 

50 Tomahawk missiles and no casualties. Russia and Assad were warned, anything of value was moved. A message was sent but not to Assad or Putin, but to faltering Trump supporters *look at me I am not a Russian puppet. I warned Assad and Putin and spent $50 million blowing up an empty air force base. Can we please stop investigating my ties to Russia?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, sure. 

Ill make you a deal, come back to me when Russia shoots one down. I realize per the Russian propaganda squad Russia can do anything, but reality is different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The zionist/jews/freemasons is who Trump's masters like to blame things on. 

Trump didnt attack a Russian ally. He gave them heads up, and put on a little fireworks display. In no way is Assad harmed. Trump just spent $50 million to give the illusion he is tough and not a Putin puppet, while doing nothing. Putin doest care but im sure he will feign outrage or pretend to come around to *how tough Trump is*, I am sure Trumpets will lap it up, but they were never known for intelligence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes Trump personally went to that base and destroyed it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well russia was warned too, but Russia is in on this. Even if Russia wasnt they couldnt do anything about cruise missiles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there wont be regime change, Trump praised Assad just a few days ago. This is just Trump putting on a little show that wont hurt the Russian agenda in Syria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He gave a warning to everyone. This attack was not made to punish Assad or hurt him, it was made to make Trump look tough and not a puppet of Putin while effectively doing nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, years of Russian propaganda has given people inflated perceptions of the capabilities of Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is not in control. He is just putting on a little show in the hopes it will distract from Russiagate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump like most in the GOP is opposed to education because it is a threat to them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this whole thing is fake. Trump wants to look like he isnt Putin's puppet and Russia will fake some outrage. They coordinated the attack together and nothing of value was hit. It wont hurt Assad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This whole thing is fake. If Russia knew Assad knew. This whole strike is wagging the tag and just a show to distract and make Trump look independent from Putin. Assad faces no harm from this strike, anything of value was moved off the base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt Russia could shoot down cruise missiles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there are no reported casualties from 50 cruise missiles. It was empty. This is just a little show to show Trump and Putin put together to show Trump inst his puppet, but its a really shitty production. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which means they warned the syrians so this whole thing was just a pointless $50 million fireworks display to make Trump look tough while doing nothing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol like Syria could pay for any infrastructure. The country is finished, there is no money to ring out of it, it is failed state. It will never recover as a country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understood. When Russia bombs a hospital in Syria or shells civilians in Ukraine freedom fighting, when people in Chechnya fight against oppressive outsiders it is terrorism. 

We all understand. It really boils to, does Russia want support this? If Russia supports something then it is freedom fighting but if Russia does not it is terrorism. This can be applied to anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You miss the point. Freedom fighting from Ukraine is heroic but freedom fighting from Russia is terrorism. The situation is different you see because Russia supports one and not the other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In many ways actually yes. Both Hitler and trump had bad policies and it it is good Trump is not like Hitler because Hitler could get things he wanted and promised done. They weren't good things, they were bad, but to be fair Trump is too much of an idiot to actually complete anything whereas Hitler could complete things they just weren't good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it proved you wrong. Your earlier source doesnt mention Sarin, you pulled a new source to cover for the fact your earlier source proved you wrong. This new source is one person saying *we dont have proof but they might have Sarin*. If that person has proof they can share it, but the fact remains we know Assad has Sarin and has used it. Furthermore notice that the source is form 2013 and there is nothing else after that? That is because Del ponte was discredited and laughed out years ago. So we see you are desperately pulling sources and trying to spin them. Nobody takes Del ponte seriously not even Putin and Assad for propaganda purposes. 

so like I said earlier there is a very small, almost impossible chance it wasnt Assad, and there is an over 99% chance it was Assad, if you want to cling to the almost impossible scenario because it may be impossible in the same way it may be possible it was aliens you are just showing yourself to either be a propagandist or a person with faulty logic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at this rate IS and Hitler will be more liked than Donald Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans like China more than Donald Trump, poll reveals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans like China more than Donald Trump, poll reveals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans like China more than Donald Trump, poll reveals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump 'won't discuss climate change' at meeting with Xi Jinping despite US and China being worst polluters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump 'won't discuss climate change' at meeting with Xi Jinping despite US and China being worst polluters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do think this. 

A lot of us millenials grew up in shitty red states with red families and we are the most progressive generation ever. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is because you only play 3d chess and cant see the genius of his 4d chess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you find glowing green material in your tea dont drink it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you wont be laughing when he has Trump put polonium in your coffee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Cops, Bad Cops: Trump loves law enforcement, except when theyre investigating him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Cops, Bad Cops: Trump loves law enforcement, except when theyre investigating him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Russian syrian position is that they are always innocent and nothing is their fault, and the trail of bodies in their wake is everyone's fault but theirs. 

I guess those Russian ovservers should have paid better attention as it looks like Assad still has weapons, who would have thought they would be negligent. Just shocking. 

Your own source works against you here. IS has mustard gas not Sarin. Only person with Sarin in Syria is Assad. It is not eays to manufacture, store, or deploy and all cases of suspected use are by Assad. Both Assad and the rebels are known to have used chemical weapons, so so much for your *but its all gone* theory, but in the past it was chlorine and mustard gas. The Sarin gas is only known to have been used once before, by Assad. So end this false equivalency of *yes yes both side have used chemical weapons but ISIS used mustard gas publically and bragged about it so this use of Sarin gas must be IS despite the fact that they dont have the ability to make, store, or deploy it while Assad is known to have it and has the ability to store it and deploy it and uses chemical weapons much more frequently. Nevermind that while IS always takes credit for their infrequent chemical weapon use and Assad lies about his very frequent chemical weapon use, this time is exception.*

Everyone knows it is Assad except for a very few retards. If by some almost impossible chance it wasnt Assad he is still going to get the blame for it since evidence wise it could be nobody else. Dont worry though he isnt going to get in trouble, Trump doesnt care, so there is no need for this Russian style disinformation. You arent helping Russia or Assad out, you are just making the Russian propaganda apparatus look bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol the person claiming *it is a false flag for an event that would almost never happen* is accusing others of sensationalism. There is no need to spam typical Russia style *we can never know* type propaganda. Everyone knows it was assad, including you, and we all know nothing will happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes perfect sense for him to do this. Chemical weapons inspire fear and end resistance quickly. A few hundred Iranians dying from Iraqi chemical weapons got Iran to agree to a cease fire that tens of thousands of dead in the war couldn't do. 

Assad figured correctly trump won't do anything and and without us Europe won't act either. He is trying to terrorize his enemies and it will probably work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could have been aliens too but most likely it was Assad. There I'd no need to defend his actions anymore, trump isn't going to do shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For terror and they are high effective at it. Iraq was losing against Iran but managed to get a cease fire by using chemical weapons. Same thing with rebellion after gulf war, one chemical weapon attack ended it. 

People will be too scared to oppose assad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How  many chemical weapon attacks has IS committed with sarin?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have no history of having sarin  and if they had it they would use it and claim it. IS is not machalvian organization that uses deception. They do the worst they can with what they have and own up to it. Assad on the other hand... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you cleared that up. Investigation is over and assad is off the hook because random Internet person said assad wouldn't do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No because trump doesn't really care. The Russian style *but what if it is false flag so ignore the 99.99% chance it was assad in the almost impossible lottery winning chance it wasn't assad* is not needed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your own doubts are not a defense. He isn't risking anything. Trump won't invade him or do anything and he knows it. He doesn't give a fuck  anymore. There is no need for you to repeat Russian propaganda as it isn't required to protect assad. Assad can use sarin gas everyday from now on. Russia can't do shit  either because they went all in supporting him. 

Good job putin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assad has incentive to use it. The rebels have no incentive to use it against themselves, nor could they even make it like assad could, repeatedly like Russian propaganda claims </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rebels don't have the capability to maufacture sarin  and there is no proof they have it or used it. Assad does have the capability and gas used it before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then kept Bannon on for months after Flynn was gone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is senile and the last person who talks to him can manipulate him and control him. Bannon had a lot of access to Trump. That is why Ivanka his now his secretary to make sure nobody can get Trump alone without Kushner's approval.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Topkek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, an alt right trumpet talking about serious arguments. I realize you don't take any facts about Trump seriously but you only speak for yourself. Judging by your downvotes and my upvotes it looks like the facts once again don't support your alternative facts. Keep yelling *tumblr* my alright snowflake amigo  it won't help you outside your safe space.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump just defended Bill OReilly  in the middle of Sexual Assault Awareness and Prevention Month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump just defended Bill OReilly  in the middle of Sexual Assault Awareness and Prevention Month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump just defended Bill OReilly  in the middle of Sexual Assault Awareness and Prevention Month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump just defended Bill OReilly  in the middle of Sexual Assault Awareness and Prevention Month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> National embarrassment: A majority of Americans dont like having Donald Trump as president, and his own base now is sick of him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> National embarrassment: A majority of Americans dont like having Donald Trump as president, and his own base now is sick of him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trumpets like you don't know truth only alternative truth. The idea of a trumpet bitching  and crying about truth is laughable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww it is cute how you snowflakes stick together when triggered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I went the opinion of an altright  trumpet like yourself I'll ask for it. Be careful you aren't in your safe space snowflake and the real world is a dangerous place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/t_d right now that Bannon has been booted off the national security Council. What a bunch of cucks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You suck at math if you think I can post 24/7. So yes I am 24/7 if you ignore the large gaps  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're fired: White House chief strategist and altright nazi snowflake Stephen Bannon removed from National Security Council likely due to ties with russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he forget to disclose his money from Russia too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're fired: White House chief strategist and altright nazi snowflake Stephen Bannon removed from National Security Council likely due to ties with russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're fired: White House chief strategist and altright nazi snowflake Stephen Bannon removed from National Security Council likely due to ties with russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're fired: White House chief strategist and altright nazi snowflake Stephen Bannon removed from National Security Council likely due to ties with russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're fired: White House chief strategist and altright nazi snowflake Stephen Bannon removed from National Security Council likely due to ties with russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House chief strategist Stephen Bannon no longer part of National Security Council </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Stone accuses Jared Kushner of leaking White House information to Joe Scarborough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumpcare 2.0 efforts are already in shambles as Republicans point the finger at each other: Trump and the GOP once again show America they are too incompetent to govern or even back up their own agenda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumpcare 2.0 efforts are already in shambles as Republicans point the finger at each other: Trump and the GOP once again show America they are too incompetent to govern or even back up their own agenda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumpcare 2.0 efforts are already in shambles as Republicans point the finger at each other: Trump and the GOP once again show America they are too incompetent to govern or even back up their own agenda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vulgar misogyny didnt harm Donald Trump  it helped him: Trump has exploited hatred of women by conservatives for political gain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vulgar misogyny didnt harm Donald Trump  it helped him: Trump has exploited hatred of women by conservatives for political gain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
