<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4900</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 02:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro....LOL..../facepalm

Btw I voted for Bernie, but it says a lot about you that you can't simply read an article and take away good points because of your political views. You're no better than all these people you probably hate.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great advice here on how to deal with any topic that is emotionally or ideologically charged https://hbr.org/2016/10/how-to-build-an-exit-ramp-for-trump-supporters
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 12:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep similarly, I remember reading in Details Magazine (I think) as a kid and an in depth article that detailed backdoors built into the backbone of the web, the ability to monitor/id modems, the data coming from the modems, etc., and the carnivore program. 

I remember telling my friends in college about this stuff and them thinking I had watched too much X-Files :P. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep it was pretty sketchy. the reason i know it was from info they sold was because it was spoofed as being the email account that I just setup on Zoho (xxxx@dogtoys.com). 

The email it was spoofing literally didn't exist until the day I signed up on Zoho and wasn't common like admin/contact...anyway, I forwarded the original emails to support, but never got an official response. They did eventually stop after about a 3 weeks though so /shrug.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Zoho share/sell your email with some pretty shady businesses. I signed up for Zoho a while back and the same day I started receiving phishing emails alerting me to "changes on my site" which were word play variations on the site I submitted.

My site was dogtoys.com (not really) and i started getting emails saying "dogtoyz.com" files had been changed and I needed to login etc. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *crosses fingers* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be higher up. Everything mentioned so far varies so much in terms of intended users/site needs/required skill level etc.

This is like simply asking someone what's the best tool.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
