<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7609</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP why did you delete your claim that the charter hasn't changed... When the news is literally weeks old. Seems awfully dishonest of you.

Because I forgot that it did change. Nonetheless the charter is not offcial and it is just a leak. Who knows if  the offical version is going to still support the extermination of Jews?

But sill this new leaked charter doesn't recognize Israel so it is just propaganda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah find it odd that there are still people that supports Hamas even thought they ethnically cleansed Gaza of Jews and want to do the same thing with the West Bank.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> occupation

1929

what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't they stab the palestinian occupiers in Gaza?  Or the 1.5 million  arabs living in Israel?

But nope. They only stab Jews apparently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 14:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> West Banks ruling party Fatah calls for Palestinian 'Day of Rage' against Israel and 'to clash with the occupier at all friction points' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 14:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lebanese PM calls for permanent ceasefire with Israel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  killing 10 of them for every Israeli killed

This wouldn't happen if Hamas stopped hoarding weapons in schools and hospitals.

Or destroying what little infrastructure they have in Gaza every few years

See above.

Or enforcing embargoes of Gaza. 

Even Abbas and Egypt agrees with the "embargo".

Or keeping them in a perpetual apartheid state inside Israel.

This is nonsense.

But no, as Netanyahu said, it's all their fault for paying terrorists.

That's right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lebanese leader calls for permanent ceasefire with Israel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netanyahu: Palestinians must stop paying terrorists, prove they want peace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... as retaliation for attack.

Sputnik is propaganda.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran bars Mahmoud Ahmadinejad from re-running for president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Times of Israel didn't made the UN documents. 

This news is reported by other sources. 

https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/world-history/holocaust-allied-forces-knew-before-concentration-camp-discovery-us-uk-soviets-secret-documents-a7688036.html

https://sputniknews.com/europe/201704181052739261-holocaust-allied-forces-war/

http://www.ibtimes.co.uk/un-war-crime-files-holocaust-death-camps-will-rewrite-crucial-parts-history-1617332 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they meant to say that the UN made documents about it, not that the UN was talking at the time (As you say the UN was established in 1945).

The unsealed United Nations files show that the US, UK and Russia knew as early as December 1942 that two million Jews had been massacred and millions more were at risk of being killed, Britains Independent newspaper reported on Tuesday.

There are other proofs that the Allies knew the extent of the Holocaust already in 1942. For example, the Yad Vashem Holocaust memorial states in a report to the UN that During 1942, reports of a Nazi plan to murder all the Jews  including details on methods, numbers, and locations  reached Allied and neutral leaders from many sources.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allies knew of Holocaust in 1942, 2 years before previously assumed, UN documents prove </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Anyone think Israel has a vested interest in seeing Assad gone?

Is not Israel the one saying it. Other source have reported it.

http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/14/bashar-al-assad-still-has-hundreds-tonnes-chemical-weapons-former/

https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/bashar-al-assad-chemical-weapons-attack-stockpile-syria-obama-trump-moscow-a7684706.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/bashar-al-assad-chemical-weapons-attack-stockpile-syria-obama-trump-moscow-a7684706.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
