<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8068</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 22:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jund is BRG. Junk is Abzan. Rock is the OG BG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 19:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> boohoohoogland strikes again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 08:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That book one description sounds pretty generic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first villain is a vagabond that thinks he is an angel. He's an able monk - good with his fists, with a few spells in his repertoire - that ultimately ends up causing an Arab Spring type event, then leaves after giving one of that region's leaders the equivalent of a magical nuke in case things get bad.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Magic is a defense mechanism that kept the Primeval Dragons and Primordial Elementals from completely destroying the setting. It may have come from the vaku, a synapsid race derived from the stunted offsprig of the Primevals. The appearance of the two at roughly the same time is what leads most scholars to believe that this is the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 01:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grab em by the Abzan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 00:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ayyy boyo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 00:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hobb knows how to succinctly communicate a threat. She does it very well with the primary enemy introduced about halfway through Assassin's Apprentice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vegeta's competitive spirit  and arrogance + Goku's playfulness = new entity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 16:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed Broken Empire - being presented with such a thoroughly terrible viewpoint character hooked me. I tend to look at novels that use these kind of characters as case studies in abnormal psychology. It took the politics of bigger novels and gave you a streamlined sword and sorcery sort of approach that made the trilogy very enjoyable. The world's expansion in Red Queen's War was equally great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 01:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 01:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> op ur a patoto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 23:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When one of the heroes manages to...make it so that the Aldrain won't be able to threaten the setting...and when another goes back to free a loved one from her captor.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 23:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the OP finds Conan to his/her liking, I think they'll like Morgan's fantasy. It reads like an update on Moorcock's Eternal Champion multiverse with a touch of the Black Company. It does have a slight horror fell to it, but the three heroes are driven by a righteous sense of indignation at a broken system.

(I've read your Broken Empire/Red Queen's War trilogies, Abercrombie, Morgan, Cook, Erikson, Hobb and I am still questing for the grimdark. It has as of yet eluded me, sadly) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 22:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conan the Barbarian by Robert E Howard

Memory, Sorrow and Thorn trilogy by Tad Williams

A Land Fit For Heroes by Richard Morgan

Try these OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 22:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://forum.nogoblinsallowed.com/viewforum.php?f=19

^ A community of MtG fans that write MTG fanfiction. Might tickle your fancy OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 22:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing whatever deck I like that is within the format rules to the best of my ability. Playing the deck as optimally as possible. It probably helps that Modern Jund is both my favorite casual and competitive deck.

1. I am both

2. See the above paragraph

3. Both enjoy playing a certain deck to the best of that deck's and their abilities.

4. I'm naturally competitive.

5. Jund em the out

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 19:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they enjoy them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the local elementary school they held some kinda mock election for Trump vs Clinton. Trump did overwhelmingly well with the Hispanic children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ryan Barger. I like his [[Tarmogoyf]] and [[Rakdos Cackler]]. [[Loxodon Smiter]] looks good too.

Ron Spencer's another artist whose work I enjoy and wouldn't mind illustrating my deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 23:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Self-loathing? The lady that started a war to make her land a better place for everyone hated her native tribe and their bloodthirsty ways. I don't study history, so its probably happened IRL somewhere or another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 18:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jund - I believe you gotta take care of yourself before you can help others. Take your passions and channel them into something worth your while. When you do good, you should reward yourself - party hard, do whatever you like so long as you aren't breaking the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 18:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would probably just set Conflagrate on the table with a bit of a flourish.

Ho lee fuk whatever LSV has been doing is working out well for him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 18:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 17:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm enjoying that neck of Hobb's fantasy land more than I did the Buckkeep environs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been Eyeing Black Sun Rising by Friedman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 17:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your opinion of this series, r/fantasy? That Michael Whelan cover art's a big part of it, but the blurb seems kind of interesting. Have you read this one and if so does it come recommended? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 16:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Loves Witcher"

Go find Elric: The Stealer of Souls from Del Ray. It is about an albino mercenary nicknamed "the white wolf" with a soulstealing sword that relies on drugs for sustenance. There's two novels in this collection, neither over 300 pages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 16:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Test of Metal* and the Kamigawa novels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 06:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Holy Triad of fantasy series are Elric, Conan, and the Dark Tower. If it feels like any of these three, I'm there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 02:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cope harder NYT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 02:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree - it gave us something that Goku couldn't beat on his own, no matter how strong he got via training. The biggest weakness is a lack of background for 17 and 18 that explains how they wound up with Gero. The second weak point is Cell's transformations; I preferred the first one over the other two, but liked how Perfect Cell didn't really feel a need to destroy for the sake of destroying. Perfect Cell knew he was the strongest guy around and just wanted to have some fun.

I didn't need anything deep for 17 or 18. We know Android Gero was probably upset about Goku breaking up the RR Army back in Dragonball, which was sufficient motivation for this series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 02:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Androids was a good narrative. We got to see Goku get BTFO by a disease. I'm not being sarcastic here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 02:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was their best shot there against Buu, so there was that. Logistically it seems like you'd need the SSJ3 protected by an army of SSJ2's that can clear a path so your SSJ3 can do its damage before the transformation wears off.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 22:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Autris* - Sentient, motile groves of carnivorous plants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 22:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They probably wrote the scripts pretty close together. Or, reminding the audience who the characters are. Probably a combination of the two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 20:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could work...

I see the dragons as being frozen in a kind of extradimensional "void." This "void" could be the starry skies stretching over the dream-plane. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 20:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember a fairly freakish one described in the Book of Revelations...I think that may have been the one I had in mind, but I'll look into the Old Testament and see what's there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lovecraft It Up - Hold the Tentacles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a lark I decided to try drafting up some fantasy critters with a Lovecraftian feel. Old primal gods slumbering...waking...lost knowledge...intrigues...all that. The meat of his stuff rather than just the tentacles and fishiness. 

I could use your help in refining these ideas. If it helps, I listened to Pickman's Model, Unknown Kadath and The Haunter in the Dark on audiobook for inspiration.

*

**Dragons**  Frozen in the depths of space like the Ogdru-Jahad from Hellboy

**Angels**  Bound by prison seals in ruined temples scattered throughout the dark woods. Visually they resemble the angels of the Bible.

**Elementals**  Lurking in the wilds bound to groves by ape-magic.

**Leviathans**  Imprisoned in trench-bottom ammonite temples by the Salamanderfolk.

**Demons**  Doomed to haunt a magical pit found in one of the ratfolk  nests-turned-library.

*

**Lizardfolk**  In the entropic lands the Lizardfolk, driven to create in response to the destruction wrought by the Salamanderfolk, ratfolk and apes, eventually began warping the aether by blending homunculi, apes, and ratfolk to create a race possessing the hunger of the ratfolk, the ingenuity of the apes, and the resolve of the homunculi  they called the new race human.  

With their newly created race the Lizardfolk seek to create a folk that would survive the upheavals that could come from freeing the dragons frozen in the depths of space. If they are to continue creating, the Lizardfolk feel that a shakeup from the freeing of the dragons is necessary  without it, they believe their world will become barren, sterile, devoid of meaning.

**Apes**  In the entropic lands the apes took it upon themselves to tame the bizarre elementals that haunted their jungles. They believed it was the emanations of their patron elemental, a great bound thing, which drew the lesser elementals. And the apes welcomed the opportunity to test their strength against these wild mana-constructs.

Unbeknownst to the apes, their bound elemental played them against the lesser elementals. It sought strong servitors, knowing that soon the dragons would be freed  and that it would need strong acolytes to stand against the chaos to come.

**Salamanderfolk**  In the entropic lands the Salamanderfolk spent their time in the trench-bottom ammonite cities where they built undersea cities that tapped their bound leviathans for power. Within these cities the Salamanderfolk began building laboratories where they could bring specimens from the surface for further studies.

Salamanderfolk found themselves experimenting on the likes of Lizardfolk, apes, and the lesser elementals that stalked the lands. From this came their bizarre servitors; these servitors were deployed against the Ratfolk. While the Salamanderfolk respected the creative drive of the Lizardfolk and the shamanic bent of the apes, they hated the ratfolk proclivity to horde knowledge without finding ways to apply it.

**Ratfolk**  In the entropic lands the ratfolk inhabited the plateaus where they trafficked with the demons that had been cast from their place in the ashen skies by the magic that kept the dragons bound in the cosmos. Gaining knowledge, and being fearful of the other races they hid in their plateau rats nests, accumulating knowledge without any need to apply it.

A covenant between the demon and ratfolk  knowledge in exchange for the demons protection  provided the ratfolk with the opportunity to weasel their way out of their service to the demons. Fearing that the demons would turn on them, the ratfolk found a use for their knowledge  binding the demons to a great pit within their greatest rats nest upon one of the planes most desolate plateaus. 

**Homunculi**  In the entropic lands the angels required servitors from which they could arm themselves with the strength of faith. Only through blades forged by faith could the angels slaughter the great darkness, bringing dawn to a world of night. The homunculi are observers, philosophers, and advisors that served in the courts of the apes, Salamanderfolk, ratfolk and Lizardfolk. 

Homunculi are strengthened by the unified desire of the other races: finding a better world in which to shelter against the uncertainties of the ever-changing world and the capriciousness of bound dragons, demons, elementals, angels, and leviathans. From their strength the angels, in turn, gain strength. The homunculi, though weak on their own, are reservoirs of power from which the angels will draw on the power needed to bring an end to the instability that gives the entropic lands their name.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 23:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dragonborn reproduce by shedding their scales into wounds inflicted on elementals during their mating fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't Eddings write like that on purpose? I'd swear I read where Eddings just wanted to see how easy it would be to get published and make money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Conan - He knows how to have a good time

*Roland Deschain - I admire this man's drive, dedication, and leadership abilities

*Hellian - I got a couple of friends IRL like her. She just clicked with me. Especially her bar-crawl in Reaper's Gale.

*Elric - I like his idea that he's beholden only to himself.

*Stannis Baratheon - I like his grit, dedication, and willingness to use the tool's he's got to get his job done.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He apparently frequented a tavern or pub where Tolkien and the Inklings chilled. He respected the Professor but disagreed with his politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Griggs: You're gonna tell him (Joker) I took care of you?

Harley: *smirking* You are sooooo screwed. Ahahahahaha

I also chuckled when Deadshot pointed his gun at Griggs, then fired it into the sky while Griggs nearly shit his pants. 

Try throwing in a nice spread of humor as it fits the situation, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 07:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been burnt out on zombies for a while. I did like the enemies that would pull G-Virus mutations when they got damaged. Give them a more zombielike look, less like soldiers, and you got a winner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 07:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Land Fit For Heroes by Richard Morgan.

The good guy gets ugly in the second book onward, but it makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 05:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Elric of Melnibone (Elric saga) - having a duke of hell in your corner might be useful.

*The Lady (Black Company) - powerful spellcasters are never not needed.

*Roland Deschain (The Dark Tower Cycle) - someone that'll stay calm in the storm could be helpful.

*El Diablo (Suicide Squad) - having a fire demon with a conscience could come in handy in the clutch.

* Hellboy (Hellboy 2004) - a brawler that can keep the spirits up.

* Liz Sherman (Hellboy 2004) - a pyrokinetic isn't gonna go amiss

* Abe Sapien (Hellboy 2004) - a telepath could be useful

* Quick Ben (Malazan) - seems like the kind of wizard you want in your corner.

* Karsa Orlong (Malazan) - good warrior all around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 15:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Imaginos album by Blue Oyster Cult </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 07:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vaku -

They're synapsids resembling wingless dragons that possess the ability to magically alter the terrain in their immediate surroundings. It allows the vaku to adapt to almost any environment. They were one of the first sentient races to emerge on my world, so their abilities reflect a need to survive an extremely variable climate in a world where Primeval Dragons and Primordials routinely clashed.

I wanted a bestial yet reptilian race that would put you on edge - are these things helping me..using me...or am I overthinking it, these are just dumb animals meant to be used? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 07:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a character named Veil that got unexpectedly vicious in dealing with the Cleric-in-Chief, to the point that she freed a shaman from one of the foundling races and used its influence to turn the Cleric-in-Chief's own people against her.

Veil had come to the wartorn country with the intent of shaking up the power structure to win the favor of an oni-demon currently bound to one of that country's big movers and shakers in the criminal underworld.

I didn't think of Veil as bad or good - just doing her thing. Then she turned a bit too vicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 06:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One big villain, the Cleric-in-Chief came from a tribal folk that delight in human sacrifice. She wants better for everyone. She never asked anyone if they wanted the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 06:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Primordials.

Dragons are all of that raw power wrapped in a husk cosmic debris from the big bang event that created the Primordials. Primordials are those the power of the dragons, unbound. It made them natural enemies that see one another as threats to their existence. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol

I live life in the danger zone

But srsly, I'm too f*cking lazy to wait for the Liveships books to come in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 18:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm enjoying Dragon Keeper a bit more than I did the Fitz books. No clue why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 18:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I'm reading Rain Wild Chronicles atm. Waiting on my order of the Liveship Traders to come in. Does Liveship Traders touch on the appearance/return of Selden Vestrit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elderlings and White Prophets (Spoilers Farseer + Tawny Man trilogies) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are White Prophets related in any way to the Elderlings, or are these two separate peoples? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheetoh dust is a hell of a drug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 01:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. One of my millennial friends shared a post about everyone being pussies nowadays. Others were liking posts about millennial tears. We're all millennials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easy - 

Did I enjoy it?/10

*

10's -

The Broken Empire Trilogy by Lawrence

The Stealer of Souls by Moorcock

Stormbringer by Moorcock

Reaper's Gale by Erikson

Toll the Hounds by Erikson

Dust of Dreams by Erikson

The Crippled God by Erikson

The Dark Tower by King

The Wastelands by King

The Gunslinger by King

9

The Twilight Reign series by Lloyd

The rest of the Malazan series

The rest of the Elric series

The Vlad Taltos series

The rest of the Dark Tower series

The Black Company series sans The Silver Spike

8

The Silver Spike

A Song of Ice and Fire


Anything below 8 is usually NyQuil -

The Way of Kings

The Lord of the Rings

Dragonlance Chronicles and Legends

Death Gate Cycle

Magician: Apprentice

Book of the New Sun

Tie-Ins of various sorts

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also:

Todd Lockwood's cover for Stormcaller and each subsequent Twilight Reign novel. Those are some of my favorite fantasy covers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Picacio's cover for Elric: The Stealer of Souls

Steven Stone's cover for The Gunslinger

Michael Whelan's Dragonflight cover
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 16:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rule of Lazy: I don't conlang and don't research real-world history, cultures etc. I just make it up as it comes to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 16:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Eyes of the Cleric**

The EC's are fallen and mortally wounded soldiers repurposed to resemble the native gods of the enemy. They are not armored; their creators turn the emotions of the soldiers used - these soldiers are effectively catatonic, preserving their sense of duty, rage at their superiors, horror at what happens in war - into psionic waves that compel the enemy to bow in submission.

**Crimson Company**

The primary military force of Kargathdra, the red hand of the Crimson Regent, and the scarlet sword with which Kargathdra's industrial lords maintain their power. They include berserkers, elementalists, munitions experts, and dragonspeakers that handle the pit-dragons.

**The Stoneforged**

These are ninjalike warriors from the southernmost continent Underworld. They use illusion, conjuration, and are concerned with the procurement and preservation of knowledge. While their illusions and conjured creatures wage war, the Stoneforged recover tomes of magic, history, economics, medicine, and the arts that are in danger of being destroyed.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 15:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most every fantasy map's gonna have a range of mountains called "spine of _____." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 14:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did mine as a giant spinelike device with the powerlines running underground from the spine like a bunch of nerves.

Because every fantasy setting needs a spine-of-the-world thing.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **REEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE** - H </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roland Deschain and Stannis Baratheon - these guys took their licks, kept their eyes on the prize, and did what they could with what they were given. They're my biggest heroes in the spec fiction genre.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it ain't Eberron

you're dead to me boyo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. I thought they were just general gaming streams. Does Pat ever talk about his influences in fantasy literature, literary literature, tabletop gaming etc during his gaming streams? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am new to the readership - what's "blanketfort?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat. Has he ever said how wildly off-course his series has veered from the original drafts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP, I came to Elric by way of the Del Rey reprints and just...really liked the character for some reason. Maybe it was that rock-and-roll antihero flair. I'm also a fan of the larger than life character I met in a bunch of Jim Morrison biographies, so that could have something to do with it.

It could also be because I found the books relatively fast-paced compared to much of what was on the shelves. That, the dragons, elementals and demons were elements I also enjoyed.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the f*ck could you not lol. Still working on Red Queen, but Mark's my favorite of the "new" voices in the genre...2011 still doesn't seem that long ago to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he had all three of these things written prior to the first one's publication. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL OP

That's what I was gonna post - Broken Empire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roland Deschain was my gateway into fantasy. His grit and determination was inspiring to me as an individual. I'm not sure if that's escapism or not, but there you have it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 02:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **MFW CUCKS BECOME CANUCKS**

**MFW CUCK CANUCKS HAND CANADA A TRUMP OF THEIR OWN** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 00:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't have called Way of Kings dense...but I usually hit the midpoint before my interest wanes.

But damn did Brandon put together a great prologue for WoK.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 00:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gonna recommend Gardens to OP lol. Its like he's floored it and all the depth of details are as blurs as you speed through the plot. The others slow down, but they get hella dense from seven onwards.

Try the Black Company OP. Its epic, but I think its what you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 23:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was surprised by the depth of politicking. It reminded me of the Ice and Fire novels by Martin, except you're hearing about it all secondhand alongside the Company. I went in expecting almost no politicking because no one ever really mentioned it in connection with the Black Company novels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking as a straight guy, I didn't find the sex all that gratuitous. I loved the focus on the underworld elements leading into the fantastic. The next two books have some great horroresque segments too. It was a damn fine fantasy trilogy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 20:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These fuckers don't learn, do they? You want a Trump 2020, this is how you get Trump 2020. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 06:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you two were talking, did she make any little remarks, like say you go by Bill but your birthname's William - if she says anything like, "I'll call you ____, I prefer that name," you can take it as a subtle sign she finds you attractive. Pay attention to what's said and communicated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bunch of idiots lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL he's white. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **SWEDEN YES** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If its Kaine, we got this in the bag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 06:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **LOCK HER UP** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I was thinking about DnD's generic five-headed dragon goddess. The Foreshi (dragon-lampreys, the ancestors of the Primevals and by extension the Primords) however, did come from the brackish southern oceans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Mixed Magery Martial Arts** - DBZ fights scaled down to Saiyan Saga levels. No world-threatening stuff, just a good show. Mostly practice by the Sajin Monks.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Yuan-Ti. They would rather continually cripple themselves (by removing their fire glands and retaining their atrophied vestigial wings), believing they are acting in defiance of the Primeval Dragons. They're hung up on the brutality of the Primevals, using an all-or-nothing black-and-white sense of morality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Visang Primord are five Primeval Dragons that were disgusted by the warlike ways of their kin. They hatched a plan that allowed them to use the Ifriti (created as weapons by the Primevals, then thrown away) to construct a great rig of magical energy that would decay the personality, leaving anyone exposed to it a vicious, braindead husk. The Primord effectively genocided their kin by throwing them into the rig.

Joke was on the Primord - because they eventually got chucked into the rig and came out as the five-headed mutant monstrosity that passes for my world's Tiamat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speak American you crazy third worlders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An immunology textbook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **#SheForAll** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the variety.

Its the only format where I can field [[Flametongue Kavu]], [[Thunderbreak Regent]], [[Chandra, Torch of Defiance]] and [[Sarkhan, the Dragonspeaker]] and manage a win.

Standard you have the fast turnover rate and small cardpool. Vintage, you have the need for Power 9 and I *think* there's fewer viable decks there. Vintage experts feel free to correct me here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kaine ever come back from the Everglades? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 19:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woot woot

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 11:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gotta look out for yourself at the end of the day - its your vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 11:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit happens.

I didn't get to where I am on the first go.

I didn't throw a fit about not making it the first go.

I found out what I needed to do, got up and hit it again, then I made it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 11:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trumper here. No. I was prepared to wake up, greet the dawn of Madam President's era by going to the gym, going to rotations, coming home, sleeping and doing it all again the next day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 11:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old Boy's going to war with the DNC dont ya know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 10:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rubber bullets a bit much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Crimson Company**

A mercenary unit from the jungle-continent Kargathdra, they are identified by their crimson uniforms with the slashed-eye sigil of Thunderbreak the Crimson Regent. They are split into different divisions based on speciality:

The Beast Kings - Ashen warriors trained in the art of berserking

The Space Kings - Elemental-slingers
 
The Star Kings - Mortar experts

The Demon Kings - They handle the pit dragons, including the breeding training and commanding of the pit dragons in the battlefield.

The use of "King" is in jest toward the rulers that would deploy the Crimson Company as expendable soldiers in order to maintain the rulers' reputation.

**The Sajin Monks**

The Sajin is an order of monks that hails from Eberrai, an equatorial continent serving as the heart of the Chain of Fire (lands near the equator). They're badasses because their order is known for binding the guardian spirits of the land's magical veins to themselves (in the form of intricate tattoo patterns).

The Sajin blend martial arts with magery, emphasizing mind and body existing in a state of harmony. They tend to find service the world over, using their experiences to better themselves as individuals. Continual education is their drive.

**The Reliquary Runebladers**

The Reliquary Runebladers hail from Jungko's contested interior where tribes old and new continually clash while enterprising individuals from the continent's coastal citadels attempt to manipulate the tribal warfare to their benefit.

The Runebladers are named from their runeblades - these come from the Plain of Rune where quills from a great white Primeval Dragon stand embedded in the hardpan. Within the runeblades they trap the souls of the land's deceased - turning them into pure energy, allowing the dead to have a bit of vengeance before being expended and moving on.

While the Runebladers attempt to remain neutral, they haven began to sway toward a rising ruler from the seaside citadels that promises stability and prosperity previously unrealized by the interior's folk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 04:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I'll just use the real thing. Kind of like when I described someone's armor as "baroque." I didn't know it tied into an actual historical period...I just saw Moorcock use it in one of his Elric stories, so I copped it having a general idea of what it would look like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 20:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Orochi**

Orochi describes a human that has become host to a Yuan-Ti hatchling. Yuan-Ti have a brutish tradition where young that attempt to shed their vestigial wings are thrown out of the mountain nest. Some of these hatchlings were found by human monks and formed parasitic bonds with them, gifting them with magical strength in exchange for use of the host's physical and psychic capabilities.

With their hosts, the Orochi undertake endeavours mimicking those of the Yuan-Ti's progenitors the Primeval Dragons. Usually these blend the ambition of the great old dragons with the temperance of the Yuan-Ti.

You will know an Orochi by their outward appearance. The skin takes on a greenish coloration with bruiselike mottling. Up close you may notice something akin to psoriasis that leaves the host with diamondlike patterns across their skin. Despite their unique appearance the Orochi will usually don a cloak or robes that protect their parasitic Yuan-Ti hatchling until the point at which the hatchling integrates with the host's spinal cord. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 19:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alrighty then.

Marching and nonviolent protest is fine. Rioting and damage is over the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
