<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2778</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The First Honest Cable Company </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 21:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 02:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First thing I noticed was the possibility of multiple sights on weapons. In the 2^nd screenshot, there's a set of iron sights off to the right. Not sure if that was in BF3, or if it's something that's normally seen, but it could be a new feature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 22:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your input! I was planning to play AC3 tonight, as it's nearly finished downloading. I generally get my 'money's worth' on games like this anyway, so I go and do every extra mission I can find. I shall bear your money tips in mind when I play though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 21:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If any of you want to get your money's worth, you might want to pick up the Deluxe edition, as it contains all the DLC as well, for a few more quid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 19:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://store.steampowered.com/app/208480/?snr=1_7_15__13  
I personally chose this, seeing as I had bought FC3 on sale in GAME for about 15. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure if these count as particularly patient purchases, but they did for me! Farcry 3 and Assassin's Creed 3 are on sale on steam, and you can pick each one up for less than 20. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 19:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Sure Harry, you're a wizard..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 20:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sit on My Face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 00:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 90s Eurodance: Captain Jack - Captain Jack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-18 21:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A handy tip for people using Windows 8 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 19:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 18:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, if you could give a full description of exactly what happens when you press the power button, that'd be great :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 18:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Run through this checklist first, if the problem's still there, we've eliminated the known ones. http://www.tomshardware.co.uk/forum/261145-13-read-posting-boot-problems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 03:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had some great ideas :) This one's a sort of run and gun where the main mechanic is a defibrillator that screws with your controls when you pick them up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 01:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! I've not played around with Unity yet, only done C++ with SFML and GameMaker really. That looks really cool though! Did you like the theme? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 01:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) The submission for the Jam will probably just include the core mechanics of running along to keep yourself alive until you pass out. I'll carry on with this in my own time, tidy up some of the botches and make it into more of a presentable game, possibly making it in C++ or something to give me practice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 22:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've been making a small sidescroller as a mid level jam. The core mechanic (which we still haven't got fully implemented) is a defibrillator to keep your heartbeat going faster, so you can run faster and get more points, but it has a price. It will randomly rebind your jump and crouch keys, giving you a few seconds to adjust, and (if we get round to it) possibly flip your screen all different ways or invert all the colours. Blood packs keep your health filled up, and you have to jump and slide to avoid obstacles. Here's a WIP screenshot of it (showing the awesome slide sprite we have): http://i.imgur.com/kmFF4PV.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone taking part in the Global Game Jam? Here's a screenshot of our WIP game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 22:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, it's my first post here. I'm taking part in the Global Game Jam this weekend, and I was wondering if anyone else here was, what sort of language are you making things in, and how you're getting along. We're using Game Maker (less drag and drop, more coding) to make a sort of run and gun. Here's a small in-game shot:  
http://i.imgur.com/kmFF4PV.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 01:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, wonder of wonders, today it's been spectacular. All three of us have been at 60mbps pretty much all day with the lowest ping in a long time. Don't know what's going on there, but it's good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 03:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's nothing. I'm on the 60mb tariff in Leicester, and I've seen 2k ping with 0.04Mbps download, and 0.75 Upload. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 01:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tl;dr: Whip pretty much anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 23:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From this advert: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=72t7KzJQQxo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 01:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries mate :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [UK] [H] Point of View GTX 560 1GB [W]  or AM3+ ATX motherboard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 21:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for either cash or an ATX board, with support for AM3+ processors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 16:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The brilliant thing about him is that the character was almost entirely created by the actor. Ubisoft had planned on a 300lb, towering muscular giant to be the secondary antagonist. What Michael Mando produced in his audition was something much more sinister, and was originally not taken on. They liked it so much they rewrote him entirely, including the last minute addition of the Spanish accent :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 15:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's from a miniseries called the Far Cry Experience. Here's the full 30 mins of it: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qKfXatOMMXY  
There's a lot of .gif-able scenes in there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shut up [X-Post from HIFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 05:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 05:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will this do you? http://imgur.com/BqN02eC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shut the fuck up [X-Post from /r/HIFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 05:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HIFW people start talking about a show I want to see, but haven't started yet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 04:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 03:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, 1000 times yes. I still believe it is, and I'm 19 now :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 17:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great! I was expecting pixelated because blowing images up does that, but this is good :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] 1920x1080 wallpaper (if at all possible) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 17:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there, I saw a documentary last night and one of the features was a group of polar bears who come ashore once a year and play with sled dogs. I really wanted this as a wallpaper, but the image is small. Is there any way of resizing this to a 1920x1080 image so I can use it as a wallpaper? Here is the image: 
http://4.bp.blogspot.com/_-64sx017tqA/Sh2xhN0IxfI/AAAAAAAACEU/VLZknWA8dP4/s400/polar-bear-husky-dog-playing-2.jpg  
Also if someone could remove the chain that'd be fantastic :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 00:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aye, the manufacturer is Point of View, which I don't think I'd heard of when I got the card. I've always liked MSI, maybe I'll get one of them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 00:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main issue I'm having is annoying drops in games like BF3. I'm using a 1920x1080 monitor, and my 560 heats up to about 90^o C, which, while it's not bad, is a little unsettling. I'd like a card that can take most games in its stride, without having to pay a vast amount for it, and something that doesn't heat up to such extremes when playing games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 00:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the way I have got liveUSBs of linux working. Would recommend this way if it still doesn't work for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
