<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1702</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the language is dead, I'm having trouble distinguishing the subtle difference between "bulwark" vs "palladium," sounds like a funny debate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Whitehouse just say Gorsuch quoted the Hamilton musical? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This subreddit might even consider not posting many stories or responses on the subject of Wiretapp, this is an honorable and worthy post, just saying this WH is such a distracter to conversation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh but I thought if the President and his cronies believe *or* pretend to believe it, it is trueeeeeeeeee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gorsuch Walks Back Testimony: From "I would have walked out the door" if Trump said overturn Roe v Wade to "Trump and I talked about abortion being 'divisive' in campaign" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy Moses, Gee Whiz, I hate to think the worst of people, gosh darn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly GOP is distracting away from Gorsuch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The precedent of the precedent. But then why do anti-choicers still support him? There must be a hidden message... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We laugh last  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call and tell your Senators to get on Reddit, if they aren't already  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said "*bigly*" and they all paused to joke and laugh about it.  Happened! Gorsuch talks to Trump everyday "probably" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy who says he understands the separation of powers between Judicial and Executive Branches just quoted obscure president Trump reference: "Big League" ("bigly?") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republican Sen. Ben Sasse just created an amazing replay clip saying "No one is watching this, no will watch this for two weeks after the vote." This public hearing doesn't matter? Pretty sure everyone will watch this "no one is watching" clip tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Programmed to destroy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Holy Backflip Batman, maybe if I start giving questions as answers I can get out of this trap, golly gosh Batman, get me a mirror!" 
-Gorsuch, Boy Wonder  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and the jerks repeat it and basically become Russian bots  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or they will just continue trying to delete sex Education and birth control.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or because men can masturbate, women can have abortions... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Holy Power Batman, Super Precedent Man is toiling away at my anti-abortion beliefs, but gosh golly, I   must   keep    my   mouth closed." -Gorsuch the Boy Wonder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "My two young daughters, I want them to have the same rights as a young man." Gorsuch on Abortion Rights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To some degree but they probably know we know. They blend in at first until suddenly they subvert. I assume they also repeat anti-trump stories that we already know about so they just fill up the stage with repeating the same story. I have doubts about some posts that are just people's tweets, because the tweets are already out there so filling Reddit with stories we know hides stories we don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming that question is to my fictional Gorsuch, Boywonder: 

"Holy Marathon Batman! No, I had no idea there would be so many questions, golly gee I'm just not prepared right now to answer." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a regular Jim Comey, that one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Holy Abortion Batman, I hope I can get out of answering Roe v Wade questions again today, golly gee!" Neil Gorsuch, Boy Wonder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Golly gee, holy Jesus Batman, a woman ought to know what's more important; a job or raising a child, they can't have both!" Gorsuch, Boy Wonder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya I was just using the FBI investigation as an example. Sure, everyone does this, I heard your point, I don't think you heard mine though, I'm not saying it's easy, I'm saying it is coming to a point where ideological narratives will not succeed in allowing a person to blindly follow one inconsistent story after another, yes this will always exist in some form, but I feel a change is coming where there will be more personal individual ideology, more parties perhaps is the physical realization of that. And with that, there will be a way to speak to eachother with different views, where a person can more easily change a mind. There is something about BrightBert that is new, there's a tone, and there is something about that tone that makes me think something better to counter that tone is coming soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When many people are talking about a thing like Russia, and many things need to be look at from many angles more and more people need to put their hands on information to investigate. As always in history, more hands equals more leaks. FBI leaks are more normal than Russia leaking private emails about an election campaign during an election.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree, I think minds can be moved away from conspiracy theories more than 1 out of 10. And I think while those websites are presenting a very clear and cohesive narrative, where each story reinforces a larger idea and builds upon a single minded ideology, I think they can be countered by other narratives, and eventually this single-minded person would pick and choose from different narratives and instead of building a singular narrative with these pieces, they will have many unique personal narratives i.e. A liberal! So while idealolgy allows a Trump supporter to see an FBI investigation as fine for Trump and bad for Hillary, one might imagine that the Trump/Republican ideological narrative is chipping away at itself as inconsistency mounts and explanations split people off in several different directions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even convicting Trump *yet* for collusion with Russia, I want the full investigation and fuller revelation of evidence collected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to put some context around that or people might think you are Russian trying to distract  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is hard to tell the difference between a jerk and a Russian troll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Greg Gordon, national correspondent for McClatchy News, talks with Rachel Maddow about McClatchy investigative reporting in the FBI looking into the role of pro-Trump U.S. newsites (and automatic Twitter bots) in Russian intrusion in the U.S." Also opens with a look at Putin opposition leader Aleksei Navalny, now literally green in face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rachel Maddow: FBI probing Russian influence via pro-Trump US websites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really sets up what is going on with abortion and how to look at Gorsuch's answers, this article says it all  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NoSuch GorSuch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SHITtoKNOW! Roe v Wade to Planned Parenthood v Casey to Whole Womans Health v Hellerstedt, How Gorsuch Can Chip Away At Abortion Rights, a quick history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> M I S S I S S I P P I ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Late last week, a federal district judge permanently blocked a Mississippi law designed to close the states only abortion clinic.


The ruling comes eight months after the U.S. Supreme Court declared unconstitutional an almost identical Texas law in **Whole Womans Health v. Hellerstedt.** 

The Texas law, like the Mississippi law struck down last week, would have required any doctor associated with an abortion clinic to have admitting privileges at a nearby hospital." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mississippi Finally Stops Defending Clinic Shutdown Law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hallie Jackson: I have a second question... Spicer: I love your counting, it's like CBO... Jackson: (rolls eyes) Would you like to elaborate? Spicer: No </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How soon until Trump distances himself from KellyAnne?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Line cutter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alex Jones probably a stupid pawn and BrightBert treasonous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Womans Health vs. Hellerstedt* is more on solid ground with defining the "obstacles of undue burden." But there is almost a precedent to mess with the edges of *Roe v Wade* further, reaffirming or unaffirming, Perhaps no longer adding-on to undermine
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard things, I think so, yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I concur, *Plan Parenthood v Casey* and *Whole Womans Health vs. Hellerstedt* have reaffirmed Roe v Wade, but the language is shakey and somewhat interpretable as this very informative article points out that I previously [posted](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/60nd0k/beyond_roe_v_wade_heres_what_gorsuch_means_for/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps there is some issue we are not lucky to have Mattis for, I dont know. But who knows, the Constitution is pretty liberal and progressive maybe Gorsuch will someday interpret it in that original way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I would like the Dems to draw-out some of those private assurances Gorsuch gave Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better to hide what he thinks on large general topics until it matters?...the precedent is the precedent until there's a new precedent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Melania what? No I don't have that STD!" Future DJT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly! Or what they don't say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gorsuch refuses to say whether he'd overturn Roe v. Wade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compare and contrast to [Gorsuch Today](https://twitter.com/BraddJaffy/status/844190201530531841/video/1)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll see, Gorsuch might misspeak or reveal something new. He just admitted he's a human for example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keith Boykin on Twitter: When Ted Kennedy asked Scalia about Roe v. Wade, Scalia chose not to answer. Once he joined the court, he called for Roe to be overruled. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it goes for Gorsuch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But wouldnt it be garbled? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, why *do* Supreme Court Judges get a pass when clearly they were picked for religious reasons  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought goverment and religion were separate, judges don't get a pass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moderation is key </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a human yells "climate change" underwater, does it make a sound? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And is this Ivanka available? Or, maybe she has a daughter?" DJT, 2018 cont. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Gorsuch leaves from Washington </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "No, you're confused because Trump is a man and he likes to build pillow forts." -Spicey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Jared Kushner? Never heard of him." Future DJT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donny's golf cart has a potty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps she'll have a pop-up purse-shop on the WH lawn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess we just have to fix the system while it tears itself apart  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Golf plays "a very limited" role in Trump's daily tasks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fundamental Right: Senator Dianne Feinstein Recounts Emotional Abortion Story at Gorsuch Confirmation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
*Neil Gorsuch's confirmation to the Supreme Court would reboot a 25-year campaign to chip away at abortion rights.*


**Whilst I am the liberalist of liberals, this article is for all sides:**


"The landmark ruling that advocates on both sides of the abortion debate should focus on isnt Roe but its 1992 revision of sorts, *Planned Parenthood v. Casey."*


**And here are some select quotes I pulled highlighting that the FREE CHOICE of ABORTION is at risk if GORSUCH is confirmed:**


""The trouble was that Casey didnt define undue burden other than as a regulation with the purpose or effect of placing a substantial obstacle in the path of a woman seeking an abortion. It didnt specify what constituted a substantial obstacle."


"In June, with just eight justices, the Supreme Court finally clarified its undue burden rule when it decided *Whole Womans Health vs. Hellerstedt.* In a 5-3 vote, the court found that a Texas law requiring doctors at abortion clinics to have hospital-admitting privileges was not medically necessarymany riskier medical procedures, like colonoscopies, did not come with these requirementsand therefore posed undue burdens.

The decision was largely seen by legal scholars as a win for reproductive rights activistsone that placed limits on what could be considered an undue burden under *Casey.* But when future Supreme Court cases about abortion restrictions arise, as they inevitably will, a more conservative court may define undue burdens differently.""


[BUT...]


"A *Roe* reversal is possible. Former Chief Justice William Rehnquist made no secret of his desire to do away with it, and Scalia, in his Casey dissent, argued that it should be overturned, writing that since the Constitution doesnt mention abortion specifically it should be up to states to decide. 

Like Scalia, Gorsuch is whats known as a legal textualist, interpreting the law based on the words as written, not their perceived intent...If Trump appointed enough justices like himin theory, he might need just one more appointment and the right case came up, the court could conceivably follow Scalias original line of thinking and overturn *Roe."*


"In theory, *Whole Womans Health* has made it harder for states to pass abortion restrictions, but the political climatea president who vows to try to overturn *Roe,* a Congress poised to defund Planned Parenthoodmay embolden state lawmakers seeking to limit it. Were waiting to see what the legislatures do in the various states, says Crepps." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyond Roe v. Wade: Heres What Gorsuch Means for Abortion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There can be too much of anything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh good call. and I'm not sure how I heard about Lion. Oh ya, lots of commercials$$$. And how'd it get nominated? Oh ya, the Weinstein's vigor. I guess the implication is they are actually in the race with these actors and two movies well-positioned and one possible back up. And that point about the back up reflects timing doesn't matter but anyway  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be, Logan pretty fleshed out and closer to Oscar than deadpool...Best Picture nomination maybe or the Hugh Jackman Award </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This been posted already, I deleted it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sen. Adam Schiff: "I hope the reason he is going to Moscow is to hand back that Order of Friendship medal" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternative Russian Sanctions: We Go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "U.S. Secretary of State Rex Tillerson plans to skip an April 5-6 meeting of NATO foreign ministers for a U.S. visit by the Chinese president and will travel to Russia later in the month."


Sen. Adam Schiff: "I hope the reason he is going to Moscow is to hand back that Order of Friendship medal" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this Twitter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, I guess the implication is they haven't positioned themselves as well in the past few Award's seasons or with as big stars as they have for the next Oscars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen a fort and I don't know a man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pretty cool how Republicans only asked Comey questions about leaks, like Wikileaks and how Russia ruined Hillary?..wait, they only asked about leaks to honest journalists that are currently exposing Trump's bullshit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey now, he's cutting cost (and losing quality). But apparently Flynn didn't do anything while volunteering? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Flynn his National Security Advisor, who Trump handpicked against protest from everyone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump distancing himself from himself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just Manafort, also Flynn and Page </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spicer tries to distance Trump from top members of his campaign team </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long until he drops an f bomb in a Tweet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If the president believes it, it's not a conspiracy theory" 
-Trump Press Secretary Richard Nixon on Wiretapp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weinstein Co. Wants Back in the Oscar Game: Mary Magdalene, Current War get awards-friendly release dates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably smart, cough cough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woody Harrelson Has Given Up Pot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Comey didn't say there *was* no information, he said there *is* no information, so, so, will there be information? I smell vindication."
-Sean the Spiciest  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Trump is a "puppet" says S. Spice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprise, not exactly, I would think a lie that isn't so obviously a lie, as Trump defended Manafort and Flynn on why they were fired, not to mention, hired them. Not surprised though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe, pic of Spicepool today. Spicey should crowd surf next time they would take him more seriously  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone start the countdown to "Spicey you're fired" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You'd be surprised how many cease and desists the campaign sent to hanger ons" says Sean Spicer surprisingly because this is the first time he's said it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Campaign Manager Paul Manafort had "a limited role," Advisor Michael Flynn was "a volunteer," and Carter Page is a "hanger-on" says Sean Spicer on Trump's Russian Connections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10-minute video detailing how Russian Hackers released information targeting Democrats in the primaries and general election in 2016. Also, Glen Kaplin from the Clinton Campaign sits in at the end to explain how the Russia hacking played out from his intimate perspective. 


Here's a link to many great comments from [deleted same post](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5zyhf5/rachel_maddow_russisn_hackers_targeted_downballot/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm dumb, I had to repost for misspelling the title! Sorry everyone 

New post here:

https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5zz5nv/rachel_maddow_russian_hackers_targeted_downballot/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry EVERBODY who made great comments on my first attempt to post this, anybody whose mad at Rachel Maddow and taxes can heap their hate on me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'm dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rachel Maddow: Russian Hackers Targeted Down-Ballot Races </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh..it blended in...or it was a Russian Hack... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this issue on one subreddit where like ten different names say similar things that all build to one coherent corrupt idea, one that would seem nonsensical in reality, but within the context they have created, logical enough. Is it one person or ten unique individuals? Eventually, after you realize you are just trolling trolls, you start to see where sincerity lies and how to be real while being anonymous. Unfortunately, the subconscious effects of their propaganda probably corrupt my opinions nevertheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best Trump Tax Return Report I've seen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it is particularly noteworthy how they hit the Dem vs Dem  Florida primary, on that smaller scale it is easier to see the effect that  the negative attacks on both Democrats in the Primary led to the Republican win in the General. 


Then compare that to Bernie vs Hillary where it is harder to see whether the noise is coming from a liberal or a conservative or a fake Russian Hacker.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **WATCH THIS** 10-minute video detailing how Russian Hackers released information targeting Dems in the primaries and general election in 2016 (including defamation by earwax eating!) Also, Glen Kaplin from the Clinton Campaign sits in at the end to explain how the Russia hacking played out from his intimate perspective. 

**AND** Hype this: Rachel is having Glen Kaplin back tonight for more information on things maybe not yet explained!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10-minute video detailing how Russian Hackers released information targeting Democrats in the primaries and general election in 2016. Also, Glen Kaplin from the Clinton Campaign sits in at the end to explain how the Russia hacking played out from his intimate perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rachel Maddow: Russisn Hackers Targeted Down-Ballot Races </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Hackers Targeted Down-Ballot Democrats: Watch Rachel Maddow Report! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's SlashFilm's Title, and they add "Rumor:" when it is just hearsay, and it says "according to sources close to the production" and I believe that's true. They also "updated" this article with more sources which I do not see, but that does mean they believe the "sources close to production"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What follows in the Esquire article after the "being sore" quote is that Evans is having a tough time fitting in his own movie projects, as he was worried he would when he first signed the six-picture Marvel deal instead of a 9-picture deal. 
From [Esquire:](http://www.esquire.com/entertainment/a53656/chris-evans-fights-back/)

"Back in 2010, Marvel presented Evans with a nine-picture deal. He insisted he'd sign on for no more than six. Some family members thought he was nuts to dial back such a secure and lucrative gig. Evans saw it differently.



It takes five months to shoot a Marvel movie, and when you tack on the promotional obligations for each one, well, shit, man. Evans knew that for as long as he was bound to Captain America, he would have little time to take on other projects. He wanted to direct, he wanted to play other charactersroles that were more humanlike the lead in Gifted, which will hit theaters this month. The script had brought him to tears. Evans managed to squeeze the movie in between Captain America and Avengers films." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downy says he's out and then in and then out and then in. I think Evans has stuck to this similar out after avengers 3/4. Probably better to follow new characters than new actors playing same characters at first. Then multi-verse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article is guessing 2019, I wasn't reading it as too gossip-y clickbait, it seemed like they had a solid grasp of the situation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Benman *should* be able to write a tight slick Batman, but I'll take Matt Reeves vision  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya the spin of the article is reassuring, like of course Matt Reeves should be working from the ground up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Evans May Be Done Playing Captain America After The Next Two Avenger Movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Batman Screenplay Being Rewritten From Scratch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad! Don't be mad! 

p.s. FDJT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald likes to co-opt and make meaningless search words before or while they are used against him. [Energy Dept. rejects Trumps request to name climate-change workers, who remain worried](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/powerpost/wp/2016/12/13/energy-dept-rejects-trumps-request-to-name-climate-change-workers-who-remain-worried/?utm_term=.1f3ed59f69f4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TedEd Cartoon- What is McCarthyism? And how did it happen? Republican Joe McCarthy Used "Communism" Claims to Turn Americans Against Eachother </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm getting new chompers boff!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy the wrap up show  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop talking to yourself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robin is fine. Go listen to Hanzi show you crazy jerk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've said nothing that hasn't been said and we still don't know what the numbers actually are, obviously he is exaggerating to some degree, as the face of Sirius he is entitled to make the claim that those users all check out the Howard Stern Show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drop the conspiracy theory that you mention every day with different names. It's boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jerk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dropping Bombs: Trump's CIA Will Not Report Drone Strikes as The Military Did Under Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Whatever is good for bosss" Sean Spicer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBO says TrumpCare is Bad for People, Good for Dollars. Spicer says CBO is "Pretty Good At Dollars, Not As Good At People." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh, you should have heard him painting while you were in the bathroom." Robin on Fred's sound-drops during Howard's pee-break </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
