<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1861</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They explained to me that it's out of stock but were still selling to primenow customers a few hours ago. To make matters worse my separate order of Zelda and the screen protector got rescheduled to Wednesday and unforeseen respectively (so even if I get my delayed switch, I still can't get Zelda). What bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None in the prime now app. To make things even better, I had a separate Zelda purchase (+ screen protector) which got rescheduled to Wednesday (and pending for the protector). They've seriously screwed up considering that they knew how large scale this event would be + they've been selling stuff to their PrimeNow customers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living in central London, ordered in February from Amazon. Their delivery date was always 3 March, until 2:30 am this morning. I woke up at 6 to check my email and they sent me an email saying it had been "unexpectedly delayed" until Tuesday. Couldn't take time off work in time, and Toys-R-Us and Argos were completely wiped by lunchtime. If they had told me in advance I could've explored other options and that really pissed me off. They'll either deliver by Tuesday night (which doesn't work very well for me cause I go to Copenhagen on Wednesday and Thursday, and don't have a case to take the Switch with me) or will further delay it again (which wouldn't surprise me since I've zero trust in Amazon right now). Emailed Amazon, got a shitty 5 voucher. Never again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they ask to have a go on your switch, just remind them that they thought nintendo sucks, so you won't be sharing the fun haha. Some of my friends think Snipperclips is a childish and stupid game.. *sigh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
