<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5443</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are in great danger: Ex-banker details how mega-banks destroyed America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 01:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 02:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friends band [StayStillPills](https://www.facebook.com/Staystillpills?fref=ts), they play melodic indy pop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sue Townsend, creator of hapless and much-loved Adrian Mole, dies aged 68 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 02:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McCutcheon took us back in time, but it might just birth the next Occupy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 19:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free online course for treatment of depression from the University of Texas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 17:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The nightmare of living with OCD - The Guardian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 14:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tottenham Hotspur: New stadium ready for 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 23:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mourinho begins mind games as he rips up team sheet at press conference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 00:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 20:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have found some by practising [these](http://www.self-compassion.org/guided-self-compassion-meditations-mp3.html) guided meditations daily.  It gives me peace and fills my mind with a sense of love.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jos Mourinho writes off Chelsea's chances of the Premier League title </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 21:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 15:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brendan O'Carroll's made loads of Mrs Brown movie, for years, way before the tv show.  Gaybo appears in them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 19:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you tell us what brought you to this point in your life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rio Ferdinand afraid to leave house due to 'embarrassing' Manchester United </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 11:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 01:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're Man U, we don't chop and change our managers every season, we're not like that - every smug UTD fan about 6 months ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manchester United fans in bid to fly plane over Old Trafford with banner showing feelings towards Moyes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 01:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dwarf planet discovery hints at a hidden Super Earth in solar system </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 20:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uruguay plans to shift to electric buses, saving 5/6ths of operating costs and cutting emissions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 19:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uruguay plans to shift to electric buses, saving 5/6ths of operating costs and cutting emissions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 19:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Major inquiry into recording of phone calls at large number of garda stations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 16:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Qatar World Cup Is Already a Total Disaster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 18:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 01:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am the [Cosmos](http://youtu.be/kR594Kkxmzg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 20:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SuicideWatch is a good place to go on reddit if you are feeling suicidal and want to talk about it anonymously.  Getting yourself professional medical is the best start to getting well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 20:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I read his name as Lazarus, pretty appropriate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 23:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why one day too late? Did something happen recently to drive you over the edge?  Lucie, your life has potential for happiness and fulfillment you can guess at now.  When your depressed especially when your younger, you feel like it's going to be like this forever.  Give it time and you will see it change, the one constant of life is change.  You can get better, you can look back on this time and think thank God I didn't do it.  Give yourself a chance, there will be better days, I promise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 16 Famous Movie Mysteries (That Have Totally Been Explained) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 09:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-13 03:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No-one scores goals like Sturridge

he's had his readybrek

he's had his porridge

oh Daniel Sturridge.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 01:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> new nadir of artistic bankruptcy from the voice, must be seen for the lulz.  Where are you Johnny Rotten when we need you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 01:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they know who you are! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 15:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He deserved it, he was amazing in '02 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 00:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SuicideWatch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 15:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sad such a talented player's flame burnt out so early, as soon as he left Chelsea it was the end.  Remember him in his prime, he burned so bright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 18:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew he'd compare him to himself.  No-one has an ego like Zaltan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Davy Fitzgerald: Clare players were on "harder stuff than drink" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 01:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The whimsical world of Gerry Adams's Twitter account or could Adams be an actual human being? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 00:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eddie Hobbs: Wake up, Ireland: multinationals are set to give us very little for our own oil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 00:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 23:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is a fascinating and inspiring story of true courage and sacrifice by a person in power, which is so rare.  It is a mostly forgotten story but it is good enough to make a film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Forgotten History Of The Congressman Who Sacrificed His Life To Fight Homelessness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 23:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coldplay Released New Single 'Magic,' Heralding Their New Album 'Ghost Stories' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 15:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coldplay Released New Single 'Magic,' Heralding Their New Album 'Ghost Stories' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 15:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 02:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But it isn't all bad.

No, it's not. I think you are an enlightened human being.  If the compassion, understanding and love you've shown was commonplace, we'd be living in a much better would.  I think you father is proud of you from on high.  Love is all we have, the only thing that counts, God bless you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 02:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has a [blog](http://www.bbc.co.uk/blogs/adamcurtis/) on the bbc website full of fascinating articles which in themselves would make great documentaries.  I recommend you check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vulnerable man starved to death after benefits were cut in United Kingdom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 19:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vulnerable man starved to death after benefits were cut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 19:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RTE gets revenge for it's 85 grand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 17:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 21:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This depression will pass.  You will be a good mom to your baby, she needs you and will always need you.  Have you talked to a doctor about your depression, you need to get yourself some help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robin van Persie to consider his Manchester United future in summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 18:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 16:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...gay *not that there's anything wrong with that* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 18:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted this comment to the article. Here as well  

I don't thing a return to shame as a means of societal control is something Ireland should indulge in.  I remember that Ireland, it was horrible.  Not only were suicides, unmarried mothers, anyone different shamed, their whole families bore the shame as well.  You would only place a further burden on the survivors, who were seen as somehow having failed as parents/partners if their loved one committed suicide.  Also it would silence the suicidal and prevent them from reaching out and speaking to someone.  Real suicide prevention will come from people supporting and caring for each other, and those enduring the worst feeling it is acceptable for them to admit they need help.  Heaping shame on them will not help them, neither will it help the dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piers Morgan talkshow axed by CNN after collapse in ratings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 04:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 03:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how you feel, I've got a past that led to bad consequences for me and I find it hard to escape it's pull.  Try and view yourself with compassion, all your friends and everyone you know was young once too and they weren't perfect either, why should you be any different?  All we can do is learn from our past mistakes, and so not repeat them, there is redemption in that, you've learnt and grown as a person.  Some people never learn, put the responsibility on other and so never grow.  The secret truth of this life is no-one really knows what they're doing and is making it up as they go along.  Always try to learn the lesson and grow, that's redemption, just forgive yourself then and let it go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 02:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he was the one with the hair, wasn't he?  The young ones liked him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone see this? Last Year's winner of the voice performed Eiffel 65s Blue as a ballad on the Late Late Show, it was cringe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 16:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 01:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I became an alcoholic self medicating (at the time) undiagnosed ocd.  I used drink 6 cans most nights, I found it easier to cope with my thoughts half drunk.  But I found in the morning my ocd would be through the roof until I popped some tablets to calm them.  Eventually I quit drinking and got diagnosed and that's when I started to slowly get better.  I found regular drinking as a method took me daily a step deeper into the abyss.  Each day sober has been a step out.  If I could reccommed anything outside of proper medication it would be meditation. This [site](http://www.therealbuddha.com/meditation/about/) is an introduction to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At Stake In Ukraine's Drama is the Future of Putin, Russia and Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 16:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kurt Cobain Day in Aberdeen hometown is marked by the unveiling of bizzare crying statue of Cobain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 20:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kurt Cobain Day in Aberdeen hometown is marked by the unveiling of bizzare crying statue of Cobain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 20:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super cool video from Irish band Toy Soldier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 15:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super cool video from Irish band Toy Soldier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 15:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super cool video from Cork band Toy Soldier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 15:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin calls for Shatter to resign, says murders were not investigated properly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 04:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 03:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've learned to love with your whole heart and that is beautiful.  To be honest, I think I've forgotten how to do that in my nearly 40 years in this planet.  Don't panic about soulmates or the one.  I've thought everyone I was into was the one until the concept became ridiculous to me.  If it's meant to be, you'll both find a way.  If not, you've had an amazing experience and to quote a tv show 'just because the rose died on the vine, doesn't mean it lied to you while it was in bloom.'  A broken heart is the risk we take when we fall in love, you can survive it, almost everyone you know has been through it, it is hard, especially the first few times, but it's always hard.  Don't let the pain close your heart again, try to keep open, not just to lovers but to all people.  You sound like a great kid, and all this passion you have discovered can give meaning and depth to your life, without it knowledge and play are empty and shallow.  Loving and learning are what life is all about.  Good luck out there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Scotland: here are 76 things we'd like to apologise for, love England </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 19:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No one who lives under constant surveillance, who is subject to detention anywhere at any time, whose conversations, messages, meetings, proclivities and habits are recorded, stored and analyzed, can be described as free. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 02:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Change to IVF rules could make Britain the first country to allow therapy to change DNA in embryos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 20:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 17:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SuicideWatch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Change to IVF rules could make Britain the first country to allow therapy to change DNA in embryos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 17:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Change to IVF rules could make Britain the first country to allow therapy to change DNA in embryos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 17:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Change to IVF rules could make Britain the first country to allow therapy to change DNA in embryos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 17:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Change to IVF rules could make Britain the first country to allow therapy to change DNA in embryos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 17:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Change to IVF rules could make Britain the first country to allow therapy to change DNA in embryos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 17:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uninsurance Rate Falls To Five-Year Low As 3.3 Million Enroll In Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 02:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Oliver reams wealthy, entitled dweebs at tech awards show: F*ck you, straight away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 23:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists in California make landmark advance towards unlimited fusion energy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 23:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zuckerbergs donate $970m to non profit group </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 00:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 19:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just joking.  I remember seeing him on a chat show saying he liked Benedict, I thought what's happened this guy?  I've no problem with anyone finding God, but I don't understand why anyone has to take up the old school Catholic view of things, they are ways of being spiritual and be open and tolerant of the modern world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 16:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He seems deeply paranoid, gay people are out to destroy marriage and thus society. He has no idea why they would want to that, I guess he assumes that's just what they're like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 15:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> now I want to see it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former 2fm boss quits live on air, delivers withering parting shot to new regime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 15:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 01:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's human nature to blame ourselves for what people close to us do.  But clearly this guy had serious mental health issues that were not created by you, they made having a relationship with him impossible, there was nothing you could do.  What were your other options?  Stay with him and let him destroy your life as well as his?  He needed psychiatric help, you couldn't give him that, he chose the wrong way to deal with his issues, it was his decision, you just got caught in the middle of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 01:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> meditation.  Journey within, find some peace that no-one can touch.  The inner universe is infinite, you can explore for ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 22:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must have been the Gardai. Barely got a mention on RTE news, I think this is edivence Ireland is an almost totally corrupt society.  This could turn into Ireland's watergate, I think we should spread the story on social media to get it the attention it deserves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leonard Nimroy reveals he has lung disease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-08 00:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF: Mike Tyson   Pamela Anderson Join Russell Brand In Werner Herzog's 'Vernon God Little' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 17:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 23:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it has been reported there's a bad batch of heroin going around the East Coast that laced with a drug called fenatyl that has killed dozens of people and it may have been that that killed Hoffman.  So if he had got it from say, a pharmacist, through a harm reduction policy he would be alive now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pussy Riot members attack bandmates for appearing at Amnesty concert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 17:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russell Brand: Philip Seymour Hoffman is another victim of extremely stupid drug laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 17:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russell Brand: Philip Seymour Hoffman is another victim of extremely stupid drug laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 17:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russell Brand: Philip Seymour Hoffman is another victim of extremely stupid drug laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 17:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russell Brand: Philip Seymour Hoffman is another victim of extremely stupid drug laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 17:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women Tortured   Raped In Iraqi Prisons, HRW Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 14:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man gets bionic hand with sense of touch nine years after accident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 14:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man gets bionic hand with sense of touch nine years after accident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 14:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 03:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we can all agree Brendan O'Connor is not capable of hosting a serious discussion or debate.  The interview with pussy riot was cringe worthy, he treated them like they just more of the vacuous celebrities he normally interviews and the debate on homophobia descended into farce, a mixture of Kakfaesque and Orwellian twin nightmares of semantics where the definition of the word homophobia was debated, but the subject of homophobia was barely touched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 people canoeing down the South Mall in Cork </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 22:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 22:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how much it cost? Millions probably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 19:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we are seeing (watered down) remedies to the issues raised by the Occupy movement seep into the poltical mainstream in America. I think that's a good thing, it shows people protest can make a difference and change the conversation going on in the washington echo chamber and the broader public consciousness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brian McDermott refuses to walk away from Leeds despite takeover chaos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 17:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 16:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shit, a friend of mine posted it on facebook, I assumed it was recent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> E-cigarettes could become 'medicines' available on NHS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 02:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 03:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try viewing yourself with compassion.  Imagine you were your best friend and he confessed this thing and how he really regrets it and wouldn't do it again?  Would you forgive him?  Someone you loved very much and really a good person.  

I struggle with this a lot myself, I ruined myself in my youth and the consequences go on to this day.  I wish I could make it right but it's impossible, I can't change the past.  I hope one day, soon hopefully, I will find redemption.  I wish it for you too.  We got to learn to love and forgive ourselves, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 00:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God this is torture!  I forgot how awful this fucking day is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 20:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Brain lock](https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/44096.Brain_Lock) is a good book on dealing with OCD, it should help her.  Really she needs professional help.  A person with Ocd knows their fears are irrational, but the fear is so all consuming they cannot dismiss it. I reccommend reading up about it in order to understand the illness better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 16:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how the grass is going to get any sun.  They'll be replacing the pitch quite often. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 15:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no but the classical compositions, with Joyce he's so impeneterable and mythologized it's possible to believe almost anything, hence the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 14:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But were they delibrately put there or is it just a coincidence?  If you invent a code you can find 'prophesies' etc in the bible, but it's usually just a coincidence and all the rubbish it turns up is ignored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 02:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> still, I think I might go see it again to make up my mind about it.  A lot of people loved it, and I love the Coens' films.  I didn't really like the Big Lebowski first time I saw it and now it's one of my favourite films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 00:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you, although I might watch the film again because I haven't fully made up my mind on it.  I think there's some great ingredients, Carey Mulligan is fantastic, it's looks great and it works as a portrait of a time and a place and a particular scene that would go on to be very important to America.  But the total lack of narractive or a character arc make it feel like a load of interesting bits strung together but don't really amount to very much.  I talking to someone who said she read the Coens added the cat to provide a narrative to hang the scenes together, which is pretty sketchy.  I don't know, I really wanted to love this film, but now I feel pretty meh about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 03:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this, I've ordered some of those books.  I find weights and squats work for me in exercising anxiety out of my body.  I read a study that showed probiotics in the gut reduce anxiety so I started taking actimel and activia every day.  Also I cut down on coffee and crucially I meditate for an hour a day.  Meditation is fantastic for creating a well mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 01:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The power of now helped me a lot in letting go of fears of some future disaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 00:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> check out [swresources](http://www.reddit.com/r/SWResources) for suggestions on how to talk to suicidal people and how to assess risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 00:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, listen, a lot of people can tell you finding a good shrink is a turkey shoot.  They're good ones and ones that just dole out meds and show no interest in your self.  If you're unhappy with the help you are getting, maybe you could check out a replacement?  It can take a few goes to find one that works for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Guardian did a write up on Cork </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 00:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Guardian did a write up on Cork </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-30 00:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 23:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Man city would dominate this as well as the league.  Yaya Toure and the Beast would handle most teams on their own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 23:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think perhaps you could give your girlfriends the benefit of the doubt, they might suprise you by being supportive.  It's important you reach out for help, it's good you have made a start here.  This boy has treated you badly, I think you are entitled to an explanation from him, maybe he has a genuine reason for missing your date.  If not, it would give you an oppourtunity to express your hurt which can be cathartic.  I'm guessing from your post you are a young girl, from an old guy I can tell you we all get hurt in love, and we learn lessons about how we want to be treated and what acceptable or not by going through experiences like this.  You've been let down badly, but not every guy will be like this.  Also, please don't pin all your hopes of happiness on the right boy coming along, develop your own life and interests as much as you can.  It will satisfy you and nothing is more attractive than someone who is living a great life, you can have one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 22:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please try and get yourself some professional help - counselling, psychotherapy, support groups.  Explore every avenue to get better, meditation, exercise, expanding or renewing your social circle.  [Here's](http://blog.ted.com/2014/01/14/real-advice-for-those-whove-attempted-suicide/) an article I found on recovering from a suicide attempt.  You can get better, you need to believe you can get through this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 04:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *not another watergate* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 04:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's like someone reading a fiarytale to her kids at night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 04:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've a stone I need mossed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 04:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah SPORTS!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 04:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't drones strikes feed extremism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 03:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it impossible for him to mention the working class or poor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 03:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> then they won't or they would have already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 03:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish they'd have a guy in the audience, John Doe, is homeless and hasn't eaten in three days.  This your fault for cutting food stamps.  Shame on you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 03:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it connects with people, the average joe or joanna can relate, it breaks up and expemlifies to policy talk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 03:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can you make congress disappear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 03:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why so* serious?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 03:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cut tax loop holes, rebuild infastructure.  I think he has said that in every SOTU and nothing's happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News analyst tells Tea Party group he can lead a military coup against Obama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 23:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trent Reznor Tweets 'F--k You' After Grammys Performance Cut Short </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 23:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possible papal encyclical on ecology saying people must defend and respect nature </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 18:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paolo Di Canio brands Sunderland captain John O'Shea 'two-faced' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 00:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guinness planned to advertise in Nazi Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 03:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 20:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL George Orwell's real name was Blair.  I think he would have appreciated the irony, or been horrified, one or the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ireland to reopen Vatican embassy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 15:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A small dog plowing through snow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 17:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Nolan on internet movie theories, his indie roots, and editing 'Inception' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 01:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Nolan on internet movie theories, his indie roots, and editing 'Inception' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 01:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 01:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I don't get is what's one million to Fergie?  He's been paid about 5 million a year for the last x amount of years, why sell out former players, break the dressing room code he was so protective of as a manager and piss people off for money he has no need for?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alex Ferguson autobiography smashes sales records - netting 1million and beating Delia Smith </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 01:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 20:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who don't know, Roddy Doyle is Ireland's most famous and acclaimed novelist who wrote the book the film The Commitments was based on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Awesome! Roddy Doyle commits to co-write Roy Keane memoir </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 20:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Awesome! Roddy Doyle commits to co-write Roy Keane memoir </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 20:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 00:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey,  a black cloud has fallen on you, that's true, but it is not eternal.  For every winter there is a spring.  Your situation is not hopeless, you are suffering from depression, there is a lot of treatment available for that.  Please take advantage of that.  Explore every avenue.  You can and will get better if you hold on and fight to get better.  Many people here have been there and back, it doesn't go on forever, things will turn around if you keep going and keep trying.  Don't give up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DISSOLUTES - Storm Gonna Lock You Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 16:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DISSOLUTES - Storm Gonna Lock You Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 21:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 20:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atomized - the rage of a soulless man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 19:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Advent

We have tested and tasted too much, lover-

Through a chink too wide there comes in no wonder.

But here in the Advent-darkened room

Where the dry black bread and the sugarless tea

Of penance will charm back the luxury

Of a child's soul, we'll return to Doom

The knowledge we stole but could not use.



And the newness that was in every stale thing

When we looked at it as children: the spirit-shocking

Wonder in a black slanting Ulster hill

Or the prophetic astonishment in the tedious talking

Of an old fool will awake for us and bring

You and me to the yard gate to watch the whins

And the bog-holes, cart-tracks, old stables where Time begins.


O after Christmas we'll have no need to go searching

For the difference that sets an old phrase burning-

We'll hear it in the whispered argument of a churning

Or in the streets where the village boys are lurching.

And we'll hear it among decent men too

Who barrow dung in gardens under trees,

Wherever life pours ordinary plenty.

Won't we be rich, my love and I, and

God we shall not ask for reason's payment,

The why of heart-breaking strangeness in dreeping hedges

Nor analyse God's breath in common statement.

We have thrown into the dust-bin the clay-minted wages

Of pleasure, knowledge and the conscious hour-

And Christ comes with a January flower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 19:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Paddy Kavanagh](http://www.poemhunter.com/patrick-kavanagh/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 13:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good to see you, L, how you're all doing okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A useful guide to recovery from a suicide attempt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 03:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought some people here might find some of the ideas in [this](http://blog.ted.com/2014/01/14/real-advice-for-those-whove-attempted-suicide/) helpful, even if you haven't attempted, you can still begin your recovery today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DISSOLUTES -- Storm Gonna Lock You Up [hardrock] (2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 01:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DISSOLUTES - Storm Gonna Lock You Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 01:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 21:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3/4 years.  We had a filmmaking collective first and then the two lads went on to form their own production company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 20:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That ones pretty insensitive.  On the other hand, Karl Rove probably liked being called turd blossom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ten Things I Learned From Hitch-hiking Around Ireland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 15:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 01:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, it was done by [this](https://www.facebook.com/EpicProductionsIreland?ref=ts fref=ts) crowd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 22:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, the boys mostly do videos for wedding bands for a decent fee, this was more of a labour of love.  But I think the quality of the song and the performances inspired them to do their best work so far.  Art inspires art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Music video shot by a friends of mine on a 300 dollar budget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 22:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Music video shot by a friend of mine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 22:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 22:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the dude that shot and edited it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Music video edited by a friend of mine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 21:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 21:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh! and a lot of smoke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 21:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just a ware house a few lights and a strobe, but Justin is a wizzard on camera and on editing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 21:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](https://www.facebook.com/EpicProductionsIreland?fref=ts) is their facebook page.  The cinematographer was doing some things I don't understand with the strobe light and the camera shutter speed.  Most of the budget went into after effects, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissolutes - storm's gonna lock you up (Cork band, some friends of mine) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 20:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissolutes - storm's gonna lock you up (Cork band, some friends of mine) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 20:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissolutes - storm's gonna lock you up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 20:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissolutes - storm's gonna lock you up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 20:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mates made this on 300 dollar budget, so proud! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 20:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mates made this on 300 dollar budget, so proud! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 19:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Jersey Residents File Lawsuit Against Chris Christie, Others Over Bridge Controversy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 03:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York Governor Announces $1 Billion For Solar Energy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 01:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York Governor Announces $1 Billion For Solar Energy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 01:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 19:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, but I still think it's funny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Moyes nominated for Premier League manager of month, serious! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 18:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man United stars could face massive wage drop for European failure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 13:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dennis Rodman says he "loves Kim Jong-un" in bizarre CNN rant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 19:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dennis Rodman says he "loves Kim Jong-un" in bizarre CNN rant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 19:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 16:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The Man in the yellow doghnut* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 04:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Who watches the watchmen?**     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Karen Armstrong: Finding Compassion For Yourself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 23:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 17:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Dissolutes](https://soundcloud.com/dissolutes-cork) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 15:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also the earth is round.  There wouldn't be this kind of ridiculous story, if right wing think thanks didn't spread propaganda designed to keep the rich rich by keeping the poor poor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 06:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, so what? Who fucking cares?  Who counts these things?  What's the fucking point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 03:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last year I made a resolution to read for half an hour a day, five days a week.  Often I would get caught up and read for longer.  It helped me get through books I would have otherwise given up on.  I feel out of the habit unfortunately, but am trying to take it up again.  The problem is I spend so much time reading stuff on the internet I feel all read out most days.  But it's low value, internet fluff 90% of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 22:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm, dude, you might as well take this oppourtunity to promote the place by telling us it's name. Can't hurt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Open Letter to the Makers of The Wolf of Wall Street, and the Wolf Himself from the daughter of one of his accomplices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 23:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rio Ferdinand to leave Manchester United in summer as David Moyes calls time on his career </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 21:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The people who challenged my atheism most weren't priests, but homeless addicts and prostitutes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 18:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The people who challenged my atheism most weren't priests, but homeless addicts and prostitutes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 18:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britney Spears opens up on bipolar disorder: 'I turn into a different person' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 01:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britney Spears opens up on bipolar disorder: 'I turn into a different person' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 01:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 11:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, The crucifixtion scene weould be immense! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 19:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved midnight in Paris too, definitely a more enjoyable film, a fantasy romp really.  The political dimension and the monumental Blanchett performance make Blue Jasmine for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Rewatched Love Actually and Am Here to Ruin It for All of You </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 17:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 14:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Saurez in the team anything is possible.  I just fear the words 'release clause.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sickening! EU chief Barroso says Euro was a victim of Ireland not the other way around </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 04:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 04:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It probably made more sense that way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
