<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7982</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 22:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'm at work so I haven't had a chance to really study the statistics, but looking at it I know I can come up with something. There seem to be a lot of really interesting trends from year to year.

Based on what I've collected so far my plan is to maybe average out how many of each type of player is above the standard deviation. So for example, if my league averages 5 QBs above, 9 RBs above, and 12 WRs above, if 6 or 7 QBs are gone and 10 RBs are gone, I should probably go for a WR, or something like that. I just need to refine it before my draft.

It also shows me how valuable some players can be, and leads me to possibly reaching. As an example, When I averaged kicker points in my league for the top 12 (12 team league), Gostkowski is so far ahead of the other kickers it's kind of crazy. 

In the past two years, only two kickers each year were above one standard deviation. In each of those years, he was not only above the deviation, he was above two standard deviations. I really think the stats can be useful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using statistics from previous years, how can I best come up with a draft flow chart? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 16:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I currently have data for the last 5 years in my league, including pts scored for every player, how they rank up against other players in the same position, and what their overall rank is in the league. 

I've taken all of these stats and exported them into a spreadsheet. I've found some trends in this data already. One is that, because of our scoring rules, there is generally about 4 QBs that are a cut above every other player, and other trends like that.

So my actual question is a general one for anybody who has data like this. How can I use the data to create a loose draft guide? I was thinking about averaging each set for a position, then getting the standard deviation and seeing how many std devs away a certain group of players may be. Like the 4 QBs that are a cut above the rest are all more than 1 std dev away from average.

My goal is to create a sort of flow chart I could use during the draft to give me general guidelines. This would be really useful because I'm usually not at full state of mind during the draft, and having easy to use flowcharts would be great. If you have any ideas please let me know, and I'll try them out. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 16:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus why are you even in this subreddit if that's your opinion on NFL players? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 16:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wahsington is pretty dang libertarian on issues like those. Have you heard the saying (or similar): "I just want a gay married couple to be able to protect their weed crop with their guns."? That's Washington. Pretty relaxed, but sensible as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 15:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aah, a bit too early for me to realize that. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 15:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *literally* did, and I found a bunch of news stories, none of which mention that statistic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 15:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  50% of the time, when a homeowner is shot during a home invasion it's with their own weapon.

citation needed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, that link was just the best summary I could find for Firestorm itself. I'll be honest, my assumption was based on what I heard from my cousins that were firefighters near Chewelah. They mentioned how many dead trees there were in the forest, and how difficult it made it to fight.

However, after researching a bit more I think the dead trees may have been caused by the whole issue of letting wildfires burn vs. immediately putting them out.

Also, 20 acres on Tower Mountain sounds incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It fell a ton of trees, and dead trees dry out and can contribute to large fires. ~~As an example, in 1990 Washington was [hit by a windstorm](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pacific_Northwest_windstorm) in November, similar to last years. The following fall was [Firestorm](http://www.spokesman.com/stories/2011/oct/16/91-firestorm-seared-into-areas-memory/), which devastated the region.~~

My bad, see below. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably a good point. I would also be happy with him filming content with them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOPE nope nope nope. I had just reached the point of being really invested in the Seahawks at that age, and that game absolutely killed me. I suppress it at every chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you live downtown, not at all. Basically the biggest issue around Spokane right now is that we had a windstorm last year that knocked down a bunch of trees in the surrounding areas. Because of that, expect to see a good amount of fires in the coming years, but no danger to the city proper, except smoke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cigarettes thrown out of windows. It happens a lot where I live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extra Life Stretch Goal idea: Colin Mochrie On The Spot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just an idea that keeps coming up in my head. If you follow Colin on Twitter at all ([@colinmochrie](https://twitter.com/colinmochrie)), you know he loves charity events. I just think it would be cool for Roosterteeth to reach out to him, and see if he would do an episode of On The Spot if Roosterteeth reached enough money raised. It may be a long shot, but I think it could happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite thing about Tukuafu is that it's fun to say his name out loud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 16:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our first regular season overtime game. Boykin walks out on to the field, nervous. He know's he can do this. He's practiced 1,327 times at home, all for this one single moment. He can barely hear the referee. The coin flies into the air.

He freezes up. He can't say a word. Time is slowing, the coin barely moving, right at the top of it's arc. All of a sudden, he hears a quiet voice breaking through the crowd noise. ^^^"Use ^^^the ^^^force..."

He can barely make out what the voice said. He looks around, straining to hear it. ^"Use ^the ^force, ^Trevone!" Finally, he spots him. In the crowd, standing between thousands of people, is the GOAT. The greatest coin flipper of all time, Tavaris Jackson, is looking down on Boykin and helping him!

"Dammit Boykin, use the force!" T-Jack yells. Boykin focuses his attention back on the coin. It's at eye-level now. 

"Heads"

Time speeds up again. The coin hits the ground. Boykin strains to see the result. "Heads, Seahawks have won the toss." Boykin is ecstatic, he looks up to the crowd to give T-Jack a thumbs up. But T-Jack is gone, nowhere near where he was previously standing. Boykin searches, but just can't find him in the crowd. 

There's no more time to search, the referee is demanding his answer. "We'll receive." The Seahawks get the ball, and Russell Wilson marches it down the field to win the game. But Boykin wasn't paying attention. He was searching the crowd, for one more glimpse of the greatest. But he couldn't find him. He gave up, and went to celebrate with his team.

---

Later that night, Boykin received a text message. He checked the sender. "Unknown number". The message was short, and to the point. "In my experience, there's no such thing as luck. The force will be with you, always. Use it for good, and Go Seahawks." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 16:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Is this primarily because of the Lewis injury, or do you think he's a red-zone threat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 16:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm in a couple of very touchdown-heavy leagues. 6 pts up to 12pts, depending on length of TD, while they only get two pts every 50 yards for non QB. Can anybody name some sleepers for a league like this? Basically, I don't care if a player only gets 4 runs/passes and 10 yards, if two of those runs/passes are TDs I'm happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Casper the friendly ghost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 05:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They only read the first five letters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend joined an all girls league last year.  Some of the girls were great! Others... Not so much. Standard scoring, one girl took Gostkowski in the first round. Following that, she picked Steven Hauschka in the third. Amazingly, she ended up making the playoffs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Map of current local fires </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 19:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm in a couple of very touchdown-heavy leagues. 6 pts up to 12pts, depending on length of TD, while they only get two pts every 50 yards for non QB. Can anybody name some sleepers for a league like this? Basically, I don't care if a player only gets 4 runs and 10 yards, if two of those runs are TDs I'm happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More pictures near fire:

http://www.spokesman.com/stories/2016/aug/21/beacon-hill-fire-burning-structures-in-spokane/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Conair CV580 dropping retardant on a wildfire near Spokane, WA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you click on the PDF on this page it gives you where the fires are at. Red is currently active. Note that the yellow in the Spokane Valley is actually Kaiser and not a previous fire.

http://activefiremaps.fs.fed.us/activefiremaps.php?sensor=modis op=maps rCode=nwx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 22:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://friendlycomputersspokane.com/

Here you go. Seems to have pretty good reviews, and a new store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 15:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found out this week that RT owns http://fun.haus. This just makes me so happy and I don't know why.

Also, I need some help in my fantasy football league. I bought a funny website domain, and am trying to prank everybody in my league. My website is going to have links to different pages, every page for different team owners I go up against. So far my plan is to have a picture of them engaged in some sort of X-Rated activity with their first pick in the fantasy draft.

I would like to put more on each page however, but I'm drawing a blank on what to do. Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 22:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! This is my backup plan if the other one doesn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 22:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect. Exactly what I was looking for. Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to download videos from the RT website for later viewing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 21:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specifically referring to Twits and Crits. I enjoy listening to Heroes and Halfwits driving to and from work and would like to do the same with Twits and Crits. Viewing on the website is really inefficient for my data usage.

I tried an extension to download it, but the way it streams means it wouldn't work. Any ideas? I don't even need video, audio would be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Omaha dad finds pot brownies, eats 4 of them, says mean things to cat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 20:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh definitely stupid. Like I said, I just like a balance between the Mayor and City Council. Once Stuckart is mayor I think the city council will pass a bunch of items without any opposition except Fagan (*shudder*).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me, I see it as very likely. Despite Spokane being a Republican stronghold, our city government is very liberal. Condon, being a Republican, will have to go through a recall vote very soon is my prediction. They will get the signatures within a week or two.

After that, we will see Stuckart as our temporary mayor. I'm kind of against this overall. I think Condon, despite being dumb with situations like this, struck a good balance to the city council. They have good intentions, but really lack foresight sometimes, the latest being this fine on railroads they rescinded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, So I grabbed a domain for my league. It's youallsuckatfantasy.football (not up yet). I plan on having a page for every person in the league beside my self. On these pages, at a minimum, I will photoshop the respective person performing fellatio on their number one pick. I think this is a good start, but would like to do more. Do you guys have any ideas for what to put on every page? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 16:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point, but RT has a lot of "hidden" content. Basically they have so much content, spread out over multiple Youtube pages, that it can be difficult to find great old videos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Northern Quest's club? I've never been inside the club proper but it seems like a popular place on weekends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 18:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new here, so if I win I might feel bad. But then again, looking at the features I might buy it anyways if I don't win so might as well go for the win to save some money! Upvoted, and thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here on the Rocket League one. I'm an addict. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My thoughts exactly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 03:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 21:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang. Okay thanks for the info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 04:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next to check out. I grabbed it this morning and it was warm like they just stocked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 04:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still looking? Walmart north spokane has it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for virsha4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Removed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 01:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to see them mix in Gmod with GTA and Minecraft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 22:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go!

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-aLXCKNEG6k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Search Operator Help - Dates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to get help with Search operators in Google Search, specifically here is my issue:

I like to search the Google Newspaper Archive for different items. I'll use Reddit as an example:

https://www.google.com/search?q=reddit+site:news.google.com%2Fnewspapers

When searching a newspaper archive, dates are really important. If you look at the first response, you'll notice that it is from 1930, at least on my search. However if I use search tools and set a custom range of 1929-1931, nothing comes up.

What I did notice is that the URL of every story has the date embedded in it. The 1930 story, for example, includes " dat=19300426". 

I would like to be able to search for these dates in a URL while searching the archive. Is there a search operator where I have only 1920's stories come up, by somehow searching "dat=192"? Every time I try something, I think the "=" screws it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you guys do an equivalent of the BoC? If so, would you ever do a PoC? Those were my favorite things to look for in the old Woot forums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scorpion prank and his sixth sense (or however many Gavin thinks there is plus one) about something filming him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bet is that, at some point, Michael will yell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem! /r/gameofthrones and many similar subreddits use Spoiler tags a lot. /r/riddles uses it in the comments as well. 

My idea is that you could flair a post, like "First Spoiler" or something like that. The CSS could then hide the posts, and you have to mouseover to see what it actually says. Or at a minimum have it flaired First Spoiler so I know not to click it, and disallow any posts that have spoilers in the title.

Honestly it might not be worth it in this sub, but it should be reasonably simple to implement. There's quite a few tutorials on how to do it around the site.

https://www.reddit.com/r/csshelp/comments/x18bx/howto_fullyfunctional_spoiler_markup_for_mobile/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/beckymegan is smart and told us to post ideas here, so here are some of my Minecraft ideas:

 - Minecraft Prop Hunt on PC

 - Roller Coaster Competition
 
 As judged by Geoff

 - Fight or Flight

 A large maze-like path in the sky, no walls. The path is usually one block wide. Each person is given an iron sword. At certain points in the path it leads to a larger platform with skeletons caged in, and maybe a creeper to make it more difficult. You basically have to make it to the end of the course without being knocked off by arrows from the skeletons.

 - Minecraft Murder

 They create an area above or below ground, as the level they will play on. Matt runs the competition. There are six rooms at the side of level, with a chest in each. The chest should also be accessible from a corridor behind the rooms, so Matt can open each one.

 Each player goes into their room, and Matt starts stocking the chests. One player is given a diamond sword, another gets an enchanted bow and arrows, and the rest get nothing.

 Plays just like Murder in Gmod. If the person with the bow kills the wrong person, Matt throws a potion of slowness at them. They key is that each person must disable death messages except for Matt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you're thinking of Gus. Gavin is the one that makes a lot of terrible puns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 16:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Axialmatt pls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 16:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh year, forgot about the Triathlon! But thanks on the other one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 16:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay another one:

Minecraft Murder. They create an area above or below ground, as the level they will play on. Matt runs the competition. There are six rooms at the side of level, with a chest in each. The chest should also be accessible from a corridor behind the rooms, so Matt can open each one.

Each player goes into their room, and Matt starts stocking the chests. One player is given a diamond sword, another gets an enchanted bow and arrows, and the rest get nothing. 

Plays just like Murder in Gmod. If the person with the bow kills the wrong person, Matt throws a potion of slowness at them. They key is that each person must disable death messages except for Matt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 16:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt they will read any of these, but nonetheless here are my suggestions:

 - Minecraft Prop Hunt on PC

 - Minecraft Olympics
   
 You could do archery, swimming, running race, etc.

 - Roller Coaster Competition

 As judged by Geoff 

 - Fight or Flight

 A large maze-like path in the sky, no walls. The path is usually one block wide. Each person is given an iron sword. At certain points in the path it leads to a larger platform with skeletons caged in, and maybe a creeper to make it more difficult. You basically have to make it to the end of the course without being knocked off by arrows from the skeletons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can /r/roosterteeth incorporate Spoiler tags? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 16:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something I noticed lately is that people like to create threads about videos that haven't actually been released to the public on Youtube yet. I don't mind it if it stays in the comments on the RT First video post, but lately people have been posting separate threads with info on the videos. I had part of last week's Minecraft spoiled for me because of posts. :(

Obviously an easy solution is to just become a First member. But I already am, I just like watching Minecraft on Friday, not Thursday.

My proposal is to simply have spoiler tags for posts that come out between when a First video is released, and when it shows up on Youtube. I'm even willing to write the CSS to make it work if it comes to it, I just think it would help the sub to have a way to hide posts like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 15:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hypothetical. Tomorrow morning, you wake up and go into your living room. There, on your couch, you find a naked Achievement Hunter, eating a bowl of your cereal and playing your video games. My questions are: Which Achievement Hunter* is it? And how do you respond?

^*Duetothenatureofthesituation(nakedonfurniture),Gusisalsoanacceptable ^answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 seconds in... Blue Scored! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 22:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 19:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEY MAN, I HAVE SUBREDDIT STYLE TURNED OFF, SO IF YOU COULD RETYPE YOUR WHOLE COMMENT IN CAPS THAT WOULD BE GREAT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could sit down and have dinner with any historical person, with the condition you must have sex with them later that night, who would you pick? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 18:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for MrNipris </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 00:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 18:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe they are hunt-able, but here is a popular one: [Bogg's Pit](https://www.google.com/maps/place/Boggs+Pit/@48.0534666,-117.4445435,16z/data=!4m5!3m4!1s0x0:0x9f540f68eda4df02!8m2!3d48.0554639!4d-117.4478441) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 18:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last I heard was that this place was closed... Too many complaints from neighbors. Have you gone recently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 16:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. 

Or alternatively they raised us to have little common sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 15:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I did fit in as well for a while... But then my loans entered their repayment period. :( But if you think about the crowd that may have grew up with RvB, it makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 15:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're banking on a Saudi prince watching the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 15:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard a discussion about this subject. Basically, think about the type of fans that Rooster Teeth (And associated streamers) probably have. These kids spent their whole time in high school and college watching RT, and now some of them have graduated. 

They are probably in a field like Engineering or Computer Science, and at this point make way more than they need to spend on necessities. So they end up having a lot of disposable income, and RT is somewhere they can spend it with little guilt. Of course this isn't unique to RT, but they fit into the model. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Data supports this answer as well. [We are ranked 15th in the nation in third party voting](https://www.google.com/url?sa=t rct=j q= esrc=s source=web cd=3 ved=0ahUKEwjrrbCs3rLOAhUD6GMKHe4BC6UQFggsMAI url=https%3A%2F%2Falt.coxnewsweb.com%2Fstatesman%2Fmetro%2F081205libs.pdf usg=AFQjCNFxt3jgbagmGsDwDs2OLFFWgvvHpQ sig2=wKTrZZdLAGM0bytTDV8Zxw cad=rja). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 08:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/17rlNKV.png

Or this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can ads on mobile websites cause my phone to vibrate? Why is this not locked in the operating system? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 05:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a hobby you wish you were in to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 07:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I visited Mt. St. Helens, but it was too cloudy to see the mountain. My pizza attempted to cheer me up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 21:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 05:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back when I was younger, my dad would hide all of the kids Easter baskets early in the morning. One Easter, he hid my sister's basket in the oven. Unfortunately the first thing my mom did that morning was turn on the oven to make a casserole. Very sad for my sister, but I liked the melting green fake grass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My car decided it wanted to try tunneling under the map </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 21:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 18:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so in interest of actually getting this free-talk thing some activity, what have you guys been listening to lately? I've been listening to a lot of Porter Robinson, Jai Wolf, stuff like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 18:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the idea, but they would run into a heap of legal problems. They would never do it because of that. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 16:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was driving to work this morning and had to stop for a chicken crossing the road.

It wasn't as funny as I had hoped.

---

Also, I always smile when I come into work, because there is a cute little birds nest at eye level in a tree near our door. Except then I realize that whenever I walk by the nest the mom takes off and leaves her babies for me. What an awful parent.

---

If different Youtube groups held a draft, in which personalities from one group could become free agents and enter into the draft, who would you hope AH, FH, and the others would pick up?

I mean, Gavin would be a goner. Once he became a free agent there is no way RT could compete with PewDiePie money. I'm sure his entire job would consist of recording facial expressions in Slow-Mo. But then again the merchandising for that deal would be excellent. Team Weird Accent or something. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [RF] You are an HR manager. Write the report on why the companies most prolific and infamous employee was fired. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 23:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 21:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an inside joke. It all started back in 1983, when Reading Rainbow came onto the air for the first time. As you probably know, Mica's dad LeVar was the host of Reading Rainbow throughout it's run. One aspect of the show that was a constant was the ending.

You may remember what LeVar said at the end: "I'll see you next time." With this phrase, he always looked at the same camera, specifically **Camera 3**. 

When LeVar moved to do Star Trek, he found Camera 3 for the main Enterprise Bridge set. He placed a small rainbow on top of the camera, as a small joke and to honor his other show.

I bet even to this day, Mica still puts a little rainbow on her cameras, and calls them Camera 3, just to honor her dad.

---

Source: Sorry, I made this up. Naming it Camera 3 was probably a mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 21:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a bit late, but I want to go with a summer theme:

---

**Sync About It**

 - How to swim

 - How to build a sand castle

 - How to put up a tent

---

**ABCs**

Person A is a fast food cashier, trying his hardest to take B's order. Person B is a rabid Pokemon Go player, convinced the deep fryer is hiding a Mew.

Or

'A' is an actor that can't leave his role as a Game of Thrones character. 'B' is a DMV agent, trying to give A a driving test.

---

**Quick Thinking**

Pokemon inspired by Xbox-Live

Things not to bring to the beach

Names you shouldn't call your boss.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 21:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredible! I love it. As long as it's not a pearl necklace we're fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 21:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, maybe? It depends. Do you have a terminal illness? Or maybe a large shipment of liquor? That's about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 19:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sharing two that I already use that are really useful:

[Everything Search](https://www.voidtools.com/). Allows instant searching of every file and folder by name

[Clover](http://ejie.me/) Brings Chrome-like tabs to Windows folders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Windows program should I have to make my day-to-day office work go better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 19:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 18:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a spoiler for the new one? :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 23:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sparks and Recreation, a new sitcom that explores a group of friends who decide to open a Recreational Pot Shop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 23:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  halo jump

Okay I liked your edits but just got to point out that it would be a LALO jump not HALO. HALO stands for High Altitude Low Opening. I suppose you could jump from high altitude and open at the height of the Space Needle. But at that point I think even the fish at Pike Place will have it better than you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 22:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stuckart from the city council calling for immediate resignations. However we already know he wants Condon gone anyways, since he wants the Mayor spot. I could potentially see another recall vote, followed by the council voting to put Stuckart as mayor. They can get the signatures no problem at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 20:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know how when the first terrorist attack happened in France, and it's all everybody could talk about for weeks? But now attacks are becoming more common there, and they are becoming top story of the day, not week? That's kind of what Trump did with his campaign.

He said so much crazy shit in the beginning that saying crazy shit now doesn't do anything to him in the polls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 16:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My completely unsubstantiated theory is that there is some crazy deals going on behind closed doors (obviously). Specifically, I think Wikileaks and Trump have a deal where Trump has agreed to pardon Snowden if he becomes President, in return for info on Hillary and the DNC.

Wikileaks and Russia's deal has to be in some part due to Snowden's asylum. I have a strong feeling e told them quite a bit about American Intelligence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 22:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I think I found the issue. When you call javascript on a page like this, every link should be https. It looks like they forgot one of these, specifically:

div id="marketing-banner"/div
script type="text/babel" src="http://roosterteeth.com/scripts/react/components/banner.js"/script
                div class="hero-copy"
        h1Sign up for DOUBLE GOLD Membership/h1
    /div

So I believe if they change this they would be okay and not pop up the warning anymore.

However on the security end the TLS connection is good, so I think you would be fine, especially since Google Chrome blocks the js by default. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 17:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because every channel is different, based on their viewers and how tech-savvy they are. If there is a channel that is primarily aimed at older folks, they will probably have less views, but more money per view as older people don't use ad-blocker as much. On the other-hand, a channel like The Know would get more views and less money per view due to the users being more likely to block ads.

There's also geographical issues. A viewer in Britain might get served a different ad than a viewer in the US. Assuming both click on the ad, the British click might be worth more than the US click.

I think $2/1000 views is a good ballpark for channels like AH and similar. If you look at the the AH channel, you can average it out to about a video a day at 150 thousand views. For comparison, PewDiePie does a video a day at about 3 to 4 million views.

The Lets Play channel may be a bit different, as it has longer videos on average. So they may get quite a bit more. However all of this isn't enough to support a company like RT. They, like almost every other big Youtuber, sell merchandise in order to make a good chunk of money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 20:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The questions are evolving! I got one similar a couple of weeks ago asking if I would refer if I alone got a monetary credit. It didn't mention the other person receiving a credit or a dollar amount. I guess enough people hit yes that they modified it to be more specific.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 16:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pssst... Check out the Discord on the sidebar! It's similar to what you are looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 15:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay new thread. I posted this in the last one, but I'll post here too:

Top Gear in GTAV. I would like to see them each pick a different car and test them in tasks against each other.
They could also do Star in a Reasonably Priced Car. I would love to see this one as a weekly standalone, quick 10 minute series. Geoff brings in a RT personality each week, interviews them, and asks them about driving and their personal cars.

To end the episode, they would have the person drive a crappy car in GTA around a track. They could hide the time somehow, then have an actual leader-board in the office. I would love to see Joel on there talking about his car, or really anybody in the office to see who gets the best time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, right?? Although it's not known when it will open yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A list of some of the new restaurants coming to, or just opened, in Spokane. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 21:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of new restaurants opening up in Spokane, so I wanted to create a list. Let me know if I missed any!

Huge thanks to inlandnwbusiness.com, it's a great site and found most of these, so check them out!

**North:**

Sweeto Burrito - Division and Nora

Sweeto Burrito - 9602 N Newport Highway

NUDO Ramen - 9602 N Newport Highway

Mod Pizza - 9405 N Newport Highway

Retro Donuts - Location Unknown

Slice - Pints and Pizza - 829 E Boone

Allie's Vegan Pizzeria   Caf - Working towards reopening after fire - 4803 N Nevada St

Kabob House - Ruby and Montgomery

Panera Bread - Looks to potentially be opening one near Lowe's on Division

Denny's - 3525 N Division St

Bruncheonette - 1011 W Broadway

King of Ramen - Division and Mission


**South:**

Tomato Street - Riverpark Square First Floor

Tortilla Union - Riverpark Square

Rock City Grill - Moving to near 57th and Regal


**Other:**

Popeye's Chicken - Post Falls

Roger's Burgers - Post Falls at Spokane and 4th St.

Grabbagreen - CDA 415 W. Neider Ave

Grabbagreen - Coming soon to Spokane


I'm sure I missed a few so let me know if you know of any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] The CIA and FBI have been searching for a dangerous fugitive for years. Entire teams dedicated to one mission: Where is Waldo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you could pick one inanimate object in the Rooster Teeth offices to suddenly gain the ability to talk and participate in RT productions, which would it be?

I'm thinking Gavin's Desk. I feel like it would be very mad at Gavin for all the shit it went through, and accordingly would get in a lot of arguments with him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 20:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish they would make a new thread, but here is my suggestion:

Top Gear in GTAV. I would like to see them each pick a different car and test them in tasks against each other. 

They could also do Star in a Reasonably Priced Car. I would love to see this one as a weekly standalone, quick 10 minute series. Geoff brings in a RT personality each week, interviews them, and asks them about driving and their personal cars.

To end the episode, they would have the person drive a crappy car in GTA around a track. They could hide the time somehow, then have an actual leader-board in the office. I would love to see Joel on there talking about his car, or really anybody in the office to see who gets the best time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's for the full service, if you're using a data-only SIM card this is what they say it works with:

Devices verified as compatible.
Here's a list of devices that weve verified will work with Project Fi:

Nexus 7 - K009 (2013 US LTE)

Nexus 9 - 0P82300 (2014 US LTE)

iPad Air 2 - Model A1567 (2014)

iPad Mini 4 - Model A1550 (2015)

iPad Pro - Model A1652 (2015)

Galaxy Tab S - Model SM-T807V (2015)

Nexus 5X (North American version)

Nexus 6 (North American version)

Nexus 6P (North American version)

Other devices

Data-only SIMs may work with devices that arent on our list. Devices need to be unlocked and work with T-Mobile (GSM radio). You can order a data-only SIM and test it out. However, we may not be able to help activate or troubleshoot these other devices.

Note on phones: If you set up a data-only SIM with a phone, you will have access to data, but you wont be able to make calls and texts across the cellular network.

So sorta what you were looking for. Side note, Google Fi is awesome and I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best video game for time compared to money spent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As always, nice job. I enjoy reading these. Quick addendum to the SIM card question: Google Project Fi also offers a Data only SIM card, and they seem to actually support the idea. [See here](https://support.google.com/fi/answer/6330195?hl=en) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 23:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go into Day 5 expecting it to be Game of Thrones, you'll be disappointed. If you go into the show realizing it's a Rooster Teeth production, you'll be blown away.

On the other point, hearing about it non-stop, I'm assuming there is a big reason for that. While Rooster Teeth has been doing great as an internet production company, it is obvious they want now bridge the gap between where they currently are and being a traditional production company. 

This means that they are marketing these TV Shows and documentaries more than other productions. They are no longer just advertising to fans, they are advertising to non-fans and distributors as well.

The result of this is a minor annoyance to huge fans, but an expanded audience, which is great for the company. I'm sure they would never want to annoy fans like yourself, but it's a bit of a necessary evil to keep growing and achieving their goals.

Also, to be honest, Day 5 is good enough they deserve to talk about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 22:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure this means that executions will be allowed... For their safety of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 17:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yes I did. It took me a bit to think of good rhymes, but you nailed the song! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 17:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should buy some eye drops. But thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 16:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New shows, New streams, On the Spot had lots of teams,

Spools out, Gus's dog, Gavin does slow-mo.

Meg Left, Rubin is gone, Geoff orphaned a small fawn,

Camp-Camp, Day-5, All your favorite shows

---

AH, Funhaus, Screwattack started out,

Kinda Funny, Creatures, Cow Chop joined too

Lets Play Live, was a hit, Tweets by RyanTheTwit

Amazing Race, Burnie lost, RTX was a zoo

---

This is your RT recap,

It was always crazy

And Gus is still Lazy,

This is your RT recap,

MDB is killing it

Lots of talking about shit




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 21:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked their food truck. Great curry fries. I'm excited to try this place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 21:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alot. 

Source: Game of Thrones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 19:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys I think we really need to consider that yesterday was just an elaborate BDSM foreplay session. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 19:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you thought of allowing karma on a Sub by sub basis? Like mods could enable it? So /r/askreddit could not allow karma on self posts but /r/askhistorians could? Or something like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael and Bruce have been texting each other. It's kinky. And sexy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 19:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 19:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point. I feel like some of the more conservative towns would love to stick it to the West side and enforce their own rules, so it's an interesting precedence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 18:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it might too, but apparently not.

http://blog.seattlepi.com/marijuana/2014/01/16/washington-ag-can-cities-and-counties-ban-marijuana-businesses/#18413103=0 18853101=0

Specifically:

Under Washington law, there is a strong presumption against finding that state law preempts local ordinances. Although Initiative 502 establishes a licensing and regulatory system for marijuana producers, processors, and retailers in Washington State, it includes no clear indication that it was intended to preempt local authority to regulate such businesses. We therefore conclude that I-502 left in place the normal powers of local governments to regulate within their jurisdictions, he said in a news release. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. So despite the state legality, the pot shops still cover themselves? That's actually pretty smart. I think it would be funny to see this go to council, just to see them argue over allowing something to be sold that has already been sold for the last two years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does city code still officially ban the sale of marijuana related items? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 16:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For clarification, I am not against pot or anything. Honestly just curious.

I was just reading some of the city codes today, and I noticed a section that was not yet repealed. Here is the link to the code in question: https://my.spokanecity.org/smc/?Chapter=10.15A

And here is some of the text that confuses me:

"Drug paraphernalia" means, but is not limited to:

any item, whether useful for non drug related purposes or not, which is displayed, grouped with other items, advertised, or promoted in a manner to reasonably suggest its usefulness in the growing, harvesting, processing, manufacturing, preserving, inhaling, injecting or ingesting of marijuana, hashish, hashish oil, cocaine, methamphetamine or any controlled substance;

And:

any objects used, intended for use or primarily designed for use in ingesting, inhaling or otherwise introducing marijuana, hashish, hashish oil, cocaine, methamphetamine or any controlled substance into the human body, such as:

So then in another section there is this:


It is unlawful for any person to sell, give or permit to be sold or given, any drug paraphernalia in any form.

So my questions is how are these laws still in effect if it is otherwise legal to sell all of this in Spokane?

Also, fun fact: [It is illegal in Spokane to: ask for or receive compensation, gratuity or reward for practicing fortunetelling, palmistry or clairvoyance;](https://my.spokanecity.org/smc/?Section=10.19.020)

Edit: It does not that there is an exception for people with prescriptions, but no recreational exception that I can see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great idea, but who will the therapist be? Gus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If somebody gave you a falcon as a pet, what would you name it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 23:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your honesty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 19:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friendship Park in north Spokane has Scyther too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 05:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 03:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you Pm me I will give you the name and number of the store to see if they will ship one to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 03:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll let you know when I find the value. The store I bought it from had a few more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Civil Defense CDV-720 Model 3 radiation detector - MFG Serial No 1. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 01:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Album here](http://imgur.com/a/qY46B)

Just picked this up at the store. Have not tested to see if it working, want to get an idea of value before I do anything to it. I figure the MFG Serial No 1 might make it worth a bit more. Then again it looks like the other mfgs sell for more, so if it isn't worth much I'll just mess around with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 20:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Seriously. What the fuck](https://i.sli.mg/0JqUMh.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 18:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may want to contact local Veterinary programs and see if they can help as well. Lots of students that may need experience! WSU has a good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 16:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Scythers at some parks up north too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 06:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [For anybody curious on the one](https://www.google.com/search?q=burnie+burns+gold+shorts) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 20:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have every right to be pissed. I'm sorry you had to go through that. They are truly awful people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 20:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ever get the chance, look up squatters rights in Washington. Fair warning, it's a bit ridiculous. Here's a local story on a similar problem:

http://www.kxly.com/news/spokane-news/northwest-spokane-residents-baffeled-by-squatters/39654356 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is on the front page of the Spokesman Review, and this game has been talked about on almost every news and radio station. I'm sure it qualifies as a current event.

Besides, he represents us better than the cheese eating lady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CW] Write a short story that reads one way when grammatically correct, but reads completely different when commas are removed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 15:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the same dude that's in the Spokesman this morning!

http://www.spokesman.com/stories/2016/jul/11/pokemon-go-hordes-flock-to-riverfront-park-in-spok/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 21:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ehh... The demographics they really look for are older women, from what I've heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 18:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really, every person I know is aware that they have essentially no chance of winning, but it's fun to buy anyways. As long as you're not spending more then is reasonable on the tickets you're fine. It's fun to dream for a couple of days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
