<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2561</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There have been no cuts yet. His proposed budget, which is not by any means official or approved by Congress, seeks to cut money in indirect funds from the agency.

Here's the article I read about it: http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2017/03/trump-s-nih-budget-may-include-reducing-overhead-payments-universities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The media attention around yesterday's bill suggested that it would fund Mars exploration. If you look at yesterday's top post on this subreddit, it suggested the same. This is trying to correct that record, not to suggest that NASA had already planned a mission that is getting tabled.

edit: here's the relevant quote from this article:
 Much of the general news coverage after President Trump signed the NASA authorization bill on Tuesday focused on the legislation's call for sending humans to Mars. (For example, the AP headlined its story "Trump signs bill authorizing NASA funding, Mars exploration"). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a lot of media stating that yesterday's NASA Transition Authorization Act would fund Mars exploration (including the top post on this subreddit). Musk's statements are trying to correct the record. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your guess is as good as mine :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, like the proposed $5.8 billion cut to NIH funding... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is definitely a possibility, but not a guarantee. Elon is saying is that the Trump administration isn't interested in pushing for Mars funding, and so the claims that the budget would fund Mars exploration are misleading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least it looks like he was sandboxed, so the bug shouldn't affect other tabbies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:

 Much of the general news coverage after President Trump signed the NASA authorization bill on Tuesday focused on the legislation's call for sending humans to Mars.[...] However, this perception is probably wrong, as Musk points out. There is lukewarm interest in Congress about aggressively funding humans to Marswhich would cost hundreds of billions of dollars to do using traditional aerospace firmsand according to sources Ars has spoken to, holds almost no interest within the Trump administration itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boil em, mash em, put em in a stew </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be denied, it is 2/90 for all credit cards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monday night's amendment to GOP health care bill will not improve coverage losses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk: New NASA bill contains no real new funding for Mars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine was a physical mailer. You can share the code which someone can then bring in-branch, though sometimes bankers want an actual mailer / picture of one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which card is this for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay. Then yes, it's worth waiting for a better offer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you already had a platinum before? If so, this might be a way to get a second bonus on the product </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a chase $300/$200 mailer. DM me if you want it. Expires 4/22. 

Edit: and it's gone in a record (for me) 2 minutes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I've read (and admittedly not actually attempted to try with the API), it seems to be the former </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For your first MR cards, it will take 2 statements for the points to post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah gotcha, that's a lot. If there's a particular airline you fly frequently, you could look into some of the co-branded cards. For example, the Delta Plat gives you an effective 1.4 miles / $ when you take into consideration its high spend bonus; plus, it would help you achieve elite status.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though this would be good for a no-AF card, especially for the millennial / student crowd who don't have enough credit history / want to spend the AF on the CSR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is currently an Amex offer for $100 off $200 at upwork, if any of your cards have it. It's also available via Amex Twitter Sync </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For large purchases, I recommend using a card that you plan on keeping long-term and with good warranty coverage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here ya go: http://www.cashbackmonitor.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for sharing this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's your personal link to the survey, which says that you've already taken it.

Here's the general link: https://uber.co1.qualtrics.com/jfe6/form/SV_0d46vJWZE9cKCWN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump was speaking Americanese, not lying in wiretap tweets, commentator says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty excited about a couple of the new features, especially the Autofill API:

Autofill APIs: Android users already depend on a range of password managers to autofill login details and repetitive information, which makes setting up new apps or placing transactions easier. Now we are making this work more easily across the ecosystem by adding platform support for autofill. Users can select an autofill app, similar to the way they select a keyboard app. The autofill app stores and secures user data, such as addresses, user names, and even passwords. For apps that want to handle autofill, we're adding new APIs to implement an Autofill service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is two approvals. See more info the FAQ's on the sidebar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't tried it personally, but it should work. Plastiq has several Vanguard address (i.e. Property Investments) in their database already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This project will probably never become much of anything

Well not with that attitude!

Good luck on your project! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google releases Android O to developers, promising better battery life and notifications </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be around june 10th (probably a couple days later since they give a few days leeway for shipping the card) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, he was given a pay cut of 26% last year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it applies to both personal and business credit cards :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [phrasing](https://img.memesuper.com/84a59a6764df9fdae2d340df679e2915_-spanish-blog-and-memes-archer-memes-phrasing_500-375.jpeg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be instantaneous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on how good the universe's programmer was. If she/he/it put in enough catch statements, you may just get an out-of-bounds error </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amid boycott, Google changes ad policy to give advertisers more control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will get it a couple days after your statement closes, not on the bill due date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amex HQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.rocketmiles.com/refer/SAUMYASG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a similar experience when returning an item I purchased via the Chase UR shopping portal. However, a few weeks later, they deducted the bonus UR's. I understand it's not the same bank or the same vendor, but just a DP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple introduces iPhone 7 and iPhone 7 Plus (PRODUCT)RED Special Edition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, Samsung also has fire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://try.plastiq.com/578069 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it's the Explorer or Club cards. And yes, you do need to pay with the card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a direct link to the spreadsheet tabulated by the Center for American Progress

https://cdn.americanprogress.org/content/uploads/2017/03/17131444/Table-of-CBO-coverage-loss-by-congressional-district.xlsx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> See how many people in your district would lose health insurance coverage with the ACA Repeal Bill (based on calculations from the CBO report). Call your Rep with specific numbers and ask them to vote no! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, you still get the free checked bag if you're the MPE holder.

 You're not allowed a full-sized carry-on bag unless you're a MileagePlus Premier member or companion traveling on the same reservation, the primary cardmember of a qualifying MileagePlus credit card or a Star Alliance Gold member.

Source: https://www.united.com/web/en-US/content/travel/inflight/basic-economy.aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Republicans unveil changes to their health care bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For anyone who hasn't used this yet, if you're buying any of their non-subscription products be sure to subtotal at least $10 so you get free shipping (as opposed to triggering the offer with a $6 shaving cream + $4 shipping) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, should go through with no problems in most circumstances, except as described below.

The one caveat: if you're paying with a Visa card, there is a chance Plastiq will attempt to use it as a cash advance instead of a credit charge. This happens in some cases, and only if Plastiq has no prior relationship with your apartment company. They will warn you if this will happen, and you can cancel the payment. My recommendation is to call up your credit card provider and lower your cash advance limit to the minimum allowed, just in case. If you're not using a Visa, then no worries!

Also, if this is your first time using Plastiq, please [use a referral](https://rankt.com/r/churning/referrals/plastiq/) to get 400 fee-free dollars (and support a lucky user in this community!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in the shopping portal for the Ink cards, not the Sapphire cards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should be okay! When you go to schedule, there is an option for Plastiq to process it immediately and deliver it by next week.

Plastiq will let you know their estimated arrival date of the check, so I'd double check with what they say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I unfortunately don't have any data to suggest either way. I suspect it would depend on the customer service rep you spoke to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Likely not. It's pretty clearly a typo and they could argue that.

That being said, I would encourage a subscription to the NYT (or any other news source), since you get to support them and that's not a bad return for a couple months' subscription. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat! I always find these photos of normal day-to-day activities fascinating. It really does add personal depth to the history that you read about in high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on your info (if you've opened no non-Chase cards in the past 2 years), you're at 2/24. I think the Amazon card is good if you have that high level of spend. However, it is not restricted under the 5/24 rule. If you are interested in churning other Chase cards, do those to get to 5/24 first and then get the Amazon. 

On the other hand, I got the Amazon card when I was 1/24 because I felt it was worth it for me at the time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are going for elite status on Delta, purchasing via UR points on the Chase portal will give you MQM's because it's considered a cash purchase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've optimized the reproduction lines at the factory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The instructions are wrong. One pi is equal to 180 degrees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard one guy survived by eating only potatoes on Mars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There have been a few bugs on the Amex website. For example, I am seeing one to upgrade by Delta Plat to a Delta Reserve for an annual fee of $175, whereas the fee for the latter is actually $450. Read the offer terms carefully (the Reserve says $450 in there), since those are what you agree too not what's on the site :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Health </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blueberry extract and amino acid supplements may prevent postpartum depression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For hotels and airfare, the Sapphire Reserve gives back 3% if you were to redeem points for a statement credit. I know there are several other cards which have gas as a rotating bonus category, or you could go for the Blue Cash Preferred or Everyday Preferred which gives unlimited 3% on gas all year round. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a referral! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White dwarf flies around a black hole every 28 minutes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tillerson signaled U.S. policy of patience on North Korea is over: White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had it on in the background at work for almost 5 hours now, it's been slow moving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can look at your Skymiles activity on Delta's website, and count the total your received as a referral (has to be done manually unfortunately by adding up the line items).

Or call Amex! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rankt.com has cataloged the latest referral threads from this subreddit. You can go to the link below, select the card you're interested in, and there will be a link to the appropriate referral thread in this subreddit.

https://rankt.com/r/churning/referrals/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would recommend not closing immediately after receiving the bonus, Amex does not like that. There are no benefits to having the Biz Gold if you already have the Personal Plat for Delta. I'd recommend canceling the gold if you need to. If you want more business cards, I'd recommend getting the Delta Biz Plat and then canceling the Per Plat too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1100 Plenti points for a $12 subscription for the Wall Street Journal (12 weeks, cancel before then so as to not get charged full price after that).

https://marketplace.plenti.com/me____.htm?gmid=1956 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! On a completely unrelated note, have you been everywhere man?

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ov4epAJRPMw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a targeted offer on Groupon for $20 of Uber credit for $10. You can check if you're targeted at the following URL: https://www.groupon.com/deals/uber-45 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The House report is still ongoing, the article will likely be updated throughout the morning. Here's the C-SPAN link: https://www.c-span.org/video/?425087-1/house-intelligence-committee-holds-first-public-hearing-russia-hacking live </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comey confirms FBI probe into Trump-Russia collusion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you post a screen shot of the offer terms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Newegg does something similar with the Everyday card </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately not, since Amex is once per lifetime. You could try for the Delta Platinum card which gives a nice bonus and has some cool features like an annual companion pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 05:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to doctorofcredit.com it likely will not work on gift cards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 04:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you won't get the bonus when you downgrade, you'd have to open a separate card to get the bonus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you've had your CSP for less than 1 year, then you will have to downgrade to the no fee CS and then to the freedom. It can be done within days of each other, no need to wait months.

If you've had it for at least a year, then you can go directly to the freedom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even more importantly, where did he spend his supernatural life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure about hotels, but The Points Guy has done some guides comparing the different major airline status programs. While I disagree with his actual valuations, I do find it's a useful summary of the benefits you get at different tiers, and he does mention some ways to achieve them. Essentially, it's going to be either through flying or spending on airline-branded credit cards.

More details are here: https://thepointsguy.com/guides/

Once you find an airline you think is best for you, then look into their co-branded cards and see what sort of elite-qualifying bonuses the cards offer. Delta, for example, offers up to 20-30K medallion qualifying miles on their Platinum and Reserve cards if you spend enough on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very subjective answer, and unfortunately one that you will have to figure out on your own depending on your travel habits, location, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately you have now "had the product" and so would not be eligible for a later bonus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, United's policy is different that of Delta or AA. You have to use the MPE for the ticket in order to get the free bag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah because that one is minute in size </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes you would still be at 4/24. It would be a hard pull if you're approved but not if you're denied. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are links in the header of the Meals on Wheels national page for advocacy, donations, and volunteering opportunities.

http://www.mealsonwheelsamerica.org/

You can also find your local MoW groups to support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meals on Wheels receives over $100k in donations in two days. Even if the latest White House budget proposal goes through, we can work as a community to donate money and push Congress to maintain funding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay, thats a bummer. Thanks for the heads up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noob question, I followed the direct link to this offer from DoC (http://www.doctorofcredit.com/ymmv-american-express-blue-cash-preferred-150-upgrade-offer/) and get an error saying "our systems are down" when logging in. Does that mean I'm not targeted or that there are actual system issues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, haven't had any HP's show up since I opened one card in late January </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was MIA? I hear it's warm down there this time of year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was already posted last week. 

https://www.reddit.com/r/churning/comments/5y15g2/targeted_gold_delta_skymiles_cc_60k_miles_50/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abe looks more blonde than I remembered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please post an update after things get sorted out, this would be a good data point to have </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to doctorofcredit, gift cards will likely not work. Out of curiosity, which cards did you receive this on? I couldn't get it on any of mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take your pick from this list: https://en.wikibooks.org/wiki/Turkish/Slang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California service workers union planning strike for May 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Foreign Minister: Turkey 'further away from EU membership than ever' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious, do you have over $2 million per annum in large purchase bonuses? Each card account can earn the large spend bonus on that amount. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DP: I was ordering catering for a department event at work, and the restaurant uses GatherHere.com to process payments. It posted to Chase as the actual restaurant, and also triggered a bonus from Skymiles Dining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I may make a suggestion, you could put that as a user-input field so the user can enter how much they value 1 MR point. You could put a default of 1cpp (i.e. redeem for statement credit). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though I hear there will be another digit discovered next product cycle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because all the carbs were onated to charity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, both personal and biz, credit cards only. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [For Discussion] If you receive benefits from a bill/law that you morally oppose, what would you do with those benefits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was talking to a friend about the GOP health care bill. While I am personally against many of the stipulations in the bill, I would also stand to gain from it based on being young and healthy. So the question becomes, if this bill were to hypothetically pass, what would you do with regard to any benefits you receive? Should one not take advantage of tax credits, or should one do that and then donate the money to those in need of health care, or should one take advantage of it while keeping on petitioning Congress to change it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What tofu you talking about??" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Do you have a similar calculator for the Everyday cards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they'll post after your statement closes. If you go the Ultimate Rewards site, it will say how many points are pending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
