<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3042</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 09:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is because at the beginning he is the one who is highest ranking and later on we meet his superiors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 09:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the Mouth of ~~Sauron~~ Vader </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 09:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  scripted speaking

This, exactly. I mean, of course these video essay guys prepare what they are going to say in advance, but with Nerdwriter I can clearly picture him literally *composing* sentences and one-upping their profoundness with each new statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 08:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If the score wasn't so God damn blaring at the start

It felt very much like a Michael Giacchino kind of thing. He does the same thing in the opening of Star Trek 2009. There is a low key theme playing during the opening company logos and then WHAM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 08:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reading your comment as a complaint. Not sure if it was meant as one. But personally I think Vader had the perfect ammount of screentime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 08:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he didn't kill her simply because he needed her for information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 08:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He uses his lightsaber and the force to straight up massacre a bunch of terrified Alliance soldiers in a narrow corridor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 01:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pros:

- They perfectly captured the look and feel of the original Star Wars world, which is both futuristic and ancient, sleek and gritty. And they expanded upon it perfectly with new locations, aliens, weapons, etc.

- The visuals are astounding. Beautiful cinematography and VFX. And all those wonderful designs! Darth Vader's hideout looked like something straight from Ralph McQuarie's sketchbook and all the aliens were neat.

- There was less fan service and nostalgia pandering compared to The Force Awakens (though it was definitely present)

- The ending was perfect. It did not shy away from character deaths and it tied things up wonderfully, leaving us where Ep. IV starts.

- We finally get to see Darth Vader kick some serious ass. You know which scene I mean. He was fucking terrifying. 

- We also see a lot more of the Empire

- Ben Mendelhson stole the show for me along with Donnie Yen. 

- The score felt very much like a Star Wars score.

The cons:

- The story is a bit all over the place and the pacing is off. The first half of the movie feels at odds with the beach planet finale. I think Rogue One could easily have been 20 minutes shorter and better paced without losing any important story beats.

- Neither the script nor the acting are perfect although neither gets anywhere near the high prequel levels of cringe.

In summary:

- Rogue One is a visual feast which captures the Star Wars feel perfectly. It serves as a great proof of concept for these standalone anthology films.

- It is not without issues of script and pacing, but these issues don't detract much from the overal very positive experience.

PS: Please excuse bad English and misspelled actor names.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 18:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  he basically repeats himself and fills it up with pretentious stuff

I think he does this in every single video, including the good ones, but to a varying degree. Of course, what really... pisses me off... are the... dramatic... pauses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 18:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking of youtubers and Nightcrawler, [this person's](https://www.youtube.com/user/Wendoverproductions) voice and way of speaking sound exactly like Lou Bloom to me. (It's a great channel with very interesting videos, but not movie related.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 17:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now it kind of sounds like he's a psychopath imitating normal humans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 17:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure what he was trying to say or point out with the scene from Doctor Strange. Why would Ejiofor wish he were in Spiderman instead? A joke? And I don't get what was such a cliche about the scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 17:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I think after almost every video he does and at some point I'm going to have to ask myself why do I even love Nerdwriter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunkirk trailer? /r/movies is going to *explode* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which brave soul will undertake to list all the movies with timestamps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 11:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> perfect, thank you so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 10:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but people noticed how stupid that movie was

people noticed big time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 10:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://imgur.com/a/xQBC8) is really annoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 08:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not sure if this was shot in Austria or Germany, but damn those two are beautiful countries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 08:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very nicely done infographic, good skill

OP, is this OC? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 08:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it in the sense that it is the best of the worst. But still one of the worst. The atrocious dialogue and hack acting are what always kills it for me but the story is pretty good. It has "wasted potential" written over every single frame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A little something I put together at work when I was bored </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 18:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 14:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish that safety car would slow down! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 14:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like something from Narcos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 13:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did I do wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 12:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the offer but I think you are the one who needs to chill and rub one out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 11:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this happens to leaves on my house plants all the time and I really wish I knew why..anyone ELI5? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 11:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeremy Renner was not the problem with that movie, though. The movie was its own problem, in a way. It felt very much like someone took an unrelated standalone spy movie and rewrote a couple of things to stick the Bourne label on it and make another movie in that franchise.  A Bourne movie should have Bourne in it. It's right there in the title of that film. There is no logical reason for doing a Bourne movie without Bourne other than to cash in on the brand recognition. Whether people would stomach Bourne being played by someone else other than Damon is another issue. 

The M:I movies don't have Ethan Hunt in their titles. So on this very basic level it would make sense to do a M:I movie without Hunt. There could be a whole new IMF team. They could even set it in the sixties and make it about the cold war. They could do what Star Trek did - have different teams in different periods and locations. Or there could be a M:I movie with Ethan Hunt played by someone else, but again, the question is how would audiences react to seeing a different actor take that name.

Of course, the Bond movies recast their main character. But it's something the franchise is know for. Ever since I can remember there have always been discussions on who would be a good Bond, whether it was just wishful thinking or actual casting rumors. I have never seen anyone discuss who would make a good Bourne or Hunt. People are used to the fact that Bond gets recast because it has already happened a couple of times and the franchise is what, 60 years old by now? I don't know what the reaction was when Connery was recast, but by now people are simply used to the fact that Bond gets recast every now and then. It is a very unique characteristic of this particular franchise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 10:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are being unfairly negative about Cruise. Jokes about his height? What is this, 2002? And how is he *manufacturing attention* ? By working and releasing new movies? Isn't that what literally every actor does? He's been less and less outspoken about his religion for years, he has no recent sex scandals or any other BS like that and despite his practically unbroken streak of success he isn't difficult to work with. In fact he is pretty well known for being a very hard worker who always gives his best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 21:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because he wanted to be as human as possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  is implied to have killed children

Younglings.

Lest ye forget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but since they were archetypes, there wasn't really anything interesting or new about them. Yes, there were characters in the movie, but they were still just window dressing. And the story between the fights didn't really give them anything interesting do, either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 13:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It has her thumb print on it.  Quark uses this method also for transactions.  It's also a show of symbolism - writing a letter by hand or just sending off an e-mail.

The iPad has her thumbprint on it physically? Yeah, I guess so, along with a couple other of her finger print and Sisko's too, since he touched it as well. But I suppose you meant that she scanned her thumbprint and attached it to the document as a sort of verification. So it has a digital thumbprint, which could be sent along with her resignation as an email. No sense in physically giving a whole iPad to someone so it could be sent to Starfleet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 11:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean but I find it difficult to agree. Pacific Rim and Godzilla both had great spectacle but neither feel like great movies, and this is due to their characters. If you are fidgeting during a film and only waiting for the big FX scenes to finally start then the film is a failure in terms of storytelling, a mere vessel for the few minutes of CG. Compare that to a movie like Aliens. You go in wanting to see more of that great scary alien and the spectacular violence and action. But you find yourself enjoying the entire hour before an alien even shows up because of the great characters. That makes the entire movie enjoyable and memorable, instead of just something you have to sit through to see a chest burster or the Queen vs Powerlifter fight. That's a scene that is elevated to perfection by the fact that you care about Ripley and her need to save Newt and destroy the alien. Godzilla has great designs, great effects, cool shots and exciting fights, but think about how much better all those things could have been if you gave a shit about the world those fights are happening in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there no data transfer technology in this universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 09:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am watching DS9 for the first time and the other day I realized something that is also true for TNG, which I watched two years ago. Despite all the incredible technology available to these characters, nobody seems to have a USB drive or wifi (nobody seems to have the sci-fi equivalents of these things, at any rate). I was watching the episode where Dax falls in love with a mam from a planet that shifts into a non-corporeal dimension and she was going to leave the normal world to go with him. So she writes her resignation from Starfleet on her iPad and then she hands the whole iPad to Sisko asking him to make sure Starfleet gets it. So what exactly is going to happen here? Is Sisko going to *mail the whole iPad* to HQ? Doesn't Starfleet have email? In another episode, Odo is investigating an explosion in Garak's shop and he meets a Cardassian Deep Throat informant. This informant gives Odo a list of names by literally handing him a tablet-like device which Odo then takes back to DS9 to investigate. Do these people have an unlimited supply of tablets that they give away any time they need to share a simple .txt file? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Godzilla (2014) have a ton of deleted scenes or were the characters really so poorly written? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 09:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I watched Godzilla again. Despite its flaws I find it to be a very rewatchable movie. In fact, I suspect it will become one of those movies I'll always watch when they're on, like Independence Day or Deep Blue Sea. I can think of few movies from the 21st century that are so rewatchable in this entertaining, non-commital way. But there is one thing that bothers me big time about Godzilla and it's those bland, dumb, boring characters. 

What were they thinking when they cast Ken Watanabe, a very popular and very awesome Japanese actor, only to give him *nothing* to work with? All he ever does is stare off into the distance with a hollow look of shock. This becomes so ridiculous so fast. One of these days I'll make a compilation of nothing but shots of Watanabe staring. And what were they going for with Elisabeth Olsen's character? Love interest? Damsel of distress? Strong female character? Plot device to give Aaron Taylor Johnson's character some personal stakes? This talented actress is barely in the movie and I'm prone to forget all about the character's existence immediately after one of her short pointless scenes ends. Is there a whole character arc they had to cut from the movie to save time? (Or because the studio wanted to favor monster action instead? I don't know, I'm clutching at straws here.) I find it hard to believe that someone simply wrote a non-character like this and Olsen's agent thought it would be a great idea for her to play it. And ATJohnson is clearly capable of a good performance (see Nocturnal Animals) but he is so boring in Godzilla. I'm not that big of a Brian Cranston fan and I thought it was a bold choice to kill him off in the middle of the movie, but for heaven's sake, at least have someone remotely interesting to cary the rest of your film! What happened with this script?

I really hope the next movies in this monster universe will have better characters and not waste their great cast (Kong, you better have something good in store for Brie Larson!) and I seriously hope that Garreth Edwards is capable of much better character work and I won't have to repeat this rant after seeing Rogue One. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 21:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels like I've already heard this type of song in other modern sci-fi movies of varying quality. It sounds exactly the way I thought it would. I am not saying that the music is bad, I actually like it, but simply sounds like other soundtracks. This could easily be an unused M83 song from Oblivion.

On the other hand, Arrival, for example, has a soundtrack that is so jarringly different from things we've heard before in mainstream sci-fi movies. That is a soundtrack that helps build an aura of mystery, wonder, and the unexpected around the mysterious and wondrous images of the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 10:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fair enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 08:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   "I have to go in totally new territory."

*goes and makes the Mummy look like Enchantress from Suicide Squad* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of wish it was neither but it will probably be both </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at first I thought this was a joke post and this *was* from Hannibal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume this is in the deleted scenes on the Zero Dark Thirty DVD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if the insides remained intact, but I guess we will never know because they wont be able to cut it in half </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's Spider Man, and presumably he got off the train on his way home so... the name checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> visually it looks to be on about the same level of awesomeness as the first one and the humor in the trailers was good as well, so I definitely have my hopes way up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 11:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pleasantly arabesque </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 10:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Groot *is* the retarded brother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 09:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [relevant](https://youtu.be/IM1-DQ2Wo_w?t=8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 09:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are you kidding? the first LEGO movie was a visual feast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 13:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hunger games for secretaries, then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 08:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It has an insufferable protagonist, zero subtlety, and a plot you can predict right from the get-go.

so the trailer totally nailed the book, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 17:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it's just grinding the whole plants into fine dust. How is that harvesting? (clueless person from the city asking, be kind) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish more movies did this instead of creating megatons of hype. I bet I would have liked 10 Cloverfield Lane less if I was hyped for it for a year in advance. Trailers and marketing these days create insane expectation for everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know! I already have tickets for next Wednesday so I will avoid this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 22:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neon Demon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 14:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is always nice when research confirms common knowledge  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Keanu Reeves plays himself in a lot of his movies

TIL Keanu Reeves is an international assassin who owns a shitty motel, likes to surf and is the one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Santa were real, Christmas would be the best kind of home invasion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 10:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 09:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is going to be Darth Vader and the Death Star, so it is already a throwback to the OT in that respect and as for scenes and lines, we won't know until we see the movie. 

Don't get me wrong, I'm not trying to hate this movie. I want it to be amazing. But lets not pretend that it's original. It's a fan fiction prequel that is bringing back the most iconic character and weapon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 08:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And VII was clearly a throwback full of fan winks and references. Rogue One on the other looks like a very very original story.

I agree about VII but come on, Rogue One is the biggest throwback of them all. It is literally fan fiction based on one line in the opening crawl of Star Wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 08:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like you put etc there because you could not think of any more examples but I definitely agree with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 08:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cannot judge a movie by the first trailer. It has a great cast and good writers. The one thing I am worried about is the director. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 20:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean by middle aged? I think of middle aged as around 50, and I can guarantee you that my middle-aged 55 year old father will never ever go see Valerian but he'll love Dunkirk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 16:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, I'm not saying there aren't people who want to see both movies. I am one of them as well. But when we look at the two movies at face value, one is a WWII drama based on real events and the other is a colorful sci-fi action space opera. Those are two very distinctive things especially from a marketing POV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 14:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like someone in the Tic Tac company just said 'Fuck the planet, lets make completely unnecessary plastic waste' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 13:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would venture to guess that in general, the target audiences for these two movies don't really overlap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks very B-movie but I will watch it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 13:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Could mean that we get a logical explanation about how the ship in the first Alien movie got on LV-426.

Are we missing a logical explanation? Can't a ship simply crash on a planet without a whole movie explaining the reason? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We are made of starstuff" - Carl Sagan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> youtube views and upvotes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  in the last century

Do you mean the last 100 years (1916-2016) or the 20th century (1901-2000)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 23:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah that movie was so obviously pandering to Chinese audiences that it took me out of the story a couple of times

Now You See Me 2 is a similiar case  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was especially jarringly true for Man of Steel, where Superman fought Evil Superman a.k.a. Zod. Not only were they absolutely matched in their powers, they were also completely indestructible. At least when Spiderman fights Evil Spiderman he can get hurt or tired. But this was just two immortal dudes throwing each other through walls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 13:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  British films?

technically foreign if OP is from US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 11:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I feel really stupid that I had no idea he had a motorcycle career </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 18:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> J.J. Abrams is pretty good at this. 

My favorite "show dont tell" moment from JJ is at the beginning of Super 8. They show one of those "__ days without an accident sign" in a factory just as someone is changing the number back to zero and then it cuts to a funeral. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 18:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jeez way to take that out of context, man

(kidding) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah even when Schumi returned after his break you could tell after races that his neck was stiff. He turned his head by turning his whole torso </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Self-imposed or did I miss something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come Together  a commercial directed by Wes Anderson

just to be correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They have almost identical cars, its very hard for them to overtake each other outside of the start

I get that under normal circumstances but Hamilton was clearly going slower than his car was capable of and slower than Rosberg could have gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didn't Rosberg overtake him if he was so slow? Was Rosberg just playing it safe, not wanting to risk a collision and figuring second place was enough?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 12:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sounds like exactly the sort of little thing I was going for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 12:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Martian uses the laziest of all devices - a video diary.

To be fair, though, in the case of The Martian a video diary was kind of inevitable for a couple of reasons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 11:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shit journalism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite examples of the "show, don't tell" approach to storytelling? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 08:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate it when movies have unnaturally sounding dialogue filled with exposition that is only there to inform the audience about something. To me that is lazy writing, lazy filmmaking and it just screams 'infodump for the dumb audience' in a way that takes me out of the movie completely. I understand that certain things simply need to be said and explained, but at the same time so many things can be shown instead of told. After all, movies are a visual medium.

Like the other day I was watching Frailty and at the very beginning there is a shot at a parking space reserved for Agent Doyle. A man parks there and gets out of the car and you immediately know he is an FBI agent, probably high ranking since he has his own parking space, and you know his name. It's a stupid, small thing, but it's so much better than this:

Person A: "Hello, man who is going to introduce me to the audience."

Person B: "Oh, hi there. As you know, you are special agent Doyle with the fancy parking spot."

So what are your favorite examples of "show, don't tell"? It could be a little thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 08:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I am very happy about their choice, too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 11:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hence what I put in the spoiler tags </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 22:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Hell or High Water

out of all the movies you listed this is the only one where the criminals are commiting a victimless crime [at least until they shoot someone during the botched robbery](#spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 14:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same in Slovakia, Czech Republic and Austria. I would assume it applies for most of Europe. Never had any issue with keeping the walls clean. Obviously a repainting job is required every once in a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 10:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why compare them and pick a favorite over the other? They are very different movies and both are masterpieces in their respective genres. One is a dark sci-fi survival horror movie with a metaphorical monster in it (a walking phallic symbol set on raping people with its equally phallic dick mouth) and the other is a lighter action movie with a perfect depiction of a military unit fighting monsters and shooting shit with an exploration of motherhood as the cherry on top </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 08:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which is why at 2.5 hours it still feels like a breeze and never bores </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 10:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Slow but Never Boring' applies for a couple of Fincher movies but Zodiac is by far the prime example </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 13:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In The Mission Neeson played a young Jesuit monk, now he is the old Jesuit monk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 13:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is a knight of Ren, whatever that is, so Ren is not even his name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 09:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> chills down my spine and tears of joy in my eyes

this movie better be fucking amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 09:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firefly was already Han Solo fan porn so this should work great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 16:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started to dislike Ferrari as a team and Vettel has become a bitchy child (honestly!). I also used to be a bigger fan of Verstappen but he got really arrogant this season and all those overtaking controversies did not help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 15:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many pages do you read in those two hours? I usually read for two hours a day, too, but I never manage more than 30 books a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 15:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it will look good on the movie tie-in edition of the source novel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 09:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reminds me of the prison they held Magneto in X2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 08:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen any of the previous Cars movies. But holy shit, the animation in this teaser is top notch and the racing looks exciting. It almost* makes me want to watch Cars.

*I expect that it will turn out to be one cool race and the rest will be aimed at kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 08:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Annakin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 23:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which episode was that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 23:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that about sums up my feelings after most of these "mythology" episodes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why you got downvoted but I agree with you about the pacing. At one point there is a sort of montage narrated by Renner's character that feels like he's doing a segment for the evening news, except he isn't and the sequence is very out of place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 16:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is kind of like Contact meets Sphere with no action scenes (unless you count helicopters taking off in immaculately composed establishing shots) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 00:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> care to elaborate on the changes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 19:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she is impossibly stunning in this picture

it's like she's just telling me 'look at how fucking hot I am' in the best way possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 12:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh, that terrible acting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 16:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can tell by the pixels? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 16:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but why would he put the recipient's name on the bottom where one would expect the sender's name? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 16:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie cannot arrive soon enough. The previous two were brilliant. I was very pleasantly surprised by Ghost Protocol and I was worried they wouldn't be able to make another one that good. But Rogue Nation was amazing as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 16:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is there any way we could have trees falling? And he said, If you want to pay for it. So we did.


Wouldn't that apply to literally every CG effect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 15:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why is she grabbing her own pussy? where is Donald? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a huge fan of that Star Trek soundtrack and I don't hear it in the Dosctor Strange soundtrack at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's my message to Charlie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 08:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why we get all those amazing screen prints from artists like Dan Mumford </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 10:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I was blown away by the movie and I was very apologetic of its flaws whet it came out but now I cannot stand the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 09:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monuments Men.

I was expecting a great movie in the style of Dirty Dozen or Kelly's Heroes with some la resistnce awesomeness dropped in. What I got was a disjointed movie that did absolutely nothing interesting with the very interesting story it had to work with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 08:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I know they aren't scary and I don't understand why. There is something inherently terrifying about an immortal nocturnal being that can suck your blood like a leech and yet filmmakers focus on all the wrong aspects of that concept. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] I am looking for a vampire movie that is actually scary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen many vampires movie but none of them were really scary. They either focus on the romanticising vampires, violence, creature effects, etc, but none of them are frightening the way other horror subgenres are. Lost Boys, Fright Nighr, Twilight, Blade, Let the Right One In, Dawnbreakers, Near Dark, From Dusk Till Dawn, Dracula etc, etc, are all vampire movies I did not find scary at all. The only that came close is Nosferatu. Can you recommend something else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
