<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6120</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 19:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gotta predict it each year, eventually you'll get a hit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 10:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try: https://www.smartflix.io/ - it's a Netflix client with a built-in proxy service, allowing it to workaround regional restrictions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 09:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that was funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 09:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too be fair, she might be subscribing to the Old Testament teachings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 19:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not exactly more moral or better, but definitely everyone wants to be as "cool" - everyone forgets how shitty they were up until the19th centuries at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 19:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spent a year on and off in Budapest. Loved it. But one thing I remember the most, from a Lonely Planet book, Hungarians has a reputation as being xenophobic.

I did notice some xenophobia, but mostly from younger men (this was early 2000s) - I'd be on a date with a Hungarian girl and some Hungarian guy would try to chat her up in Magyar, without even acknowledging me - it happened maybe 4 or 5 separate times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 18:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just give them time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 18:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet more shit. Star Wars was great because it was "starved" and Lucas and his team had nowhere to go but be creative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 02:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they could've used a little less jump cut, but I agree with your assessment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 18:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The alternative is to become dinner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 00:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It probably wasn't allowed. Whoever recorded it was recording it surreptitiously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 22:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've got dividends, ~0.50 a share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 21:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if that's the reason why he was an extra in Apocalypse Now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 21:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there good book to read about these? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 21:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was fucked up and cold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 21:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's when you do the butt-stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 20:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> made me snort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 07:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She can choke my chicken anytime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 02:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 18:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't keep track of movie stars lives, but that's what I suspected. Even the way she walks indicates some nerve impairment similar to a stroke victim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 18:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the sanest and clear headed comment I've read here so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 05:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that's so hot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 05:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not religion. But it's the same principle of conditioning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 05:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah I get it now: weed makes you cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 19:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traditional jobs you mean? Software Enginneers for example probably won't have an established caste (or is there?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 07:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of that scene in Prometheus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 07:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was his most terrible. 

It really just read like someone's tidbit on things they picked up on their visit to Italy. It seemed almost pointless - I stopped being on the lookout for Grisham's book after that; my girlfriend back then was speculating that maybe Grisham just got to the point where he just hired a writing team and all he does is give a plot outline and affix his name once the book is written. 

Three of his earlier ones I thought were good though: A Time to Kill, The Firm, and The Rainmaker.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 03:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curious: how does everyone knows each other's caste?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 20:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like bandits and thugs. Just like the remains of the New People's Army. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 20:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot twist: it's not the same dog. Her parents replaced it when it died 5 years ago as a puppy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 07:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually fines reduce these from happening. 

If a bank is fined every time there is a leak or breach of their customer's account, you can bet your ass it'll be a much rarer event. 

SaaS providers, like Steam, no matter how charismatic their CEO's are, should step up and be compelled (via fines and other means) to protect their customer's data. An empty promise like "We will not share your data" is not enough.

Hopefully Steam is fined for these, not just face a class action suit, as it might pave the way for laws or regulations that will improve the way businesses "protects" their customer's data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 23:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why you were getting downvoted, you were just stating boob facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 21:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By your reasoning we should also have a mandated jail sentence for people going over the speed limit, because speeders *might* ruin people's lives by almost running them over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 06:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually if I was there that's day, I'd be pissed. 

But I wouldn't be thinking about suing them. I'd expect that they get a slap in the wrist - which would piss me of even more, because they lengthened my commute by 15 minutes or so, but I'd be horrified if anybody pushes for more severe forms of punishment.

Caning would be acceptable, he'll recover from it. Unfortunately we don't have it. 

Multiple lawsuits and/or 6 months in jail - that would be fucked up. Considering people at most just got inconvenienced.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 06:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt we'll see an epidemic of these. Fine and community service ought to be enough. Any more and it's unjust.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 06:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> off with their heads!!!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 05:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was an innocent act, there was no malice in it. Any more than a hard slap on the wrist would ruin this guy. How is that fair?

People need to chill out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 05:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 months in jail may as well be a lifetime of punishment. Especially here in the US.

Hopefully he just gets fined and get to do a long enough community service. 

Any more than that is injustice, legal though it may be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 03:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That should be the extent of it. It was foolish, could've caused an accident, they got lucky that it did not - so let's just move on, give everyone a slap on the wrist but make sure nobody's life is ruined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 18:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *ADAMANT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 08:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing good will come of this as it is all supported by weed money. Jesus would be rolling in his grave right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 06:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where might you get them? How could you get infected by these? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 02:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. WW2 (and most or all wars) I think are mostly choices between bad and worse, with very little room for even the most pragmatic decisions stemming from idealism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 02:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Japan was the weird one? :-) (hookup wise) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 02:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :,-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 22:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :,-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 20:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It borne out a peace loving Japan and Germany. That was good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 20:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1 on Europe. Eastern Europe specially. Some Asian countries like Philippines, but you can't be coming off like douche or too aggressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 01:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just barely 10 years after getting nuked twice and they're slutting around by the beaches already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 01:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens to his Wu Tang Clan album? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 17:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You evil little fuck. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 17:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was cute that his mom used a tablet to take a photo of him skydiving. She also held the tablet like a camera peeking through a view finder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 19:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if only you were joking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 18:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> would love to help you grool :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 18:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are hot as fuck!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 17:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the first one I see here who took the time to fix "their" to "they're". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 21:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 19:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Roomba! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 18:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Closest I could think of in real life is in Lawrence, KS - if I remember correctly it's called the Bourgeoise Pig.  Serves good snooty coffee, any cup you order may be laced with brandy, whiskey, or liqueur.

No one pretends though.

EDIT: Added last line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 20:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sort of like freeze dried coffee granules in a sealed container.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 20:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also call him The Dudester, El Duderino, His Dudeness... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 17:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was very lucid. And very untypical as most pro gun rights arguments I've heard/read.

I still would like to see guns banned or severely reduced by in the US, but now I see/understand the other side a little bit better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 19:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True dat. But I imagine it's different for people growing up wealthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 18:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to read his entire comment :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 17:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See: John Wick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 17:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think of Pierre Woodman? would you ever do a shoot with him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 20:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tinker, Tailor, Soldier, Spy while not straightforward is comprehensible. 

You have to pay close attention though, and work to keep the threads you've untangled so far. And if you've done this, at the end of the movie, when everything is laid bare, you get the satisfaction of having unravelled parts, or if you were really astute, most or all of the mysteries and sub-mysteries that drove the story.

There's some movies however that are convoluted just for the sake of; Mulholland Drive comes to mind. Everyone seems to love it and claims it's a wonderful mind-fuck - but I think the writer/director just really did not have a story to tell: just finely crafted scenes/vignettes (which are all weird and memorable) - but as a whole, totally worthless and might as well be random. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 05:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Office retreat party at a resort hotel in Lake Balaton, Hungary. Communist era hotel and our company was the only guests. 

Ended up chatting with a female employee from Croatia which eventually turned into a make out session and progressed from there.

Fucked behind the bar, behind the sofa in the lobby, the elevator, the hallway to her room, the odd waiting area in the hallway - we never got to her room (she had a roommate) - so finished there and fucked some more. 

Went back to my room with a shit eating grin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 04:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL, Linga. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 03:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the thinking back then, probably now too, is that babies grow up and could take arms later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 18:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're still using teal + orange color schemes. I wish movies would stop using it so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 17:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a dick. He was also hitting them at the back of the head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 15:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aesthetic describes someone skilled at sports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 08:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to guess India.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 22:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jean Claude Van Damme will disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 20:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that would be Africa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 18:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For stealing trash? you gotta be fucking kidding me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 17:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The aftermath too, when Samuel L. Jackson was chatting with the boy, relating his own first experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 08:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they beheaded this guy with a dull spoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 18:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once they have the single-payer thing locked down, might be time to move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 01:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how much per night? is it more expensive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 09:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep it was. you could imagine her doing that after a sloppy blowjob. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 19:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Medical Bills are forgiveable. You could even arrange to pay them $1 a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 17:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or chatting up dullards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 19:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> man, I hope Trump wins the Republican Primary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 19:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude, NSFW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 03:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess :-) 

But I was thinking more along the lines of Machiavelli's recommendation on states with issues of lawlessness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 19:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever his motives are, it's still a net benefit. Though it should not have to come to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 18:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes that's what a city needs. The problem is when and how to transition away from that mode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 17:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be permanent. But it would be very hard for him in the job market in the next couple of years.

If he goes to prison, he's fucked. It's not fair, but that's how it is in the US at the moment. And unfortunately won't be changing anytime soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 22:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 18:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to respond that it's not that hard to lose weight, plenty of good and healthy food to help, etc., then I saw your last sentence: "Denial is easier" - yep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 18:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're talking about glory holes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 18:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first laugh of the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 08:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the caption in his voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 17:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> were we talking about boobs?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 17:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep. that's what she'll be: thor and unable to walk straith. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 04:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes it does. but if you eat the chick out or suck somebody off you'll get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 04:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what if 1 or 2 of those prostis were midgets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 01:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is like OPs retard brother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
