<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1145</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 23:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Who would win in a match between you and James Ellsworth?
2. What is your favorite magic trick (yours or others)?
3. Do you consider David Blaine a magician or a novelty act?
4. Do you ever use your tricks in the bedroom?
5. Who was in the Gorilla Position?
6. Who would you like to team with out of these Superstars: Phantasmo, Goldust, Booker T, Papa Shango, Boogeyman or Broken Matt Hardy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC the opponent can't get heat by attacking the botcher. They have to wait to make sure they're okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't Bloomingdale's also a Sax 5th Ave during most of the 90s? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guitar Re-strung </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Busted a string on my guitar. Looking for a good San Diego (around Northpark, Downtown, Hillcrest, etc) place to get the string replaced. Where's a good local spot I can support that isn't Guitar Center. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you protecting the hijab? I know it's a head covering; but it implies more than just the head being covered. Feel me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tommy Oliver (played by Jason David Frank) has played at least 5 rangers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rita: And now, Cee No Gold, go down and take out the Power Rangers!

Cee No Gold: Imma rape them in their sleep!  

Rita: What? No. Just kill them so I can conquer Earth! Ahahaha!  

Cee No Gold: Then we can rape everyone in their sleep!  

Rita: No. We'd have everyone be our slaves. What's with you? Raping people while they're asleep is still rape.  

Cee No Gold: If someone is passed out, they're not even WITH you consciously.  

Rita: What the heck? How did you even get to be a part of my team? Like, what if I was sleeping? Would you fuck me? That's some Ooze shit right there. Not even Zed is that terrible. 

Cee No Green: You make my monster grow. I see you drivin' round toooown--  

Rita: No. No more of that. Just get out.  

Cee No Green: But we in space--  

Rita: GET OUT!  



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Galisia Garcia  

Where are Max, Axel, Blaze, Skate and Adam when you need them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go down on them with a twist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it! There can even be an action scene at the end where after Chappie has learned to love; he learns how to kill and the action scene is him running and killing police, then his creator tries to talk him out of it and just as we see Chappie start to turn, the big heavy shoots him in the head. Last scene we see is the creator dude staring into green fields, then he turns around and begins work on another robot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's photo shows off the beautiful curves, hair and all around beauty that women have...that shouldn't HAVE to be hidden under a hijab.  

Edit: Spelling of "Hijab" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking LOVE the Boogeyman!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Awesome Things I'd Like to See </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A primary shotgun blaster (spinning cylinders that fire three shots at a time)  

A 6 shot style Magnus Mega Pistol  

A single fire that fits on your wrist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #letsrapeceelogreen #whilehesunconcious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then they go to the Juice Hut, fight some putties, morph then get into their zords. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here to induct Teddy Long........  

"I'm Comin'" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I wasn't sure if they were disbetes appropriate or not! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the foreplay fucking master, got my technique down an' everything, don't be ticklin' or nothin'! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have apps and codes that help you make the font bigger. Feel me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be happy you have a small dick. Seriously. You can fuck tight chicks. I can barely fuck an Asian woman without splitting her in half; white chicks usually take about a half bottle of lube and sometimes I just can't even get it in. I'd love to just be able to throw my dick around in everyone and have anger problems...I'm just chill and satisfying most of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You have My sword" -Stryder  

"And my AXE!" -Grimley  

"^and MY **EYES**" -Legeyeless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually off meds, I haven't ridded myself of the BP2 (and have had one texting incident) but for the most part I keep a good eating schedule with meal prep, I workout regularly and take nightly walks to the harbor. I also smoke occasionally (tobacco). My SO helps a lot too with understanding and being patient! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some natural non-sugar sweeteners are: bananas, apples, and the big one: dates! Idk if these are diabetic friendly but they're sweet and taste delicious! I like persimmon pudding: blend ripe persimmons, dates and some pumpkin pie spice. I also enjoy a nice Larabar: in the food processor use half dates and half of your favorite nuts (almonds, cashews, walnuts, etc) process until the ingredients stick together, empty ingredients onto plastic wrap, close plastic wrap, press mixture until it resembles a bar, refrigerate or leave out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should also practice open carry laws with non white people. We'll see what happens when non white people legally carry firearms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do this to kids all the time. They just scream and run away. Then their parents don't want my homemade back alley ice cream bars! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a sign of equality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Styles was considered a cruiserweight at one point in his illustrious career, do you think he'd have as much success as he has been in the WWE?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ultimate Warrior was a part timer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone care about CM Punk anymore? After he had mouthed WWE, treated his fans like shit and lost his MMA fight, isn't he just done? Like can we treat him like the shitty wrestler and person he presented himself as, not the legend he pretends to be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sort of! Stone Cold and Rock were both heel characters with massive face heat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're cheering for a blue collar worker you want to tune in every week and see him best the bad guy, in this case the bad guy was the boss of the company, Vince couldn't fire Austinn because he brought the boss lots of money but he didn't want Austin around because he would make him piss his pants and do other things to humiliate him.   

Then, after one match, without seed planting or any rhyme or reason, the guy that you tune in to see suddenly sides with the boss...for no reason. Would you still keep tuning in? Would you want to see the guy, the reason you forked over 60 bucks a month, 20 dollars for a t shirt, 10 bucks for a bop em blow up bag for the kid, 5 bucks for an awesome big gulp cup, etc. Would you want to see him being the boss's stooge every week?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the office is going to fight in the best way!!! Maybe take a vid of some of the hijinx? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 21 year old is stupid. The fun co guy is being funny most likely from the fact that many women enjoy a gentlemen on the street and a bad boy in the sheets, this is a parody of that in which the jokester is saying he will give in to the matriarchy outside of the bedroom but return to primal roles inside the bedroom (which a number of women seem to like as I can say from my own experience), the joke is a joke though a joke can't be a joke without offending someone. Chickens crossing roads offends PETA because a chicken shouldn't be used in a joke since it undervalues the importance of a chicken's life. The third chap is trying to treat women equally and fairly. If you expect a man to pay on the first date then you are either against equality, pro chivalry (which supports the patriarch) or conditioned to believe that you deserve someone else to pay for your meals and drinks.  

I usually go on first dates that don't involve money exchange of any kind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two beefcakes in pajama pants on either side to entertain your friends and excite your lives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find out where a nearby greyhound station or homeless shelter is, spend a few minutes walking around there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of my penis in the morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a guy who's working on a graphic novel I'd like to thank you for taking the time to make this comic for not only me and several other people to laugh with, share, and stare at. Good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seasoned stage and screen actor here. The framing is off, if you can't get the golden ratio then go for subject center framing. The focus seems a little off as well. The lighting was good as well as the location and ambiance.  

Good intensity on delivery. Nice planned gestures. You were dressed for the part (but I would lose the shirt, this makes you look more confident and gets you used to being topless). One of my biggest pet peeves is inhale or exhale gasping, you only did it once but I caught it, the reason I have a problem with this is because it reminds the viewers that you're acting, we don't gasp like that in real life (look at any female actor and you'll hear at least one per movie), I say take the time to breathe, control your breath and you control the audience. Unfortunately you have wonderful natural gaps in your speech pattern, every one does, in WWE this would be filled by Whats, I hate the What's so be mindful of this if you're ever in New York.  

You built up your opponent slightly. Not enough for my personal taste. I would have gone for the full manipulator angle and tried to get sympathy for myself, that's just me. I'd suggest reading about extreme personality types and gearing your character towards one (Mankind is a psychopath, Edge is a sociopath, Vince is an Ego maniac, Triple H is inadequate, Stone Cold is an anarchist). I'm not sure if the Cupids Arrow is a submission or a ddt, also what is the opponent's finisher? Ultimately it's your finisher against theirs...or do you have other intentions in mind??? Also we assume the match will end in a three count, no need to remind us of the finish unless it's a specialty match, Kurt Angle breaking your ankle is different than him saying he's going to makem you slam your hand on the mat to tap out, Lesnar doesn't pin his opponents he conquers them.  

Hope that helped! May your match go as planned! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm sofa king high rise now! I can't smoke anything else...but this sun warmed, previously fried and frozen pressed potato nugget dipped in hash oil aoli is so good I can't stop man."

"Good sir, up next are crusted chicken fingers served alongside warm meat pouches and cheese dusted tortilla triangles. Then after that is green chili's, beef and pinto beans wrapped in a tortilla served with smaller warmed pouches of meat that contain pepperoni cubes, marinara sauce and cheese."

"Duuuude! That noodle soup infused with Oriental flavor was a look good!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life RPG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to marinate my meats the night before meal prep. Then I usually broil the meats in the marinating juice. Adding a bit of water helps with reheating, but my meats usually aren't dry after cooking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Casey Abrams is my favorite PMJB vocalist and bassist! Love I'm Not the Only One and Staceys Mom! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should also get this kid called Johnny Mundo!!!  

But seeing some short hires from other companies (even local talent) would boost seat buys! Is love to see some of my pro wrestling friends get beat up by Kendrick and Neville! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a graphic designer, film maker and artist in general I'd say they the reason strobe lighting is done by hand is to give it a natural and organic feel.  

Think about the movement in VFX for a moment. Those scenes that have tens of millions of people in them who are obviously digitalized are easily spotted. But you get tend of thousands of dedicated extras and you have a more organic feel. You animate a guy riding a dragon and the movement of the animated actor isn't going to be as human like as using then actual actor in front of a green screen.  

The same is for music and strobes. You'll know the minute there are zeros and ones controlling the light. The lighting artist controls the lights like an artist controls lines or brush strokes.

Kayfabe answer: Brock Lesnar spends money on hiring a lighting guy to make sure his entrance is unique every time. Brock Lesnar is also so mean that he doesn't have friends so he hired Paul Heyman to be his "manager". When you have as much money as an MMA and WWE Superstar combined, you can get cool things like a guy manually strobing your entrance lights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mania is all about celebrity a appearances. You're looking for Survivor Series, an annual wrestling event in which top WWE Superstars compete in wrestling matches. The big draw of classic Survivor Series matches is that there are usually four wrestlers per team and match ups that don't often occur may happen at any time. There's also Royal Rumble, Armageddon, No Way Out, Extreme Rules, Great American Bash, Night of Champions, Clash of the Champions, One Night Stand, And several more monthly and weekly shows that revolve around Superdtars wrestling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell I'm not casual and I'm looking forward to it! Big Show is an attraction. He's going against an NBA legend, an actor and a certified film maker! Big Show has fought a Sumo wrestler, a boxer and not to mention WWE Superstars on a weekly basis! It's two of the BIGGEST ATHLETES IN THE WORLD in the same ring together!!! Why would you smark up and talk down about this match? This is literally what makes new fans of the product! This is pro wrestling at its roots. Don't be the guy who keeps the title in his retirement match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about they face Russo in a Russo on a pole match? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I subscribe from Rumble to Mania and enjoy the network during those months. Then bounce after mania and keep my nose open for good matches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mom is hot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like the stubble I get at 3 in the afternoon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think if he was in the TNA "cruiserweight" division he'd be as successful on the WWE? I'm just wondering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at a Greyhound Station in Atlanta. Some guy claimed he was jumped, they stole his fiddle and his shoes. We were on the same bus together. We both did the "You go first thing" but he did his second so I went. I was the last person on the bus before it was full. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really weird to me right now! I just got back from Maui and it took an hour for pizza, a burger, some breakfast sandwiches etc. at the small shops. Everything was made fresh and no one really complained (weird since most people were tourists).  

A few years ago I had to make everything fresh in the fast chow section of the chow hall. Marines would order a burger then go through regular chow line while waiting for their fast chow.  I believe the fresh fast chow was due in part to me cooking batches of burgers in the oven. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheap chairs, cheap oven, no fire alarm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The proper, legal way, of doing this would be to put the food in the trash can then inform homeless people there are burritos in the trash can. The proper, humane way to do this is to find homeless or hungry people and hand the burritos to them. The realistic way to do this is to make a bunch of burritos because even non homeless, low income or just hungry people like free burritos and if you make one for one person then you make one for everyone. The trump way to do this is to enforce martial law, force all the burritos back to Mexico(for the filling) and Israel (for the Jewish idea of using the tortilla to wrap Mexican food) and build walls on the border of each country (that the other country pays for) then rape a young woman and fly out to where the good burritos are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's my take:  

1. Show Bruce trying to earn his money back. 

2. Catwoman steals Bruce's things. 

3. Batman is put in the hole. 

4. Bruce has to make it back through tricks and stealth. 

5. Batman gives Robin a costume since Batman is unable to clean up the mess himself. 

6. Talia is revealed to be Bane's pawn. 

7. Robin takes down Bane proving he's capable of protecting Gotham. 

8. We get the same ending at first. 

9. Alfred is happy. Then he stops smiling.  

10. Robin approaches Bruce in the restaurant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OWA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rusev is in the Snake Pit. He gets guys ready to be champion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might try this. I have sensitive eyes and I can sense when someone sees them get bloodshot. They start rubbing their eyes or yawning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some porn companies (Playboy, Wicked, actors and actresses) have pay per month sites. If their scenes are leaked online it's great marketing for them. Who wouldn't want to interact with their preferred person of lust?  
Hollywood doesn't make money by giving their movies away. Producers give money to a Director, the Director tries to make a movie good enough so that people will pay enough money to the Director so the Director can repay the Producer. If the movie is given away for free then the Director and Producer don't get any of the money they deserve.   

There are more scenes of porn than full length movies available online. But porn operates the same way as Hollywood. Porn just has a smaller amount of money to earn to repay the Producer.  

TL;DR: Porn and Hollywood both use free scenes as marketing. It's just easier to masturbate to one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 05:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bipolar Type 2 here. My moods last for months with negative behavior (yelling, harsh words, etc) only coming after certain events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 05:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warm Bodies (which I was able to watch for free by borrowing it from my local library) was a decent movie. iZombie is a better concept. Which do you like more: sentient zombies that solve crimes or twilight zombie style? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For speed drafts be sure to use a sans serif font such as verdana or arial since you can read it faster (as we are conditioned to read sans serif in everyday life due to helvetica being the prominent display font on street signs, etc).

When editing a small section use a serifed font since it will cause you to stop and read a bit slower.  

Source: AA in Graphic Design </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wanna come over to my symphony hall for some jazz and chill? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Self-diagnosis (in competent hands) can do wonders...in fact it's how I learned I had Bipolar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neville might be the perfect pure heel right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold on! What font is that? It seems like a common times font...until those W's come into play. Is that the same font for VW? Is that some sort of Raleway font? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Face..then watch New Day merch fly through the roof!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Figured it's a good name for a variant of the Canadian Destroyer (made famous in TNA by Petey Williams). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too, and my SO to. Wtf? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a recovers alcoholic, but I was diagnosed as one (due to a bipolar Hypomanic episode). I was hooked up on a free cruise through some awesome luck on Reddit. I had a beer. Haven't had a drink since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 12:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say brother a lot, can't stop talking about my dream mania match, order the network, get disappointed with the show, cancel the network, watch classic five star be happen stuff for a year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My SO is casual and I'm a long time smark. The fact that her boy Reigns came in last, after suffering so much, made her pop. WWE knows what they're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call it the American Annihilator! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad life decisions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a writer I have to come up with characters all the time. 

I sometimes open a dictionary and discover new words then see how the sound without certain letters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just thinking about this. The Rumble is my least favorite gimmick match; my least favorite match style of all time. But this year I'm pretty excited to see what happens!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yeah! Final Deletion should be a match type if Matt goes back to WWE for a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What area of downtown was this?  

Also, why are the bikes not locked up? Even with other residents there I would lock my bike up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "She said it felt like the whole thing."  

-black tips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he were a Wild Samoan he would just pop it back in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fixing Jupiter Ascending </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Introduce Characters; establish their motives.

2. Have Mila Kunes' character not care about her family; change it to a Galactic Love story (Princess Bride in Space).  

3. Fire Mila Kunes and hire Emma Stone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The salmon and the couscous held up pretty well; I'd suggest eating it cold since it gets a "fishy" taste when reheated in the microwave. The salmon burgers held up well and the fishy taste is disguised by everything else mixed with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read it as Eric Clapton and looked at the photo for a solid minute =/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a tramp, he's a roooooad cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe you would post this! Here's how you really fix Space Jam: Make it R-Rated:  

Bugs Bunny and Lola have the hottest sex scene two animated rabbits in a Hollywood movie have ever had (and believe me I've seen lots!)  

The MonStarrs rip apart NBA players for their powers, limb from limb, sockets from sockets, tooth for tooth. They gain the powers and abilities. Their goal is to pillage and plunder every city on Earth, and procreate to make an army of Monstarrs. Only problem is, birthing a Monstarr is not easy for a human woman and most of them die.  

Michael Jordan, tired of watching the year long tyranny of the Monstarrs from his television, decides that he has to do something. He wields a baseball bat and a football as weapons because (in an earlier scene) when he tried to buy a gun, Edward Norton with a mustache wouldn't sell him one due to some racist antics.  

Bugs Bunny comes to the real world, along with his animated friends; they do weird shit for awhile until Porky Pigg is eaten alive by a Monstarr. The toons and Jordan happen to confront the Monstarrs at the same place and time. Jordan gets his ass handed to him, and Porky Pig dies protecting Jordan from a Monstarr attack. Porky is taken away by the Monstarrs while Bugs helps Jordan up. They exchange words and kisses, Michael Jordan professes to thinking Bugs looked good as a woman; they kiss some more (possible sex scene with all the Looney Toons reacting in character to the public display before them).  

Bo Jackson shows up at the next Monstarr confrontation, he has a basketball. Jackson and Jordan exchange balls so they can fight evil better. Shaq joins the fight and claims he has beaten the Big Show and knows Shaq Fu. The three sportstars team up with the Looney Toons. They destroy the Monstarrs with cool moves and funky beats. Their efforts thwart the invasion. The last scene Michael Jordan holds the remains of his fallen ball stars, he lets out a resounding "Noooooo" yell as Shaq and Bo Jackson (covered in the blood of their enemies) fist bump in the background.  

As transitional scenes, Bill Murray uses a golf club to mercilessly beat the life out of orange cats, he says traditional phrases heard during Saturday Morning Cartoons such as "After these messages," to being the beating; then "And now, back to the show," after he's removed the living breath from his victim. 

EDIT: Put a mustache on Edward Norton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I am Back Alley Brawler and we are **DOWNVOTE LESS!**" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally, a size that fits me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Salmon Burger: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tMVBlZECNNw  

Salmon Filet Advice: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jD9VJ92xyzA  

Honey Mustard Recipe (Raw, Vegan): https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KxYRsobLvnQ list=PLA-BsXd3JzPVbLbn8L2pR7DJnUtxhV0PJ  

Chicken: Salt, Pepper, tajin, broiled for 10-12 minutes.  

Pickled Salad: White Vinegar, Balsamic Vinegar; Sugar, Salt, Pepper, Onions, Heirloom Tomatoes; Combine, toss in the fridge covered until ready to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> salmon was featured this week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's one entry word for word (I write as soon as I wake up so sometimes it's not very cohesive...though usually funny):  

Sat, 02 April 2016  

I was moving to somewhere in Australia. My new friends and I were at embarass trying to find sea food. I was scared. He caught a crab then let it go back into the ocean. Before that he caught some minnows and put them back. I was wondering why he was letting them go back in. I realized it weeks be easy ttyl cook an ask crab meal. He traumatized me by scaring me with crabs. He thought it was funny. I lucid told him to stop because every time I was traumatized it dry me back 40 days. I die with an accent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [I Made] Salmon Burger with pickled salad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But...I just farted... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially since this is not a necessity, but it helps keep the homesick blues away. This is why a lot of wrestler, soldiers, etc drink. There's no place like home. To have something that you can sink your time into means you spend time thinking about where you are; not where you aren't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to watch the gif five times, head to the comments then watch the gif again to finally see the lad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's something so sexy about a woman in uniform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes sense! I was probably doing both or either of these things. It was right around the time I was studying Greek and Egyptian gods; and I write my dreams down when I wake up. Hell, I could publish some weird books about what's in my Awakening App journal! This is one I didn't write down; but remembered when I saw the photo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.thefreedictionary.com/za  

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zebra  

My most trusted resources on this project xD  ...and I know no one is going to look up Zorilla; but there's a fun meaning behind it and as it turns out, an appropriate name for a zebra ;)  Thank you for recognizing the effort xD xD xD Now I need to get back to writing my novel =P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually weight is an issue. The happiest people tend to be fit; generalizing but true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to meet women sooner rather than later, because they usually find me pretty cool irl; but my phone sucks and I can't get nudes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a kid, whenever a wrestler would leave the WWF I would just assume he had a heart attack xD  That's what happens when you don't have cable and only watch Superstars, Heat, Jacked, Shotgun Saturday Night and (thankfully) eventually Smackdown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either people or the books...perhaps both. I had a team with me and we were taking out another team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't memorize everything. Memorize chunks. The first series inside the ring. The spots outside of the ring; the first series in the ring upon re-entry; the second series in the ring, etc etc and so on.  

I like using this formula:  

Leave the house  

Go to the store  

Check out  

Go back home  

Prep the meal  

Mix the ingredients  

Cook the meal  

Serve the meal  

(sometimes) dessert

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a dream of that picture. I was in the library in that picture, in a blue flight suit, and I was defending something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Day 1: Being a zebra is hard; had to learn how to walk pretty quickly. Now for something to eat.  

Day2: Zane is being a dick. Then there's some new kid, cream color. I think I'll try to name him Latte.  

Day3: I got kicked in the face by Latte's...I mean Gertrude's mom. I hope my heart is okay. Then her mom said I should look in the mirror because I'm white and brown too.  

Year1: I left the harem today. Me and Zane are going to chill with some other Zeebs and get a bit stronger.  

Year2: All these girls are hooking up and I'm just focused on all this grass. #grassnotass

Year6: Challenged and won against Old Man Zorilla. Now the harm is mine  

Year6: Just fucked the shit out of Latte, finally! She should have my foal in less than a year!  Also fucked every other mare that was within mounting distance. My harem is nearly complete!  

Year6: I'm so thirsty. I just need a drink. My boy is going strong. He should leave pretty soon with the other guys, I don't want them around. Fuck I'm so thirsty. It's been super hot lately. Just a nice cool drink of water.  

Year7: We lost one of the new kids today. I'm not sure if it was Zax or Zerk; but a croc got him. We were crossing the water in what I thought was a low enough depth... Nothing to do but wish him a painless death. I hear the water splash whenever I close my eyes.  

Year8: My harem is strong. I'm not. I can sense some of my first borns edging in on my turf. My heart isn't what it used to be. Latte's kid keeps eyeing me for a couple of hours then going back to hang with the bachelors. I need to keep my strength up. I think I've got the lesions I've heard so many of my elders talk about whence in my youth. I can feel my bones weaken. It's time to go to the water hole one last time before Latte's kid, Za, that's his name, that's a good name. He'll make a fine leader. I'll get one last drink before our fight-- 
**HOLYSHITAFUCKINGCROCODILENOBODYTOLDMEABOUTTHISI'MDYINGI'MDYINGTELLLATTETHANKSFORTHEBONEOHSHITOHSHITI'MBEINGEATENALIVEARETHOSEMYBONESCRACKINGOHMYGODTHOSEAREMYBONES** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
