<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6969</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 04:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, just a little.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 03:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe would be in the Weasley's prank shop 24/7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 03:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who would Barb be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gathered as many behind the scenes photos I could find and made an imgur album of 100+ photos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 00:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so this is the song that will be stuck in my head today. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is quite apeeling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went into this thinking there was no way NPH would be better than Jim Carrey as Count Olaf, but I was dead fucking wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet they're still just as good a boy as before! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elvis in his Messerschmitt car (1956) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 22:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is cool but not having the tactile feeling of pushing the keys would really throw me off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit no answer! Reception in the bat-cave is terrible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe he's just really that ugly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll give you 24 septum for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 20:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is history being made right before our eyes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 20:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trees are so resilient! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 20:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Dawn of the Final Day](http://i.imgur.com/Z1kZ5rd.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The way the snow curls off this roof </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 19:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 17:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a privilege, the professor is an expert on that topic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 01:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done the technique used [here](https://vimeo.com/11447568#t=277s). It works really well for a quick sweeping shot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 00:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the ol' reddit [jerkaroo](https://www.reddit.com/r/Unexpected/comments/5nd1k0/flying_multicopters_is_an_outside_activity/dcb1a9x/?context=3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 00:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plasticore Board. First check out [TrekPak Dividers](http://trekpak.com/pelican-1510/), this is what you're going to make on your own. You can find plasticcore at art supply stores or sometimes home improvement stores, and cut it yourself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 00:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Murakami's new book is coming out soon. I can't wait! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 00:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Is that due to continental drift? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This kind of stuff is fascinating from a psychological side. I was on set once and the Production Designer was flipping through [this book](https://www.amazon.com/Color-Harmony-Compendium-Reference-Anniversary/dp/1592535909) that had hundreds of pages of every shade of color, paired with other shades of complimentary colors. [Example here](https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/41TFPWPV8VL.jpg)

 I picked one up myself and look through it every once in a while for inspiration. Highly recommend it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mandy.com is pretty good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's been research done to determine if biome/location an egg is picked up in has correlation to what is hatched, but it's inconclusive. Most likely it's completely random what you get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pissing off the Church has terrible side effects </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typos are never small issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd take a guess and say 400mm, wider if it's cropped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great video, thanks for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome colors! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember those cross-section books full of the insides and workings of all Star Wars vehicles? Here's an imgur album full of 100+ of them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone should make one of these for the mountainsides of Skyrim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which Beachtek are you using? The DSLR version should work fine with that setup! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Credit to u/battleship_hussar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember those cross-section books that showed the insides and working of all Star Wars vehicles? Here's an entire imgur album of them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL of the Pana-Wave Laboratory, a Japanese cult who attempted to capture a famous Arctic seal they claimed had been led astray by electromagnetic waves, in order to avert doomsday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had great results from [CastingNetworks](http://home.castingnetworks.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Studio Ghibli consistently puts out gorgeous images </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Queen's "39" is a great ballad about astronauts who go into space thinking they are on a one year voyage, but when they make it home discover 100 years has passed instead and all their loved ones are now dead.

For the earth is old and grey, little darling we'll away

But my love this cannot be

For so many years have gone though I'm older but a year

Your mother's eyes from your eyes cry to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they meet up every once in a while and grab a hotdog and just catch up and talk casually  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might be because the edges are [just black](http://evanerichards.com/wp-content/gallery/grandbudapest/GrandBudapest077.jpg), although I do think shots lose a large amount of their meaning when the aspect ratio is messed with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Duzi is awesome. I've been using Duzis since the Version 2, and the 4 is the smoothest slider I've used (other than the Dana Dolly). The flywheel is great when I'm doing slower shots and I need the momentum and slow stopping power the wheel gives. When I don't want all that I can unscrew the flywheel underneath and the slider feels entirely open, which is great for faster shots.

What the Edelkrone has over the Duzi is travel size. If that doesn't matter to you, I highly recommend the Duzi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What led to you receiving this? Looks great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I switch around from Canon to Sony depending on what the job requires, and I usually will shot Cine4, and then go into the matrix/color settings and tweak towards red/orange to get closer to the Canon look. I find that without color correcting, even with my tweaks its really hard to get an identical looking color as the Canon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which camera are you using?

And which monitor are you asking about, no link is in your post! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I was discouraged at the thought of a fake ad, but the data is really interesting. I wish there was more to be honest! This kind of data wrangling is really up my alley </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats not normal. The pan knob (bottom center of head on the operator's side) should completely lock the head from panning when tightened. What legs are you using (or slider/crane, etc), and/or are you using a half bowl adapter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might be tough at Zion right now as the trams (which drive you to each trail and monument from the visitor centers) are shut down for winter. You'll need a vehicle to get to most of the attractions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oof no. Generally you'll never need to power up attackers since they have a huge advantage in gym battles. Save your candies for a good defense moveset Snorlax.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rhino from James and the Giant Peach is approaching </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Andywilson92*

Good times! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome story and photo!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That's no moon! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 04:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sincerely hope your 2017 is everything you want it to be. I know exactly where you're coming from, as most of my family members on my mothers side broke ties with my mother and consequently me and my brother. I havent been able to contact them for years, one because I don't know where they are now, and two because I'm afraid of how my mother will react if I do reach out to them. 

My brother has autism and him being one of only two family members from my moms side I have contact with he means a great deal to me. These Star Wars books were one of the few things we had a great time talking about. He loved the diagrams. 

Have a great rest of your night, thank YOU for sharing your story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember this from a Star Wars book years ago. There were a couple of these with diagrams on everything, even the Cantina and of course all the vehicles. Great detail throughout! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars - Jawa Sandcrawler [1600x1044] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gotta pay the frost troll toll if you want to get into this nordsoul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Around the 10 second mark during the 180fps shot there looks to be a ton of aliasing going on in the white parts of the building. Hopefully this isn't normal for the sensor, although I do remember hearing the the GH5 doesn't have an OLPF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd argue that Canon's Dual Pixel Auto Focus is the best auto focus out there right now (for photography as well as video). It's incredible quick and spot on when using Canon lenses with autofocus. Even for video, using it on the C300mk 2 is a breeze.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine would be [Strawberry Meadow](http://i.imgur.com/T7v8ItK.jpg) through Strawberry Peak. I love the San Gabriel trails </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm sorry I wasnt a good enough boy!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favorite socal hike of 2016? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to hear some stories or see pics from your favorite hikes of last year in our beautiful part of the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one in New York is the Mark Twain tree, now called Big Stump where it used to live. [Here](http://i.imgur.com/7td1gxa.jpg) is a picture of it being cut down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 08:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tommy Wiseau's [The Room](https://youtube.com/watch?v=1Gqv2bOp7xI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 07:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me a money needing a lot now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4k? I don't believe the Ninja Flame accepts 4k 60p, only up to 30p (60p and 120p in 1080 however)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thelma and Louise (1991) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Portfolio. Amazing work is never going to be brushed aside simply because the person doesn't have a degree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love operating because I feel like I've physically contributed to a film, and is a good mix of the art and vision of a project with the skill necessary to execute that vision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you've got any of the LED line (Celeb, Diva-lite 20 or 30, Select 20 or 30), Kino makes a [V-Mount battery adapter to 3 pin for power](http://www.kinoflo.com/Products%20Button/LED/Battery/Battery.html).

Otherwise you'd be looking at an inverter/car battery adapter setup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty cool that the places in the video were added as map links in the video description. Thanks for that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Benro has really been killing it in the lower end tripod area! I'm a big fan of their BV series as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With your camera setup it should be fine. And yea you're right, the head on the Benro screws right off!

The plastic is in the knobs, they really feel like they'll break in a year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wooden Camera makes a really nice one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've used both, here's my input:

**Benro Aero 4**

*Pros*

-Better head for video

-One of the legs transforms the tripod into a monopod

*Cons*

-Lots of plastic on the legs

-Can't take head off and switch it out

____________________________________________________________________

**Manfrotto Befree**

*Pros*

-2 lbs lighter than the Benro

-Better leg locking mechanism

-Better tripod bag included

-Can take head off and switch it

*Cons*

-No free monopod

-Head isn't as good for video

_________________________________________________________________

Overall, I love the compact feeling of the Befree, and the leg locking mechanism is cool, but I did find that it would malfunction every once in a while. While the Benro has a lot of plastic, it worked a bit better because of the more traditional knobs. Both have a 8-9lb load capacity, but I wouldn't put anything larger than a dslr with medium or small lens on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Storm causes Sequoia's tunnel tree to fall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This pisses me off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 20:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really love the way the light is reflecting off his helmet. Awesome work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are ALL temporary on this blessed day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Double-Double with cheese, fries, and a chocolate shake.

My mouth is watering just thinking about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 17:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [website here](http://www.throwingrocks.co.uk/)

It's a personalized poster printer. They mention Linda on their [Twitter](http://www.twitter.com/throwingrocksuk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 02:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can use a color temperature's Mired Value and Shift to determine what gel would be best to get to a specific color temp. There are calculators out there that will do all the conversions for you, such as [this one from Lee](http://www.leefilters.com/lighting/mired-shift-calculator.html) or you can print out [this one](https://www.stagespot.com/downloads/Lee_Conversion_Chart.pdf) and draw a line between two temperatures.

To be specific, the mired shift equation is 

(1000000/C1) - (1000000/C2) = Mired Shift

Where C1 is the color temperature you are starting with and C2 is the color temperature you're trying to get to. Use the Mired Shift value to determine what gel to use (the value can be negative as well) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 02:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Canon Vixia hf r700 does not have phantom power unfortunately 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 02:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately your camera does not provide phantom power, and because of that only mics which can be powered off a battery will work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 01:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> second menu from the left, looks like a gear  Page 6  APS-C/ Super 35mm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 01:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Small Oval 6011 (Large Oval 6012 if you have the glasses version) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angleplateception! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. Reading through your AMA on the project, sweet stuff! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay hydrated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't be a problem. 

Upside is you can take the head off, throw a slider on the flat base, and then the head on the slider as well if you ever need to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard good things from the Surface Books, as well as the ASUS Zenbooks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Audio Recorder, like a Zoom H4/5/6 or F4/8. You'll notice a huge boost in quality when you record to a recorder versus into a DSLR itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot agree more. This is an awesome ring light, and the magnetic gels are great. Make sure to get the "milk diffusion" filter as well as the Power Adapter to be able to plug it into the wall.

And for those using it on rails, the rail adapter is an additional piece, learned that the hard way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Night to Remember is hilarious, and I love how there are different ways of completing it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 07:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Placebo effect or not, you feel better. And thats awesome. Hope you have a great 2017. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Russia With Love (1963) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lynda.com is pretty great considering you can get the whole site free with a lot of public library cards/university accounts.

Masterclasses are awesome and if you can make them go for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 22:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible for you to rent before buying? Especially if you're going to be using it a lot, renting a camera before purchase to make sure it fits your style of shooting best is always the way to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 21:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might like [A Shot in the Dark](https://www.amazon.com/Shot-Dark-Creative-Digital-Lighting/dp/143545863X), it has some pretty cool DIY rigs, like the infamous [covered wagon](http://filmmakeriq.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/DV101_0311_Main_Finished.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure! Lenses are either manual (no electronics in them, you change focus and aperture manually and physically on the lens itself) or electronic (electronics inside the lens connect to your camera mount, and allow for auto focus, aperture change, even exif data display from the camera).

With a lens adapter that allows electronic control you would retain all or some of the features listed above from electronic lenses. With a lens adapter that does not have electronic control you will not get those features.

One thing to note is if you are using a lens that can only have it's aperture changed electronically, using a lens adapter without electronic control is going to not allow you to change aperture, unless you put the lens on a native camera, change the aperture on it, and move back to the adapted camera </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's just boys being boys" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Time Machine" from H.G. Wells has this! It's done really well and worth a read </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's absolutely edited in photoshop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's photoshopped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The camera is photoshopped out in post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Konami at e3 2010](https://youtu.be/f6OCnvvkSLM) pairs really nicely with Sony 2006 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. The a6300 is E-Mount, not MFT, the same adapter won't work, unfortunately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metabones makes [one](http://www.metabones.com/products/details/mb_ef-m43-bt2) that works for both EF and EF-S with electronic control. Auto focus is going to be slower than on a Canon body.

If you don't need electronic control there's some cheaper ones out there from Vello that will work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's such a good boy, he's really out of this world! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally we can end the debate of over the top or under the roll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You too" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you working an hourly wage, went to high school but didn't do great? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 12:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His new years resolution is to take people on happy adventures! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 12:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great game. The sequels are a bit underwhelming but this one was a lot of fun. The dialogue gives off a good Mark Watney feel (The Martian)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 06:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I nearly had a heart attack. Thank you based Carter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 05:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I know lots of shows shooting on Canon, specifically C300's. The LA Kings just switched over to a C300ii system </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the ol' reddit [pickleroo](https://www.reddit.com/r/BoJackHorseman/comments/5ls3vt/an_ass_cancer_sunset_must_be_an_original_sarah/dbykcig/?context=3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your preference for securing your camera in the bag? On it's side, standing up with the handle on, standing up without the handle on? 

For on it's side, Cinebags are really great. The [CB35](http://www.cinebags.com/cb35-stryker-tcv) (or [CB40](http://www.cinebags.com/cb40-high-roller) if you want wheels and a trolley system) has tons of room and pockets **everywhere.** USA made, great warranty, zippers are top notch. 

For standing up with the handle on, you'll be able to fit it into one of the new taller Manfrotto [195N bags](https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1257832-REG/manfrotto_mb_pl_cc_195n_pro_light_camcorder_case.html) or the [192N bag](https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1257833-REG/manfrotto_mb_pl_cc_192n_pro_light_camcorder_case.html). The 195N has more room for accessories though. Manfrotto has good warranties and these are well pretty well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Mountaineer is fantastic for hiking and travel. I love my 0 version. I've used Manfrotto and Benro travel tripods as well, and they don't compare with the quality of the Gitzo. 

Of course for production work where I don't need to hike 7 miles to get to or in studio I prefer a 1030 OConnor, but for travel it's a much different story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 22:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it still under warranty? Manfrotto has different warranty tiers depending on what model kit/legs it is.

If not, try and find a tripod repair/parts place. If you're in the L.A. area, [Transylvannia Film](http://www.transfilm.com/) is fantastic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 22:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! Done in post. Such a great show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 22:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have to agree here. There's a reason it has been one of the most rented out cameras for years. Pop a lens on, a battery in, and a memory card in and go. It just works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 22:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really love shooting with the C300mkii. Clog is great, and colors (especially skin tones) really pop in post (even straight out of the camera with the right profile and tweaking in camera they're great). 

It has the best video auto-focus in any camera. I scoffed at the notion of using auto focus for video at first but the DPAF on the mkii (and to a lesser extent on the c300 mk i) is incredibly versatile, easy to use, and dead on accurate. 

EF or PL, Canon (or you) can change out the mount if you decide down the road to switch to the other. 

In any case, definitely rent before buying any camera system. Make sure it works for your specific needs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of my pans were slow for that series so I didnt have any issues. Definitely get a ball setup if you plan on moving the head a lot. The 535 CF legs from Manfrotto are amazing, but will take most of your budget for just the legs, but do sport a ball </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the chance to test out Manfrotto's Befree live as well as Gitzo's Mountaineer 0 out in the mountains. I had a Benro s6 head on the Gitzo for fluid panning/tilting. The Gitzo blew away the Manfrotto. The Befree has so much plastic on it compared to the Gitzo, and everything about the Hitzo was buttery smooth and rigid. 

The one thing I like about the Befree is the leg locking mechanism, however it started malfunctioning after a fee uses and one leg would come loose and slide down. 

For reference, this was for a series of landscape videos and photos in the mountains, which is why I anted to try the lighter options, both were incredible easy to hike with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 16:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the most fascinating parts of this area is here you have fields of the largest trees in the world, large meadows, lakes, animals of all kinds, etc, and then directly to the east, over a small hump of mountain range is Death Valley, where there's *nothing* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 16:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how incredibly *soft* their bark is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 18:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cue the [Benny Hill theme song](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=MK6TXMsvgQg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 18:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oof, here's [Garland in her 40s](http://www.oocities.org/%7Ethemistyone/images/JGARLAND.JPG). Poor, poor girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the ol' reddit [europearoo](https://www.reddit.com/r/gifs/comments/5kre5f/forget_a_dog_i_want_this_guy_gaurding_my_house/dbqdjzh/?context=2) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how are supplies acquired for living there?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Anyone who lives or has been to a Nudist colony, what are common etiquettes or guidelines that are followed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 01:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are ALL gifv's on this blessed day :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. I think the problem was everyone thought they would be valuable and saturated the market. Even the "special" ones like the Princess Diana beanie baby are worthless now. The ones that are worth something are those with tag errors or ones manufactured at a very limited amount.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone remember error Beanie Babies? Theyre just about the only Beanie Babies worth anything nowadays, but they go for thousands on eBay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 20:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a Panasonic NV-MC30, Japanese model. You can download the camera manual in English [here](http://www.instructionsmanuals.com/modelo-4794-en-Camcorders.htm#.WF2CCn3e1e0), or view it directly [here](http://www.instructionsmanuals.com/u2/pdf/camara_video/Panasonic-NVMC30-en.pdf).

Battery type is Ni-MH, 9.6V. You can find batteries all over ebay, but no power adapters unfortunately.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 07:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mimikyu really tears through the Battle Tree. I'm using Focus Sash on mine and Mega Garchomp instead of Salamence and the only difficulty comes from levels 41-50 when more legendaries show up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: If you have a Los Angeles Public Library Card you can access Lynda.com for free </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 01:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who haven't used Lynda.com, it's full of a giant amount of camera and editing tutorials.

Simply having a LA library card (completely free) lets you access lynda.com in all it's glory *remotely*!

And if you can't make your way to an LA Public library location, you can [sign up for one online](https://www.lapl.org/about-lapl/contact-us/e-card/e-card-registration) (has limited access when reserving real books, but looks to include online resources, including lynda.com). 

If you've already got an LA Library Card, here's a [direct link to get access](https://www.lynda.com/portal/sip?org=lapl.org)!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 00:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, it's fantastic! Link [here](https://www.lapl.org/collections-resources/articles-and-information/lyndacom) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the first generation of Metabones were a bit wonky, and are much, much better now. If you have the option to buy and return if it doesn't work that may be the best route. If not and it's a buy and no return thing, you might want to splurge and go for one of the newer models.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely another vote for the C100mkII from me (with external recorder). Really easy camera to use, built in everything that you've been missing or had to build onto to the GH4, and a really great color science especially if you're shooting people or nature. 

Also, if you head down the LS-300 route, rent it before buying (in fact rent any camera before buying). The specs are decent but usability is really difficult. The menu system is convoluted, the colors that come out of the camera need grading, and the m43 lens options are slim. Even with a EF Metabones you'll have a lot of difficulty utilizing the zoom rocker or focusing correctly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's that model: [Nikon G - M43](http://www.metabones.com/products/details/MB_SPNFG-m43-BM1)

Looks to be an older model of the one linked above, most likely a 0.71x magnification </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking the C100 mk 1. It's still an awesome camera being used, especially with an external recorder. But if 4k and more frame rate options are something you'll definitely need, I think the UX180 will work for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To answer one of your questions:

DSLRs can only record for a short time period because of certain classifications put forth due to import tax, see [this article](http://www.tested.com/tech/photography/44445-why-digital-cameras-have-a-30-minute-video-recording-limit/) explaining it. However you can get around that by hooking your camera up to an external recorder and recording to that instead (for example, the Atomos Shogun). Even then you may run into overheating issues which will shut the camera off. 


As for a recommendation, definitely take a look at Sony's PXW-X70. It's a small camcorder that will shoot for as long as your card holds (a 128gb SD card holds around 4-5 hours of 1080p, or 40 minutes of 4k), and there's two card slots, which you can set to either record the same thing twice onto both cards (as a backup), or record to one card and then to the second if the first fills up. 

It's better in low light than a lot of camcorders out there, because it's got a 1" Cmos sensor (same size as most DSLRs), and it has a really nice Zeiss lens attached with a pretty decent zoom throw (nothing crazy long).

It comes out of the box as a 1080p camera for $2000, however you can purchase a 4k license (firmware download) for the camera to upgrade it to 4k for $500. 

It's as easy to use as any other Sony camcorder, has actual XLR jacks for good audio in, and has both manual and automatic functions (including focus, white balance, and exposure) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
