<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6914</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 13:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A similar study in 2015 by Dr. Sarah Ellis showed that even when the cat belonged to the participant, only four out of 10 humans could correctly identify the context of the different meows. And no one performed better than random chance when classifying meows of unfamiliar cats.

And another study has the rate at only 34%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL people are only about 40% accurate at identifying the meaning of a cat's meow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 13:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 15:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scholars have connected elements of the Lord of the Rings with Tolkien's experience: https://theconversation.com/for-another-view-of-world-war-i-look-to-lord-of-the-rings-24378 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exoskeletons are starting to be used in physical therapy and rehab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 15:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 15:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Outside the Box Festival This Week Provides A Global Perspective On Boston Common </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 12:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 12:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In fact, studies show that when older people reside with others their age, they have more fulfilled and enjoyable lives. They do not feel stigmatized when they practice retirement-oriented lifestyles. Even the most introverted or socially inactive older adults feel less alone and isolated when surrounded with friendly, sympathetic, and helpful neighbors with shared lifestyles, experiences, and values  and yes, who offer them opportunities for intimacy and an active sex life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
