<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2527</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try Earl Grey. I subtituded coffee with Earl Grey with milk, even thought black dark roast coffee is way better, Earl Grey is easier on the stomach and it has tannins or some shit that is supposed to reduce the amount of water in your stool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, you know, *you seeing this shit* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yes, Yes... Indeed.. It would seem like this is a dog" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's saying he got pants on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 10:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a song that has one note in the middle of the song *exactly* like my alarm. So eveytime I hear it in the middle of a song my heart skips a beat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be happy with the result! It would probably take me more than 5 hours to make something like this. 

There is always someone better than you at everything but there is also some worse than you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never really liked Micheal so him leaving didn't really bother me that much. For some reason his personality was very off-putting to me in episodes like the yankee swap episode, but I guess that was the point. 

But they did his leave very well "this is gonna hurt like a bitch" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same when I was trying to teach my brother to use Photoshop. Or any other adobe programs. I had to really focus on not using shortcuts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, A for effort </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You dont always need to cut zip locks. You can use tip of of box cutters to open the "lock" that keeps it in place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 07:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I see that "Copy this to your wall and facebook can't use your content without your permission" I just want to link the Facebook Terms and Agreements in the comments and say read this and see what you already have given facebook permission to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually really clever bot. Goes around reddits spam filters by making a self post and using imgur link with link to the website inside instead of linking straight to the website which would be easier to detect by automods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best thing about Premiere Pro is how well it pairs up with rest of the adobe CC. No issues making some graphics in Illustrator or animation in After Effects and just throwing them in Premiere. 

God I love adobe CC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 07:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I too love coffee to the death but unfortunately had to stop drinking. I sometimes drink a cup with milk on good days but when my ibs-d started I had to go from 5-8 cups of black coffee to zero. 

Also dark roasted coffee is more friendly to the stomach than light/regular so you might give that a try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first thought was that where are the rest 5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably. I find it weird that people have crush on Ciri in the games since in the books she is a kid and Geralt's foster daughter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 09:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From books or game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 08:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, share and comment "898" to watch the magic happen!!

How stupid you need to be to think that something actually happens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had pretty good experiences with the support so far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 13:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely *love* ESO. Been playing for 2 years. I dont know why they haven't made new LOTR mmo already, that would be awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it is very fun game if you don't look for very deep story or immersive experience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your favourite post-apocalyptic shooter that is not Fallout? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be good for op since he said he doesn't care for story. Because the thing that pushed me off from Kingdoms of Amalur was that the story and world were pretty meh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 11:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it depends on where you are from. The netflix shows aren't same in every country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 11:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont mind this. My playlists are 200 tracks tops and they are all good music. This is why I make a lot of playilists with different genres and moods etc. so I can get more individual tracks when I feel like listening to certain type of music </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 07:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be called 1994-2014 (20 years of elder scrolls would sound better anyway)

They probably put 2017 in there as clickbait so people would think there is new footage released </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I didn't know that you can paste images to imgur </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 19:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if you dont want to screencap the whole window but crop certain part of it. Thats why I prefer paint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prtn scrn

Open paint

Ctrl+V

Crop

Save as jpeg or png

Done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually ESO doesn't really have any class restrictions on gear or stats/role either so thats good to hear. I've been playing the game already like you said, just exploring and stuff. I was just wondering about these things on longer run </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 16:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Druid is specialization of Ranger right? I'm mainly asking because I might be interested in healing/playing healer so I dont want to level a character that can't be a healer. Also I already have lvl 12 elementalist from when I tried this game out a year ago  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people not responding to others, people leaving dungeons

This is true. I've played this game fairly actively for 2 years and the game got ALOT better once I joined my current, active PvE guild where there are the usual people I often raid with.

But I really enjoy the game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been playing for 2 years now and yes, it very much is. Main reason I bought some of the dlc's was that they added new group dungeons and trials which I love to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 13:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm laughing out loud at the waiting room of a hospital. People probably think I came in because of mental issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 11:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always get those two mixed up. I always thought the Skellige was scottish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 09:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the books before playing 2 and 3 and I can say that you will get more out of Witcher 3 if you have read the books. It references them much more than Witcher 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was so dissapointed that they cut her out on the games. I guess they thought it would be hard to explain why Emhyr wanted [Spoilers](/s "to marry his daughter") without going deep into the events of the books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What /u/ArkBirdFTW said is very true, but Skyrim is still amazing game and does some things better than Witcher 3. Skyrim is much more free game, you don't need to worry about playing too much ahead in main quest that you miss some side quests. Also Skyrim has much better RP in my opinion. The replay value is better because you can play in different playstyles. You can choose to play a heroic dragonborn and save the world or you can play a thief and steal everything that isn't nailed down. Also with mods you can play just a simple wanderer, hunting and fishing and selling goods if thats your cup of tea

I love both games alot. They both have their strong areas and weak areas. One big difference is that Skyrim is high fantasy and Witcher aims for more realistic. Both games have great lore, but Witcher has much better writing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, wait till you finish the series, so many amazing moments ahead. Especially a scene where [Minor Spoiler](/s "Geralt and Yen are having sex after Geralt said I love you to her for the first time and after Yen is reading Geralts mind and Geralt starts thinking about things that would make Yen happy. He accidentaly thinks about dream about him and Yen living quiet life in a cabin in the woods that Geralt has build himself, with Ciri, who is basicly a child to Geralt and Yen, visiting them time to time") I always found that scene to show what their relationship truly is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to come by similiar rough humour and great writing. A Song of Ice and Fire has similiar aspects but Witcher series is definetly more high fantasy than ASOIAF. 

I enjoy the LOTR books as bit of a counterweight to witcher series. While Witcher had this kinda dark, real life mixed with high fantasy feel, the LOTR has more lighthearted fantasy.

I think the Witcher books are unique. Simply because the characters are so amazing and the dialoque is very well written. Witcher is definetly one of my all time favorite series. I'm suprised how few game fans in this sub has read them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outstanding work! That Yen looks kinda WIP because her face has less texture than Geralt or Ciri. But I guess it might be just the lighting in the photo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Udalryk*

*Udalryk*

*Udalryk*

*Udalryk*

*Udalryk*

*Udalryk*

*Udalryk*

*Udalryk*

*Udalryk*

That one fucking name was stuck in my head for ages. Cerys saying it in her Skellige accent sounded so great and it was like earworm. I love the accent tho. Sounds kinda like ~~scottish~~ Irish accent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why you do this to us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, its not bad if you have found a actress your own age attractive. I mean you probably did found some of your 15 year old friends attractive when you were 15? 

But when there are bunch of old dudes masturbating over young girls, thats when it gets reeeally creepy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time I visited a celebrity specific sub (i think it was an actress, may have been an artist) I was linked from another subreddit about her newest movie/album/whatever and thought there might be some interesting discussion there. The sub was so damn creepy. The amount of people posting pictures and then creepy comments is so weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 07:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knowing 9gag, that person probably has a phd and md in audiology and headphone engineering. And also is a mathematician on his freetime.

I thought that everyone was expert on everything in reddit, but holy crap the amount of experts that go to 9gag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 07:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC Snowden can't request clemency because he hasn't had a trial in the United States. But I'm no lawyer so dont quote me on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm done for I'm afraid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Even Georgia Moffett (who played Jenny) said that she would be interested in reappearing in the show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moffat does this. I remember an interview about on Doctor Who character that people were hoping to make a reappearance on the show. When Moffat was asked about her, he just said "She won't be seen in the show again, she crashed her spaceship on a moon on her first flight" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 07:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually stopped the game after 8 hours because of this. I was at the same spot as OP's girlfriend (and the same class) and I kept dying and losing my souls and once I just stopped playing out of fristration. Have tried to get into it few times after that but never really got into it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why was this whole Sherlock and Watson are gay such a big theory? I mean they have joked about it in the show but there is a shitstorm in twitter about this whole thing. I mean people are legit mad.

I kinda feel like people wanted them to be gay just for the sake of it. Not because it would have added something to their story or character. I have nothing against a series where Sherlock and Watson are a gay couple, but I dont think it would have made much sense here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title reads like her brother just one upped their dad

"Oh yeah dad, you're gonna die right before the wedding to make everyone cry? Well I'm gonna make them cry even more with my song! Take that da!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brooklyn nine-nine, one of my all time favorite comedy shows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 19:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/design_critiques  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 17:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definetly. It takes huge amount of physical and mental training to be a witcher plus the mutations and living in seclusion. But I doubt it would be much of a dreamjob in the witcher universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 15:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the official app might work better on iOS than Android. On android sometimes when playing wider gifs it would cut the sides </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 15:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Works fine on Reddit is fun. I stopped using the official app because the gifs loaded so slow (if at all) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 10:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Artist most likely painted the original picture in Photoshop (digital painting) and then animated it in After Effects </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 18:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless they are some sort of european larch tree, which has needles that turn yellow/orange in the fall (not that red though, and I guess shape is a bit off for a larch)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 20 and was recently diagnosed with pretty bad IBS a year ago. It has been hell, it kinda controlls my life (makes my job harder and social encounters can be difficult) but I have been pretty open about it from the start. All my friends know that I have it. The only reason I have been able to cope is that I can joke about it. Especially with my siblings who understand what I'm going trough.

Thank god I'm able to laugh to myself, even thought it can be really embarassing to just do an Irish exit from social situations because I get explosive diarreah. I still feel really bad about it to the point where I could cry. I know how you feel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The word "pee" followed by "ste" like the word "dre" in dr. dre but with st </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Witcher and the Elder Scrolls games are great for loosing yourself in and forgetting about the worries of the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NV=Fallout New Vegas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Piste is also finnish (means dot) and pronounced like its ~~said~~ written </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 07:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually enjoyed the movies. Sure they are not as good as LOTR or absolutely true to the book, but they were still a fun watch.

And the bts is great watch. You see how Peter Jackson really struggled to get these movies out and Sir Ian McKellen kept a copy of the book in the pocket of his costume so he could make suggestions about making the movie more like the book.

Thing I most hate about these movies is that they were filmed infront of a greenscreen while LOTR had this amazing scenery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's not just any spicy food, Carolina Reaper is one of the hottest peppers out there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MYSTERIOUS WAL-MART BEAUTY

"Walks away" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breaking Bard. Breaking bad but with swords and knights (and a bard ofc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "MICHAEL!"

"..."

"... Oh right, the poison" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In books scoia'tael is just a trick created and funded by Emhyr to bring chaos to northern empire. The young elves and dwarves think they are fighting for freedom but in reality they are just pieces in Emhyrs plan and dying for nothing

This is why I didn't have much love for the Scoia'tael when playing Witcher 2 second time. Iorveth and Saskia are great characters though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 10:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should visit a local shop that does advertisement printings and tapings. I used to work in a place like that and we did sell some that type of tape.

Also this way you dont buy too dark one or too little tape to cover your window </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 10:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I guess Morrowind would be better example since it was more story driven </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 07:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://media.giphy.com/media/JWZmzj1KNzZBu/giphy.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the first book it is said that the Dursleys hate anything that is not ordinary so they probably would have thought fantasy books as waste of time. 

Also it would have given Harry some bad influences about magic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn you're ugly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks like Neil Patrick Harris to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is actually really nice person. I really like his Twitter feed where he retweets and often compliments other people's tries  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they do add a certain type of gravity to your actions, but they can be a bit annoying if you're a completionist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I also grew up playing games on NES, SNES and N64. Still, I dont have so much time these days to play the games so I prefer doing as much as I can in one playtrough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 07:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if its from tutorial, they can get usefull tips to improve it beyond the tutorial and learn something new from it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 05:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I most likely will play again. But with full time job and limited free time I always try to get as much as I can out of these kinds of massive games on my first playtrought </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else hate when games have point of no return? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing Witcher 3 (big fan of the books, love the game) and I keep stressing about reaching a point of no return and missing out on side quests. The main quest is amazing and I'm interested playing it but at the same time I want to complete side quests. 

I've had this in other games too. I kinda don't want to leave from the mainquest to spend hours around chasing chickens while world is in danger (or in witchers case, closest thing I have of daughter). It feels like stopping book in the middle.

This is one thing I liked about Skyrim. No quests automaticly failed after completing main questline.

Anyone else get overwhelmed like this? Whats your solution to this problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I can finish the ugly baby? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing I asked now then. Gonna let Yen wait a bit and go out to the world and do side quests. See ya next winter Yen!

So am I actually close to completing the main quest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I dont need to do minor quests like contracts and such which I can do after main quest but should do bigger side quests like Deadly Plot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moment she said her name means "Eastwind" I got instant goosebumps. And the fact that she confirmed it then moments later just made me more amazed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 09:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just love the puns and the sarcastic humour in this game. Tickles my funnybone just right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 20:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait to play it. Need to play the base game and HoS first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 19:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC 15 or 17 for the feline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Then you're going to love this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T3DP6gldKTA) -- Minor "Last Wish" quest spoiler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feline armor and Griffin gloves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 16:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Cahir wasn't a nilfgaardian* (as he kept saying, he's from Vicovaro) but I see your point. But when talking about Nilfgaardian empire, I dont think Geralt would be much of a wanted quest, especially in the eyes of Emhyr since the last time Geralt and Emhyr met (before the game), Emhyr left Yen and Geralt to kill themselves in a bath tub.

The game Nilfgaard differs alot from the books, they potrayed it kinda badly in games imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nameless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was doing the quest where you go to the garden to search for the dude who helped out Ciri. There you go down to search for marks left by him or the beast and Yen stays up on top of the stairs. Once you find a body in the bushes (not the dude you were looking for) Yen shouts that she can't hear you. Then you can go to the stairs and chat with her about the beast and what you have found so far.

"To transform into a werewolf... It's a dog's life, eh?" is one of the dialogue options </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] As if these two weren't meant together </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 14:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 11:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giving illegal substances to children. You monster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have imagined it would have already translated in english since it is such  a common languange </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is it released on march? It was first publiced in 1999 and translations started coming last spring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. And little more than marry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
