<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4485</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> late Q2 according to another comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> depends on the rest of your stuff. gpu and cpu. and how much overclocking you do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was Chemical attacks last year  too

and this: Very NSFW (Dead people) https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3hSMr6QzCjA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how fast can you really go in new york anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hvis du giver blomster hver dag, s tror de bare vi er dem utro!

sandheden er jo at vi godt kan lige de herlige svenskere, selvom vi driller dem - bl.a. her p reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR

I HAVE A BOYFRIEND </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It needs to be much thicker

for battery life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> imgur link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i used to work as a cashier.. and no. i don't care. why wouldn't you judge us for selling it, if we'd judge you for buying it?

i'd rather you'd leave quickly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'd be equally as happy as the girl. get that thing away from me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the danish queen and her husbond (he's not king for some reason) don't sleep in the same bedroom either. and when they are on trips they have their own hotel rooms. i dont think it was like this always, but for the past years.. not sure when it started. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tried another cable?

another video source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. or non 3rd person RPGs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! it makes sense - somewhat (Weird symbol to use though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But i dont want flowers, cards or gifts ... I just want a hug! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not 100% sure what roaming is... english networking terms dont always translate well into my language. 

but there's wifi data and regular cellular data. i mean cellular data :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Galaxy S7 Edge, Nougat] What is this symbol next to my clock, signal strength and such? how to remove it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys! i have a little symbol in the top of my screen next to my bluetooth, wifi and what-not. and i have no idea what it is.

I have disabled various things such as sync, bluelight filter, and such. it's still there.

http://imgur.com/a/I4Ysc - it's the circle with a + inside.

Any idea what it is, and how i can disable it?

It looks sorta like it could be 33% done with something? but it's been like this since it appeared shortly after i updated to nougat.

any suggestions are greatly appreciated.

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My samsung (S7 edge) has Sidesync software i can download. it basically mirrors my android screen on windows, allowing me to send texts, and basically use my phone with my mouse. it works alright... works through local wifi or usb, but not "roaming" unfortunately. also im pretty sure it requires you to have a samsung phone. 

i can imagine there are similar non-samsung apps and software that can do it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> snok? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> corrected*

this video is so old its in 4:3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also another angle  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All 3 of those are translated into "Troldmand" in danish

Yes... Troll man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard good things about gaming on ryzen as well.. the smoothness. fewer drops in framerate and such. I have a 6600K currently and i feel like i've somewhat wasted my money getting that chip. (I upgraded from a i5 2500K)

i do gaming and some (not a whole lot) of video editing. I have considered getting a 1700. Though because of money, i am considering just waiting a year or whatever, for "Zen 2" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Det er simpelthen for groft... alts en kat kan snildt d af fx blive pkrt af en cykel, knallert, bil eller lign. Men... det der er helt 100% bevidst dyremishandling. Personen/personerne som str bag har nogen voldsomme psykiske problemer de burde f noget hjlp til... 

Hber snart de fr gjort noget i de der ghettoomrder... synes det bliver vrre og vrre :/

mske riv alle undtagen en blok ned og spred folket ud over hele landet istedet for at pak dem ind i ttte omrder .. er det ikke en potentiel (men ja, meget dyr) lsning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ja, du m undskylde jeg kom til at rive hovedet og et par ben af den her kat, men det var alts en fejl"

den var kun get som politikker..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Det er jo underordnet hvad folk "mener"..

vi har en lov, og dyremishandling i den grad der er direkte ulovligt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eftersom der er s mange problemer i vollsmose, tnker jeg faktisk at folk slet ikke opdrager deres brn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark souls combat is so good, i cant stand the witcher 3's combat :(

It's really annoying, as i like the world, story telling etc. in witcher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's like bloodborne, for senior citizens...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im still waiting for it to actually work

that short track they had a short while ago was kinda pathetic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its the same as original, just scaled down. including the cable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LLABESAB!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pre built office pc's?

why is he smiling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he has 2 year warranty so i can only assume </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 11:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> babies that age sleep 20 hours per day... 

Source: i have a kid too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda expensive, for what is essentially some cheap metal and plastic... still, the best cooling solution is custom water loops..

though personally i hate all the work it requires, and maintenence and so on. i simply cba. I appreciate pictures of peoples builds :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont agree with the microsoft one

rest are great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah. i didn't notice the letter : </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lake Farts?

sounds like the lake could be connected to some underground volcanic activity or something... i need to dig some more before i'll know for sure though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hvor langt tilbage skal rdderne ligge?

for tror da de fleste stammer dernede fra, hvis vi gr langt nok tilbage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hjst sandsynligt ubetalt, eller betalt i form af fx. frokost og lign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish you could do that

sleep for 9 minutes 55 seconds on a 10 minute bus commute, for example

sleep while pooping

it all adds up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wendel (The guy in the video) has done multiple "korean monitor" reviews and they are all interesting. 

Those prices.. damn
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He could do some awesome pranks in kindergarden and preschool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. wasn't there some screenshots of some changes a few weeks ago.. lighting fixes in BOTW ?

and i heard some mentioning of the link sticking through the ground was being fixed too.. (I might not be remembering correctly on that 2nd one though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Japanese steel" is also a major selling point these days, for kitchen knives etc. at least in Denmark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's weird how your GPU temp also drops a bit... 

anyways. i have a 6600K and i have considered upgrading as well. though im not sure if its worth it for me - yet. i think ill wait for a Zen 2. New generation, better motherboards (bioses etc)

Im really looking forward to it, after seeing these screenshots. thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed.

Stan Lee even said it a few months ago... don't change current characters. make new ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freesync wasn't mentioned on the spec sheet for my new ultrawide LG monitor either.
It's kinda weird. i havn't checked LG's site though..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats next? 

a car as controller? (pedals, gear stick, wheel etc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed.

Jeg har aldrig set det. Kun enkelte klip p youtube for nogen r siden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, im socketrience.. not /u/sarcastic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 07:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i modstningen til xfaktor hvor millioner af kroner gr direkte i lommen p Simon Cowell - per sson : </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 07:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not  only that.. plenty of research says those weird plant-based "butter" replacements are extremely unhealthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 07:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They wouldn't believe it's not butter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's an open world action RPG kinda game, with weapons, skills and such

the alpha currently doesn't really have many quests and enemy types. but there are different biomes

You can explore forever.. that aspect of it is kinda cool

but you cannot build stuff, at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jeg har ingen anelse om hvad det er der foregr med alle de pixel billeder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find being with people is fun

but being by myself is great fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
