<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2724</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hacked T-Mobile Records For Sale For $1 Apiece On Dark Net, Payable In Bitcoin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 18:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trans-Pacific Partnership trade agreement reached, sources say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 15:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pokmon copyright lawyers demand $4,000 from party planner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 15:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experian Hack Continues Pattern Of Recklessness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 20:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experian Hack Continues Pattern Of Recklessness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 20:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 18:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately I'm not sure the other credit bureau companies are much better. We need to make a total example out of Experian so they all shape up. Honestly all companies that house any type of digital information should be having a huge wake up call right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem here is that CISA doesn't provide ANY government "oversight." It just gives companies an easy out to basically shift the blame to the government. They participate in the program, share data with the NSA etc., and then when they get hacked they get to say "we were doing everything we could" when they weren't even using basic security practices. Meanwhile they get legal immunity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 17:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing that's really whacky about CISA is it doesn't just give companies legal immunity for sharing data with the government, it also gives them legal immunity for sharing data with other companies. There are just so many bad possible scenarios embedded in that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 16:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a bit of a Zombie bill so... https://www.decidethefuture.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 16:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's true. In some ways it may make more sense to pressure T Mobile and hold them accountable for trusting their customer's data with a company that has a track record as bad as Experian's. But one thing for sure: giving them legal immunity for sharing data with the government is basically the worst plan ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Airstrike Hits Doctors Without Borders Hospital in Afghanistan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 16:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 14:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually LOL'd at this and then started coughing because I was drinking tea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Following a massive breach of data held by Experian, a group of web activists is trying to oust the companys chief executive, Brian Cassin over his support for the Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act (CISA). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 03:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 03:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 03:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I totally agree -- it's a pretty ridiculous racket </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Following a massive breach of data held by Experian, a group of web activists is trying to oust the companys chief executive, Brian Cassin over his support for the Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act (CISA). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 01:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experian has been lobbying for CISA, a bill that could give them legal immunity in the event of a hack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 00:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experian has been spending millions lobbying Congress to pass CISA, a bill that could give companies like them legal immunity when they get hacked as long as they share data with the government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 23:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cancer Patient Disrupts TPP Talks over "Death Sentence Clause" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 04:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the founder of #ShoutYourAbortion had to go into hiding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 22:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 20:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't agree more. This is really critical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comcast plans to implement what it calls a new data usage trial. Everyone else calls it a data cap. Under the plan, customers who use more than 300 gigabytes of data in a month will pay $10 to buy 50 additional gigabytes or $30 for unlimited data use. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 20:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy groups gear up to fight cyber bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 17:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These German artists tried to persuade NSA employees to quit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 02:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These German artists tried to persuade NSA employees to quit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 02:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CISA could come up soon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 18:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now There's a Tool That Tells You How Your Representatives Feel About Government Spying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 23:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Suddenly Banned an App That Maps U.S. Drone Strikes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 21:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The American public now has a comprehensive set of scores for each member of Congress regarding their positions on Internet surveillance reform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 20:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's what the VW fraud is really going to cost us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 20:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 20:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call and tell them what you think of their score! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 20:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. Good call. 

I was looking a bit more too and another interesting thing is that the Intelligence Committees are both totally opposed to reform, which is significant because they also get some of the most donations from the defense industry. I bet if you overlayed this data with data about contributions like that it would map pretty well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 19:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing that's interesting here is that party affiliation (Democrat / Republican) isn't a good indication of where a politician stands on surveillance. Both parties have their fair share of privacy champions and detractors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political scoreboard: where do your lawmakers stand on recent surveillance legislation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 18:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Helpful political scoreboard shows where lawmakers stand on recent surveillance legislation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 18:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Political scoreboard: where do your lawmakers stand on recent surveillance legislation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 18:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 22:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually wrote an op-ed calling CISA a dirty deal between Google and the NSA. Google has been silent this time round making it had to peg things on them. That's a strategy companies often use. That's why it's important that we don't let companies hide, and get them on the record about where they really stand on our privacy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 21:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely feel your fatigue for fighting this particularly tenacious "zombie bill" (accurate term.) That said, working on this issue daily I've seen a big shift in the narrative around this in DC and in the media in general and I do think we still have a real chance at defeating this altogether, or at least delaying it again to give ourselves more time to build up opposition.

A lot more members of Congress are understanding that a bill like CISA won't do anything to stop breaches like the OPM hacks. The media is starting to make them sound like fools if they still think that. Those are good signs.

Getting tech companies on the record as opposing this bad legislation is one of the most effective things we can be doing. Everyone should tweet at / email the web companies they use and ask what their position is on CISA. With the entire BSA backing away from CISA there's a really awesome moment right now where we could get an avalanche of companies opposing it, like what happened with SOPA after the GoDaddy boycott. 

At the very least, we better go down fighting or the next bill they come up with will be 100 times worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 20:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a positive note, though, the Business Software Alliance, which represents Apple, Microsoft, Adobe, and others backed away from their pro-CISA position last week and said they're against it: http://www.bsa.org/policy/security?tab=0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CISA could return to the Senate agenda this week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 20:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CISA could return to the Senate agenda this week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 20:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FB Screwed You Over. Changing Your Display Pic Means You Just Voted Against Net Neutrality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 20:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DARPA is implanting chips in soldiers brains </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 21:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SalesForce Says It Doesn't Support CISA After Signing Letter That Suggested It Did </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 01:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facing public backlash, Salesforce CEO backs away from pro-CISA position </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 19:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> reddit, in light of the fact that Heroku is supporting anti-privacy bills like CISA, what other web hosting services do you recommend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 21:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Background: https://www.youbetrayedus.org/heroku </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CISA is back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 20:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 19:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TLDR: CISA is bad for security AND privacy

Yeah, in this case I think even if you trust that the U.S. government is benevolent and just doing the best it can to protect us all (which I don't, for the record) security and technology experts are saying that information sharing bills are STILL the wrong way to go, because they will result in lots more sensitive private data being spread across a lot of government agencies who are using antiquated systems and have a terrible track record of keeping their data safe. So CISA could actually result in even more devastating Cyber Attacks like the OPM hacks happening more often and the hackers making off with even more data.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple, Microsoft, others slammed for supporting cybersecurity bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 19:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple, Microsoft, others slammed for supporting cybersecurity bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 19:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 18:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, fuck them, but just FYI this has nothing to do with net neutrality. They're facing backlash for supporting so-called "cybersecurity" legislation that would grant companies legal immunity to share private user data with government agencies. So, it's about mass surveillance, which impacts free speech just like net neutrality, but it's not the same issue. Does that help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy group calls for a boycott of tech companies supporting CISA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 18:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy group calls for a boycott of tech companies supporting CISA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 18:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 22:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These tech giants just asked US government for more surveillance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 18:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 18:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's interesting that your work blocks fightforthefuture.org!

HEre's the full letter:

Fight for the Future has published this open letter to the CEO of Salesforce and Heroku following their endorsement of the Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act (CISA). We urge others to join us in boycotting Heroku and any other hosting service that supports mass surveillance legislation.

September 22, 2015

Marc Benioff
CEO of Salesforce / Heroku
The Landmark @ One Market, Suite 300
San Francisco, CA 94105


Re: Boycott of Heroku and Salesforce services

Dear Mr. Benioff,

         I was disappointed to learn that Salesforce joined Apple, Microsoft, and other tech giants last week in endorsing the Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act of 2015 (CISA). This legislation would grant blanket immunity for American companies to participate in government mass surveillance programs like PRISM, without meaningfully addressing any of the fundamental cybersecurity problems we face in the U.S. Your support for this legislation is a short-sighted move that will decrease consumer confidence in American tech companies, both domestically and internationally, and, if CISA passes, will create broad new risks for every user of US-based cloud services. Accordingly, we will be abandoning your Heroku service within the next 90 days, and are encouraging others to do the same.

         As a former security professional and the CTO of Fight for the Future, an organization that fights for security and privacy, I strongly believe that national security and civil rights are not mutually exclusive. Its possible to craft meaningful cybersecurity legislation that protects peoples rights by encouraging strong encryption standards and responsible security research.

         Unfortunately, CISA does none of these things, and your endorsement of it reflects badly on Heroku and your other subsidiaries. Heroku has been an exceptionally convenient web hosting service, but in order to use it, we need to trust you with our supporters personal data. Salesforce is actively supporting a bill that would undermine that trust. If CISA passes, it will be impossible for us to guarantee our own privacy policy with our users, because Heroku may broadly violate their privacy agreement with us to share information about our users with the government.

         CISA provides enormous leeway for companies to share Personally Identifiable Information (PII) with government agencies like the NSA and the FBI, granting companies blanket civil and criminal immunity from any existing privacy law in the process. This blanket immunity might seem desirable to a tech industry that has been forced to participate in PRISM-style mass surveillance programs for years, since constitutional challenges to this surveillance may soon prove that the government and companies have been violating U.S. privacy laws all along. You may benefit from liability protection, but supporting it is short sighted.

         By supporting CISA, Salesforce is effectively lobbying to make their privacy policies null and void when it comes to sharing data with the government. You want to just give them the data and be done with ita remarkably irresponsible approach. The meager benefit of immunity from privacy laws will be eclipsed by the long-term cost to the tech industry as consumers lose confidence in American cloud services and abandon them for international or open-source options. Companies like Cisco have already had their revenue wiped out from the perceived threat of U.S. government surveillance. If CISA passes, billions of dollars could be erased from the greater U.S. tech economy, causing catastrophic damage to the same companies that endorsed it.

         In addition to being bad for business, CISA fails as a cybersecurity bill. Regardless of whether you believe the so-called safeguards written into CISA are adequate to protect people from government abuse and warrantless mass surveillance, it is incontrovertible that CISA will put more private data in the hands of a staggeringly wide array of government agencies. Agencies like the Department of Commerce, the Department of Energy, or the IRS are not equipped to safeguard this datain fact, both the IRS and DoE were recently breached. How would giving more private sector data to the U.S. government protect our cybersecurity when these government agencies cant even protect the data they already have?

         If its not clear already, Fight for the Future believes that CISA is not a cybersecurity bill; rather its a mass surveillance bill disguised as a cybersecurity bill. We hope you will reconsider your companys short-sighted support of this legislation. In the meantime, we will be migrating our tech infrastructure off Heroku. There are many alternatives, and we will be encouraging others to join us in moving to platforms that dont endorse government surveillance of their customers.

         Sincerely,



         Jeff Lyon
         Chief Technical Officer
         Fight for the Future
         https://www.fightforthefuture.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 18:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reporter just told me that many of these companies are heavily invested in by members of Congress -- someone should go track down that data, that'd be pretty interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 16:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's true. U.S. based tech companies already took a big hit after Snowden -- this would be a very shortsighted move on their part if more companies support a bill that blatantly expands and codifies mass surveillance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 15:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's simply not true. Right now if a company shares data with the government in a way that violates their privacy policy or isn't in accordance with law, you could absolutely sue them and win in court. There are privacy laws they could violate or you could sue them for breach of contract if your a customer and they violated a written agreement. Yes, it's true that a ton of spying and data sharing happens in secret, but CISA would codify that and make it all 100% legal, removing any chance that we might have future court victories like the ones ACLU and EFF have been fighting for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why we're leaving Heroku: Fight for the Future has published this open letter to the CEO of Salesforce and Heroku following their endorsement of the Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act (CISA). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 14:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 21:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, some companies were more surprising than others. I guess legal immunity is a pretty bright and shiny thing for a company even when they're concerned about their image. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 21:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the source letter, list of companies at the bottom. Notable names: Apple, Microsoft, Adobe, Salesforce (Heroku), Symantec: http://www.bsa.org/~/media/Files/Policy/data/09142015CongLeadershipDataAgendaLetter.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 19:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a good point. Mozilla has opposed similar legislation in the past, when it was called CISPA. Google has been largely (and notably) silent -- though they did quietly lobby on CISPA a few years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple, Microsoft, Adobe, Salesforce, Symantec and other companies just endorsed CISA cyber threat sharing legislation in a letter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 18:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Android lockscreen hack gives attackers full access to locked devices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 22:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In response to this news about Ahmed Mohammed, what if high school students all brought clocks into school on Monday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 18:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like that would be awesome. I really did think of this in the shower.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 05:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is true that the thing holding them back is they have to figure out this issue with ads. That said, it's unacceptable and unethical for a site that houses this kind of sensitive user data ([related to a user's drug use habits, mental health, sexual preferences, sexual history, illegal activity, etc. etc. etc.](https://cms.fightforthefuture.org/okcupid)) to run a business model that prevents them from offering all their users at least a baseline level of security. HTTPS is standard web encryption -- we as Internet users need to start demanding it or companies will always drag their feet and choose the status quo and short term profit over longterm security and sustainability. It may seem to OKCupid like dealing with this ads question and switching to SSL is going to cost a lot of money and time, but I highly doubt it will cost them as much money and time as when something like Ashley Madison happens to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 00:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twitter is a publicly traded company with more than 1 billion in revenue every year. It may be free to get an account but it's not like they're not making money off their users. If they say a message is private, it should be private. The issue here is breach of contract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 23:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They could totally make more money if they just start messaging their users demanding payment or they'll release their messages to the media. Now THAT's a business model </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 22:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Standard security practices should be... standard, not a pro feature </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter Hit With Suit Claiming It Snoops on Direct Messages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 22:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 21:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone spying on your private OKCupid messages is pretty different than someone looking at something you post publicly on twitter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 21:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahahahahahahaha :::cries::: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OKCupid still hasnt fixed the problem. For users who havent upgraded to paid accounts, their emails, chat sessions, searches, clicked links, pages viewed, and usernames are transmitted over the Internet in unencrypted plaintext, where they can be intercepted and read by anyone on the network. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 21:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OKCupid still hasnt fixed the problem. For users who havent upgraded to paid accounts, their emails, chat sessions, searches, clicked links, pages viewed, and usernames are transmitted over the Internet in unencrypted plaintext, where they can be intercepted and read by anyone on the network. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 20:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I kind of want to get arrested just so I can have Justin Bieber as my attorney </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 20:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter hit with class action lawsuit for eavesdropping on direct messages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 19:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New "Smart Home" program will let Comcast know every time you open or close your garage door because that's not creepy at all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 19:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 19:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, pages where you enter passwords are HTTPS but other pages or not. Although I'm now hearing from users with paid accounts that they get HTTPS, so it's possible they're offering security to paid users but not to others </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OKCupid still isn't using SSL encryption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 19:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Species of Crayfish Named After Edward Snowden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 17:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Species of Crayfish Named After Edward Snowden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 17:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Online dating site OKCupid doesn't use basic HTTPS encryption to protect user privacy, so everything you do on the site can be seen by anyone who wants to spy on you. Every question you've answered. Every message you've sent. Every profile you've visited. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 17:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 00:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cost of sitewide SSL? Probably less than OKC cofounder's [new condo](http://nypost.com/2015/09/02/inside-okcupid-co-founders-2-1m-greenpoint-townhouse/) in Brooklyn.
Not becoming the next Ashley Madison but with a way more sympathetic user base? Priceless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OKCupid *still* isn't using standard HTTPS encryption sitewide, which means anyone who wants to can see every question you've answered, every message you've sent, and every profile you've visited. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 22:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston still tracks vehicle license plates, lies about it, and leaves sensitive resident data exposed online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 15:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter shuts down 30 international versions of Politiwoops, sites that record tweets that politicians and public officials delete </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 21:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Civil Rights Group Backed by Telecom Industry Seeks to Block Net Neutrality, Instantly Contradicts Itself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 18:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attorney credits public with sparing Chelsea Manning solitary confinement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 17:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows 10 Checks For Pirate Bay Torrents, Bootleg Games And Hardware Automatically </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 14:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea Manning contraband case to be heard amid concern over punishment. U.S. soldier could face indefinite solitary over possession of banned items  a magazine, books and expired toothpaste </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 19:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea Manning allies tell army to drop charges with 100,000-strong petition. Delivery of petition to protest infractions involving unapproved material comes as lawyers for Manning say they have been barred from Tuesday hearing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 18:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea Manning denied access to legal library prior to prison hearing, she says. Imprisoned soldier faces potential solitary confinement after alleged violations including possession of unapproved reading material and expired toothpaste </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 23:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 21:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Releasing any number of documents to WikiLeaks is not more dangerous than allowing governments and militaries to operate in secrecy. The military even admitted that the documents Chelsea released likely posed no real threat to national security.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 21:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems like it might be headed for the frontpage, so it seems astute to leave this link to the petition mentioned in the article right here: http://www.freechelsea.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 21:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Everyone who complains that Snowden is a "coward" for not coming back to the U.S. should be required to read every news article about Chelsea's case in the last several years.

EDIT: here's the petition mentioned in this article: https://www.freechelsea.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 21:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chelsea has access to hormones but is still being denied access to various other types of healthcare related to her gender transition, and is being held in a men's facility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 21:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just false. Chelsea is proud of being a transgender woman and has written about it as a columnist for The Guardian. Trans women are strong. We are not anyone's laughing stock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 21:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She dictates tweets to supporters who then type them out word for word. News source: http://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2015/apr/16/chelsea-manning-reassures-twitter-followers-its-really-me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks whistleblower Chelsea Manning is now being denied access to prison legal library ahead of disciplinary hearing where her lawyers will not be present that could lead to solitary confinement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 20:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 16:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're one of those people who thought the Nazi's were "just doing their jobs" aren't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 16:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been widely reported by most major newsmedia, and confirmed by Chelsea's attorneys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 04:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many rules in prisons but its also widely known that rules are selectively enforced. The fact that Chelsea is facing such outrageous potential punishment for such innocuous "charges" is a clear example of abuse, and nonjudicial punishment being used to silence free speech and free expression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 04:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exposing government abuses is not treason, except by the most twisted definitions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 04:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chelsea's pronouns are she/hers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 04:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chelsea's pronouns are she/hers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 04:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chelsea's pronouns are she/hers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 03:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the toothpaste part is just over the top. The list of books and magazines they took is perhaps the most alarming part, though. Seems to point to blatant attempt to target Manning's freedom of thought and expression

EDIT: i'm adding a link to the petition calling for her hearing Tuesday to be open to the public and press, which also has a complete list of the "charges" she is facing: http://freechelsea.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks whistleblower Chelsea Manning faces "indefinite solitary confinement" for charges including possession of Vanity Fair Caitlyn Jenner issue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 02:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 02:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for the treasonous politicians who are keeping whistleblowers like Chelsea in jail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 02:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Even Bernie Sanders hasn't said a word about Chelsea yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks whistleblower Chelsea Manning may face indefinite solitary confinement charges including possession of Caitlyn Jenner Vanity Fair issue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 02:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 01:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The charges are so absurd. Guardian has more of the scoop: http://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2015/aug/12/chelsea-manning-solitary-confinement-toothpaste-army </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 00:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't see a paywall either. Weird? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea Manning faces indefinite solitary confinement for having Caitlyn Jenner magazine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 00:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea Manning Faces Solitary Confinement Under New Charges, Lawyer Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 23:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea Manning Faces Solitary Confinement Under New Charges, Lawyer Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 23:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks whistleblower Chelsea Manning faces possible indefinite solitary confinement for sweeping food onto the floor, possessing LGBTQ books and magazines including Vanity Fair issue with Caitlyn Jenner on cover, and ... an expired tube of toothpaste </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 22:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks whistleblower Chelsea Manning faces possible indefinite solitary confinement for sweeping food onto the floor, possessing LGBTQ books and magazines including Vanity Fair issue with Caitlyn Jenner on cover, and ... an expired tube of toothpaste </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 21:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks whistleblower Chelsea Manning faces possible indefinite solitary confinement ... for having a tube of expired toothpaste? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 21:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Open letter to progressives: Youre doing it wrong and itll cost the Democratic Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 20:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 17:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is bad. Very bad. I called.

For the skeptics (are there any skeptics on reddit?) here's some links:
-How CISA allows more upstream NSA collection [(read)](http://thehill.com/blogs/congress-blog/technology/249521-cisa-the-dirty-deal-between-google-and-the-nsa-that-no-one-is)
-CISA lets companies share your data (think emails, medical records, etc.) with 12+ government agencies and even local cops. [(read)](http://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2015/jul/29/congress-stop-high-profile-hacks-reduce-your-privacy)
-Cybersecurity experts say CISA won't actually stop high-profile cyber attacks like the OPM hacks.[(read)](https://d1ovv0c9tw0h0c.cloudfront.net/files/2015/03/CISA-2015-Sign-On-Letter.pdf)

If you don't have your phone, you can still take action at https://www.faxbigbrother.com or https://www.stopcyberspying.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook patents technology to help lenders discriminate against borrowers based on social connections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 14:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 14:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not gonna lie, that would definitely help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Senate is considering a bill to make it easier for businesses and the government to share data about cyber threats. Proponents say it would enhance security; opponents call it surveillance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 04:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House endorses CISA cyber bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 01:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House endorses Senate version of CISA cyber bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 01:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 20:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I think this is basically true for all extremely centralized forms of power. Big institutions tend to screw us over, whether they're governments, monopolistic corporations, religious institutions, even big NGOs and charity organizations.

Bills like CISA inherently push us toward more centralization and authoritarianism during a time when we have unprecedented ability to actually EXPAND democracy thanks to the power of the Internet.

Makes me mad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 17:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this is a good point. Rand Paul (while I disagree with him on many many things) did the Internet a solid when he filibustered renewal of some of the worst sections of the PATRIOT Act. 

Your huffpo jab is legit. But yeah I think the point of the headline is that people aren't talking about this bill as what it is: a deal between companies and the government to trade free information for legal immunity. This piece tries to get into the technical details of how it might work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 17:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah totally, we've mounted some big opposition to previous incarnations like CISPA. I think the point of the headline is that not many media outlets are representing the bill as what it really is: a pretty sketchy "deal" between giant companies and the government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 18:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slowly but surely it seems like more people are talking about it. This piece in The Hill today is pretty intense: http://thehill.com/blogs/pundits-blog/technology/250070-is-cisa-gift-wrapped-for-hackers-and-nation-state-actors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CISA: The Dirty Deal Between Google and the NSA That No One Is Talking About </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 18:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 21:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> interesting tidbit in this Guardian piece is that members of Congress love outdated technology like the fax machine for sending stuff like their financial disclosures because it's a lot harder to spy on and sift through: http://www.theguardian.com/technology/2015/jul/27/congress-fax-machines-cybersecurity-cisa-protest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CISA: the dirty deal between Google and the NSA that no one is talking about </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 20:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 16:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Congress job to *represent* the American public, and in order to do that they need to hear from us. They hear from corporate lobbyists ALL THE TIME who drop by their offices, have their personal cell phones etc. The tools we at FFTF build are designed to give the general public that same level of access to Congress.

So yeah, i guess i'd have to say #SorryNotSorry :-)

I'll let others answer the first part of the question. Thanks for asking! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress is about to get a shit ton of faxes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 19:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 04:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote this op-ed with some good info about TPP: http://www.theguardian.com/media-network/2015/may/08/trans-pacific-partnership-obama-irony </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 19:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is that Congress doesn't understand modern technology (which is why they're pushing for this bad bill) so maybe they'll understand faxes?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
