<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5238</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 05:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this looks great, where did you find the artist?  any trouble communicating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minimum wage workers of reddit, why don't you just work as waiters since they get all the tips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 05:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 05:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed reading the reviews more than the movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 22:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> most autistic lpt i've seen yet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We want Heisenberg, not Eisenberg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the same except with a layer of melodrama  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> korea is still in Japan's shadow lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 08:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hollywood is all about connections </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 06:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> donnie!

crazy how one movie could make me into a fan, talking about ip man of course  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 06:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can't believe they ripped off chronicle after firing chronicle writer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 06:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can agree with Train to Busan and Zootopia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 06:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have you ever seen Contact? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 06:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bad writing.  watch true detective instead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 06:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he did just do an interview on hannity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 05:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought one recently and the point is too thin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 05:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks like Europa needs some freedom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The lowest RT rating a movie can get before I won't watch it seems to be about 40 percent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 22:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite its many, many faults, I still could find some things to enjoy in Jack Reacher 2, but this leniency reaches its limit around 26% - I'm thinking of Suicide Squad, it actually made me hate myself for watching.  So I definitely won't be watching either Passengers or Assassin's Creed this holiday break.  I know there's hype but in the end that makes my self-hatred worse and I'm tired of subjecting myself to that when there are so many other movies to watch which I know while I may not love, that I won't at least hate myself for  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> copied Contact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 09:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lone survivor was solid though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Korean parents are paying for their kids to get plastic surgery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 08:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Korean parents are paying for their kids to get plastic surgery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 08:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 05:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> love first season, want third season with woody and matthew back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 03:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's all shills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 03:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the sound of Stockholm syndrome in space </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 07:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe all the whining before the blast had something to do with it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's simply that what Tom Arnold said recently reminded me of something else Tom Arnold said before.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hypocritical that Tom Arnold is calling Trump a racist when he made ching chong noises at one of the directors of the Fast and Furious and True Detective series
http://blog.angryasianman.com/2007/02/tom-arnold-professional-ass.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hypocritical that Tom Arnold is calling Trump a racist when he made ching chong noises at one of the directors of the Fast and Furious and True Detective series
http://blog.angryasianman.com/2007/02/tom-arnold-professional-ass.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hypocritical that Tom Arnold is calling Trump a racist when he made ching chong noises at one of the directors of the Fast and Furious and True Detective series

http://blog.angryasianman.com/2007/02/tom-arnold-professional-ass.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justin Lin, one of the directors of the Fast and the Furious movies and True Detective, while doing a photo shoot at Sundance was heckled by someone making ching-chong noises who turned out to be Tom Arnold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Justin Lin, one of the directors of the Fast and the Furious movies and True Detective, while doing a photo shoot at Sundance was heckled by someone making ching-chong noises who turned out to be Tom Arnold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Always give people the benefit of the doubt, your assumptions can be wrong, it is less stressful for you, and you would want them to do the same </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] KFC Japan releases special finger sheaths for hassle-free fried chicken eating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In an alternate universe, Passengers could have been made with Keanu Reeves, Rachel McAdams, and a director from Game of Thrones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 00:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that Fantastic Beasts has been out a while and we've gotten some distance from it, where does it rank among the Harry Potter series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 09:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As an American, I am finding it impossible to follow British dramas about medieval royalty, they talk about people and events many times in passing, is it as hard for Brits to follow too? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 21:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What parts are hot dogs made of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 19:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it that older literature seems to have more vocabulary and difficult words and use of language than modern literature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If a post involves a big brand name, know that companies hire shills to promote their brands and may try to drown out negative opinions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's interesting the thinness of the line between love and hate: I used to upvote every The Walking Dead post but after this season's premiere, I downvote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If urine is a disinfectant, why do people get UTI's during sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arrival, with a Cinemascore of B, is lower than Jack Reacer: Never Go Back's B+ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 18:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The problem fake news was created by mainstream media's bias and many times 'fake' reporting. People would not read fake news if they felt they could trust msm. Also, polarization of media has led people to see truths being spun any way and still appear truthful. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary didn't really try to reach out to Bernie's people because their corporate elites didn't want too many grassroots progressives in the party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by eating with my fingers after cooking bacon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 02:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Brits who've been to America, how do race relations compare between the UK and America? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 08:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can think of few worse things than being Mexican and working at Taco Bell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 22:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White privilege is never having someone assume your parents are foreigners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went gift shopping and was asked by the white shop employee if my parents were headed back to their homeland for the Christmas break though they were also born here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make an app that turns a guy's chest into boobs so they can ask themselves for nudes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 05:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judging by the celebrities who supported Trump, his voters have incredibly bad taste in every field of entertainment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What non-MSM sites on Reddit would be considered untrustworthy and thus fake news? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 07:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberal and conservative America go to war, who would win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research On Chinese Haze Helps Crack Mystery Of London's Deadly 1952 Fog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 01:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something you wish your parents had taught you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In four years from now, how will life be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 08:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> u/tmstms gives a handy description of British newspapers' political leanings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 17:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watching this doc on British culture in Netflix and it's striking its the similarity with Japanese culture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 01:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the feeling of not wanting to impose upon others

of wanting to be polite and not wanting others to feel bad 

being indirect and euphemistic 

being reserved

wanting to avoid people

valuing order 

not wanting to stand out in public

keeping your emotions in

bringing everything from home with you on holiday

saying sorry all the time 

rudeness as the worst thing 

being horrible at dancing and singing

social awkwardness

long goodbyes 

one accent for home and one accent for work

drinking lots of beer and getting drunk excuses any bad behavior 

rigid with schedules

school uniforms

love tea 
 
uncomfortable with touch and intimacy 

lots of rules and traditions

etc

one thing that isnt similar is wanting to be alone while japanese like to be with the group </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My neighbor whistles incessantly but I cant say anything because my family screams at each other incessantly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Does it cost more for a Mexican immigrant to sneak into America or an unemployed Midwesterner or Southerner to move to the city to find a job? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 21:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you are unemployed in the Midwest and South, why don't you move to the city like the immigrants and Chinese do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 21:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The problem isn't Islam, it's that the West has bombed half the Middle East into oblivion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 19:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it's also allied with dictators who've oppressed the people.  It's as if America had to fight Britain AND France during the Revolutionary War  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If we are the heroes of our own story, then we can either be the friends or enemies in other people's stories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 18:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would your job prospects change if all the immigrants in your city or town left? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 16:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to history books and the news, every country America has invaded and is an enemy has had crazy and bloodthirsty leaders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump supporters think oppressing minorities is a good idea but don't seem to know that even in all white England, division was found between Protestants and Catholics by opposition leaders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unemployed Trump supporters are only willing to work if the jobs come to them instead of moving like the immigrants they condemn do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been seeing UK newspapers pop up often on Reddit, can we get a quick description of their political stance and general standing in the UK? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make the Republican and Democratic nominees marry their children to each other like Europe's monarchies have done to increase the peace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 19:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conor MacGregor, how good is his boxing really? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 08:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We want Islam to be eradicated but we have Christians all over America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 01:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In America, beans are associated with Mexicans, so how did beans become popular in the UK? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 01:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After a friend married a guy who said he had money but is actually broke, I've come to think that that is also a form of sexual assault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 00:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Westerners make fun of other culture's foods being gross but will eat hot dogs and McRibs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Successful men are like women, they won't give you respect unless you've proved yourself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 07:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Blaine is Vin Diesel with hair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What driving at night looks like for someone with astigmatism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I hate driving at night - astigmatism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT request: how do you know if someone really likes you or is faking it because of school, work, or family politics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you know if someone really likes you or is just faking it because of school, work, or family politics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars Revenge of the Sith was actually critically well-received with a 79% on Rotten Tomatoes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In China, the unemployed move to where the work is whereas in America, people want the multimillion dollar factories to come to them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> During England's War of the Roses, what percentage of the male population actually fought? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 01:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Across history and the world, have indigenous peoples been relatively better off submitting or resisting invading forces for example the Indians were decimated in America while the Scottish now have become a central part of the United Kingdom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 00:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does r/Scotland think of Braveheart? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 21:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to keep fake news out of your newsfeed? College professor creates list of sites to avoid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 19:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seconds into watching Highlander and I'm hit with this awesome music and who is the music by but none other than Queen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 18:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of millions have migrated from rural parts of China to the city for work, but unemployed rural Midwest workers in America want the jobs to come to them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunday cable ratings: Westworld ticks up as Walking Dead slips a little more </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryan Gosling, starring in another romance, is just the Ja Rule of actors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Negan is just latter day Al Pacino </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any good online anime stores? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 05:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to a huge anime store but they still didnt have what I wanted despite also being organized.  I tried Amazon but its selection is small and expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any good online anime stores? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 05:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the book cover of The Cursed Child, what is it that I presume Albus is sitting in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like a bird nest with wings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMA request - A likely Trump voter in 2008 or 2012 who actually did well under Obama's economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If there's money to be made in a subreddit, the full time mods are likely paid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good news sites that are either unbiased or like realclearpolitics, clearly identify and feature different points of views? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mainstream media should be publicly funded and overseen by a bipartisan Congressional commission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 18:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only good thing about Trump's election is getting rid of the sense of entitlement of Mexicans, stop waving your flag! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 17:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We could've had Bernie but instead we got Trump. This is all Hillary's fault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 09:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton put a Trump to America's head and it pulled the trigger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 08:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I say how creepy it is I was talking to a friend about taking a trip WITHOUT Google searching, then a few minutes later I got on Youtube and saw an ad for exactly the same place we were talking about going to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 19:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's happened two separate instances for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has George R. R. Martin's condemnation of Trump changed any redditors' minds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 04:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recommendations for great shows like Breaking Bad, Fargo and The West Wing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are probably a lot of porn stars who changed their names because of Tom Cruise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 15:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some things in the movies you would've like to see more from the books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 22:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't cut off your nose to spite your face. If you're in a battleground state, doing or will do well economically, vote Clinton to continue Obama's policies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 04:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> system's fucked either way but do what's best for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary put Trump to America's head and is surprised we're pulling the trigger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 05:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Don't assume things. More often than not, you're injecting your own insecurities into a situation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 17:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Chipotle nightmare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is half the internet down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 06:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the breakdown for what you watch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 09:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a variety of options, possibly a surplus, what's the breakdown for what you watch, it can be movies, tv shows, youtube videos, free and for pay streaming services like Netflix, Hulu, Amazon Instant Video and Prime, HBO Go, and other apps, cable, video rentals online or physical discs, movie theater, illegal downloads, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hacksaw Ridge or Dr. Strange this weekend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 08:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both got great reviews at over 90 percent on Rotten Tomatoes, Dr. Strange seems like Inception which is really cool and it's a Marvel movie, that said I have to say I'm actually leaning towards Hacksaw because I haven't seen an exceptional war film since Fury, Mel has made some classic movies, and I love to see a real life comeback story, how about you guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Negan promises he's just getting started but have Walking Dead fans already seen enough misery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 22:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you've stopped using Facebook, what are your reasons? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 19:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All authors should be anonymous so there can be no claims of bias or actual bias </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 07:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Too much bias, just unsubscribed to r/politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 01:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Given the Irishes' history of oppression, "the luck of the Irish" probably was meant to be sarcastic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 20:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making of Star Wars Prequel Trilogy - World building Set Design Interviews </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 18:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ghosts like Headless Nick after Chamber of Secrets in the movies seemed to disappear, did the same thing happen in the books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 17:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Ask people you trust to give an honest assessment of how you appear because you'll have to calibrate your interactions with other people your whole life based on it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 21:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Gaslighting" is an extremely effective form of emotional abuse that causes a victim to question their own feelings, instincts, and sanity, which gives the abusive partner a lot of power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 21:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL "Gaslighting" is an extremely effective form of emotional abuse that causes a victim to question their own feelings, instincts, and sanity, which gives the abusive partner a lot of power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 21:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who has made the better movies, Tom Cruise or Brad Pitt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 08:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the nineties, the rivalry between them dominated the entertainment magazines.  It's mostly gone now but I've still got to wonder what people think about who has the better movies, basically if you could have one of their careers who would it be?

http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0000129/?ref_=fn_al_nm_1#actor

http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0000093/?ref_=fn_al_nm_1#actor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We always blame others when they have bad days but we never blame ourselves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is it the media can ignore Trump's claims the election may be rigged after the DNC was found to favor Hillary, and with it's close margins, likely decided the primary for her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking to expand my world, what are five websites you visit every day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 08:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we have tags identifying news sites like Daily Mail which is a tabloid but given more credibility since people not in the UK don't know it is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watching movies with heavy CGI is like watching Now You See Me 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 18:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now You See Me 2 had some really cool effects but I kept thinking it's all fake.  Ironically it's a movie that's about magic but it forgets that magic makes you believe in what's possible first then wows you, but in Now You See Me 2 and most CGI-heavy movies these days, nothing is impossible so it all becomes a one note bonanza.  I am much more impressed by a movie like The Prestige or the underrated Shade with Sylvester Stallone that is realistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what are the signs that the person commenting is American and not british? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 23:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders In Town Today to Stump for Proposition 61, Which Aims to Lower Drug Prices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 08:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is it that Nixon can get impeached but Hillary can still run for office despite her scandals? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 08:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DC Comics is so short on heroes they have to have female versions of all their popular characters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being a woman is like being a cat, you go about your day and everyone seems to want to touch you for just being you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 21:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Birth.Movies.Death offers an insightful analyses both good and bad of Star Wars: The Force Awakens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 04:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://birthmoviesdeath.com/2015/12/16/star-wars-the-force-awakens-review

http://birthmoviesdeath.com/2015/12/18/star-wars-the-force-awakens-review-a-good-movie-with-bad-problems

http://birthmoviesdeath.com/2015/12/24/will-star-wars-just-be-fanfic-from-now-on

http://birthmoviesdeath.com/2015/12/31/how-rey-reflects-the-strengths-weaknesses-of-star-wars-the-force-awakens

http://birthmoviesdeath.com/2016/06/28/star-wars-the-force-alluded-to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teenager is convicted of murder in 2014 beating death of USC graduate student from China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 04:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teenager is convicted of murder in 2014 beating death of USC graduate student from China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 03:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breaking news: Gorilla that just escaped London zoo has been shot and not killed wiith a tranquilizer because they're not savages over there </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 22:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If it's good enough to be proposed for politicians, corporate paid redditors should have tags identifying which company they're working for </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone seen the Duffer bros' previous show, Wayward Pines? How do the two shows compare? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The "Theory of Everything" is one equation that would explain the entire universe, what is your one line that explains your profession to yourself or others? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever treated someone poorly who turned out to be very successful? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What's the farthest you've gone with "locker room" talk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Arndt Reveals Rejected Plots From Star Wars: The Force Awakens; A Much Larger Role For Luke Skywalker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 18:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blacks should have a spare clown mask to put on in case they're pulled over by police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 18:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All the hot women subs are more pointless than strippers, you can look but can't touch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 03:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As an extremely satisfied owner of the unheralded HTC One, maybe Apple creates problems like the notifications for iOS 10 so people would keep talking about the iPhone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 22:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've seen thousands of naked women online, I know their bodies are mostly the same and that I shouldn't be turned on for the millionth time, but I still am. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW the whole class is disagreeing with me and then one person has my back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redpill guys are idiots. They actually blame woman for not wanting to be with them when choosing a partner is a lifetime commitment. Look honestly at yourself to see why someone doesn't want to spend their life with you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 19:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leave the Jackass guys in the middle of the hurricane, film it, and release the movie in theaters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 19:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans are spineless hypocrites, all their talk about values and now one by one they're kissing Trump's ass </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 07:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The time Hillary planted a question at a town hall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit remembers the time Hillary planted a question at a town hall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mods are useless. I got banned from r/movies for posting six different articles about the Star Wars prequels being better than The Force Awakens. Mods exist only to enforce the majority opinion and "manufacture consent" through censorship. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 04:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The links were from reputable sources as well, RogerEbert.com, DenofGeek, one was a James Cameron interview.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plagiarizing "Star Wars": The Problems with "The Force Awakens" | Roger Ebert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 01:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars: The Force Awakens: James Cameron adds his thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 01:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars The Force Awakens is the most Disappointing Movie of All Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 01:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is there a limit for gold members for how many subs we can filter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 23:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Prequels VS The Force Awakens: Star Wars Debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 22:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any critics on youtube that love the Star Wars prequels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 07:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saw Mr. Plinklett's video, all flash, no substance, and also I'm tired of people shitting on Lucas.  The guy is behind Star Wars original and prequel trilogies, he has more courage in his pinky than all two hours of The Force Awakens.  I'll reiterate the prequels were flawed but were original and had some really great stuff and deepened the OT, also episode three alone is a classic.  It's shitty that people give him no credit for Star Wars when as a director/writer he was ultimately responsible for episode four, and as exec producer he was ultimately responsible for five and six. 

Anyone know of defenders of the prequels on youtube? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have two cats, one chases the other after that cat pees in the box, anyone know why and if it's a playful or aggressive chasing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've hated on many popular movies recently but there's one I can wholeheartedly recommend, Train to Busan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 23:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only mods who can mod full time are corporate shills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If humans are hard-wired to fear the dark, why is it racist to admit to being more fearful of black people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 19:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best-Sellers Initially Rejected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 09:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best sellers initially rejected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 09:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever had a partner who looked normal but was wild in bed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 19:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
