<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8754</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 11:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had something to contribute here. I'm Chinese and lived in France for a month, looking very non-native. Contrary to French stereotypes, no one insulted me in French. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 10:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, I think you can already guess which branch I was in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 09:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2013-2015. I'm sure I can be doxxed with this information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 13:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cool!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 13:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you really own an Aventador?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 06:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not really renting per se, but more of a usage right. After 10 years, the car is still yours but you can't drive it around anymore. You'll have to either sell it and get a new car with a new COE or renew the COE at around the prevailing market rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 06:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's still something called an Additional Registration Fee (100%) and Excise Duty (20%) based on something called the Open Market Value of the car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 02:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha could have bought an S550 plus a load of options elsewhere in the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 02:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to search for those before I posted but apparently their sales are so poor that I think they exited the Singaporean market. Who would pay $50,000+ for rubbish that even the Malaysian government is reluctant to buy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 17:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is only half of the Arizona map.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 17:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brand new? Absolutely nothing. The cheapest car on sale in Singapore is an absolutely rubbish Chery Fulwin 2 (Chinese car) for about US$54,000. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 12:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's faster than a bicycle though. But even at $20,000, it doesn't seem like a good deal since motorcycles are so much cheaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 09:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea so no point in holding back electric cars here since most of their revenues aren't coming from domestic demand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 09:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that would require a side window which this doesn't have. Actually even the doors are an optional extra. This runabout will be useless in the rain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 09:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no opposition party that aligns to such beliefs. Maybe it's because hard truths are a political suicide.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 09:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this has something to do with it, but with such a small population here I don't think the demand is that substantial. Maybe any profit is good profit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 05:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called looking for validation. I'm just hoping that my opinions are shared by some other people as well, unless everyone's a bastion of selflessness here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 05:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's frustrating how electric cars are so slow to take off here. One would expect that such a small country would be the perfect place to have electric runabouts. It's really embarrassing to still see electric cars on RU plates. What's there to research? It's not like electricity is a new concept. We need some big player to start installing charging stations island wide.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 05:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you're being sarcastic because I'm being a huge dick here but I wonder if anyone else shares my sentiments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 20:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Murali Pillai is more of the same, which I think is what people are voting for. 

As a selfish Singaporean, I would hate to see most of CSJ's ideas implemented. I don't want my tax money to be spent on keeping others afloat when they're unemployed. If universal healthcare's like NHS, isn't it ironic that those who keep themselves healthy benefit the least from the scheme? I'm neutral on minimum wage and have no knowledge on the HDB market. I am neutral towards 377A as it doesn't affect me or anyone I know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 19:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's worrying if 39% of people voted on that philosophy of having opposition for opposition's sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 18:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea if you're posted to do HR stuff it's usually OT galore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 18:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone ELI5 why a person would vote for Chee Soon Juan? Honest question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 17:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 17:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's half cutoff. Don't worry, Arizona's bigger than that. And it's beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 14:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was ASA. OT like mad for 2 years. It's a rare occasion to book out when it's not entirely dark outside. Had $400 in OT taxi claims in just a month. I live in Tampines and went to Selarang. Had to work through the night on several occasions. Not fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 10:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's why SMRT argued contributory negligence. Maybe she was looking at her phone like everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 05:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of adjustment but I'm sure at that price you can find an even better one. (The one I'm sitting on is my office's chair) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 05:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yes, it's a diesel. No, it doesn't spew soot." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 04:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you currently using it? I'm sitting on one right now and I think the seat base's not deep enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 04:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel that the flipped learning model is just a lazy excuse to let the professors do less. It's getting closer and closer to being largely self-study now, so you're just paying for the exams.

1) The videos they use for e-learning were prepared years ago and just reused. Some lecturers don't even bother to hide the fact that the slides were made years ago. Loads of errors not corrected over the years. If I wanted to learn online, why not watch free lectures from Harvard instead of paying for NTU's?

2) Only one was held in the hive. Not much group discussions unless it's business law. I don't know how you can active discuss Accounting or something similar.

3) Yes, 1 tutor per class. No wonder the tuition fees are so much cheaper compared to overseas universities. The larger class size does nothing to enhance learning since people don't participate even with participation counted in the final grade. There's less personal attention given by professors in such large classes since he/she can't wait for 1 person to understand while holding the rest of the 49 students up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 04:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From NTU Business. Lots of projects and presentations but there's fewer and fewer physical lectures to attend. NTU's going forward with the trend of e-learning, which to me is a total rip-off. I would also complain about the huge tutorial class sizes, which can go up to 50 students per class. Exams are not too difficult and you don't really have to mug to do well. Just keep up with the readings and do the tutorials and you should be good for exams.

Since the time table's quite sparse and there's a lot of e-learning, pass your time either by joining a CCA or just relax at home. JC was much more hectic than Uni is now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 20:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried these and they weren't that good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 17:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. That makes sense on how it's 'giving in' sometimes. 

For me, personally, there isn't really much that I'm dissatisfied with in Singapore, other than NS. But that's over now, after having served my 2 years. I don't really care what they do about that anymore.

I really have no statistics on the support for death penalty here but from my personal experience and interaction (which by no means represent any significant portion of the general consensus), most people are in support of it.

And yes, I do believe in eugenics, but that's so politically incorrect that I'm not going to speak about it here. I still care about Reddit karma as a Singaporean who wants to save 'face'. 

What was wrong with Carnegie and Beethoven? And please don't put Steve Jobs in that list. I don't see why he's so great. He's just fantastic at marketing. He's a terrible person in general and I can't respect anyone who believes in homoeopathy. I own an iPhone, but I never liked him as a person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 16:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting how you term it as 'giving in to the law'. Why isn't it just 'abiding' by the law? Giving in suggests unwilling sacrifice. I certainly don't feel that way living in Singapore. 

You talk about death penalty, but isn't that something that's still supported by the local populace? I know I'm a supporter, because I don't believe in human rights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 12:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the internet. Of course only my opinions matter here. What are you trying to get to? In any case, this isn't a free market transaction. It doesn't matter whether those two agree or not. SLA is going to get back their land anyway. This is not Hong Kong where people can freely protest, refuse to move and hinder the construction of the HSR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 10:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never have I considered what those two old men wants as 'fair'. If they were allowed to ask for what they wanted, why not ask for $2 million or more? Perhaps the government has to take a hard line on this and force them out of their homes, otherwise more problems will surface in future land reacquisition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 10:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's how democracy works. Most of the residents have already sucked it up and left. Those two should leave too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 07:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sort of. Power of the people, for they voted in the government.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 06:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 05:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes if you're the government and if it's required by law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 05:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's fair to pay the correct assessed value and not anything more to compensate their feelings because it is unnecessary to do so and an utter waste of taxpayers' money. If these people refuse to move out, they should be prosecuted. Don't waste time and money on a few peoples' hurt feelings and delay the benefit of a new train line to hundreds of thousands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 20:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The front looks like a Mitsuoka Le-Seyde. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 19:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it should be made according to the guidelines set in law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 18:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so market valuefair value. Nevertheless, I feel that those residents shouldn't be compensated beyond what another seller of a similar dwelling size, type and location should be paid. Basically, just follow the Land Acquisition Act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 18:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly my thoughts. Why make a luxury car and then ruin its ride with huge rims and low profiles? My tyres are 225/50/R17 so they're quite 'high profile' already. Maybe I'll look for 55 or 60 in the future, but I'll run the risk of them looking awkward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 17:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely overinflated. The ride quality was significantly poorer prior to me checking the pressures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 17:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Point taken. I'll stick to the recommended pressures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 17:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're stock tyres (Michelin Primacy HP). Are there more comfortable tyres that I can perhaps change to in the future? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lowest safe tyre pressure? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 17:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was checking my tyre pressures today and realised that after the last dealership service, they overinflated it to Front 280kPa and Rear 270kPa, which explains the unusually harsh ride. I got it back down to 220/210 which were the recommended comfort pressures. Ride comfort improved tremendously; squeaks from going over harsh road irregularities were entirely gone. 


This got me thinking, what's the lowest tyre pressure that's still safe to commute daily on to maximize ride quality? The lowest my tyres have gone was around 185kPa from not pumping them up for about 3 months, and by that time the ride was exceptionally smooth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 16:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't fair value just market value? If it's what you described, then fair value is basically what the current residents want, which could be much more than what it's worth. Overcompensation is fair for them, but not fair for taxpayers who stand to gain from the MRT constructed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 09:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is why pay more than fair value? It's not like returns to Temasek like you mentioned will be higher if more were paid to current residents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 07:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And where does that amount come from? Your taxes right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 18:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well my 2015 Volvo S80 does it in 12.8s... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Most prefabs are like that in ETS2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so third-world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm it's much improved. Banking on curves are more consistent too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 08:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use LHD. RHD just feels too unfamiliar even though I drive RHD in real life. I think it's mainly because I hate the MPH scale.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 20:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a non-issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 08:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well income taxes were raised in the last few years. And there's an increasing number of social assistance schemes and things like GST vouchers. I'm a selfish prick who doesn't care about other people so any money spent on welfare is a waste of taxpayer monies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 18:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure about that. Anyway the suggestion was meant as a joke. No way the government will allow SMRT to go 'backwards' in technology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 17:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overground stations are well ventilated so maybe it'll stink a little but underground stations have platform screen doors to keep the exhaust out. I don't think it's a serious problem. If I'm not wrong, those RER trains in Paris run on diesel and they serve underground stations too (and without screen doors). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 16:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would argue that the government is helping them too much these days. Too much social spending. What happened to the good old days of lower taxes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 15:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we should trial using Diesel locomotives so that a electricity fault won't disrupt services. Back to the basics. Communicate through walkie talkies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 12:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad at least MOE isn't caving in to these ridiculous demands. It's worrying to see the rise in such religious lunacy in recent years with megachurches and the likes. The government must keep true to being secular and not legitimize such nonsense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 12:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would argue anything more than $50/month is too much for what's basically a connection to a cell tower. 

I have no friends, so Whatsapp usage isn't a problem. I'll be lucky to get a message a day... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 08:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time you want to stream a video over 4G, just think of how much it'll cost. I spent 2 years in NS browsing the net on my phone and I never once exceeded the then 2GB monthly limit. Just don't play videos at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 19:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does the US have a higher COx allowance than the EU? I feel that a standardized emission standard will help to alleviate some of these problems.

Isn't the CO poisoning only an issue with very old cars? I've read that since the introduction of catalytic converters, this problem shouldn't be much of an issue unless there's an exhaust leakage. Unless such cars are common in the US?

I live in Singapore, miles away from any emissions saga. The only interesting thing that is happening is a VW owner suing VW Singapore over the emissions scandal, wanting VW to buy back the car. It's technically possible since VW Singapore is not a dealership but a direct 'branch' of VW Germany. Living there means I'm safe from any natural disasters, although I experience an outage about 14 years ago, for about half an hour I think. So no experience with power generators whatsoever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 19:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that's strange. For me any overclock is noticeable. I haven't run into any issues for the past year I've been overclocking. I would guess heat is a potential issue but since the games I play never actually use 100% of the GPU, it doesn't go above 81 degrees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 18:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read about the VWs. I'm guessing the ones tested (Euro 6) aren't the ones with the cheat devices? I'm guessing one solution to exceeding NOx levels would be to have an extremely hot combustion temperature (to produce more NOx and lower COx) and use AdBlue to counter the NOx? I think that's what Citron and Mercedes are doing for their diesels? From what I've read NOx wasn't really a concern for the EU because they are not greenhouse gases. Are COx bad for our respiratory systems like NOx? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 18:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a placebo. If you use the normal mode, it's around ~1200+ MHz, so there's a boost. It's just that you can go beyond the highest setting. A stable overclock I'm using is Power Limit @ 110%, Core Clock @ +175 and Memory Clock @ +150. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 17:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that's the highest the GTX 970 goes with the Gaming App. You'll have to use Afterburner to get it higher. I'm running around 1513MHz on both cards now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 17:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mercedes. If I'm doing okay I'll just buy an E Class and if I make it big in life I can go for the Maybach/S-Class Pullman. 

Also, they have vans, trucks and the Unimog.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 17:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what is VW doing right to get an A rating for so many of its cars? Honestly it's quite amazing that even in urban environments, those A rated cars can still meet the emission standards. They must be performing much better than that when in lab conditions. Also, how do you actually get an engine to produce less NOx? Catalytic converters only reduce COx no? What steps should car manufacturers take?

And yes, my S80 is in the E band. Not that great for my asthma.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 17:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really irks me when people talk about creationism. How can someone be so daft?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 17:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I hear from local and foreign bank's HR here:

Australia: Easy to get in. Singaporeans go there because they can't get into a local Uni (many of my JC classmates did this). Singaporean foundation will make you a top scorer. Not great degrees.

US: Really depends on where you go. UCLA, MIT, Harvard are obviously very good. But places like University of Phoenix are rubbish.

UK: Oxford, Cambridge are obviously good. Glasgow and Manchester are places you go to if you can't make it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 07:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JC will be an uphill struggle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 05:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 05:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's your Chemistry? Bio and Chem are is the usual JC combination. I did Physics and Bio though, as my Chem was beyond help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 15:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I struggled with A Maths, went to JC, struggled with JC Maths but did very well for Physics. A Maths is definitely much more complex than what's needed for A Level Physics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 15:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Err I have no idea how to. PES E don't touch firearms so that was my first experience with a SAR21. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 09:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PES E but got to fire the SAR21 during a cohesion. Never fired any other gun before so these are just general observations. It's quite light and the recoil is really very impressive. It's quite silent too, but the thing jams all the time. Got to fire 10 bullets but then it got stuck on the 7th. The instructor at MMRC couldn't fix it so had to forgo the last 3 bullets. I hope if ever we go to war these things don't jam so often. Was fun anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 11:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't she have gone without being an inconvenience to others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 06:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just the lack of empathy. Aside from that, won't someone be afraid of being caught and panic instead of chilling and having a chat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 15:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nizam then went to the beach to chat with a female friend

WTF?! After all that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 12:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Trump actually good for business? Won't his stance with Mexico cut the number of low-cost workers in the US? Correct me if I'm wrong, but Americans like Trump because he speaks with little filter and political correctness? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 12:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like a circlejerk community of Trump supporters. Just like Bernie supporters. I'm trying to see if there are more 'independent' users who don't try to speak for a community but just from their point of view. I'm not an American citizen, but I did some political quiz on isidewith.com and I'm surprised at the results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 11:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honest question, are there no genuine Trump supporters on Reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 07:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Singapore, where a car is a luxury.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 07:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 1.5L Ford Mondeo/Chevy Malibu, because that's what they cost here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 06:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shall ruin the surprise for everyone. E47 in Denmark has been rebuilt. Kolding is new. Jyvskyl has been rebuilt. Autobahns 95 and 7 have been rebuilt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 06:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting licenses for old trucks are very hard. Just look at how many of those manufacturers still have any mention of trucks with Euro IV or lesser engines. European trucks are about efficiency, I don't think brands like MB or MAN wants their old trucks with laughable engine outputs to be represented in-game. Getting a licence only entitles SCS to certain models, not all trucks from the same brand; maybe rigids aren't ready yet because of licencing issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 06:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for a small family car (MPV or hatchback) for my father. Car should be 4.6m long and give excellent fuel consumption (90% city driving). Car should be spacious in the back and easy for old people to get in and out of. A comfortable and quiet ride is highly preferred, don't want none of that stupid sports suspension on family cars. Must have bluetooth connectivity, GPS, reverse camera and electric seats. And lastly, it should have good resale value. Budget is around Singapore Dollars 130k (~US$97k) or lower. Currently looking at a Citroen C4 Picasso (poor resale value and questionable reliability) and a VW Golf SV (not much equipment). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 06:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any car that has air suspension. Why aren't there more mid-sized cars with really soft suspension? I don't care about handling or driving feel, I just want a car that glides down the highway and bobs up and down over bumps like a boat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 08:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Driving faster than 90km/h. It's ridiculously slow, especially on the TPE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 08:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now to get an Amex card... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 10:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a title like that, I expected a much more in-depth look into the economies rather than just an analysis of the Phillips curve and a over-generalized conclusion into how HK should adopt Singapore's monetary policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 09:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, what's Singapore's 'own role' in Haze? To install gigantic fans out at sea to blow the haze back to them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 09:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 120 isn't really that fast, but crossing a double yellow at a bend is quite the risk to take. I guess Singaporeans just aren't knowledgeable enough about driving in such roads in foreign countries. Just like no one knows how to properly use a roundabout here, or to give way to the right at a non-controlled junction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 07:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You definitely have some mod enabled. There are no such stock trucks. Any screenshots? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 20:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Volvo S80. Making more money to be able to afford my dream cars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 20:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me re-using the 5S' design for the SE shows how stuck in the past Apple is. And also the perennial 16GB option.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 17:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if ST used the inverted commas to quote or to suggest sarcasm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Zero chance" of haze like last year in Singapore and region, says Indonesian official </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 17:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 15:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm quite proud of my mods, which you can find [here](http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=649848705).

It replaces all the interior dashboards in-game for a more authentic experience. I feel that it's important that something you'll be looking at most of the time is as realistic as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 20:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The old model which is more stable? The new one is tall and bouncy. 130km/h feels way too fast. And 69 HP means it struggles to stay there too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 18:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 170km/h in a rental Ka, in the rain, downhill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
