<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7826</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 21:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GEB is really great. His more recent book "I am a Strange Loop" is very concise and makes many of the same points without so many of the clever literary excursions, so that is another option. It also has the benefit of being produced much later in his career, after he had been talking and thinking about the subject for a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 19:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That plus a little bit of shockiness from the needle? A juice or a piece of fruit or candy would probably help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 18:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A complete quadrangle (four points, no three on a line) implies six lines, which you see here. The dotted line is then defined by "diagonal points" of the quadrangle. The four points sectioned by this line form a harmonic set for the quadrangle, and have important geometric properties that, as you can tell, I could go on and on about. But I'll spare you the details. Projective geometry constructions can be very beautiful, yet spare. I think that makes them good candidates for ink? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Projective geometry construction - harmonic set of points. Thx to Jeff Tarinelli in Portland who did it for me yesterday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 02:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 08:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice piece. By coincidence, I'm getting a wrist-to-wrist Turing tribute piece done tomorrow inspired by one of his papers. I'll post it when it heals - look forward to seeing the rest of your sleeve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 20:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respect Queen Latifah and Dolly. Why did they do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 04:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So do I. What do they know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Gilbert and Sullivan style patter song about Gdel's incompleteness theorem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 00:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> in honor of Douglas Hofstadter - cat loop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 00:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't usually think of fireside rooms in Vegas (which is even more hellish than usual this week) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 09:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 06:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. This is strangely riveting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 17:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 16:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should have said "commentaries on Georg Cantor". Cantor himself is brilliant, duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 16:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, ancient Greek mathematical notation had nothing to do with letters standing in for constants, although they DID use letters as numerals for a time. I concede your point, although it is somewhat meaningless! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 23:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google "sacred geometry" to find plenty of pseudo-math quackery. Also the work of Georg Cantor.

(And only slightly off-topic: being a mystic myself, I'd say that bundling us in with the fanatics is a bit unfair. Among my own acquaintances, there are a fair number of hardcore mathematicians who look for deep insight in the universal truths of math.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 22:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how the Greeks say it...just sayin'... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I am a man", says the beard, even before the man himself has opened his mouth, a gaping hole in a hairy surround, grunting his joy and his sorrow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 18:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 20:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard on your body over time, though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 07:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs tl;dr; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 21:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for unintentionally ironic spelling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-06 21:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone give me detailed information about the "heartbeat tones" that were used to track status during the EDL? I would be very interested in finding a recording of that data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> some ents deep in conversation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 07:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 07:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Band-aide is awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-17 21:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, he's got a nice post about this on his blog:

https://irandrus.wordpress.com/2012/06/17/the-periodic-table-of-finite-simple-groups/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> periodic table of simple finite groups - nice job! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-17 19:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 19:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All drummers who have put their backs out moving their kit, take note: who needs a snare, when you use a maraca as a drumstick? She is talented - she's got a real groove despite equipment impediments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-12 04:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it is fascinating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-11 08:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buzzkill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-11 08:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does he do for the edge cases - books he doesn't finish, things like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-05 22:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Systematic and coherent? Maybe. Elegant and expressive? NOPE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-05 21:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Controversy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-05 21:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, Ninja Kill is really, um, *special* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-05 21:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geometry versus algebra?

Can you provide us with anything profound here?

NKS certainly seems to make a case for the importance of finite geometries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-20 23:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Margaret Atwood's "Chickie Nobs" have come home to roost, so to speak... http://goo.gl/L3fL0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-13 07:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Algebraic geometry rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-13 07:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. I have a younger brother with Down's, but he could never do this. He is just as tender, though. I also wish that people could see how awesome they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-12 08:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, the axiom of choice gets you to the promised land of ZFC.

Second, choice is more like "valentine innuendo" than "sexual innuendo." As in "be mine" - which is a choice.

Do I have to spoon-feed you *everything*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-12 08:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no, union includes all combinations. Pairing is just plain old-fashioned! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 16:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh c'mon, the obvious pun is axiom of choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-08 21:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you have lots of existing music, which is good as demo material. On the music side of things, you can just start talking to people and showing them what you do. Indies are a likely bet.

You are probably missing demo material for the sound design side of things. Putting together a demo reel will also tell you if you like the process; sound design is very different than composing. You'll want to do both field recording based and synthesized kinds of sound if you are actually doing the final product. Another option is to specialize and sell specific varieties of sounds, bundled into packages, to be used by film/game people doing foley/fx. There is a biggish market that resembles the samples and loops market for music; engineers in it tend to be really into recording and post-processing. Don't know whether that describes you. If you are more of a synthesizer person, specializing in providing collections of electronic sounds would be the way to go, rather than doing game sound design directly (which also includes location ambience and acoustic sounds). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
