<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4091</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 06:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ggwp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 22:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get you. Too many subreddits are like this. Some reach their peaks and just downwards from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 22:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww that sucks. Id really love to love r/writingprompt and i do enjoy it sometimes but i get frustrated that i cant write shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 21:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soundtrack 2 my life - kid cudi

With or without you -city of prague philharmonic orchestra (goes 15/10 on climax) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 19:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love fucking satan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 19:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darkweb. From browsing to using cryptocurrency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 19:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or anything that youve posted. I was able to search my friend's username using a few keywords from an fb post. Maan he posted fucked up shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 23:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im sold. Im def gonna pick the pico. Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Guess id keep the melo 3 as. Backup then :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you tell me more about why the melo 3 isn't ideal? I was planning to get the bundle simply because it's $3-4 more expensive than the battery-only counterpart. Thanks btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I don't have 22mm or any tank for that matter but i'm def going for Pico now :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 08:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay cant wait! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 16:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do dev my own films. Its the films itself that gets expensive due to scarcity. I literally have to ship them if its something like neopans or ilfords. I got rid of my digital gear and bought rangefinders. Just like you i only shoot digital through phone now. #filmsnotdead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 10:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah fuck skrillex killing that genre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 08:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~0-10~~ 0-60 real quick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 08:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd honestly love to have this power now. There's just something about how the image are captured on analogs. If only it isn't so expensive I'd shoot with film all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can learn fast but can forget it just as fast. I dont know what a verb, adverb, noun, pronoun, etc. but i can learn it quick for a test and forget in a matter of days. I guess the biggest benefit to this is that i can quickly process and respond to critical things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who rarely listens to music for the lyrics, and i guess this is easier to achieve with instruments rather than voice but i love how the intensity is built up on this cover

***With or Without You*** by the city of prague philharmonic orchestra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money, money, MONEY!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who click their tongue. Also, when i do click mine, you'll know im pretty pissed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Refined rotary engines. I feel like there's a potential here yet to be fully realised. Also, actual powersuits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 11:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No whispers for 2 hours. Went to toilet and still no whispers kappa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow. My mom always has these migraines, they were so bad that she's gotten to a point where shed bang her head to the wall just to get a temporary relief from them. She also often has tonsillitis so i'm thinking this is relevant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **"...This world, is an illusion... Exile..."**

This. I always say this line at home, outside too sometimes at random hoping someone playing the game will recognise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zana used to be my bb

I need my russiana back!~~exile~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 06:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started again, ended up with a 136 flat 93res(2 T1s) and a stun/block. Crafted 3rd resist then yolo exalted it and rolled a %hybrid! after crafting %es it's sitting at 740ES. With divine maybe 750-760 which I'm pretty happy about :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 05:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive been to a similar situation before. First thing i did was i ask:assigned them a specific field to work on to. When that didnt work i tried to finish the task anyway but upon submission i asked the professor if i could perhaps work alone instead for the next projects. It was something that i could do alone tho or rather something i was comfortable doing alone. Yours might be a different case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 05:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id drink a girl out of cow titties js </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 14:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm crafting to use it tho I'm aiming around 800+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 14:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> went ahead and scoured it. No luck so far with woes and alt-regal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 11:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was doing it this way until I ran out of woes. Best I rolled was 600 ES. I might try to buy some again tho. Thanks man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 11:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toughest decision of my poe life. Scour and repeat sounds less painful.
and then there's that, what if it could roll a T1 %ES...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 11:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone suggested to exalt it or multicraft it. I'm more inclined to doing a multicraft but  I've never tried it before. How do I go about it and how much ES can I possibly roll on it?

Appreciate any help. thank you

Note: chest ilvl is 100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 09:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant believe no one has said it yet. It's a wallclutch!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
