<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7087</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New writer looking for artist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got several stories that I want to offer to people for free (probably on reddit,) and just sort of get my work out to readers.  I need an artist who is preferably also a no-name looking to show their talent.  I'd love to pay the artist who helps me (if I find one here,) but I currently work a full time job to support my family and can't spare much considering the fact that I'm not looking to make money through this project.  I love these stories and ideas, and I really love writing.  I hope that I can work with someone to create something great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 04:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Commented on your post but im double responding because I, well I double want you to PM me so I can bounce my ideas at you at possibly start writing for you.  Ive never written in a capacity where people other than friends have read, but I know I've got chops.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 04:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been looking for an artist to collab with on some great ideas I have.   I really want to get my stories out and I just need an artist man.  My stories lean toward twilight zone type stuff and id love to talk more if you're interested.  PM me if you are, I just wanna write! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The concept of a handkerchief is disgusting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 02:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 21:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://discord.gg/PZ6KfNA

join that discord server we got some pretty active folks on and im sure you can make friends and get in groups </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 18:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That moment when you're color deficient and atheist and dont know how to feel after looking at this map. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Join our Discord server for people to hunt with! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 15:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've got a pretty nice community going where you can organize groups and meet other hunters!

All you have to do is either download the discord app on your phone, or install discord on your pc, and then join the server via the link at the bottom, and you'll be all set and ready to play with others.

I hope this can help us build the community to have more active hunters, and help people make friends and get the armor and items they want!

Happy Hunting!

https://discord.gg/PZ6KfNA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 17:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I've been in several management and team leading positions and people do not follow the rules.  

I really wish that people didn't cut corners or lied, but they do man.  Denying it will just make things harder than accepting it and moving forward with finding solutions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is DC Rebirth a good place to start following DC comics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 15:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive always been a Marvelite, but now that DC is going on with this Rebirth launch, I'm wondering if its a decent place to start.  Will I be lost if I dont go back and read all the New 52 stuff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 22:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple in my family who notoriously cheat on each other started a go fund me to try and get money for fertility treatments.  They essentially lied about all medical expenses as he was in the army and had Tri-Care.  

Again, they notoriously cheat on each other and constantly fight and curse at each other in front of everyone.

Her parents constantly pay for everything in their lives because he constantly spends money on nonsense and never prioritizes bills or her child from a previous high school relationship.  

They reached their goal of a thousand bucks from a single donor (wonder who it was,) and by the end of the week he bought a new motorcycle. 

Oh, and after 3 years of "trying" (shes incredibly unattractive and over wieght and initiated the cheating,) they now have a baby girl that im sure will be just as terrible as the step kid.

Also, these two are the kind of "Catholics" who have no problem cursing in church and have no idea what the bible says.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
