<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1963</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 02:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on what's being injected? Sort of. Some injections are supposed to go "wherever" in the arm or leg or stomach or hip. Little kids used to get shots in their butts. Some stuff needs to go directly into a vein or a port or whatever but yeah, some things... Stabby Stabby.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [subject1963] Flair Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 20:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 09:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can at least speak for today - I think this was the least crowded summer weekend day I've ever seen. I worked in the parks for several months and have been an AP for as long as I can remember. Most of the lines were ~15 or less. The major ones like Soace Mountain, Racers, etc we're all longer, but it seemed like ONLY those major rides were ever longer than 20. Also, the walkways and stores and everywhere else seemed less crowded. Downtown Disney was almost, dare I say, easy to get through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 19:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just remove the downvote button. It works well in other subs and honestly, the discussion in this type of sub is mostly opinion anyway. What we think about this episode/character/ship/storyline. There really isn't enough here that is "irrelevant" or off topic enough for the downvotes button to be anything BUT a "disagree" button. It's like "Here's my opinion/theory about A B and C." The upvotes are "I agree" or "I find this interesting" while the downvotes are mainly "I do not agree". 

And if there's weirdo posts like you mentioned, that kind of thing goes beyond an anonymous downvote and straight into "Report Comment" territory anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 04:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahahaha. I love you. I make one goddamned wine drunk post about what is actually and without contest a manipulative, predatory, batshit cray relationship and the downvotes come rushing in like A helpers in little black hoodies at that park that one time. 

I feel like this sub is so bizarre because there are so many people on here who are only on Reddit for PLL and don't understand how Reddit actually works. It's not a Facebook like button, people. And it's not like that's hard to figure out - it's been said on multiple occasions. 

Ship what you're gonna ship. Do I still ship Spencer with Andrew? And Aria with that guy who punched nails? And Emily with someone far away in CA who is a normal swimmer who doesn't try to drown her? Or Hannah with Lucas (guilty as charged!). Damn right. I also ship them with a few newer partners but... Jesus, these girls need normal relationships where they watch too much tv and fight over where to go to dinner. 

Ezra is still a creep tho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 02:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which explains why Aria was so fucking upset, because of the fact that she killed Shana.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 00:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear to GRRM, if the first Gendry scene after all this boat nonsense isn't him rowing up to somewhere, in the same little boat, I'm going to be so disappointed. 

I guess they could give him a bigger boat, too. As long as he comes back on a boat. Gotta bring everything full circle. 

And when it does happen, and his doofy smile comes rowing up to wherever the fuck he ends up, I will scream at my television, and I'll take a shot, and he'll be my new top contender. Yissss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 22:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted those pants before but now I want them 10x as much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 06:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I am SO doing that this weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. If I hadn't been drunk when writing the "LIAM GETS IT" post I put up (that was downvoted like crazy, because ~EZRIA (barf), this is what I would have said. That's an awesome point about the actors, too - they are much closer in age so it never really LOOKS weird, which I'm sure alters people's perceptions. In the books, I believe it's A who calls the cops on them while they're at Ezra's place, and he gets full on arrested and charged. Even A (at least in my head) was like "okay, this is fucked up, excuse me while I get your pervert teacher thrown in jail, bye".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 21:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use a physical sunscreen. There's a reason zinc is still on the market - it can be a bitch to rub in but it works like 10x better for me. I'm in the same boat - pale and easily burned, fades to tan. Using a better sunscreen has kept me burn free so far this summer, and I've been outside chasing after the kids I nanny for all day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 09:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, now they have to kill him. Damn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 07:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I eat Cauliflower Rice upwards of three times per week. That's not including leftovers that I inhale at midnight. It's not only a decent substitute, it's like.... A tasty healthy thing. Shocker, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 02:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I turned to my SO and was like "Ah, the sweet sting of bureaucracy."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 09:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the same, and yes, I feel like part of a minority when it comes to this pairing. I like it though - so far, I take it to mean that the bravery isn't completely fearless, that there's a strength of mind that backs up the Gryffindor qualities. Think Neville. He was certainly not the picture of the typical Gryffindor hero, he was more subdued. Quick thinkers, not necessarily strict academics. The best kind of person to find yourself with in the middle of a dangerous situation - someone who doesn't just charge in, head first, but someone who can come up with a battle plan while in the midst of things. (Now I'm thinking of The Doctor. This works.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LIAM GETS IT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 09:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I think you were seduced by your English teacher when you were in high school." 

And

"Try by telling me how you would explain it to yourself!"

THANK YOU, SIR. 

THANK YOU. ~~even if you have douchey nerd glasses~~

I dgaf how many times she says "IT WASN'T LIKE THAT", she was a teenager lead on by a grown man who was secretly stalking her and her friends, to "write a book" about her ALSO teenaged friend who had disappeared and then was probably also around Alison/in her diary before she disappeared?? And also, like, she knew all this but continued to see him/sleep with him because "chemistry" and a bar bathroom make out? 

Liam didn't even need to KNOW the smaller details to know that this shit was way beyond kosher. Thank u bb LIam. Bless. 

And Aria's whole speech about her magic button (cough) and her messy true self and taking all that away is like... No thank you. Liberal emotional awakenings in Iceland do not mean that you can magically erase the ramifications of people being freaked out that you slept with your high school English teacher before AND AFTER finding out he was a lying weirdo who was obsessed enough with your missing/dead sort-of friend that he had a "lair" dedicated to research on her "for a book". 

Also, Spencer's defeated "I got fired!" Whilst falling onto the barn couch with what is probs a whiskey in her hand. Bless. Spencer, even Shady AF Spencer, is my favorite. That is all. 

~~PS am wine drunk right now, if this doesn't make perfect sense in English rn, it makes sense in my head. sorry fam. U da best.~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 21:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your situation sounds so much like my old one. The mom worked from home, the dad owned a business that dealt with custom cars. The mom told me it would be all childcare with occasional household chores, but it ended up being "clean the whole house and do all our laundry and also we haven't bottle trained the newborn yet, that's your job, if she doesn't take it I'm going to be upset with you, bye". 

They didn't like dustpans being used when sweeping. You had to sweep everything from the whole house into one tiny corner of the kitchen, and at the END of the day, after the naps because the vacuum woke up the kids, vacuum up the pile. Okay, kind of weird, but sure. The dad came home one day like just after noon, usually home at like 6, and went NUTS because the pile was in the kitchen. I tried to explain that his wife told me to vacuum everything around 4 but he wouldn't have it. It should be done. "A man shouldn't have to come home to a dirty house after a hard day at work!" He had left at 10 that morning. He couldn't have been at the office for longer than an hour. And his wife NEVER backed me up. This dude was weird and the mom was weirder. She'd tell me to do things one way then, when the husband didn't like them, she'd claim that she'd given me totally different instructions. Wut. 

To add insult to injury, they knew I am disabled. We had long talks about it. The mom wanted to be as accommodating as possible. Instead, she would watch me carry very heavy things around the house and not bother to help. She'd literally just watch me. 

I lived almost an hour from them, but there were a shortage of jobs near me so I had taken this job anyway. I figured I could tough it out for the summer and wait for school year jobs to open up. Nope. I drove the full hour to their house one morning with new craft stuff for the toddler. (I usually work with older children, 5-10, and toddlers are weird). They're both sitting at the table looking very serious while the baby is crying on the floor. I'm thinking something really bad happened so I go to pick up the baby and they tell me to leave her. This is super bizarro so I ask what's up and they basically only say "this isn't going to work out. The house is such a mess every day. What did we even hire you for?" Uh. You hired me to take car of your kids. And I spent 2 hours every day cleaning your house even though that's not what we originally talked about. You are all just crazy. 

They paid me cash for my last week. They short changed me. Over the next few weeks I realized the big red flag - they'd straight up told me that they'd had FIVE different nannies. Their daughter had just turned 2. And they didn't get a nanny until she was almost a year old. Five nannies in just over a year. Yeah. It made more sense then. These people are just insane and this is just a game, or the other five got smarter, faster than I did. Derp.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 11:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, you did almost exactly the thing I want to do! I'm 5'8, topped out at 205. Hoping to get down to your size. Awesome work!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 10:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My SO did the same thing, initially. He was a virgin when we met, I was not but had never acted out some of the raunchier stuff I had always thought about. We finally start messing around with it and he's so weird about it - like he'll choke me and it'll get both of us off then he'll talk about how he doesn't like doing it and it feels like he's hurting me. 

On the surface? It's a good thing that he feels that way. But he needs to be willing to have an open, honest discourse about your sex life. It took almost a year to get my fianc to do that.  Once we talked a few times and I encouraged the things I wanted, he warmed up a bit. (We actually, just a few days ago, FINALLY got to try something I've been wanting to try for years. I sort of just had to jump him and make it happen.) 

If he's not willing to talk to you alone, make a therapy appointment. If he does want to talk to you alone, make a point of letting him know WHY these things turn you on. Not just "I like it when you x/y/z" but "I like it when we do these types of things in the bedroom because I enjoy the sexual release of being a bit submissive to my partner". Breaking it down and separating the word "pain" from BDSM talk seems counterproductive, but when you're talking to someone with no experience with BDSM and you tell them about the other facets of control and the dominant duality of a relationship, it can help it from turning into "I'm just hurting her, even if she says she likes it, it's pain!" 

But the biiiiiiggest thing that you can point out to him is that if he doesn't want to do those things with you in the bedroom, he doesn't have to. That you noticed that he seemed to enjoy it at the time, but that if he has thought more about it and decided it isn't for him, that's his choice. He will probably revisit the idea with you at some point but if he doesn't, that's okay too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 10:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may take a few months. I need to train pigeons first. And catch them. Which should be hard because I'm drinking the wine. Damn it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 09:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is basically me. Lived with the guy all of the 4.5 years, we're getting married next year, and every time I do something dumb I still go *yeah but he probably just thinks you're annoying and definitely thinks you're the worst*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 09:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flair checks out. If you were near me I would bring you wine. How many carrier pigeons would it take to bring over a bottle of wine? New business idea. Writing this down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 09:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to play this game where if a dude sent me a dick pic out of nowhere, I had an arsenal of weird shit I could comment on. 

"Looks like it smells bad." 

"You should probably get that mole checked out. By someone who is not me." 

"I'm really more of a butthole girl, myself." 

"That's so interesting! Did you know I Facebook stalked you and found your mom? How cute! Maybe I should add her so when we get married I can tell her this is how we met." 

Or I just sent back pictures of other dicks. Like, *weird* other dicks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 09:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am also sad about family drama, but reaching the end of a two year period of it. Am currently coping with copious amounts of wine. 13/10 do recommend. Also, never forget about your BFF Netflix.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I realize I've been with my fianc for 4.5 years and, yes, that means he "likes me, likes me", despite the fact that I am all 19 of the major types of crazy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 09:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 09:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please PM me the link! I wish someone close to me had had a community like this a few years ago. Bless you all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 09:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still wouldn't do it. It's the principle of the thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 08:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sometimes known as ~~that asshole~~ someone who compares every single book to tv or book to movie scene. ASOIAF/GoT has been a rare exception, and that's mostly because my SO's friends roped me into watching starting S02E01. I backtracked, I didn't want to stop watching, etc. So now S06 is over and I am just getting around to reading. 

And I've seen all the posts that say "oh! This scene can be sooo much better explained if you read the books" and I don't like it ~~when other people know more than me~~ when I feel like I'm missing something, so, here goes. 

I'm like 12% of the way through GoT and I loooove it so far. I don't have as much time to read anymore (I quit my boring desk job to be a full time nanny to three kids, thus my reading time has been diminished from several leisurely bathroom/reading breaks per day and an hour after work to a handful of hurried moments with the bathroom door locked hoping nobody sets anything on fire.) I have tomorrow off, so I intend to at least finish another half of this first novel. We'll see. I'm currently ~~wine drunk~~ comfortable in my house with no distractions. 

This season tho. Besides the fact that E10 was amazing (and a fan service wet dream) I feel like this season had me more hyped, more excited, and still more curious than any season before. This sub really got me into the ~~tinfoil~~ finer details and theories regarding future plot lines, heritage, the bigger picture regarding the full setting and the characters. 

I feel like, with winter arrived and Jon looking like he's about to swing Sansa around and be all "Do you wanna build a snowman?!" but also being crushed under the weight of all the responsibility constantly cast onto him, and with Dany crossing over (and also going a little bit crazy! And sapphic! Both of which I appreciate), and Arya really maturing a ton in the past few episodes especially, and fucking Cersei fucking Lannister you fucking insane person... 

Where was I again? Right. With all this happening we're at a crucial turning point in so many story lines. Shit is about to hit the fan. Such hype. I know it's not really plausible to include every book detail, especially given the scope of the novels, so I think it'll be interesting to see the real contrasts. Plus I can't wait another 42 weeks or whatever it is for the next season. So far the only weird thing I've noticed is that most of the characters have non-descript book character voices, except Tyrion, who sounds just like Peter Dinklage. Works for me. 

back to wine and GoT, I drink and I read things, bye now ~~nerdlords~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 08:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That and "source?" Killed me. Fuck. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 07:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I'm gonna give her another one, next time I see her. /shakes fist  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 08:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My SO and I used to roll out eyes and didn't care for tiesto one bit. We were super super surprised by this year's set! We stayed the whole time and... It actually might have been one of our favorite sets of the weekend. Wut. 

For reals tho breaking out The Great Escape. I. Can't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 09:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big butt + long curly hair that sheds everywhere + some kind of tactile aversion to loose hair = my life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 09:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This show was the BEST.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 09:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time my SO and I moved, one of his fairly flirty friends ended up being the one who carried my lingerie drawer. The drawer I didn't get to pack into a box because SO insisted he'd carry the dresser himself with the drawers in it. To this day I can't look the guy in the face without thinking about him thinking about me in my favorite corset.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 01:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just reading the word back talk made me flinch. Oh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 01:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fianc (27M) and I (25F) have had a roller coaster of a relationship. (4.5 years) Three years ago I was diagnosed with a degenerative spinal condition. I have depression and major anxiety issues. My fianc has stayed by my side, but I have felt like I'm not getting the support I need. I have tried to explain this to him but I don't think he realized how bad it was until this last week. We joke all the time that he's a robot, but he can be really emotionally lacking (weird childhood) and misses a lot of emotional cues (we're in therapy!) which means that I feel pretty neglected sometimes and it has put a strain on us since it can be hard to get the support I need. 

We had an INCREDIBLE vacation last week. A better week than we'd had in years. Got back this last Tuesday. We were hungover and dehydrated and I had a massive panic attack, and I just blurted out exactly how bad all of our problems were and how alone I felt and how I felt like we weren't being good to each other anymore and I hated feeling like this but I felt like we didn't deserve each other. 

He cried. My robot, chrome, rock of a boyfriend actually cried. Which made me cry more. I almost didn't notice it at first but he started sniffling (I thought we just had the same cold) and then wiping at his eyes and then I looked over and he's got tears rolling down his face. And it just... Damn, you know? And there was lots of hugging and lots of realizing we were being stupid and we didn't know why we were being like this lately. We had a huge talk about attentiveness and affection and love. We are each other's best friends. But we'd been neglecting the romance. 

So yesterday, two days after this happens, we have a therapy appointment. And we talk about some stuff and he finally takes it seriously, and it went really well! He's been so affectionate and wonderful the past few days. I think we finally just had this big turning point where we know we need to keep "dating" each other and we're finally remembering all the perfect romantic magical things that make us special. 

We're making dinner tonight at home and thinking of all the good things we're going to do, and things are great! :) 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 21:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they won't exchange them. I bought a busted bottle last year at EDC, didn't even walk away from the tent. Opened the box, took out the bottle, which had clearly been dropped (it didn't even stand up, just fell over) and they wouldn't take it back. I told them "I didn't do this, you just sold this to me and it's defective" and they were just like "we can't do returns or refunds or exchanges on bottles, its policy." I asked every tent and they wouldn't do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 01:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just squealed out loud at work. Whoops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 16:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 16:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprisingly, the grassy area near Sky Bridge. There wasn't even any puke! That I noticed. Fianc and I spent at least a few minutes there last night and tonight. Grass felt so good wtf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks for an amazing 3rd/20th year, EDC Redditors! 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fianc and I took our third pilgrimage to EDC this year. Our first was in 2012 (the winds!) and he had bought my ticket like a month after we started dating. Last year was okay, but we had a fight TWO nights and it just didn't feel as special. 

I brought it up to Shane earlier in the day on Saturday - in general, barring obvious exceptions, I feel like the crowd this year was more welcoming, respectful, and loving than either of my prior years. We met some amazing new people, I got a sweet piece of kandi, and since we didn't come with a group this year, we got to just chill out and do whatever we wanted and... Well, and make out all over the place, lmao. The 19th is our 4 1/2 year anniversary, and six months since we got engaged. This couldn't have been a better weekend for us. 

Can't wait to see you crazy fuckers under the electric sky next year! I love you all 3
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 06:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. We're staying until sunrise for Galantis, and I'm planning on asking our shuttle staff whose number I can get to call at the end if the access line is five hours long and all that. I'm thinking worst case scenario, we grab an Uber just from the main gate to the outside part of the shuttle lot and explain we just need to get to the shuttle stops. Either way, a wonderful facet of my personality is that I am both good cop and bad cop.  I will ask politely to be accommodated, to a few people, and if not I remind people that the ADA was created for a reason and that I will have assistance or I will sue. *shrugs*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 00:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. I feel like we should get people together to give Insomniac some very necessary feedback regarding their supposed ADA compliance, or lack thereof, and what is really needed in the future for this to be a festival that can actually allow people with limitations to have a good time. I mean, the first 10-11 hours were fine. The whole part about walking in circles with nerve pain and a destroyed back at the end of the night? Or waiting two hours for no cart in sight? Not so much. I'm going to access tonight first thing, and letting them know that this is really not a functional program. I know it's insomniac's fault, not theirs, but at the very least I can tell them that they're sending people like 2+ miles out of their way to get to the wrong place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 23:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much better. We went to Access after sunrise and there was a wait of like 80 people. Couldn't wait that long and decided to take the walk, as long as they could tell me exactly where I was going. They swore that this way that they pointed and told me to turn was the right way. It wasn't. So I walked for roughly a mile before being told that this wasn't the right way. Walked all the way back in, I'm in a lot of pain at this point and it's killing my mood. Finally some helpful person at an info booth told me I could wait another hour for a cart (no thank you, it was already 6:45) or make the walk. I made the walk. I'm feeling it right now but not too bad. I'm just pretty much convinced that getting IN is going to be super easy and getting OUT is going to be a nightmare. Oh well. 

How did it go for you guys?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 00:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How funny! Out of like ten zillion people. Good to know about Gate A. it was so insane getting out of there last night. We'll head back out through A and figure out a ride back to our shuttle stop. THANK YOU! Have an awesome night 2 and hope we run into you guys again! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 23:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had no problem with juscollege shuttles. We got to Tropicana by 5:30, walked right on a shuttle, and were at the speedway just before 7.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 23:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing special. And the tree thing was right in front of one of the screens. Seemed like an odd choice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 23:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We bought some cheap combo locks off Amazon for our Camelbak. Keeps zippers where they're supposed to be until we want to move them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 22:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrapped in neon tape? Like pinkish? If so I think I sat next to you at Circuit Grounds for Adventure Club and part of Eric Prydz! 

This is our third EDC. I've got a degenerative spinal condition so I can walk on my own for short distances but the mile back to the green lot is a no go. And nobody, at any point, told me where to go to get a ride back to my shuttle stop. Access just told me they have shuttles stopping at all the different points on their map and that if one didn't come in twenty minutes, to call. When I finally got picked up ~75 minutes after waiting an additional ~20 minutes at the stop, it was after having to ask at Lost and Found/Info and have them chase a cart down for me. And that cart had two people on it who were just too messed up (insanely drunk) to be able to walk back to their cars, apparently. 

Yeah, there are too many people who take advantage. Tonight I'll just bring my collapsible cane for the walk back and take breaks. Even if it takes me 30 minutes to walk the almost-mile back, and even if it hurts, it'll be better than last nights nightmare. Agh. 

We're taking the Tropicana shuttle. We had no problem getting a ride into the venue, one of the JusCollege people just radioed in and got me and this other guy a cart in. But getting back. Ugh. We left Gate D at 2:30. We weren't able to get to our shuttle stop until after 4:15. That's just ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else having trouble with ADA/cart pick ups? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 12:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the sound of things in the emails I had back and forth with access, this was supposed to be easier than this. 

There have been zero carts by the outside pickup at Gate D. I asked at the info booth and they had no idea. I called the hotline number for access and they said they'd send out a cart, that it would take a while... It's been well over half an hour since I called and 45 minutes since I tried to start waiting where the cart pickup is at Gate D. I'm not supposed to be standing like this for his long and I'm more than a little frustrated. I know Day One is crazy and I'm sure they're super busy but at this point I could have crawled back to the back of the green lot faster than this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 11:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconding this - text that number and see what he has left. Bought a single use kit just to be sure. Super cool guy. Test worked just fine. It can take a while to get a response - he's probably got hundreds of people texting him per day for these things, from the sound of some of the posts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 02:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking love you guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 04:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got my kit last night! Super easy and test worked just fine. Thanks for providing such a great service! 

Gonna have a goooood time Sat   Sun...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EDC packing porn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 20:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 00:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were 20+ highway patrol cars at the Fashion Outlets within the last hour. We saw people pulled over left and right. Set your cruise control and don't be dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 19:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 19:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is King's Canyon looking right now? What site are you at? My fiance's family goes every year in August and we didn't get to go last year because of the fire. We're hoping it doesn't look too bad back around our usual spot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 18:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fianc and I are currently doing PMC through a marriage and family counselor in our area. My FH is a bit of a skeptic and doesn't have a great opinion of therapy, but we're only two sessions in and we don't plan on getting married for a while. I'm glad we have time, because it can take some people a while to come around to the therapy thing and we're going to use the next year to the fullest. I suggest at least trying it out - if you feel you aren't getting anything out of it, there are at-home options that will bring up all the same questions that therapy will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 18:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take a deep breath. Focus on your family first. EDC will be there every year, it's not going anywhere. And it's sold out this year, so if you need to sell your ticket it shouldn't be hard to do so if you do it today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 17:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! And it's right downstairs from our hotel. I'm leaving in 22 hours. And I haven't packed. Sweeeeet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 09:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The two my fianc and I are going to this year  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 09:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put an order through on your website for festival pickup and got a confirmation email, but no instructions on how to pick it up or anything. Just making sure one will be held for me and wanting to know how to grab it. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 21:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so weird! I keep thinking I must have missed something important but I've gone over it like four times and we only have like one or two minor conflicts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 21:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Off work since Friday, leaving in 44 hours, haven't packed anything yet and just set up an almost conflict-free EDC schedule for my fiance and I...  

http://imgur.com/YEkVQCr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 04:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let us know, I'd love to be there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 20:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can always just walk around the speedway to the main entrance, too. I did that last year day one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 18:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What that other person said is actually incorrect - you don't need the actual prescription or a doctors note over here. If you have your prescription medication in the original bottle, which has your name on it, you check it in at the medical tent and they hold it there for you so you can go take it whenever you need to. 

As for your birthday, you'll be fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 18:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the AM before leaving, layer on something REALLY heavily moisturizing - either petroleum jelly or some kind of natural oils. Layering will help plump your skin up and keep it from drying out. If you get super dry while you're there, head to the general store or the med tent - general store might have something for you and if not, med tent will probably have aloe and petroleum jelly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 00:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh Jesus  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 00:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on the app which is pretty much useless lol I'll check his posts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 00:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A week from now I'll be just about ready to go, getting ready at the hotel room with my fianc and pre-gaming! We leave Wednesday morning so I've only got 4 days, 18 hours until we head out for Vegas! It snuck up on me but it really shouldn't have been a surprise with how often I'm just refreshing this sub over and over and over again  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 00:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out r/nanny! There are tons of "mannys" around that are just like you. Society teaches us that women are the main childcare providers and that men are uninterested in the lives of children, but that's changing every day! More and more families are accepting men into childcare positions. And as a professional private nanny, I know exactly how you feel with kids. They're so fun, they are wacky and imaginative and loving, good-hearted little humans. Props to you for knowing what makes you happy even though some people are being jerks. 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 00:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second the link thing, this is just fucked up funny enough to get me through the rest of Friday  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 22:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! We're getting Icees and we went out to lunch and ran around the pet store and stuff. I could be super firm and pull out all the stops with discipline but they're not really acting BAD, just crazy. So hey, sugar! Let's go eat it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 22:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they work with tons of different stuff! They're super helpful. Just let them know you'll need to bring in a few things for whatever reasons. They don't usually ask for a doctors note or anything but you would have to contact them ahead of time so they don't toss your food at security!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 20:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check the sidebar or search the sub. Very easy to find out without cluttering the sub with redundant posts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 20:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is the first day of summer break for my nanny fam (3F, 7F, 9M). Everyone is hyper and nobody can follow directions and I'm at the end of my wits. 

BUT 

It's also the last day I'll see them for two weeks (family coming to stay with them so they don't need me + I'm going on vacation for a week) and I know I'm going to miss them like crazy, so I'm just turning it into a chaos day and we're having little treats as a "goodbye for a while" kinda thing. They're going to be crazy anyway. Might as well make them not hate me on my last day for a while :P  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 19:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can bring in anything that doesn't have a detachable lens. Anything with a detachable lens (namely SLRs but also the "fancier" point and shoots with interchangeable lenses) won't be allowed in without a press pass. If your lens doesn't come off, you're good. If it comes off, you won't be able to bring it in. Simple.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 18:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll be fine if you're under 21. It's on the site. 

ACCEPTABLE FORMS OF ID
Any US government-issued drivers license or ID card containing a photograph and date of birth

US or foreign government-issued passport containing a photograph and date of birth

Foreign government-issued drivers license/ID with color photocopy of passport (Not valid for 21+ wristband. To purchase alcohol or enter VIP areas, a physical passport or US ID will be required.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 10:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contact Access to ask. They're the ones who would know. Access@insomniac.com 

They're pretty understanding when it comes to health issues. Just explain why you need them and ask how you'll be able to bring it through security without them tossing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 09:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calm down. I'm trying the stupid app and it has issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 09:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhhh I need to hear this at EDC D: !!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 09:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhhh I need to hear this at EDC D: !!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 08:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rachel got her first Good Girl Justice Boner and I couldn't be more proud. That she was willing to work with Sarah at all said so much for how she realizes this is her problem now too, and she needs to get involved with the right side - albeit in strange ways with cars and Ira the "Abercrombie Model". It was a power play but it wasn't entirely personal, as so many of her previous deeds were. Spending time with Charlotte, especially, has been good for her I think. I also noticed that Rachel seems to have the biggest troubles with her speech when talking to Evie - makes sense because she's under stress, which is undoubtedly hindering progress. 

Also seen: the return of Feral Helena, bless. "You look like roast pig." As she just pats his calf after straight up murdering a dude with a bow and arrow. Blesssss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 07:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally called the Helena thing but it was awesome nonetheless. Haven't had a good Helena Murder in too long. Alison is willing to die for her sestras. Helena is willing to kill for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 06:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zedd vs DB is my biggest concern. My SO and I's two favorites.... Shiiietttt. We've seen Dash like 8 times before but never Zedd, but Dash is our thing, but Zedd is also our thing... ugghhhhhh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 06:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. You might get lucky with someone letting you in, but why risk it? Yes it's risky to bring your passport, but protect your shit and you should be fine. Showing up to the gates hoping that they accept something even though it clearly states otherwise in the rules is not a wise decision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 20:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wear it! In 2012 I wore my favorite outfit two days in a row - the wind shut shit down on Saturday and I didn't feel like I got a "full use" out of the outfit so I just wore it again Sunday. Unless you're like soaked with sweat for hours on end, you'll be fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 01:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My nanny fam is just generally good to me, which is nice. They're also super accommodating with time off, they respect any repercussions I've had to give for the kids, they tell me to stay home and rest if I'm sick, and they're friendly and respectful in conversation. The $500 check for Christmas didn't hurt either, but it's understandable that not every family can do that. Nice cards, stuff like that. The stuff you'd do for a spouse, minus certain aspects :P 

The biggest thing that has let me feel appreciated in this family as opposed to others is respect. My last family changed my pay on me, or tried to get me to do extra chores, and once told me that my job wasn't a "real job". The family before that, the parents were jerks. The kids were jerks too but the parents were worse. They played nice but they tried to get me to do laundry, dishes, stuff they just didn't bother to pick up during their night even though I was only supposed to clean up kid breakfasts. 

Respect. That.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 01:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Accept it. Sleepovers are a whole different territory full of crazy behavior and kids psyche each other up.  If she offered its because she knows it'll be more work than you think it will be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 23:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay, you're like me! On the pale end of the spectrum, similar tones, similar eyes, and pinky purple lips look amazing. Great pick!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 20:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are too many comments here suggesting you get some kind of device (white noise machine/fan/whatever) to cover up the noise. 

NO. Your mother is a grown adult and her involving you in her sex life after you have made attempts to warn her is fucking unacceptable. There are two people you need to talk to about this, and you need to talk to both of them. 

Have your sister call your dad. Have her tell him that you asked nicely, that you tried to give them time at home alone, but that it continues and it is keeping you from sleeping and it's disturbing. 

Then talk to a counselor at your school. Seriously. This could impact your performance and a parent refusing to shut their mouth during sex and keeping a kid up is beyond wrong. Let them know you were living with your dad, I'm assuming peacefully, and that you had to move in with your mom and that this situation has gotten out of hand. Tell them what your mom said: basically "oh well" and refused to quiet down. Tell them that you'd like it if someone could reach out and let her know that it's not okay and that it's affecting your sleep/stress/school performance. 

Don't just let this go and don't let this continue with a fan adding to the noise. This behavior is bizarre.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 18:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any time someone says "But it's a drryyyyy heat!!" I want to stab them. I'd rather the humidity of a late spring in Texas than a scorching desert.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 03:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck yeah. I've been hoping for an update to this one. So happy for you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 03:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pathological liar, flaming narcissist, abuser, quitter, complete and total asshat. My father. 

Took me way too long to realize I shouldn't have to fight to be in your life. You should have fought to be in mine. Now you never will be. 

Peace out, ya little bitch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cut contact with my emotionally and physically abusive father four years after he abandoned us for his new family. Finally realized I was wasting time chasing after someone who doesn't give a fuck about me. Feels good, man. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 03:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 02:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take a picture of your taco poop, send it to her, and be like "Birthed that baby you announced to everyone! I named it Asshat, after you!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 20:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take the Stila eyeliner!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 20:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you. Luckily my kiddos (3/7/9) understand that K gets headaches and can't play a lot sometimes. Luckily I don't do cleaning so my responsibilities on migraine days are "make sure kids don't set things on fire or end up in hospital"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 19:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is such bullshit. Don't sell your customers shuttle passes with a faster route being a perk and then not deliver. JusCollege is fucking up hard this year. It's still better than driving but we bought these so we could get in and out faster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 19:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lyrica gave me a similar reaction and didn't even help my pain. Fail. Get your doc to prescribe new meds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 04:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot about this, and also, you can go to any ER if you're in crisis and it'll be covered. ER services are covered, even if Mental Health. For routine help Beacon works well but if you're in any kind of crisis at all relate to parental issues and mental health GO TO THE ER. They'll blood test you and help you out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 01:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds good! I'll PM you my PayPal email.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 00:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interested in the Too Faced heart blush and Nars Laguna!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 21:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some folks hold it under their tongue for as long as they can take it, too. Taste is nasty so I could never, but a friend does it and it hits faster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 20:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were acting immature and left in the middle of your wife's birthday dinner, because you were upset by the behavior of one stupid friend, and you're surprised that they think you were being an asshole? Let me repeat this. 

You left. In the middle of your wife's birthday dinner. Because like a petulant child, you couldn't just be a mature person and deal with some crappy friends. 

And you don't understand why she's upset? 

Look, in the long term, you need to be clear with your wife that she's a different person when around Alex. My fianc had this friend who was similar to Alex and who I hated. His name was Shawn and he was a raging narcissist who kept trying to get my guy to break up with me. They'd been friends for over a decade. It took FOREVER for my guy to see that this friend was miserable and toxic, but it eventually happened. Did I storm out on birthday dinners and snoop through my then-boyfriends phone for information? No. I let him know, over and over again, that this friend was bad for him. He eventually saw what I saw. 

But in the short term (as in, immediately) you need to see that your behavior is only working against you. Alex tells your wife she needs to leave you, Alex is a bitch, whatever. When you act like a child and can't behave like a functioning adult on your wife's birthday, you just prove Alex's point. Your wife starts to doubt you. She's going to act up. And you never realize that it's YOUR behavior that is changing your wife, not Alex's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 19:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely get in contact with a hairstylist. They have tons of ideas for quick hair makeovers. Something as simple as a clip-in bun or braid and working with your existing hair can look amazing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 04:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Body Glide! It's cheap on Amazon and works so so well. Powders tend to melt off and deodorants can really irritate your skin if you use it often. Body Glide is super neutral, no smell, and stays forever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 04:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. You'll still want your passport. Most places are super strict about ID and I've seen people get turned away for foreign ID cards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 05:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually might be Catherine tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 03:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably won't be able to bring in either. Depends on who checks you but not worth bringing good stuff and having them throw it away in front of you. Last year I brought in a cream concealer stick for touch ups and tinted Chapstick and was fine. 

They don't allow you to bring any liquids in. It's kind of a stupid rule for makeup but the wrong security person will throw it away when they check you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 02:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you hit the nail on the head. Work on me, and if he wants to come crawling back into my life later, approach with caution. I just need to stay strong and stop giving him these damn chances. I just feel like something should be said, but I wouldn't know what to say anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
