<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4592</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The road was already there AND they only put the panels on one lane.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 15:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paradox wants turks to have the historical borders, so no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get out of here with your logic and sense.
We have to take care for EVERYONE!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worlds first solar road opens in France: Its ridiculously expensive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 20:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S,o in effort to combat propaganda, the state created a propaganda department. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monte Paschis Fatal Sin Brings Nationalization for Oldest Bank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 14:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europeans Are Getting Poorer, And More Unequal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 14:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ragusa, the With a little help.. achievement especially.
It's not about difficulty, but about how tedious it is. 
All the waiting, placating Ottos and praying that they don't ally France...

I never had enough patience to finish it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's their culture, you bigot. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Witch-hunt

Wiki is a good starting point.
As for Sweden specifically https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Witch-hunt

Edit:To clarify. The witch trials were very rare until the reformation and early modern era. 
During medieval times the Church mostly considered witchcraft to be a superstition and not worthy of investigation. Heretics were a different matter.

The rulings of Council of Frankfurt and Council of Paderborn are especially interesting. As well as opinions of Church Father St. Augustine and Pope Gregory VII. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Less intrusive church led directly to witch hunts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that the whole Communism thing vaccinated us against the censorship prevalent in western Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope in Christmas Speech Blasts Vatican Resistance to Reform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No but it was example he used so, yeah.

Plus Kaczynski is far from Hitler or any dictator for that matter.
Don't get me wrong, he IS a dick but not competent enough or crazy enough to try to become dictator.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if Chechnya were to fall under some little Hitler and we'd say: fuck them, we got bigger problems to deal with.

It already did and EU did nothing.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what are basic values of EU? If you don't mind me asking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he should be more careful with what he says. 

It's not that I like what Polish government is doing with polish Constitutional Court, but right now the EU has more than enough problems. 

This will only give more ammo to radicals across EU, supporting the narrative that EU is club which seeks to punish anyone conducting independent policy. And I don't think we need to lose any more members. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Many ways to divide Empire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think he did it for any sane reason, or at least not that one.

He was offered a place in a state home several times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will be an autopsy but I don't think the results will be made public, unless there are any relatives or indications that it was murder we will never know for sure.

But yeah, with that kind of lifestyle it was probably lung cancer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was mentally ill and obsessed with burning stuff and covering himself in ashes.

And when I say stuff I mean everything, wood, rags, tires, plastic, newspapers. The guy was really into fire and smoke. 

He refused home several times and instead lived in abandoned stable, as far as I know he wasn't dangerous to anyone, at worst he was annoying because of the smoke.

The fact that he made it to 60s is a miracle by itself.

Edit: here are some more photos http://hradec.idnes.cz/foto.aspx?r=hradec-zpravy c=A161220_143724_hradec-zpravy_the </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 12:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but you are suspect and rightfully so. While I do know that many of you fled your countries because of local violence I also know that many of you did not.

In fact many among you are terrorists or their sympathizers, many others would gladly see homosexuals killed or imprisoned and woman on trial for being raped.

And many more are simply looking for easy money.

So sorry but our life, my life, is on the line here and I can't take that kind of risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 12:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you telling me that humans are not idea-carriers?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 12:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, well I shouldn't be too surprised I didn't know this. 

Aspergers is hell of a thing.

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 11:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know it's bad when an oligarch formerly connected to secret police sounds sane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 11:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, can I ask a completely unrelated question? 
Is the pepici thing just from Cosmo or is that a real word for us?
And if so why? I mean its derived from Joseph/Pepa but why use it for Czechs in general? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 21:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any astronomers writing stuff down in 15000bc are probably aliens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 14:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but I think that the methodology is a liiitle bit off on this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to (really) divide Turkey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 14:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to (not) divide Austria-Hungary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 14:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 14:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, well at least they now how to use twitter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 21:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was bound to happen eventually, there were already way too many close calls. 

Maybe now the Germans will understand what kind of mess they are in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 21:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is means? And which war are you talking about? There have been quite a few.

Anyway I said MOST of the time not all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diplomatic insult </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Armenians did have a state once, palestinian Arabs never did. 

Edit: Until they got Jordan, which included much of the west bank. Too bad it wasn't enough for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see the one I posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who says its a fault. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is the original? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They broke the law, they must be deported. Its simple as that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. The Joint List which is the third largest party in Knesset will be surprised to hear that they didn't join the institution they sit in. 
2. They never had a country, there was Mandate of Palestine which was administered by UK and before that it used to be part of Ottoman empire. There never was a state called Palestine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Fights $13.6 Billion Tax Bill as EU Lifts Lid on Case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not as easy as it used to be. Barely a decade ago there was barely anything bad to say about EU, NATO or USA. 
But now with ISIS, Syria, Brexit and, lets face it, EUs failure that is the refugee crisis its harder than ever before to convince people that Putin is actually a threat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that was UN, Arabs didn't accept that ruling and were very clear that they don't want any kind of Jewish state to exist. Preferably no Jews at all but if there are to be Jews they should be ruled by Arabs.

BTW that proposal didn't give Jews all the land they have now.

UN did it anyway and told Jews that if they want the country they have to deal with Arabs themselves. Arabs started war with stated goal of pushing Jews into the sea.

They lost. And Israelis took some of their land.
Arabs didn't like that so they attacked again few years later. 
And lost again and Israelis took more of their land. 
And so on and so on.
Most of the time the Israelis were heavily outnumbered and outgunned, not to mention without any help from Europe.

Over time the Arabs mostly decided to let it go, except for Hammas and Fatah who still want to kill all the Jews and "Reclaim Palestine".
Arabs who live in Israel and have citizenship mostly don't care.

The territory used to be administered by UK so thats where some of the confusion comes from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 23:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any idea for achievements to pursue by developed and westernized Pueblo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 10:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but [esk zbrojovka](http://www.czub.cz/en/#/) still does.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 20:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good article and really informative.
I once tried to implement AES just to know how it works and boy that was something. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any idea what to use instead of JAVA for the whole "multiplatforming" thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about OpenJDK?

Oracle is involved in that project right?
I mean, I'm not a lawyer but are we sure that they can't somehow shut it down or mess with them? 
And just to make sure that I cover all my nightmare scenarios, can't Oracle try to make the language itself proprietary, the syntax and all?  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 14:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  From the weakness of the mind, Omnissiah save us

From the lies of the Antipath, circuit preserve us

From the rage of the Beast, iron protect us

From the temptations of the Fleshlord, silica cleanse us

From the ravages of the Destroyer, anima shield us

From this rotting cage of biomatter,

Machine God set us free

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No but we could make stuff more effective with relatively few adjustments. Say vitamin C production would come in handy and that's just one gene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genetic diseases are, almost without exception, incurable. Once you have them they are with you for life and that life can be very short and painful because of them.

Unfortunately even if you yourself don't show any symptoms you can pass it to your children, only option, until now, was to get checked, which is not cheap, and if you are positive not have any children.

In this case the problem is in Mitochondrial DNA. 
You see inside all of our cells are these incredibly small things called mitochondria. Very long time ago they were bacteria but our very distant ancestors (Billions of years ago), absorbed them. Since then we and all other animals and many other organisms use them as powerplants. We provide protection and food, and they convert the food into energy.

Mitochondria have, over time, lost most of their DNA. They didn't need it since we took care of most of what it was responsible for.
But some of it is still left. If it is damaged you can suffer from some pretty horrifying stuff. And in worst case you can die, young and in lots of pain.

Now the mitochondria are passed from mother, they are present in every unfertilized egg. 

This technology allows us to take out the defective mitochondria and replace them with functional ones. The child has all the characteristics of its mother, all of that is encoded in nucleus of the egg which is NOT changed at all during the procedure.
Only thing that it takes from the donor is functional metabolism.

Now here come the awesome part, since mitochondria are passed from mother to child we can, over time, essentially wipe out ALL mitochondrial diseases just by performing mitochondrial donations on sick human eggs.

This technology was already tested in USA several years ago and it's completely safe. The children are healthy and according to all data show no signs of abnormalities. Unfortunately due to luddite scaremongering the US government decided against allowing the technology, despite being advised to allow it by its own agencies and experts.

And thus children kept on dying, in pain, couples experienced multiple stillbirths, women were abandoned by husbands and slipped into depression. All because people were afraid of something that is impossible.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 07:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harsh, but there is just no other feasible way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be bigger but, well Ottomans happened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job UK. Hopefully others will follow. There is no reason to let people suffer if we can prevent it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 19:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost as if the pedophilia thrived in places with lots of children and few people in charge of the, but that can not be true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess we need few thousands dead for people to give a shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a fan of Chinese government but this is probably a good thing to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice that at least some mainstream politicians get that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Machine morality and ethics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been pondering this for some time and I wanted to know others opinions about this.

The control problem is, in a way, something humanity already encountered. After all, society is composed of individuals with conflicting goals and yet we do not, for most of the time, slaughter each other for food.

Yes there are laws, police, army etc. but when you think about it, unless people get desperate we don't need them that much.
Because, in a way, most of us have our own inner police officer who watches everything we do. 
Some call it conscience, you could also consider it to be amalgam of social norms and morality.

What I mean to say is, the best way to control AI might be the AI itself. If we could teach AI to be moral and to have sort of conscience, we could minimize the chance of it hurting us.

Of course it wouldn't be sure thing, morality does not have just the good side after all. But it would be better than leaving the responsibility to humans, who, after all, are proven to be unreliable.

What do you think?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes it less ridiculous but it does not make it a good feature.
With coalitions turned on player has one more ticker to worry about, most of the time you don't have to care for it, but take a Kingdom William the Conqueror style and suddenly you are black sheep of the Christendom. 

It makes wars into a minefield because the calculation is more or less hidden. Sooner or later you will have to throw away your claims and you can forget about being next Genghis Khan or Justinian.

All and all it was a useless feature and a bad idea, not to mention the fact that it's very ahistorical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Labours Starmer Says Brexit Must Include Migration Curbs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Essentially if you conquer too much land other rulers will band against you, as other countries would in EU4. Unfortunately they do so without regard for your CB, their religion, mutual relationships or distance.

Therefor if you, for example, conquered entire Egypt as a Catholic ruler you would face coalition of Caliph, Pope, Roman Emperor and bunch of others. 

They later nerfed that somewhat, but the feature was so unpopular that they made it optional.
That is you can disable it if you don't like it and get the achievements anyway. They even admitted that it was not exactly a good idea, and by making it optional they more or less consigned it to oblivion.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Copy of my post from /r/eu4:

Sorry but this feels wrong on several levels. 

1. Since forever have been players asking for more diversity, for the game to be about more than just Western Europe. This update does the exact opposite. The ages are even named after events that primarily concerned western Europe and its colonies.

2. The abilities for specific nations are going to railroad the game even more than it is. Time to prepare for more Blue Blobs, giant Kebabs and Iberian Americas. 
Am I seriously the only person around who doesn't want every game to turn out the same? I get it realism is cool, but these buffs make the game arguably less realistic. There is difference between realism and historic outcome.

3. The goals seem like really unimaginative and boring. Everyone gets the same ones it seems and again they seem custom made for traditional "easy" nations like Portugal, Castille, Ottomans and France. These nations didn't further buffs since three expansions ago, at very least.

4. The golden age mechanic is so gamey that it makes me laugh. Magic button that lowers cost of all your stuff for next 50 years, that you can use only once? Seriously?

Sorry this seems like a worst patch in long while. And arguably waste of developers time. I wouldn't be surprised if it ended up like coalition feature in CKII. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but this feels wrong on several levels. 

1. Since forever have been players asking for more diversity, for the game to be about more than just Western Europe. This update does the exact opposite. The ages are even named after events that primarily concerned western Europe and its colonies.

2. The abilities for specific nations are going to railroad the game even more than it is. Time to prepare for more Blue Blobs, giant Kebabs and Iberian Americas. 
Am I seriously the only person around who doesn't want every game to turn out the same? I get it realism is cool, but these buffs make the game arguably less realistic. There is difference between realism and historic outcome.

3. The goals seem like really unimaginative and boring. Everyone gets the same ones it seems and again they seem custom made for traditional "easy" nations like Portugal, Castille, Ottomans and France. These nations didn't further buffs since three expansions ago, at very least.

4. The golden age mechanic is so gamey that it makes me laugh. Magic button that lowers cost of all your stuff for next 50 years, that you can use only once? Seriously?

Sorry this seems like a worst patch in long while. And arguably waste of developers time. I wouldn't be surprised if it ended up like coalition feature in CKII. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make America (Measurably) Great Again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germanys Next Nuclear Headache Is Over Cash or Reactor Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And often those monsters as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I heard it the Google is getting rid of them for PR reasons. 
Every time the BD robots show up in news bunch of people start yelling "They'll tak ur jerrbs!" and thats not something Google wants to be associated with.

Plus they can't sell them to military since Google didn't want to deal with DoD, and those things are really expensive so no one else is willing to buy them.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 20:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One correction, Bohemia converted willingly and that conversion was not related to northern crusades. The Great Moravian prince Rastislav even requested missionaries in 9th century, Cyril and Methodius, authors of Glagolit alphabet, precursor of Cyrillic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They fly flag of Greek Orthodox Church, which happens to be crest of house Palailogos. 

It's not Byzantine flag, well except for the time period.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big part of Christianity is that the body is not the real you, or at very least there is more to you than just the body. Therefore as long as the corpse is handled tastefully you can do pretty much anything with it.

Thats why Catholic church had little to no problem with autopsies. Hell Holy Roman Emperor Frederick II passed law requiring all future doctors to perform autopsies, that was in 1200s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you will never be a skull. We don't live in DnD, once you die here you are gone. The leftovers can rot in the ground, be burned, used for science or even art but it does not affect you in any way.

tldr: Corpse of a person is not the person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 13:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck them all to death... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 10:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the slaves got payed and were not slaves at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they are from Germany so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know, but I really don't want them to get more fucked then they are and right now it seems that's where we are going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 14:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit I don't know. I'm scared as fuck about what is going to happen. 

We got Puntin pushing from the east, immigrants from the south, bunch of close calls with ISIS in just last month, EU establishment acting like everything is fine and on top of it the USA will have total nutjob for a president.

So forgive me for getting little bit desperate since right now all I can see is one potential disaster next to another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 12:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so what a fuck is going to be done about this?

Am I seriously only one around who thinks that its time for action, indictment, inquiry, rerunning the elections, something. 

Jesus Americans start doing something to stop this madness.
I am serious here, time for shock and questions is long past, get your shit together and start doing something.

I'm not american and I don't even live in USA so I don't know if there is anything I can do to help, but you are and you live there.
Contact members of electoral college, force recounts, do something, while there is still time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might be best to not leave anything to chance. 

Time to get the Crown Jewels, you do yours, we do ours, just hope the Hungarians can get st. Stephens crown from the chest properly this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey can we join too? If we get Lusatia we will help you get Tyrol and minority areas in Romania. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/Austria Can we get the KuK monarchy back together?
Because things were not going well since it fell apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 10:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about Soviet computers but there are lot of Czechoslovak computers on sale if you know where to look. 
Of course the shipping can be a problem but most people around here are at least little fluent in English so you can strike a deal. 

Try this site, [http://aukro.cz/historicke-pocitace-ceskoslovenske-pocitace-100822](http://aukro.cz/historicke-pocitace-ceskoslovenske-pocitace-100822).

It's something like Czech ebay, the link will take you to section dedicated to old Czechoslovak computers.
The Didactic computers are the most common, followed by PMDs.
Sadly it's kind of hard to get PMD power source but you can make one your self if you look up the specs.

There is also a Polish version of Aukro if you are interested [http://allegro.pl/stare-komputery-pozostale-77927](http://allegro.pl/stare-komputery-pozostale-77927) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German refugee murder arrest in Freiburg heightens tensions - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 10:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> European Parliament committee says reject EU-Canada trade deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece to pay out benefit to low income pensioners - PM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VWs Lost, Destroyed Phones Are 'a Bright Red Flag,' FTC Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well right now the Greeks don't have the best reputation and at the same time EU wants Turkey to take care of the refugee problem.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ECB Expands Stimulus to $2.4 Trillion as Monthly Purchases Slow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.K. Isn't Safe From Terror Threats While Russia Aids Assad, Says Spy Chief </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now Volkswagen's Porsche Is Being Investigated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Religious leaders push for Muslim alternative to Peppa Pig - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love to member RTFA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 12:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, we indoeuropeans are not very inventive folk. 

At least when it comes to words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 09:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asylums are not a bad idea. With modern methods they can be used to help people while still being more cost-effective and reliable.

Unfortunately there is a "collateral damage", meaning, patients who get worse due to mistreatment, isolation from outside society or influence from other patients. I have seen some relatively functional individuals get completely deranged in record time, after about a month in an institution. 

On the other hand I know about many people who got better and are now reintegrated into society, they now have jobs, home, even started families. Not just addicts, anorexic and suicidal people, but even guys you would run from if you have seen them before, and for a good reason.

However in some cases only the most radical solutions can help.
For example, in my country the most dangerous sexual deviants, I'm talking murderous psychos, serial pedophile rapists etc., get a choice if they want to be interred for life or submit to chemical or mechanical castration and a long treatment with eventual chance of release into society. 

Many have taken that path. But it's very rare since they have to be proven capable of understanding their situation and commission of doctors have to believe it can actually help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think, and my thoughts cross the barrier into the synapses of the machine - just as the good doctor intended. But what I cannot shake, and what hints at things to come, is that thoughts cross back. In my dreams the sensibility of the machine invades the periphery of my consciousness. Dark. Rigid. Cold. Alien. Evolution is at work here, but just what is evolving remains to be seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has been some promising work in that area. Stronger, smarter, healthier rats are not impossible. But the regulations make actual sale of such pets almost impossible. 

But if you are willing to fake some info and break few laws you can get your hands on some pretty weird critters.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 17:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thing is that when you initialize something with some default value you must keep that in mind whenever you use that variable/structure. If you forget what value it is you can end up with code that compiles but is completely useless. 
The compiler won't scream and you will waste time tracking an issue you could have easily prevented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 17:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good article. 
It makes one wonder how many more "standard practices" exist, wasting cycles and compromising security, just because no one looked deeply enough or too few people read an article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merkel Seeks German Full-Veil Ban in Convention Pitch to Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 15:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 23:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most of their restrictions are tailored to minimize chance of their community being compromised by outsiders. Meaning, they don't want their believes to be challenged. The self sustenance part is more of a means than an end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VANCE MOTHERFUCKING STUBBS  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so what did the Amish you met tell you about their believes?
Because those I met, almost completely secular expats btw, told me the whole self-reliance/distance from sinful outside deal. 
Which is btw supported by other sources such as wiki.

Edit: One more thing. I completely agree that religion should not be exempt from criticism. In fact, criticism of religion is how Anabaptist/Mennonites/Amish got started, well it's how all religions got started.
Also I do agree that approach to technology Amish took does NOT make much sense.
I just think that its important to consider their real positions, not what outsiders think their positions are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I struggle to see a pattern here. Well except for one.

It seems like he deliberately picks the worst people he can find. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 14:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. That's part of reason why they don't want it. 
The rest is that it would bring them into closer contact with outside world, and since they consider outside world to be sinful they want to avoid that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 14:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those things are great. I had so much fun in them as a kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 14:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about you reading up on their believes instead of judging them without any idea what so ever. 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mennonite#Worship.2C_doctrine.2C_and_tradition

Edit: In other words: It's better to know than to believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 13:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is discouraged but not exactly banned. The real problem for Mennonites is that Mexicans are mostly Catholic and well that has some implications in their theology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 13:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Electricity requires you to be connected to grid. Building materials can be substituted more easily.

Mennonites are basically 19th century preppers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 13:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The idea is to be as independent as possible. 
Until very recently the electricity required large central source, using it means that you have to be connected to outside world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, to be honest I was considering editing the headline at first, I thought it was a typo. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $38 Billion Finnish Fund Moves Assets to U.S. as Europe Founders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mook: Clinton's 'deplorables' comment 'definitely could have alienated' voters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 18:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we could settle for Thrake first. Leave them the city but take the countryside. That being said there are some logistical problems.

Namely the bunch of kebabs that occupy that region.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 18:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could consider this to be a good news.
I mean, sure Austrians didn't pick the populist that's nice. 
But the fact that all other major parties had to band together to win, and using candidate who holds some pretty fringe views that should be concerning.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 14:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice job bot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clash in German forest as red line is crossed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 14:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 14:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention Elon Musks ex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 12:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much every country has it. What varies is how visible and harmful it is. 

Countries with many checks on power and strong, politically active society like Austria, Germany or USA can endure incredibly corrupt/crazy people in charge and recover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, saves resources for next round of deportations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is also the fact that calling your country Macedonia gives you implicit claim on the region called Macedonia, which is partially in Greece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit. Well it was shot in the dark, but to be honest there is so much ridiculous stuff about Trump that I hoped that no one will notice. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
