<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7498</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 08:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In no particular order..

- Flowers for Algernon by Daniel Keyes
- East of Eden by John Steinbeck
- 11.22.63 by Stephen King
- To Kill A Mockingbird by Harper Lee
- The Count of Monte Cristo by Alexandre  Dumas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome haul. I have pretty much every one of these on my to-read list still, the only one i've read being East of Eden. Since you said you haven't read in awhile it may be wise to start with something that won't require much commitment in order to get you back into it. Night is a short one, but might be painful to read though judging it solely on its topic. I'd say Vonnegut might be a good start, although he has a very particular style his reads are rather short. Only ones i've read by him so far are Sirens of Titan and Cat's Cradle, both being simple to read while still dense with ideas.

Don't be afraid to jump into East of Eden when you're feeling up for it. I find Steinbeck to be very simple to read and he also produces beautiful imagery. It's an amazing character study of good vs. evil. If you like books where you are strongly connected with the characters despite their flaws and these characters grow throughout, then you will like that one. It's one of my personal favorites.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what i've been hearing. Looking forward to it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard great things about it. I will definitely check out your recommendation as well, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I put my holiday gift cards to use this weekend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 08:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nerlens No-L  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 03:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished off the second half of 11.22.63 by Stephen King in 2 days, which is over 400 pages considering the book is about 840 total. This was quite an impressive feat for me. It had me locked in the entire time. Look up a description of it and if the subject matter appeals to you its definitely worth a go.  

I still need to give more of his books a try, but I can confirm from this one that his storytelling is very engrossing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 21:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Set my goal to 52 this year. In the middle of my own reading challenge right now but I plan on reading some long ones this year once I finish. Can't wait!

[Goodreads](https://www.goodreads.com/user/show/2829998-ian) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 05:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the suggestion. I've intended on reading more King since finishing 11.22.63. I saw the movie years ago but forget enough that the book should still be a new experience for me. I haven't had a chance to pick up any Stephen King books because I started this list, but I definitely plan on it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 20:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great job! I have read 25 books since early August, which is a lot for me. So now I am trying to decide what should be my goal for this coming year. 93 would be quite the feat for me assuming I don't read a large number of short reads.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 20:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really look forward to Cuckoo's Nest. I saw the film years ago and I think I really liked it but can't remember that much about it. Your description of the imagery sounds like something I would really like. We might have similar tastes. If you haven't read East of Eden yet I would highly recommend it. It really paints a picture of each scene as it goes through and each character has so much depth. Also, I would recommend Flowers for Algernon. Both of these books are emotionally engaging and have social commentary relevant to our everyday lives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! Will you be starting from the beggining of the list? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Along the lines of coming of age I really liked Perks of Being a Wallflower narrated by Noah Galvin.

Some others I thought were fantastic performances, although im not sure they fit what you're looking for:

* Lolita narrated by Jeremy Irons

* East of Eden narrated by Richard Poe

* 11.22.63 narrated by Craig Wasson

* Ready Player One narrated by Will Wheaton  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay good to know. I actually usually like depressing books, and music for that matter, if thats what you mean. But I will definitely keep that in mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 15:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really looking forward to being introduced to those writers. Ive been looking into Bukowski's work for awhile now but haven't read any yet. Post Office is last on my list so i've got a ways to go. The good news is if I like it enough I can jump right into more of his books.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 02:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That copy of Monte Cristo looks awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Just curious, which ones did you love the most on the list?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Update) After rediscovering my love of reading I will attempt to conquer a list of 40 (mostly) classic books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 14:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Original Post](https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/51phev/after_rediscovering_my_love_for_reading_i_will_be/)

(Scroll to the bottom of list for updated post)

From original post:

"It has been over 6 years since I graduated high school, and I'm still in school studying boring old textbooks to earn my second college degree. During that span of time, I thought that someone would have to pay me to get me to read outside of my schoolwork. I suppose I was too tired of staring at all these words for class, not to mention staring at a computer screen all day at work, and it was easier to lay down afterward and turn on the latest hit Netflix series. 

That was until recently.. For a couple of months during the summer I had no classes, freeing up a lot of time during my weekends. I was playing with my phone one morning and found a free trial of Amazon Unlimited-- so I decided to download the ebook of *1984* by George Orwell (Can't remember what made me pick that one but I knew it was considered a classic). The book completely sucked me in. I don't want to put out any spoilers, so lets just say that some of the story scared the shit out of me. After that, my college buddy mentioned he watched a cool tv series called *11.22.63*. I looked it up and found out it was also a Stephen King novel about JFK, time-travel, and altering history..woah..sounds like I could get into this. "Oh shit, the book is over 800 pages, I will never be able to get through this." Well, I checked this one out from a nearby library and decided to give it a shot. I couldn't believe how quickly I got engrossed in the story and didn't want to put it down. The storytelling by King made me feel like I was actually in the main characters shoes. Loving every minute of it, I finished that behemoth in only 2 weeks. I knew I needed to find another read fast to fill the void inside me that *11.22.63* left behind. Then, my best friend from my hometown suggested I read *Ready Player One* by Ernest Cline as it's one of his favorites (We're gamers at heart). This one..well this one was just flat out fun. I finished this one in another week's time. 

After telling my friend about how much I've enjoyed reading lately, he told me he was also looking to read more. We both wished we read more of those so-called classics back in high school and so on. So I suggested we do a reading challenge of some sort. Well, we decided to come up with our own list. He would pick 20 from a few online lists of highly regarded books and I would pick another 20. We both picked some of the same books, leading to us just filling out the list with a couple of our own choices. We picked our books from the following lists:

[Reddit's Favorite Books](https://www.reddit.com/r/raerth/comments/cpxkq/reddits_favourite_books/)

[Guardian's 1000 Books](http://www.listchallenges.com/guardians-1000-novels-everyone-must-read)

[and also here](http://www.loved.la/books/genre/Collections/1001_Books)

Once we had our 40, we shuffled the list and agreed to read them in the order they fall. So here is the final list. *drumroll*


**Book List**


* Cats Cradle by Kurt Vonnegut

* The Old Man and the Sea by Ernest Hemingway

* Brave New World by Aldous Huxley

* All Quiet on the Western Front by Erich Maria Remarque

* American Psycho Bret Easton Ellis

* The Perks of Being a Wallflower by Stephen Chbosky

* Fahrenheit 451 by Ray Bradbury

* Man's Search for Meaning by Viktor Frankl

* And Then There Were None by Agatha Christie

* The Call of the Wild by Jack London

* Sirens of Titan by Kurt Vonnegut

* The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy by Douglas Adams

* Any Human Heart by William Boyd

* Cosmos by Carl Sagan

* Animal Farm by George Orwell

* One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest by Ken Kesey

* A Farewell to Arms by Ernest Hemingway 

* Watership Down by Richard Adams

* Walden by Henry David Thoreau

* East of Eden by John Steinbeck

* A Clockwork Orange by Anthony Burgess

* The Giver by Lois Lowry

* Of Mice and Men by John Steinbeck

* The Last of the Mohicans by James Fenimore Cooper

* A Wrinkle in Time by Madeleine Lengle

* Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas by Hunter S. Thompson

* The Things They Carried by Tim OBrien

* The Great Gatsby by F. Scott Fitzgerald

* The Handmaids Tale by Margaret Atwood

* The Long Walk by Stephen King

* The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night Time by Mark Haddon

* The Stranger by Albert Camus

* To Kill A Mockingbird by Harper Lee

* Wuthering Heights by Emily Bronte

* Crime and Punishment by Fyodor Dostoyevsky

* The Catcher in the Rye by J.D. Salinger

* Catch-22 by Joseph

* Lord of the Flies by William Golding

* Slaughterhouse-five by Kurt Vonnegut

* Post Office by Charles Bukowski "

**New Post - Update:**

It has been about 3 months since I started the reading list and I have been enjoying every book for the most part.. some more than others. I have currently made it through the first 13 books up until Cosmos by Carl Sagan. In addition, I have read 5 more awesome books not on the list! This was because my friend was a bit behind me and I wanted to let him catch up so we could enjoy each one together. 

The 5 not on the list are:

* The Journey to the East by Herman Hesse (actually read this for school, but was pleasantly suprised) 

* Cannery Row by John Steinbeck 

* Lolita by Vladimir Nabokov

* Flowers for Algernon by Daniel Keyes

* The Most Dangerous Game by Richard Connell. 

My favorites so far from the list of 40, in no particular order: All Quiet on the Western Front, Perks of Being a Wallflower, Man's Search for Meaning, And Then There Were None, Sirens of Titan, and Any Human Heart

Currently, we skipped ahead and are reading East of Eden because many people have been trying to get me to read it and I gave into my own desire to do so. We will then be jumping back to Cosmos after!

I wanted to post this update to have an open discussion about the ones I've read, as well as the ones that are still to come. I did get a lot of people in the original post suggesting I write reviews on Goodreads as I go through them. While I did some written reviews early on I have been slacking recently, but I intend to be more committed in the future. I am still very active on Goodreads otherwise. Mostly rating books and adding books to my reading lists. 

[To anyone who would like to follow my journey on Goodreads](https://www.goodreads.com/user/show/2829998-ian)

Happy reading! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been on my own list for awhile. Maybe I will have to read it asap. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I will check their stuff out. Any specific titles that are your favorites?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 03:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love this heading.


11.22.63 by Stephen King got me feeling lots of emotions.

I also second Flowers for Algernon. Right in the feels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suggest me a book for a friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 03:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My buddy and I are doing a book swap on Christmas this year so I want some suggestions on what he might like. 

Books he loves:

Ready Player One - His absolute favorite book. He loves the gaming aspect of it. Also the love story tied in. 

11.22.63 - says he's a sucker for love stories. 

Perks of Being a Wallflower- again, love story aspect of it. Straightforward writing that gets you emotionally involved. 

American Psycho - I think he likes stuff that depicts a lavish lifestyle like the life of Patrick Bateman...Money, wall street, clubs, girls, etc..not necessarily the all the fucked up stuff in it. 

Elon Musk: Tesla spacex and the quest for a fantastic future - He likes inspiring and motivational stories. He wants to start his own business one day and loves technology. Wants to make a boatload of money (don't we all). 

Harry Potter series- loves Harry Potter. This may be hard to match with the stuff above but thought I would mention. 

I understand most of this stuff doesn't mix well, but I wanted to include all I could to narrow down what he looks for in a book. I'm thinking something with technology/gaming with a love story would be great. 

I might try to read the book myself before making the purchase. So, what do you think Reddit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. I have added these to my list! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 02:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome collection. I absolutely loved 11/22/63! Could you recommend other King books, or any book for that matter, that really connect the reader with the main characters like 11/22/63 did?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 20:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11.22.63 confirmed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions for fans of The Man in the High Castle by Philip K. Dick. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 15:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 03:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read Cannery Row a couple weeks ago. Loved the writing. Can't wait to read East of Eden as I've been hearing such great things about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 17:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He's got a can up there" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 17:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I think you will like it in that case. It's definately not horror by any means. You could always read a preview of the beginning on amazon or goodreads to get an idea. I would stay away from the TV adaptation until you read the book first, but I enjoyed both of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 03:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished All Quiet on the Western Front today. I've gotta be honest, it's probably my favorite one I've read from my list so far.  The language used and description of the pain Remarque was able to accomplish while still making it simple to read was admirable. I won't get into much detail, but the part where Paul goes home on leave and describes how out of place he felt really struck me hard.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 22:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to hear! I hope it has that effect on me. I will be starting that one very soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 22:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard 100 years of solitude talked about a lot on here! I have been reading physical copies and intend to keep doing that for the most part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 22:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly recommend 11.22.63 if you're intrigued by the topic and if you don't mind love stories. It does look like a brick of a book but it is a breeze to read while still including a lot of historical content. It has a feel about it that gives the younger generations an idea of what the overall lifestyle might have been like in the late 50's/early 1960's. 

I can't say that I'm all that well-read or anything, so I don't know that it stands up to powerful pieces of literature or anything, but it is a good story. I suppose if you have liked any other Stephen King works in the past you might like it. It's not known as a "scary" novel by any means, but some parts were rather eery to me due to the fact that someone is attempting to change a gigantic moment in U.S. history. 

I have heard a lot of great things about Jane Eyre so I will definitely keep that one in mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 20:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I know most of these books are pretty common, but that's quite impressive. I'm looking forward to seeing what I'm getting myself into. I will also check out those King novels for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh oh. I was kinda hoping to hear it was a breeze to follow along dispite all the fancy words supposedly used. I'm glad I didnt include that yet as it would probably halt our expectations of when we would complete the list. It's still on my personal list though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there were a couple in there we added at the end to fill out our 40. I believe it was on one of those lists though. Maybe instead of classics  its more like..a list of stuff taken from other lists of stuff to read before you die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive actually already started rating them on goodreads! However, I havent written reviews yet but I think your right, I definitely should. I guess its hard for me to come up with what I should say and I find it tedious. I'm really going to try to find time to do this though, even if they are very short reviews. 

I also wanted to create a list on goodreads with these titles, but it is apparently public. I dont want everyone editing it. Any suggestions on the best way to make a locked list on there? Maybe just create my own shelf?

Once I get better at using goodreads I will for sure share with you and the rest of r/books </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah im trying to be careful not to wear myself out. The good news is a lot of these titles are pretty short. 

I've heard great things about East of Eden! I have a feeling i'm going to like it. At least I hope I like it, cause it is one of the longer ones on this list.  I already own a copy and have been eyeing it down for awhile now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for all your suggestions. C P seems to have those vibes so i'm glad you told me that. I'm making a promise to myself that I won't be scared away from Dostoyevsky even if I don't like it. Ive seen many suggestions on this subreddit for Notes from Underground, The Idiot, and the Brothers Karamazov. 

Not what I was hoping to hear about American Psycho as I will be starting that soon. Its also interesting timing since I will be at the beach next week. Should be an odd read on the beach to say the least. I remember seeing the movie years back, but it has been quite some time and I dont really remember what happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 17:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will check these out. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 17:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, some of them I guess arent necessarily classics, and a few of them we added on afterwords that might not have been on those lists I mentioned. 

I tried to pick stuff that ive heard positive things about and also interest me. I thought if I included some of the classics you mentioned it might deter me from continuing with the list as some might be tough reads or be harder to get into. Things like the Oddysey, the Illiad, and Moby Dick intimidate me for some reason, even though they could be my favorite books and I just dont know it yet. I guess I also didnt want to make my buddy run away from the challenge by putting a bunch of historical classics in there. But they are definitely books I want to get to at some point in the future, I just figured they would be better off on a list that is completely my own.

Not gonna lie, Crime and Punishment is one that intimidates me but I thought I would give it a shot cause of reviews and the topic intrigued me. If I like what I read with that one theres no doubt I will check out others by Dostoyevski and also give Tolstoy a shot. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 17:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip. I tried to pick ones on my end that interest me, but there are some that look rather intimidating. Luckly though, many of them are relatively shorter in length with only a few being over 400 pages. The few that are longer than that are the only ones that I'm worried about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 15:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is already on my to read list! I will let you know when I finally get to it, but i definitely plan on getting to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 15:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been intending on reading this ever since I saw the movie End of the Tour. It might be one of the first things I read after im done this list. 

I have a question for you though. Is the book relatively readable with characters that are easy to follow or is it more like the type of book that is hard to put all the pieces together and follow along? I seem to enjoy books the most when they suck me into certain characters and their different environments. Since it is a massive book, i'm hoping it will have that effect on me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
