<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject792</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 09:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ramsay killing roose has been in your face foreshadowed for ages now, and although annoying, is in keeping with show ramsay. Not really that in keeping with show roose, but hey, it so seperate from the book that i don't care anymore.

 However, even in show, how does Ramsay expect to lead the boltons and its 'coalition'? The men are loyal to roose, they know how mad ramsay is. For reasons unknown the young karstark didn't care that roose just got stabbed by his notoriously insane bastard son, unless he's smart and is playing a longer game. Which is what im interested to see how it plays out. I would be very surprised if that maester, whicj i assume has served roose for god knows how long, keeps what he saw to himself. As things continue to unravel for Ramsay, i wonder if he the men around him will stay loyal as they have no reason to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 14:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its doesn't sound legit as theres no mention of certain characters that we know have big parts in the episode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 14:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "hold my beer"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 14:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even in show logic terms, unless jon is up and running, how is anyone gonn a stop ghost from ripping his throat out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 14:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't like this idea of seperating each argument to a seperate thread. The whole point of this sub is about discussion. If its a worthless meme, it will drop like a stone anyway. A massive initial response is expected and a part of this thread, why run from it? Having each thread appear on the sub is the best way for people voice/argument/discussion to be heard, nothing good can come out of dividing it up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 13:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is almost a poster for game of thrones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 09:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is faker than your mums tits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 09:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> horrible accident, but the 2 lorrys on the other side did extremely well not to make it worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 19:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my point is that the 'meltdown' happens everywhere anyway. Its a completely pointless thread. All opinions should be treated equally anyway, i mean how far do you go with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 19:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> apart from littlefinger? Alright, he didn't exactly come from nothing, but i'm not sure he would class as 'highborn'?

If varys is to believed, which i don't btw, he started off as a petty criminal and he's done alright.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 19:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which i hope they get rid of in the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 18:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i mostly agree, generally speaking any voice against the show is immediately shouted down by its defenders, who seem unable to take any criticism against the show.

 But there are still plenty of book readers (or show watchers) who will offer an opinion against the show, it just takes longer for that argument to pick up steam. Altho yes, often this leads to it never being seen, because its downvoted into oblivion before it gets a chance. 


The real difference for me, very generally speaking, is that there are a lot of people that simply won't take any critique about the show unless its a positive one. Whereas book readers are fully prepared to find fault whilst critiquing the books and its author.

 Imo, its very rare that i see an unjust criticism of the show. It annoys me when a well thought out argument is downvoted simply because they don't like a negative opinion on the show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 14:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep, you have to guess a lot of stuff lately, not much of it making any sense. Gone steadily down hill for sure.

 Still annoying, but i've come to expect it now, so i can still enjoy it. Show loyalist will rage on about how they need to speed things up and fit it all in etc, but last seasons 30 mins of arya sweeping a floor, begs to differ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 14:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow what a reference. Now i must find the kissy sellout remix of the theme tune </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 14:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are big problems with some stuff at the wall, but as said already, they're not really protecting the corpse, they are just staying loyal to jon and protecting themselves in the process. I guess they left the body in the open as its a message, he was a traitor in their eyes. Why he stabbed him now is questionable tho. 

Its not explained why mel can come n go, but thorne shouldn't have  a problem with it. What is baffling tho, is why Davos isn't pinning her down to gett he details of whats happened to stannis and shireen. Stannis, the person he's devoted his life to for how many years? and yet is happy for mel just to walk off?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 13:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is uncle kevan number 1 lannister atm? Did jaime get anything through tywins death or is he still bound to the kingsguard? Cuz i'm looking forward to jaime bustin up some sparrows. Kevan, with the lannister heritage in mind, is surely the only person who could stop cersei and jaime from wiping them all out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 12:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WORDS ARE WIND </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 12:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no mention of tormund or bran, i'm thinking fake. Plus ramsay killing roose so early woudl be madness and would make bookreaders like myself cry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 19:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [gwobbllelellalalalala] (https://49.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m035lbssZ11r94ueyo1_500.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 20:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wildings led by tormund are gonna help dead jon out yes, but do you think there will be much of a fight? If thornes killed i'd imagine thatll be the end of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 20:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah last scene is the balon bungee jump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 20:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tommen doesn't wanna see his mummy.

Margery is turning to the dark side, but it doesn't matter cuz jaime makes it clear to everyone that the lannisters n co can fuck shit up at the drop of a hat.

Robby strong has a nibble. 

Tormund arrives with an army of wildlings, unsurprisingly pretty keen to help if it means killing crows. Stand off.

Balon, who everyones forgot about, has 'a moment' with his daughter. Subsequently dies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 20:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah good point, hadn't thought much of it before. Maybe Brienne will feel a bit of guilt? Not sure how the show will go about it, in the book she's more complex. She's so desperate to be a 'proper' knight. But ends up breaking oathes and changing shields. I wonder if she will have an enlightened moment or carry on the journey becoming the exact opposite of what she wants to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 08:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 23:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 22:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great song by a great band. Glad they're back on the scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White Lies - Farewell To The Fairground [Indie Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 22:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 22:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah thats what he says, but if he wanted to hide it, then it would be part of a cover story no? Altho i don't think he can warg, personally i'm in the 'varys is a faceless man' camp. Either way i would be very surprised if theres not a big reveal about him this season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 20:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> techincally no, but that doesn't matter anymore anyway. Throughout the series (esp this season i think) and books, people change, especially after 'dramatic' turns in their lives. I don't think it will be the same Jon after resurrection. Its not as clear in the show, but he's very uncertain and ponderous, constantly questioning himself whether hes doing the right thing etc. After rebirth i think he'll be far more ruthless and straight to the point. For better or worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 20:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yh this could be the gift, of rickon? or simply more men? Incidentally, was it just bolton troops fighting against stannis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 19:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in the show isn't he an ex pit fighter anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 19:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeha, i think it will be the sma ein the books too. In the show varys birds will probs dramatically reveal this  just as jorah gets stabbed up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 19:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure that will come up in the next episodes. I'm going for a mel jumps in the fire with jon and boom ting, jon is reborn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 18:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, if they made that make sense then fine. But the fact the hord knew of khal drogo, but not dany? and more so took danys word for it, just after laughing at the rest of what she said? Stinks of lazy writing to me, but hey, at least we had a scene where a sweaty dany was whipped eh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 23:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow gross, she's super old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was a good scene. I really really hate Brienne tho. The shieldchanging oathbreaking wench. I hope she meets her end soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah it makes little sense. The wildings are already beyond the wall, all he's done now is make an enemy of them and divided the nightswatch at the same time. And the fact the whites are coming, which for some reason he doesnt care about. Its one of those book vs show things again, where it makes sense, if not still short sighted in the books. In the show, its more like, i'm the boss, fuck jon snow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 19:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yh it really is the little things that bother me. Not the fact that they killed him off, but how. Poison would've been bearable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 19:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah man, thats a good way of looking at it. Maybe still room for a dornish master plan afterall. Although i do think dorne will eventually fall into civil war, in book and maybe in the show too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 19:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read it as ott foreshadowing for show watchers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 19:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> could not agree more


 if only he had the bad poosy line, he couldve been up for an emmy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 19:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8.5 out of 10?!?! you are madder than king Aerys on his stag night.


Some people jump so quickly to defend the show and refuse to accept any criticism towards it. And no, its not just book readers upset that its 'off book'. Its the piss poor writing and direction. Last series the show gave up trying to make any sense, to run logically, its almost a lack of respect to its viewers. More and more they seem happy with sweeping ideas and shock value, rather than joining the dots in a coherent narrative. It stinks of a  'don't worry, we're making millions' attitude 'it doesn't matter, this matters' etc. The same path as shows like the walking dead and back in the day, lost went down. They could so easily have a tiny bit of dialogue here, a little scene there, to join it up, but no. It doesn't matter.  That trend seems to have continued this season.



Having said that, yes, there was good things about this episode. Ramsay and Roose and most of castle black was great. But, no negatives? Really? Where to begin. Hide there, oh, found you. Disappearing dogs. Wheres Tommen? How long was that boat trip and why didn't they turn around? Why is trystane on a different boat, then shit at fighting. Areo hotah?! Jorah still in his blood soaked clothes? jorah and daario 'heading north' managed to find exactly where they landed? No one recognising khaleesi? Personally i think this will be on of the lowest ranking episodes, the only thing it does is what they wanted it to do, and thats look forward to the next episode. 4/10


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 08:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do we know far from meeren did jorah and daario go? Very concerning that jorahs no longer takes care of his appearance, that blood stained shirt must be smelling a fair bit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 08:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a really lucky coincidence that jorah and daario found the exact place where drogon landed with dany. Whats are the chances eh?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 08:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> didn't she say she was 200 years old when she met thoros? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 08:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as ever, its the way they go about it. They have time for 'bad pussay' but not for a sensical plot for doran? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 08:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry to disturb you further in relation to your mother, but women don't stop having sex at 40... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 18:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whos saying the sand snakes killed him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 16:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep, used to it by now. Any comment against the show is downvoted to oblivion. Strange, considering how they've chosen to adapt the source material. And yet a sub supposedly devoted to that material, won't hear a word against the adaption. Judging by the opening episode tho, plenty of people will of finally had enough. Although, again, we will all still watch it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 16:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 of your 5 a day right there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 16:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're insane. Trolling or real, you're still insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 15:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was an instinctive bite, because its a badger. Then he shit himself and ran away, albeit, only as fast as he needed to. The dog hero comments are coming in (and are not sarcastic) which is confusing me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 14:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yh it couldve been to play/mock attack or a simple nibble. Either way the bullshit about running it away from the owners is being taken seriously for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 14:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this guy gets it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 14:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either its genuine and nonsense or trolling, but being treated as sanity. Reddit often struggles with sarcasm, soo.... i give up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 13:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like any criticism of the show gets downvoted to hell on this sub, which is strange. But maybe, yet another slap in the face with a D D shit stick will be enough to shatter peoples delusions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 13:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seriously tho, this statement is nonsense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 13:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually i've known many a badger intimately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy St Georges day England </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 10:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 10:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is a badger. Not a honey badger. I can confirm (i don't what the dog in the clip is, some mongrel cross by the looks) labradors very much enjoy brutally murdering badgers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 08:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh. Yh, thats what i thought.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 08:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cuz he ran away after shit got real? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 08:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On their own most dogs are likely to run. Two or more and that badger wouldve been ripped to shreds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 08:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 23:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really hyped for the show, yes, but last season kinda changed my stance on everything GoT. Only today i finished the rewatch in preparation and it struck me that season 5 is absolutely dire. Even the bits i thought were good at the time look dodgy rewatching. Some of of the dialogue is laughable, never mind the inexcusable 'shock factor' scenes.


I really hope this season nails it (and of course i will continue watching) but for me, GoT has become a fan fiction to fill the time between books.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 20:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoulda cast jayden. Also will tom jones and pierce brosnan be in this one too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 19:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bran sees dead people. 

Danys on holiday living out some dothraki bdsm fantasy.

Brienne DOES NOT confirm stannis is dead.

Ghost rips ollys throat out. Full screen, close up, gullet munching action.

Tormund takes no shit. 

THE END. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 08:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> feedback, the links i've already clicked on should be easier to identify. Light grey doesn't look hugely different imo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 20:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an icon. You only need to turn on mtv to see how influential he was. And he did with style. His own style, relentlessly. RIP to a genuine legend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 20:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i believe that your beliefs on prestons jacobs beliefs are cancerous also.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 20:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "a bunch of unrelated facts".... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 19:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i'm not sure on this speculation. Dany, their mother, can't control them, but indiana quentyn can? I would say running away along the way they came (edit, whilst they are being chased) is more likely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 19:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dead tired at your lack of enthusiasm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 19:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, i like watching both, but alt shift tends to just state the obvious, telling us what we already know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 19:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad preston fleshed out the 'Quentyn is alive' theory. People are really angsty over his videos huh?

 Personally, i can't see how anyone can say for certainty either way (and get upset with the otherside of the argument) Clearly there's enough evidence that GRRM intentionally wrote it to spark the readers curiosity. The possibility that he's still alive is undeniably there, however unlikely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 14:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was only slightly better than the entire season 5. I'll give it my lowest rating ever, 7 thumbs up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 13:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mr burns in the background "excellent" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 09:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 95% of the time when i think food smells horrible it's just onion and or garlic cooking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 00:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure about ramsay killing roose. I know it seems likely on the show, but bookwise Roose is completely in control, he knows how mad Ramsay is and his men are loyal to him, not the crazy dog loving bastard freak of his. 


 I can see an alternative where Roose, who has already essentially seen his plan to secure the north fall through, figure that he's in an unwinable situation and withdraws from winterfell. Leaving Ramsay to sort the mess out, which means in reality means sacrificing his son as a punishment, if not to help him escape. Ramsay, keen to prove he's actually useful, jumps straight in, but enevetibly loses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 22:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2006 is coming back hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 20:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> on the subject of cleganebowl, surely this would be a terrible fight? The hound is badly injured and even after recovery would never be as good as he was, and even that would be nowhere near enough to beat his brother anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 18:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so why does he tell him to fuck off?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 18:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also, this must be after they retake winterfell with the help of the vale? Littlefinger is confused and worried cuz a dead jon snow(stark) just trumped him and became king of the north.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 18:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You fucking legend! This is why i love this sub. I remember last year half the series was already figured out by super analysing the trailers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 18:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true, but there is a lannister king atm, that debt looks safer. Stannis, in the show (apparently), completely failed, costing them big with zero chance of being repaid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 18:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you got downvoted for this, but i have often thought that jaquen could just be a con man. Is it ever properly explained how he was captured to start with?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 18:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like this idea. But i'm not convinced she will make it as 'no one'. Shes too much of a stark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 18:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If i was talking about pretty much any other character i would agree, but not Arya. We're given so much time with her, unavoidably investing ourselves into her story. Why else go into so much detail with her if she is simply another character. Why make us care, why follow her at all? Clearly she is meant for something, even if its a 'something' thats happening around her. 


And no, things, especially in the world of GRRM, cannot just exist for their own sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 21:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is plausible fo the show, except theres a lot of miles to cover to get that point. They would have to 'wrap up' the house of black and white pretty quickly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 19:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know! seems to have sparked enough conversation?! I thought arya was worth discussing anyway..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 19:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is a wildcard i guess, but as you say GRRM uses her to show us whats happening in different parts of the world. I totally agree about the 'slow burn' sentiment. Hopefully building to something great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 19:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not getting paid as such, just punishing people for not doing so. Its mentioned  a few times in the show that 'the iron bank will have its due'. They don't like being messed about and have a reputation to uphold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, i don't think Dany is going back via braavos, although that doesn't rule out Arya being sent near Dany. Not sure why she would want her in her company anyway? I guess Tyrion must have met her at some point. Unless as you say, she takes  a new face. Who and why i don't think we have any clues on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the point of Arya? (Spoilers Everything) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To start let me say that in no way is this meant to be against the chracter of arya in the book or show. Both i think are brilliant. 

However, for such a 'main' character, what is the point of her? Where is she going to end up? What impact will she have on things, if any? 

For me, for nothing to come from her journey would be more of a let down than Dany dying in the desert. I've put forward a few theories of how she will eventually get back to westeros but the way the show is going has me leaning toward a different idea involving mr onions and sansa. Previously i thought that Arya would be 'contracted' to kill littlefinger, for all his dodgy dealings, that would eventually piss off someone enough to put a price on his head. Subsequently some kind of drama happens involving LF, Sansa and Arya, equalling a death. But now, looking at the show, i think that the same thing will happen, only with Davos as the one with a price on his head. 

The iron bank are surely pissed at the apparent waste of money backing stannis was, with no chance of getting paid back. Scores need to be settled. Davos was the man behind the deal, so i think he will be the one who Arya is sent to kill. Resulting in any number of outcomes, although the accidental death of Sansa at Aryas hands wouldn't be out of place. 


I can't see how Arya can get drawn back into the story if not to assassinate someone. 

.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> makes a good point about the brotherhood being at riverrun, i forgot about them. Although i do think its bronn grabbing him, 'jokingly'. 


Is everyone certain that its jaime stabbing the mad king? I thought that happended with more people around them and it looks like robert strongs shadow anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its not baseless or pointless. There's plenty to go with the theory, which is why it is one. But yeah, its just speculation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just him. And its only speculation. But because you don't see him die and the dialogue beforehand. (and the huge plot points,  but they are circumstantial) Brienne, whos whole story is about how desperate she is to become a proper knight, is reminded to "do her duty" by stannis. 

So yeah, if he is alive, it would be no surprise at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [yahuh] (http://www.reactiongifs.us/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/shut_up_baby_futurama.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, after all the hatred towards politicians lately, turns out all party leaders pay their taxes. Great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sooo, is this real? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 18:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah me too, it could just be sansa moaning at him about how bad ramsay is tho. I've thought for a long time that the vale forces come to help the starks reclaim winterfell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 18:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All those horses he's been eating have made him massive. 


The whole dany with the dothraki makes me think that they will somehow show dany how to tame him properly. At least i hope. More wandering round the desert is not what we need. Narratively speaking, she must be there for a reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 18:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh how i would love it to be roose. Behind sansas back. Let me have winterfell, and ramsay, and you can keep the rest of the north..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 21:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah, thats someone trying to stab up zombie clegane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 20:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roose. The brotherhood without banners. Oldtown.


Oh, and [never forget] (http://imgur.com/gallery/vyBayME) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 20:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Davos and sansa recruiting the northern houses? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 20:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe a bit of time away from littlefinger, and the poison he's been giving him, will have changed him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 20:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks the same kinda snowy setting as the only littlefinger glimpse we see? I would love it if Robin comes to sansas help in taking back winterfell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 19:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like LF is meeting with someone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 19:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is littlefinger doing in the snow? Probs meeting with someone, but who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 19:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah it bronn, but not 'attacking' him so much, just playing around? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 19:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree, why would Tormund think that of Jon anyway? Looks like he gets in the thick of if before relying on the resurrected Jon to out flank the phalanx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 19:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> top right of that image catches my eye, but that looks baratheon colours?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
