<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4585</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adults of Reddit, what core class in high school is the least useful in normal adult life? Example: Eng Literature, algebra, geometry, us hist, bio. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 15:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 14:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All over a state standardized test that they couldn't replicate after. I was in 4th grade taking pass testing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best of ifunny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 03:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 02:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elyse, do you ever get weirded out thinking about how some 13 year old kid has probably wanked to you? This can also be answered by Lawrence's hernias as I know they've been wanked to ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 15:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a family vacation I tricked my younger cousin, who's 10, that when you turn 13 you turn into a bale of hay. Sounds preposterous but yes me and my older brother took a week out of our life to trick our cousin he's going to turn into a hay-bale. We got everyone in the family in on it so no one called us out on our bullshit. By the end of the week he believed us. He even called his dad, who wasn't with us on vacation, and asked him. Little did he know he had already planned for that and told his dad about our plan. His dad said that we were right and he was going to turn into a hay-bale. The cousin broke down and started crying because he didn't want to turn into a hay-bale. His mom had to come over and assure him that he will not become a hay-bale. Then I had to tell him sorry and explain it was all a lie. He doesn't trust anything I say anymore  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 15:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you getting all flustered and acting upset that people enjoy the taste of it? If the majority of people agree it tastes good, although most agree it's bad for you, then maybe you're the one who's different. It only tastes like shit to you it seems like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [serious] What is your great teacher story? What impact did the teacher make on you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 15:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 13:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do any of these free the nipple teen girls realize that boys and girls have the same amount of Liberty when it comes to clothes at school? A boy can't wear a shirt that is hanging barely above his chest, he just doesn't bitch and rebel about it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 13:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I don't want a daughter, if I look on my Facebook and see my daughter post something similar to this I'm going to Kurt Cobain myself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm not really atheist but y'all will love this gem of inaccuracies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 15:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lolz Why am I such a fatty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 20:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 15:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *tips fedora*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 01:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude that sounds awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 18:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot to address you saying he doesn't have a hatsu. I never thought of that and that's a good possibility. He's one of the original spiders so he didn't make it in by defeating an old member so he might not be that strong compared to capable nen users. He could definitely be a pure enhancer, someone who only enhances himself with no special power. I'd love to see how he handles someone with a good hatsu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 18:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This wasn't pretentious at all. What you said is actually very well thought out. I do have one thing that goes against him being an air fighter, that's his sword style and how he thinks to use en more than the average hunter. His sword style is one that's meant to be stationary, if you've ever seen katanagatari there is a character with the same sword style and he's most powerful in a small room where he basically sits down or stands still. Does that ring a bell? Everything you've said about agility is right but his actual style of fighting goes against that sadly. But I do wanna see a fighter who fights the way you said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nobunaga's Nen ability possibilities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 17:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of all the phantom troupe we seem to know nobunagas personality best. Or atleast he's had the most screen time talking about himself to gon/Killua. But we still don't know of his actual nen ability. We know he's an enhancer that relies on speed rather than strength. We also know that his ability can be replaced easily which makes it seem like it is more of a fighting ability rather than utility.  So what do you think his ability could be? This doesn't have that much evidence but I feel like it has something to with him getting a buff every time he cuts someone. What other ideas do y'all have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 19:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One time me and my older brother convinced our cousin (10 yrs old) that at age 13 boys turn into hay bales. We talked about how hard it was being haybales and we got the entire family in on it. Eventually he started crying because he was scared of becoming a hay bale. His mom then scolded us for tricking him for over a day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to find your main? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 17:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing smash for a little while and still can't find a substantial main. The 3 characters I play most are ike, cloud and Marth but I don't feel like they are my main. How do you find your main? Also what are some good mains for an offensive player? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 15:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm crying.  I've never seen anyone else put ping pong the animation and monster on a list of best anime to watch. I'm so glad someone else enjoys those shows that don't get enough love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 15:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best thing about this post is that this is actually a good nen ability and would be useful as hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 21:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The show is mekkaku city actors. It's a little bit of a brainfuck of a show  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 17:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen this show and I can confirm that this post is cringey even to people who enjoy it's source material.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 19:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in middle school people called be VaJonah. My names jonah btw. My friend and his gf were arguing and she said "you can either hang out with your friends or have my vagina" (yeah middle school sluts are weird) so I pipe in and say "why not have the VaJonah, best of both worlds". And since then I was VaJonah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 14:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fat man dressed as Santa coming down the chimney  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 17:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean yes Killua has strong ties to gon and would never betray him but even his inner monologues show signs of him being in fear of gons strength. Like before gon fought pitou, Killua was actually scared of gon. Now imagine what would happen if Killua feels betrayed by the one he loves most, gon. Killua is almost in denial when it comes to how he thinks of gon. Gon isn't the beautiful human being Killua once thought and Killua is terrified every time that thought is challenged.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 14:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ok it's all good then that's your job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Theory] [All Spoiler] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 14:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So basically here it is. Gon and Killua are foils of each other since gon is a normal hero going on his journey while Killua is a tragic hero. At the moment Gon can't use nen and Killua is in his version of peace with alluka. This just isn't right with there characters. My theory is that during the time during the dark continent where we can't see gon and Killua, gon will get his nen back but it will he unstable and he will have a new really OP ability. Eventually he will refind Killua and they will venture with alluka to the dark continent as well. Somewhere in that arc Gon will truly surpass Killua and at another place alluka will die and Killua will be distraught. Alluka will die in a way where gon could be responsible. With Gon's strength scaring Killua, Killua will fear and resent gon. Eventually Killua will try to overcome his fear and fight Gon in blind emotion. Thus the fight that silva predicted will commence. Thoughts? It's not the greatest theory, any tips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 14:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just a fan fiction. You would die instantly In that story unless you're a super genius like komugi and none of the ants would like your human ass. You couldn't stop anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 17:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like the kinda guy who goes on blind dates and asks if they wanna "head out and see where the night leads" even before the food comes. Then when she doesn't sleep with your desperate ass you go around claiming how much of whore she is to all your friends, whining about how all you want is just a chill girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
