<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9801</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will never read your letters. CALL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CALL THEM. Do not email. Your emails will never be read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CALL. Emails will never be read. CALL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Call your Senators TODAY and tell them to oppose Sessions as attorney general.** [Senate contacts.](http://www.senate.gov/senators/contact/)

Actually CALL them. Do not email. Your emails will never be read.

**EDIT:** Thanks for the gold, but donate to NORML or the ACLU instead!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 21:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIGHT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 20:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not necessarily easy, nor complicated. 

It all has to do with the composition of the court. If a justice or two has been replaced, the court may hear a case similar to one they have heard in the past...and since the composition of the court has changed, the outcome might change as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Again, its fear mongering.

We're not going to agree here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not fear mongering, it's fact. In Casey, Scalia, Thomas and Rehnquist were ready to throw Roe out the door. They didn't care about stare decisis then.  

You think justice Thomas gives more of a fuck about stare decisis now than he did in 1992?

You think justices like Alito and Roberts aren't salivating at the thought of overturning Roe? 

That's naive, if you really believe it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Kennedy hasn't resigned. He's the only justice standing in the way of PP v. Casey and Roe being overturned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Point out exactly where I am incorrect. 

There is currently one vacancy on the Supreme Court, which Trump will get to fill. That means the divide on the court will be 5 conservative leaning justices, 4 liberals. 

If Kennedy, the only conservative justice that has been even remotely friendly to reproductive rights resigns, then Trump will get to appoint another justice. 

With Kennedy (or Ginsburg) gone, there will be nothing in the way of the court reversing Roe. 

Don't think they would be willing to overturn that many decades of precedent? They did it with Citizens United. That case proves the conservatives on the court don't give a fuck about stare decisis as long as the outcome benefits their agenda. 

Where exactly was I incorrect in regard to how the court works? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 15:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words, if this bill passes, all those people who mindlessly chant "abortion is murder!" will get their way. 

And if Trump gets to appoint Scalia's replacement plus one more supreme court justice in the next four years, it is likely this law would be upheld. 

Also, Republicans in Indiana have a super majority in both the state senate and state house. This could actually become a reality. :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 19:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fetus. FTFY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 19:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It is extraordinarily unlikely any conceivable SCOTUS would overturn Roe vs. Wade.

Not if Trump gets to appoint 2 justices in the next 4 years. There's already one vacancy... not out of the realm of reasonable possibilities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 19:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should note that the HRC revoked their endorsement after he made those comments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same HRC that endorsed one of the only Republicans in the Senate who supports marriage equality. FTFY. 

Though we may disagree with Kirk on many, many issues, it'll be difficult to argue he isn't good for gay rights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can read about Trump's potential Supreme Court nominee William Pryor [here.](http://www.pinknews.co.uk/2016/11/16/one-of-trumps-potential-supreme-court-nominees-thinks-gay-people-should-be-jailed-for-having-sex/) Hint: He thinks states should be able to arrest gay people for having consensual sex in the privacy of their own homes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can read about Trump's potential Supreme Court nominee William Pryor [here.](http://www.pinknews.co.uk/2016/11/16/one-of-trumps-potential-supreme-court-nominees-thinks-gay-people-should-be-jailed-for-having-sex/) Hint: He thinks states should be able to arrest gay people for having consensual sex in the privacy of their own homes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 15:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that makes sense. Let's let the states handle it, and then when you get transferred to a new state for work, you lose certain rights. Sounds reasonable! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 01:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good question. I'll have to think about it and research it. That's one I've not considered in detail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. 

The Fourteenth Court of Appeals heard the case twice. First, a three judge panel found the arrest and law unconstitutional. Then the state requested an en-banc hearing, which means ALL the judges in the Fourteenth Court of Appeals heard the case. The second go around, the law was deemed constitutional and the original three judge panel's decision was reversed. 

Then, it went to the supreme court. 

William Pryors brief was after the case had been heard en banc and deemed consitutitional by the entirety of the Fourteenth Court of Appeals.


Confusing legal shit. Check out the wikipedia page for Lawrence vs. Texas to see what I'm talking about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 23:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A dead body has 46 chromosomes, does that mean it is alive? Find a biologist that will tell me definitively when life begins and we'll talk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abortion isn't murder. Unless you can prove to me definitively that life begins at conception, you're just repeating a sentence over and over with no proof. (I realize I'm doing the same thing by saying "abortion isn't murder." I'm trying to make a point.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because they *believe* abortion is murder does not mean it is true, and does not take away from my argument. Abortion, regardless of what pro-lifers think it is, is a medical procedure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either abortion is wrong, or it's not. I do not believe that abortion is wrong. It's not my place to tell another what reasons are "acceptable" for abortion. If the government can limit the number of abortions a person can have, what is stopping the government from limiting the number of children a person can have? Reproductive issues **must** remain with the individual.

I don't care if a woman has an abortion at 3 months or 8 months, it's not my call. Either abortion is wrong, or it isn't. If it's wrong, it's wrong at 12 week or 9 months. If it's not wrong, then it's not wrong at 12 weeks or 9 months. 

That's my personal opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be pertinent if abortion was actually murder. It's not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When there is no definitive proof regarding when life begins (which there isn't one way or the other), then the only argument left is over personal autonomy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fetus and child are not the same thing. What is inside my body is none of your damn business, or the governments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've fought wars over this very debate. It makes no damn sense to call ourselves a country if we have huge inconsistencies in the law from state to state. Having different property tax rates in different states is one thing, but giving up reproductive freedom or marital rights simply by crossing from California to Arizona is a bit much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But it is not about your personal life.

When deciding whether or not I will reproduce, that absolutely is about my personal life. And the government has no damn business trying to butt in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I edited in the word "personal" in my previous comment. Does that clarify what I meant? 

Obviously, who one marries or whether or not to have a child is a bit more personal than the decision whether or not to steal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much control a government exerts over the personal lives of its citizens is, in my view, indicative of the size and scope of that government. The laws are the evidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and let some dude blow a load in you.

Right, because women are always in such a position of control during sex to determine where and when a man blows his load.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He wants people to be able to get married without marriage licenses.

That's not how it works. 

You mentioned getting the government out of marriage. I gave you an example of a place where the government has gotten out of marriage. And no one can get married in those counties now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny you mention that!

There are several Alabama counties who have, in protest of the Supreme Court's decision legalizing gay marriage, refused to issue marriage licenses to any couples, gay or straight, essentially keeping marriage "out of the local government."

Meaning that couples now have to travel across county borders to find a probate judge willing to issue marriage licenses. 

Funny how the GOP wants to throw a fit and make people travel elsewhere when they don't get their way on an issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither Ron nor Rand support federal marriage equality or abortion access, which /u/marclemore1 specifically mentioned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  use protection

Right, because condoms never rip. Any dude with a dick over 5 inches will tell you that those damn things aren't fail proof.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We believe in small government!!!1!"

Says the people who want the government to dictate what medical procedures one can get, who one can marry, where one can piss and mandate prayer in schools. 

Sure sounds small to me. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  abortion is effectively outlawed for a good chunk of the country.

And the people you have to thank for laws that restrict abortion are the same people who ranted and raved about "government taking over muh healthcare!!!11!" when the Affordable Care Act passed. 

Convenient how they don't consider the government dictating what medical procedures one can and cannot legally obtain government overreach. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sad part? These protesters are tame compared to some others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it make a difference? 

The impact of deporting "millions" of people would be catastrophic. 11 million less people paying rent? That's going to be great for those with investments in real estate, I'm sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm very much pro-immigration but illegal aliens presumably don't pay income tax or property tax.

According the the info I cited in a previous comment, undocumented immigrants, as far back as 2002, paid as much 16 billion in taxes per year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  CIS report: Households headed by illegal aliens imposed more than $26.3 billion in costs on the federal government in 2002 and paid only $16 billion in taxes, creating a net fiscal deficit of almost $10.4 billion, or $2,700 per illegal household. [Source.](https://www.factcheck.org/2009/04/cost-of-illegal-immigrants/)

$2,700 per illegal household is a lot less than over $10k per person deported. 

Yes, that's from 2002. I'm trying to find more recent stats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is estimated that the cost of deportation is roughly  $10,070 per person. [Source.](http://www.newsweek.com/how-much-would-it-cost-deport-all-undocumented-immigrants-364316)

How the fuck does Trump plan to pay for that? When you multiply that by "millions," that's a lot of $$$. Honest question. I'm legitimately curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 16:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't directly related to atheism, but it goes to show that the very people who claim you can't be moral without being a theist are the same people extorting money from parents who just lost a child in the name of religion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 16:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps we could have one day a week where such images are permissible?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 22:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pam Bondi is worse than Nancy Grace. Listening to that woman speak is painful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 22:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point, I'm expecting him to come out any day now and say that he can't wait to pardon Hillary. Talk about some fucking quick 180's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He played the entire GOP. 

The day after he's elected, he nixes his Muslim ban.

Three days later, he says parts of Obamacare are cool with him. 

Everyone who voted for Trump because of those two issues got fucking played.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 06:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is truly beautiful. Thank you for sharing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what I'm arguing. I can't attest to whether it's real or fake. What I know is that a reporter tweeted it, then I shared it here, and was subsequently lambasted by comments and messages claiming I personally faked the note. I did not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha ok, carry on, you don't care about the truth. I don't even live in North Carolina and my post history proves that. Shoutout to  r/Chattanooga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pic of that note was tweeted by a ny daily news reporter hours before I posted it. You can claim I faked it all you want, but i never even saw the note personally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're obviously someone who doesn't care about truth. This photo was tweeted by a reporter hours before I posted it. You can claim I faked it all you want, but that doesn't make it true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just don't want my integrity questioned, it's all good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some are claiming I faked this pic. This was tweeted 20 hours ago by Shaun King with the NY daily news. Anyone who thinks I personally faked this is delusional. https://twitter.com/ShaunKing/status/796542537255239681 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This pic was tweeted by shaun king 20 hours before I posted it. If people think I faked it, they're delusional.

https://twitter.com/ShaunKing/status/796542537255239681 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad! I thought it was Chattanooga.  Thanks for letting me know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chattanooga? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's also [THIS VIDEO](https://vid.me/nwtD) of a Trump supporter losing it on an African American gentleman in a parking lot. Says "black lives don't matter," uses many racial slurs, then calls the guy recording a "transgender fagot" before storming off. 

**This is a must watch, truly abhorrent behavior.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this isn't appropriate for this sub, sorry. I'm too disgusted not to try to post it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 16:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It takes more than controlling the Presidency and one legislative chamber to change the electoral college. It would require a constitutional amendment, which means congress has to pass it with a supermajority and then 2/3 of all state legislatures (majority GOP) have to ratify it. 

This is not something one President or one political party in power can accomplish alone. It will take the whole damn nation to achieve electoral reform.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who tries to talk politics in line to vote with me is going to get an earful as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, I think the whole law against ballot selfies is a little silly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not as obstinate as some. When proven wrong, I will correct myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to check the edit I made to my post lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me why you think a ruling from the 9th circuit is nationally binding. Stop spreading misinformation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is the legality, and the reason every state has legal access to CBD.

Not quite, again. The 9th Circuit only has jurisdiction over a handful of western states. It's rulings are not nationally binding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Colorado transitioned from medical to recreational, marijuana prices dropped drastically. [Source.](http://www.businessinsider.com/marijuanas-getting-cheaper-in-colorado-2016-9) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  CBD is actually legal in all 50 states. 

Not quite. For example, in Georgia, it is legal to possess up to 20 fl oz of CBD oil with a prescription, but there are no legal channels through which a patient can obtain CBD. It's still illegal to produce or distribute in the state. The only thing they legalized is patient possession. **Every single patient in Georgia using CBD has to break the law to obtain it.** [Source.](https://www.georgiacannabis.org/obtain-medical-marijuana/) [Another source.](http://www.safeaccessnow.org/georgia_lawmaker_breaks_law_to_bring_medical_cannabis_to_patients) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be surprised how many people I've seen on this very sub say they were voting no on legalization because they were pissed about some insignificant aspect of implementation, regulation, etc. 

There are naysayers even here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 21:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A "jackass mother" who lives in a state where CBD oil is illegal. 

"Sorry honey, I have this cannabutter that will stop your seizures, but it's illegal. Guess you have to wait a few years for our state to change the laws on CBD first."

That's more reasonable to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 21:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if it had been CBD oil, it still would have been illegal as Idaho hasn't even legalized that yet. 

"Sorry, honey. I've got this cannabutter that will stop your seizures, but it's against the law." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 21:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even had she given her kid CBD oil instead, that still would have been a crime in Idaho and she would still be facing consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 21:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with the notion that a spoonful of cannabutter is more damaging to a child than a dozen seizures a day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is there any proof that siezures cause mental development issues?

Yes. I guess you missed Sanjay Gupta's CNN special on medical marijuana. There was a girl who was having so many seizures daily prior to beginning treatment with CBD oil that her development was years behind her age. Watch the documentary and you'll see what I'm talking about. 

Marijuana has certainly never slowed anyone's development by years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if she had used CBD oil instead, that still would have been a crime in Idaho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if she had administered CBD oil instead, **that would still be a crime in Idaho.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  1.) Find a mommy group that will hook you up with a high CBD and low THC grow whereby you can then utilize the oil extract.
 2.) Order online and have oil shipped from the producers of Charlottes Web, for instance, in CO.

Had she done either of those things, possessing and administering CBD oil in Idaho would still have been illegal. The mother would still be facing charges had she done what you just suggested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That kid got high as fuck, which at the age of 3 will fuck up your mental development.

You seriously think getting high is going to fuck up a child's mental development more than dozens of seizures a day?

 Idaho should come around on all of it, but she wasn't using CBD oil and that is why her kid was taken away, and rightly so.

CBD oil isn't legal in Idaho, so even if she did as you suggest, she still would be facing charges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 19:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shouldn't have to move to another state to be able to legally treat your child's medical problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A kids health  the law.

Just my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are the links where you can find your precinct location in each state voting on RECREATIONAL marijuana:

[Arizona.](https://voter.azsos.gov/VoterView/PollingPlaceSearch.do)

[California.](http://www.sos.ca.gov/elections/polling-place/)

[Maine.](http://www.maine.gov/portal/government/edemocracy/voter_lookup.php)

[Massachusetts.](http://wheredoivotema.com/bal/MyElectionInfo.aspx)

[Nevada.](https://nvsos.gov/votersearch/)

Here are the links where you can find your precinct location in each state voting on MEDICAL marijuana:

[Arkansas.](https://www.voterview.ar-nova.org/VoterView/RegistrantSearch.do)

[Florida.](http://dos.myflorida.com/elections/for-voters/check-your-voter-status-and-polling-place/)

[Montana.](https://app.mt.gov/voterinfo/)

[North Dakota.](https://vip.sos.nd.gov/wheretovote.aspx) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you suggest she get CBD oil when Idaho doesn't have legal medical? 

Would you rather your kid continue having seizures, or maybe get a little high but be (mostly) seizure free? 

I can't be critical of this woman due to her circumstances. You can't say "she should have used CBD oil" when her state hasn't legalized it. Even if she had used CBD oil, **that would have still been a crime in Idaho.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if that 3 year old is having dozens of seizures a day and marijuana is a better alternative than the pharmaceuticals that treat seizures? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idaho likely isn't, but this could happen to any parent with a sick kid in any state where medical or recreational marijuana is not legal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 00:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize Bernie raised more than Hillary during the primary, right? Clearly votes are more powerful than money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 21:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't remember exactly, but Obama won.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 21:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for participating! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 21:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Referendums and "elections" happen on the same day. This year, it's a Presidential election year. If you don't go to the polls when the President is voted on, you miss out voting on legalization. Nothing here is being taken out of context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 21:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As someone who lives in a legalized state, that's not true.

In 2011, there were around 30k people arrested for possession in Colorado. In 2014? Under 5k arrests. Arrests for cultivation and distribution also dropped from around 40k a year to under 5k. [Source.](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/wonk/wp/2015/03/26/after-legalization-colorado-pot-arrests-plunge/)

The simple truth is this: legalization drastically lowers arrests. Most people aren't growing 1,000 plants in their basement or trying to get high on the public bus. Don't be stupid, you won't get arrested. That's a lot better than getting locked up period.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 19:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only they had done this back in April or May.... he might have actually had a shot at winning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So are surgeons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They're toothless against organized religion

And they will remain that way unless we fight back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can start with the Catholic Church in Boston. They donated 850,000 against the marijuana measure in Mass. [Source.](https://www.greenrushdaily.com/2016/11/01/catholic-church-donates-850000-fight-cannabis-legalization/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you would like to see a list of businesses who have donated against legalization, you can view that list [here.](https://np.reddit.com/r/trees/comments/5b3ywf/these_businesses_donated_big_against_marijuana_in/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 23:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol not me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't. I'll redo it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it highly unlikely that in the first 3 minutes after i posted it, 20+ people voted for Trump. Speculation, but it is what it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, if you don't want to vote in the Presidential race, more power to you! A lot of people are disenchanted with our process because of the electoral college, but the electoral college only impacts ONE race, the President. All Senators, all representatives, all Governors, all Mayors, all City Council members and ALL state legislators are elected by popular vote -- and are arguably more important races than the President. 

**At least vote in local races, please.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone already acted like an ass and voted for Trump 17 times in under a minute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 19:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you're wrong again! You can repeat something as many times as you like, but the Bible is quite clear why Sodom and Gomorrah was destroyed. 

Ezekiel 16:49 "Now this was the sin of your sister Sodom: : She and her daughters were arrogant, overfed and unconcerned; they did not help the poor and needy."

Notice how it doesn't say a damn thing about homosexuality? 

You probably don't care though, as this verse doesn't fit the narrative to which you're clinging.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 19:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of, "Ho, ho, ho!"does he say, "toke, toke, toke?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure. That's why the Catholic Church paid out nearly a billion in settlements to abuse victims in 2007 alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read the Old Testament? It's full of bits about who should die for what crimes. 

Also, in the US at least, child molesters don't get executed. In some places, drug traffickers do more time than child molesters. Not sure where you get that from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm more concerned with protecting children than I am about ensuring that a child molester "seeks salvation or the Lord again." 

Check your priorities, bro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Of course I would. Even if the punishment was something terrible. In fact, the more draconian the punishment, the more likely I would be to sign up.
I would absolutely be willing to be arrested in order to defend the pedophile's ability to confess. I said already, everyone deserves the ability to confess. Everyone. 

And then this.... 

 I honestly do not care if it sickens you are not. The fact that you would deprive someone of the ability to confess to their sins and thereby preserve their immortal soul is the most inhuman thing I've heard in my entire life. You would risk sending someone to Hell just to get a temporary, worldly punishment.



People can apparently defend anything as long as it's about protecting religion... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to not understand that requiring the priest to report child rape does not prevent anyone from confessing. You want pedophiles to be able to confess **without consequences.** I want pedophiles to be able to confess AND face the consequences of his or her actions. 

No matter how you want to frame it, you're going to be hard pressed to find anyone who thinks it's more immoral to "prevent" confession, which isn't what mandatory reporting laws do, than protecting a pedophile. Good luck with that one. 

Protecting sexual abusers in the name of your religion is the most inhuman thing I've ever heard in my entire life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one deserves to confess committing child rape and not face the consequences. Your perspective on this sickens me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope I misunderstood you...

Did you really just suggest that you would become a priest simply to help a pedophile evade justice so you can get arrested and become a martyr?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 16:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legalization hasn't even passed yet and communities are preemptively banning it's sale. That's bullshit. Vote in local elections! They matter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mods plz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what Trump is suggesting here. Trump wants to allow churches to participate in the political process **without** paying taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 18:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tennessee? Fuck, the feds will legalize before we do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 18:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Voting matters not. 

I think the good voters of Colorado, Washington State, Oregon and Alaska would disagree with you. They aren't, you know, getting arrested for possessing $50 worth of weed anymore. Because they voted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 18:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My title is a little confusing. There are 9 states voting on weed. Early voting has started in all of those states, plus a number of others. Tennessee is not voting on marijuana this year. :( from Chattanooga.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not here to tell anyone how to vote when it comes to the President, but here's my speculation on what would happen under a Clinton administration. Though I don't think Clinton favors legalization, I don't see her taking a position to the right of Obama in regard to states that have legalized it. I don't think Clinton will push for further legalization, but I don't think she will work to prevent states that have legalized from doing so. 

Again, just speculation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If passed, possession will be legal starting December 15th. Setting up regulatory shit for selling legally will take time though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 00:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The southeast saw gas shortages a few weeks back because the same pipeline was simply down. Now that it's rendered unusable, I'm assuming there will be more shortages.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 00:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The explosion was a mile from the previous leak. The southeast gonna experience another gas shortage?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all. But if Cranston doesn't like Clinton, he's going to hate Canada.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope he realizes that Canada has socialized medicine and accepts Syrian refugees with open arms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 17:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any church that violates the law should lose tax exempt status. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 01:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd prefer them not do it at all. Do good with that money, don't spend it on tv air time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 00:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I'll never run for president. Maybe state senate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 00:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be 35 to serve as president.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 00:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll let you know when I run for office. /u/subject9801 2024! 

....holy shit I'll actually be older than the presidential age requirement in 2024.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 22:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I don't know, maybe the 3,115 people who have upvoted my original comment so far. 

I'd love to go back and forth all day. You don't have to agree with me, but claiming that I don't understand the law when I made clear in my original comment that I do isn't going to get you anywhere with me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 22:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article includes a response from a Mississippi Superintendent and a quote from the FFRF saying they may file suit in federal court. This, I believe, is inherently political. If it's not appropriate for this sub just let me know!

Also, if you want to watch a video of the baptism, it can be found [here.](https://vid.me/3GHq)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 21:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not a matter of understanding the law, that's a matter of opinion. If the Catholic Church cannot donate to or endorse political candidates, it's not a stretch to argue, for the sake of consistency, that the Johnson amendment should be expanded to prohibit churches from donating to and endorsing political initiatives as well. My post isn't about what the law is, it is about what the law should be. My original comment made that clear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 21:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am the OP. I posted the link, then my comment immediately afterwards. There was no backlash, and I have an impeccable understanding of the law. If I didn't, my post would have likely said "Catholic church violates law by donating....." But it didn't. Because I understand the law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 21:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt the same way when I saw it on fb. That's why I felt the need to post it here. This mentality needs to be shamed out of existence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 20:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a fair observation, but it's also important to make the distinction that NORML and MPP don't have literally millions of congregants nationwide giving them money (tithes) every single week. When people donate to NORML, they know it's going to a political cause. When people give to the church, many assume the money will be given to the poor and needy....not to a political campaign.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 20:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you think change ever happens unless people discuss the laws they would like to see changed? Just because the church didn't break any laws doesn't mean we shouldn't have a conversation regarding whether or not the laws should be changed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 20:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 20:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am the OP. I posted this in r/trees, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 19:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was posted in r/trees, not r/atheism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. The law prohibits churches from bankrolling and endorsing candidates. The law allows churches to endorse and bankrolling campaigns for or against ballot initiatives. I'm of the belief that loophole should be closed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Catholic Church wants to operate like a superPAC using the 10% they get weekly from their members paychecks to bankroll political campaigns, they need to lose their tax exempt status. 

I'm not arguing that what the Catholic Church is doing is illegal, I'm arguing that the Johnson amendment should be expanded to prohibit churches from endorsing and bankrolling campaigns for or against ballot initiatives as well as political candidates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Greenpeace a religious organization taking in 10% of their memebers paychecks weekly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not arguing that what the Catholic Church is doing is illegal. I'm arguing that the Johnson amendment, which prohibits churches from endorsing candidates, raising money on their behalf (basically operating a church like a superpac), should be expanded to prohibit churches from endorsing or funding ballot initiatives as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not arguing that what the Catholic Church is doing is illegal. I'm arguing that the Johnson amendment, which prohibits churches from endorsing candidates, raising money on their behalf (basically operating a church like a superpac), should be expanded to prohibit churches from endorsing or funding ballot initiatives as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 16:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A competing proposal that will legalize medical marijuana without allowing patients to grow their own will remain on the ballot in Arkansas. Vote, folks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THAT is how religious freedom should work. If a church does not wish to officiate legal same-sex marriages, that church should not be forced to do so. If a church wants to officiate legal same sex marriages, the state should not be able to tell that church it cannot legally do so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 17:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's simple: supply goes up, price goes down. YAY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 05:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The United Church of Christ is joining the national debate on the future of gay marriage in a novel way: The church filed a lawsuit on Monday challenging North Carolina's ban on same-sex marriage, saying Amendment One violates the church's constitutional guarantee to freedom of religion.

That's from the first paragraph. Exactly which parts don't fit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 17:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can read about the defunding [here.](http://archive.knoxnews.com/news/state/senate-panel-votes-to-strip-ut-diversity-office-of-all-state-funding-2d1a1026-4385-38a6-e053-0100007-370858871.html)

You can also learn about Gardenhire's current opponent, Khrisy Wilkinson, [here.](http://www.khristywilkinson.org/justice) She is very pro-LGBT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 16:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My biggest takeaway from this: legalizing marijuana nationwide would likely, based off these stats, create more than a million jobs.
Get it done, folks. Vote next month. Or early.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 23:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can view a video of the baptism [here.](https://vid.me/3GHq) 

I posted about this a few days ago, but since then the school district has doubled down. That is included in this article.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 18:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about Mass., but many colleges in Georgia are dry campuses. No alcohol allowed. You think they're going to allow weed just because it's been legalized?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why local elections are just as important! The people who run your cities and towns make these kinds of decisions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 22:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can watch the video of the Newton High School coach baptizing a student [here.](https://vid.me/3GHq)

Specifically, his comments about "real men" choosing God is disturbing to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 22:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can watch the video of the Newton High School coach baptizing a student [here.](https://vid.me/3GHq)

Specifically, his comments about "real men" choosing God is disturbing to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 18:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Virginia residents can register to vote online at [THIS](http://www.elections.virginia.gov/voter-outreach/) link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't personally view it that way. I'm fine with disagreeing on this, but hear me out: 

The Supreme Court has twice ruled, first in Loving v. Virginia, which legalized interracial marriage and then in Obergfells v Hodges, which legalized gay marriage, that marriage itself is a **fundamental right.**

I don't buy the argument that judges can refuse to grant marriage licenses, which has been ruled a fundamental right, just because they're refusing to grant any marriage licenses, not just same-sex marriage licenses. 

This is almost worse.. not only is the fundamental right of same-sex couples being infringed upon, but the fundamental right of all citizens of those counties to marry is being taken away by a few rogue judges. 


On another note, this brings us to another problematic issue: the practice of electing judges. It's likely these judges will be overwhelmingly re-elected, despite infringing on the rights of the people in their county. To these judges, it's not about following the law... it's about getting elected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't refute shit. [Source.](http://norml.org/laws/item/massachusetts-penalties-2) Notice the 6 months to 2 years jailtime for repeat offenders caught with merely more than 28 grams?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Growing up" would be not throwing a bitch fit because the proposed initiative doesn't cater exactly to your perfect view of how legalization should happen. 

Perhaps you should take your own advice ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to know how /u/jambears will explain to his friend who gets arrested for possession a year from now if this measure doesn't pass that he voted no because he's afraid the way the law will be written will be friendly to big money and fuck the little guy. 

Basically, regulations are more scary to him than jailtime. WTF? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds reasonable, but are you consistent in regard to states rights? For example, if Maryland wanted to legalize abortion up until the day before the fetus is due to be delivered, should Maryland be able to do that under the states rights argument?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marijuana legalization. Yeah or no? Also, if you don't support legalization, what do you say to the voters in the many states that have already legalized by ballot initiative? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 22:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **There are only FOUR DAY LEFT to register to vote in Massachusetts.**

[Here](https://www.sec.state.ma.us/ovr/) is the link to register to vote  in MA online. Do it, folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 00:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think I wanna get banned by a handful of subs just to post on Donald's? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 00:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pointing out their hypocrisy publicly  is more effective than confronting individuals. They would likely further entrench in their views.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 23:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was aware this is technically legal when I made the post. I'm not arguing that they are violating the law. I'm arguing that the law should be different. 

Churches shouldn't be allowed to act as superpacs, and superpacs shouldn't exist. That's just my opinion though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 21:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a few ways that campaign finance could be fixed. 

The next President could appoint a replacement for Scalia, and the litmus test should be whether or not that judge wants to overturn Citizens United. 

Or, Congress could initiate a constitutional amendment that would limit the amount corporations and individuals can contribute per cycle. 

I would prefer a change on the court and a reversal by them, as amending our constitution should always be a last resort.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superpacs shouldn't be legal in the first place, in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to know which parts are "factually incorrect." Do you deny that the lds church made this statement? Deseret news even reported it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is bigger than merely preaching from the pulpit. That directive was likely sent to every Mormon congregation in the country. Millions of members ready to volunteer and open their wallets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 00:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not here to tell anyone how to vote! But, I'll give my two cents on ALL of the candidates. Trump is vitriolic and vile. Bill Weld should have been the top of the ticket for the libertarians. He's more articulate and more intellectual than Johnson, though they were both pretty good governors. Clinton is....meh. Not very excited, but I'll vote for Clinton simply because I want a liberal supreme court. To 2020! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 23:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "The worst part about it is listening to people trying to belittle it, just saying, 'Well, it's locker-room talk, it's locker-room banter,' " she says. "Anyone belittling sexual violence, sexual abuse, they're doing a huge disservice to victims of violent crimes, violent sexual abuse. There's no justifying it  ever."

I'm not here to tell anyone who to vote for, but everyone please participate in the process. 

A few states voter registration deadlines have already passed, but many are still open as well! Get registered to vote!

31 states + DC offer online voter registration. You can find your state's online registration link [HERE.](http://www.ncsl.org/research/elections-and-campaigns/electronic-or-online-voter-registration.aspx)

If your state does not yet offer online voter registration, you can use the national mail in registration form [HERE.](http://www.eac.gov/assets/1/Documents/Federal%20Voter%20Registration_1209_en8242012.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I edited this into my post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but I expect that Clinton will continue Obama's policy of taking no action regarding states that have legalized recreational marijuana. Under Trump, I'd be terrified he would appoint judges that would crack down on legal states, and I would HATE to think of the kind of people he would put in charge of the DEA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, Florida is voting on amendment 2, which will legalize medical marijuana in Florida, if passed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 00:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Florida is one of the states voting on medical marijuana. Also, all of your House districts are having elections. More than just Trump and Clinton! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 00:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize there are a shit ton more races happening than just Trump/Clinton, right? 9 states are voting on legalizing medicinal or recreational marijuana. A few states are voting on raising the minimum wage. Colorado is voting on single payer healthcare. Maine is voting on ranked choice voting. 

Trump/Clinton isn't the entirety of this election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 23:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone in another comment said, not voting is an act of surrender.. not rebellion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The juxtaposition was to convince people to vote for any candidate other than Trump. That could easily be Gary Johnson or Jill Stein also. I didn't bring up who I am supporting until you asked :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm voting for Hillary, but I want **everyone** to register to vote and participate in the process, even if they're voting for the pussy grabber.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is way more than just Trump/Clinton on the ticket. Local races, state legislature, judges, ballot initiatives, etc. 9 states are voting on recreational/medicinal weed. A handful of states are voting to raise the minimum wage. Colorado is voting on single payer healthcare. Maine is voting on ranked choice voting. 

If you think Trump/Clinton is the only race worth voting for or against on the ballot this November, you should think again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not telling you who to vote for, but in order to be a felon (by definition) you actually have to be convicted by a jury of a felony.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here we go again with that crazy shit: 

*"Ignore the fact that our Presidential nominee is a misogynist who freely admits he believes the rich and famous can sexually assault women without consequence on a whim....cause this ancient text written over 2000 years ago says that women can't tell a man what to do."*

For fucks sake.. Register to vote, ya'll. The people who think like that guy sure as fuck are going to be voting.

31 states + DC offer online voter registration. You can find your state's online registration link [HERE.](http://www.ncsl.org/research/elections-and-campaigns/electronic-or-online-voter-registration.aspx)

If your state does not yet offer online voter registration, you can use the national mail in registration form [HERE.](http://www.eac.gov/assets/1/Documents/Federal%20Voter%20Registration_1209_en8242012.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 16:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which crime deserves a harsher penalty, though? Raping a teenager with a pool stick so violently that his colon ruptures and he requires surgery? Or having a pound of an herb on you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 16:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those not familiar with the case, they raped a fellow team mate with a pool stick. [Source.](http://nypost.com/2016/08/31/high-school-basketball-players-convicted-in-pool-cue-rape-case/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be cool with screenshots being allowed. As with license plates and possibly bumper stickers. I've seen some truly hilarious ones in the south. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 21:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIGHT? I'm not mad that he is supporting Trump... he is free to support whichever candidate he wants. My issue is the fact that he holds Trump to one moral standard (tolerating his filth and immorality), yet wants to chastise and shun me for using the exact same words Trump used! Nothing more,  nothing less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 20:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That link takes you to a site with info on where to register to vote online in the 31 states that offer online voter registration. 

If your state does not yet offer online voter registration, you can use the national mail in registration form [HERE.](http://www.eac.gov/assets/1/Documents/Federal%20Voter%20Registration_1209_en8242012.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 20:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, if your reasoning for voting NO is because you're worried about regulations, cost, limits on growing, etc.... thinking about how you're going to explain to a friend, a year from now, who gets arrested for possession that you voted no because you were pissed about $300 ounces and not being able to grow 50 plants in your basement.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a woman falsely reports a rape, she has committed a crime. Your point?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kind? 

I don't mind discussing Islam. They're just as batshit crazy as the Christians.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Railing against political correctness is just a talking point the GOP realizes fires up their mostly ignorant base, in my opinion. 


The same people who rail against liberals for political correctness just want it to be socially acceptable for them to say things like the "n" word while chastising others for saying "bitch," "fuck" or "pussy....." then voting for a guy who uses those same words and not realizing the contradiction and hypocrisy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As of now, if your registration form is postmarked by TMRO AT MIDNIGHT, the state MUST process it. GET IT DONE YA'LL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub isn't about Presidential politics. When I'm trying to convince people on this particular sub to vote, I'm going to remove my own personal opinions in regard to Clinton and Trump. 

If you want to know my opinion, you can find it in my history of commenting on other subs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 18:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 31 states + DC offer online voter registration. You can find your state's online registration link [HERE.](http://www.ncsl.org/research/elections-and-campaigns/electronic-or-online-voter-registration.aspx)

If your state does not yet offer online voter registration, you can use the national mail in registration form [HERE.](http://www.eac.gov/assets/1/Documents/Federal%20Voter%20Registration_1209_en8242012.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 23:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Grab them by the pussy." -Donald Trump

Ladies and gentlemen, register to vote.

31 states + DC offer online voter registration. You can find your state's online registration link [HERE.](http://www.ncsl.org/research/elections-and-campaigns/electronic-or-online-voter-registration.aspx)

If your state does not yet offer online voter registration, you can use the national mail in registration form [HERE.](http://www.eac.gov/assets/1/Documents/Federal%20Voter%20Registration_1209_en8242012.pdf)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 23:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Grab them by the pussy." -Donald Trump

Ladies and gentlemen, register to vote.

31 states + DC offer online voter registration. You can find your state's online registration link [HERE.](http://www.ncsl.org/research/elections-and-campaigns/electronic-or-online-voter-registration.aspx)

If your state does not yet offer online voter registration, you can use the national mail in registration form [HERE.](http://www.eac.gov/assets/1/Documents/Federal%20Voter%20Registration_1209_en8242012.pdf)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 23:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Grab them by the pussy." -Donald Trump

Ladies and gentlemen, register to vote.

31 states + DC offer online voter registration. You can find your state's online registration link [HERE.](http://www.ncsl.org/research/elections-and-campaigns/electronic-or-online-voter-registration.aspx)

If your state does not yet offer online voter registration, you can use the national mail in registration form [HERE.](http://www.eac.gov/assets/1/Documents/Federal%20Voter%20Registration_1209_en8242012.pdf)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
