<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9409</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your client expecting an enterprise-level solution? Ie: With reports, analysis, data-based choices in your posts, etc. 

If so, you'll have to track your success -- you'll need analytics that tells you your most engaging keywords, hashtags, and filters so you can get the results your clients expect. That stuff isn't free either, though, so you should build that into the price (for 30 accounts, you're looking at a minimum of $400 a month for most analytics solutions). 

Are you monitoring these pages as well?

It sounds like this is going to be an almost full-time job, or at least a half-time job. Look up the salaries for social media managers at companies the same size as your client. That should give you some idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, that's 420 posts per month. Are you creating unique content (photos, videos) for each post?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely think this is a more accurate way to slice medal data. Athletes per capita is a cool metric to track </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love animated graphs! This is amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll want to increase new like sources from your city  to ensure the right people who will actually go to your restaurant are seeing the campaign. I think that's a key metric to track, and you can get it with most Facebook insights reports (PM me for an analytics recommendation).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's definitely something to it. Crowdculture marketing is the new content marketing -- the only way to get eyeballs now. Of course, it can go horribly wrong, but I think it's the way forward.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Activity and Ads is performance measuring, keywords is listening. Crowbabble does activity, ads, and mentions, but not keywords. I recommend Crowdbabble for Facebook, Insta, Twitter, and LinkedIn (I'm biased), because it's significantly more affordable than competitors with the same features. 

If you want listening and performance measurement in one app, you will be paying a lot more. Radian6 is probably the best social media listening out there, and I have no idea how much it costs. Simply measured offers an API, but looking at its monthly pricing plans are $2,000+ per month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get a free trial to almost every analytics tool out there. Crowdbabble has one at crowdbabble.com/app/signup_trial. You could also get this information manually: manually calculate follower growth, engagement rate, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 05:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd have to look into the train options more closely, but you could easily take a train to Fort William from Edinburgh (about 5 hours). The Jacobite train then goes up to Mallaig and back. You'd then take the train from Edinburgh down to London, the milk route that goes along the coast. 

Flying option 1:

 * Fly Dublin -- Edinburgh
 * Your nights in Edinburgh
 * Edinburgh -- Fort William (regular train)
 * Fort William -- Mallaig (Harry Potter train)
 * Night in Mallaig
 * Mallaig -- Fort William (Harry Potter train return)
 * Fort William -- London (regular train)

Flying option 2 (one more stop):

 * Fly Dublin -- Inverness
 * Inverness -- Fort William (regular train)
 * Night in Fort William (or you could do Inverness)
 * Fort William -- Mallaig (Harry Potter train)
 * Night in Mallaig
 * Mallaig -- Fort William (Harry Potter train return)
 * Fort William -- Edinburgh
 * Your nights in Edinburgh
 * Edinburgh -- London (regular train)

If you don't want to take the train both ways from Fort William to Edinburgh, you could take a bus then a ferry from Dublin to Fort William. 

Ferry option: 

 * Dublin -- Larne, Northern Island (2hr bus / taxi / shuttle / bicycle?)
 * Larne -- Ayr (Ferry)
 * Ayr -- Fort William (train)
 * Night in Fort William (you'll probably need this if you go the ferry route -- will be difficult to do the whole journey on one day and get the times coordinated)
 * Fort William -- Mallaig (Harry Potter train)
 * Night in Mallaig
 * Mallaig -- Fort William (Harry Potter train return)
 * Fort William -- Edinburgh (regular train)
 * Your nights in Edinburgh
 * Edinburgh -- London (regular train)


If you do go to the highlands, aim for April/May -- the sun is out late because it's so far north, and you're more likely to have nice weather.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 05:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why Liverpool? 

I love your itinerary so far, but I do not get Liverpool. Fly Dublin to Edinburgh. 

If your GF likes Harry Potter, go to Edinburgh, where it was written. You can sit at the little table in the Elephant cafe where J K Rowling wrote the books, and look out the window where she saw Edinburgh Castle (which is what Hogwarts is based on). 

I would do:

 * 4 nights in Dublin (3 full days)
 * 3 nights in Edinburgh (2 full days)
 * 2 nights in the highlands - 1 in Fort William, 1 in Malaig -- this is so you can take the Jacobite / Harry Potter train (for the true fan)
 * 3 nights in London (take the train along the coast, aka the milk route, and do not do any train travel in the UK on Sundays, when all track work is done)
 * 3 nights in Amsterdam
 * 4 nights in Rome

That gives you at least two full days in each place with no travel. 

Bring a great rain jacket if you're going in March. I'd suggest April or May. May in Scotland is beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is something a little bit like this -- it rewards employees for sharing company initiatives. Gamification of employee advocacy. 

Hootsuite.com/products/amplify
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 19:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of that sounds awesome. You need to mobilize all of the headliners and give them the content they need to promote (hashtag, link, sample posts). You want to get the bands to be tweeting / posting with the hashtag and link to buy tickets as far in advance as possible,  ASAP. 

Create some media assets to be shared by key players in advance: images and posts that can be shared on Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram. 

Along with the hashtag, people should be tweeting a bit.ly/donatenow or bit.ly/getyourtickets link that goes to a webpage where people can donate. They can either buy tickets or just donate in a few clicks. 

Once you've got the hashtag and link made, you should get those to the bands as soon as humanly possible. Pre-write some tweets and facebook posts for them as well, individual ones for each band. 

Hyper target your Facebook ads to people in certain locations who also like the bands who are playing. 

Reach out to music bloggers and journalists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is your audience? Suburban parents, urban hipsters? What does your product look like?

You should be on Pinterest and Instagram, and have content ready that showcases your product in a way that your target audience will value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 03:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really interesting. On social, Trump has a larger and more active audience than Hillary -- he blew past her in March, basically sealing the nomination for himself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree. Starbucks actually has a lot of diversity programs in place that are wonderful, but they don't publicize them and didn't include them in #racetogether. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So you guys like reading about big brand campaigns that failed miserably. Here's another one: #racetogether by Starbucks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 02:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL @ Ryan subscribing to /r/HillaryForPrison. He definitely would </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 01:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who are your favourite artists on Instagram, that you aspire to be like? What are they posting? Who are they interacting with? 

You have to post what your audience finds the most engaging. You can find that out with basic social media analytics -- a lot of companies have free trials. You need to know your most engaging hashtags and filters, as well as the best time to post. You need to engage with other artists in your community -- you'll build your community of fans on top of others. Crowdbabble has a free app for Hootsuite, and there are a bunch of other ones on there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 23:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Find a contest deadline or 10 that match the genre you want to write in. Do the same for journal entry deadlines for tiny journals and websites that publish fiction. 

2. Write short stories first, even just scenes of your book

3. Ideally, workshop them with other authors

4. Submit them to the contests and journals

5. Whether you're rejected or accepted, you're a real author now. 

If you wait until you write that huge book all in one fell swoop, you will wait forever.

If you want to be filthy rich, master writing and then get extremely lucky and sell ten million copies (authors typically get 10% of list price in a conventional publishing deal). Journalism is tough: investigative journalists can maybe earn $75,000 per year if they're at the top of their fields. The barrier to entry in journalism is one of two things: a Masters from a prestigious program, and/or a portfolio of solid investigative pieces that actually prompted change, published in well-regarded papers (any size -- doesn't have to be big). Most entry level journalism jobs pay $20,000 to $30,000 , even in major cities. If you balk at those salaries, that's a sign that you don't love journalism enough to make the sacrifices needed to actually be a journalist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 23:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally don't feel qualified enough to make edits to this doc, because they might impact your admission chances and your entire career. High stakes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on your vertical. Donald Trump, Hillary Clinton, and Bernie Sanders have Instagram engagement rates of more than 100%. Most brands have Instagram engagement rates of less than 5%. Benchmark using your competitors, not random numbers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And does that archetype match your target audience? I'm just trying to figure out how this would line up with user personas. Would an Explorer brand have Explorer customers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't think of a better example than IBM's #hackahairdryer campaign, which went down in flames on Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 19:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crisis management in advertising: when a campaign goes very, very wrong (IBM's #hackahairdryer) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 19:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 19:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone here actually applied the idea of archetypes in their work?

As a UX designer, this is interesting to me. I use user personas to refine brand strategy and UX.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you manage the API limits? 

Big social listening apps usually have to use work arounds to actually scan for every single keywords, because your requests are limited.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should see /r/advertising, much more hostile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 04:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say that this is too high stakes for random internet advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 23:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that you should hammer out the numbers for what shipping and inventory management will cost you per order. A lot of people go with dropshipping because it's expensive -- but you wouldn't be able to oversee the branding yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 21:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're going to be ordering from China and doing branding in house, you'll be handling inventory and shipping yourselves. That will make your margins razor thin.

In terms of branding, you have to start with research.

First, figure out your audience and influencers in that space. Create user personas and find all the info you can about your target market. 

Next, figure out your brand identity based on your audience's needs/wants/location/other demographic info.

Finally, to fine tune your strategy, look at your competitors who are going after the same audience: who is the best in class in your category? What are they doing in terms of branding and social media? 

To set goals before creating a marketing strategy, use your competitors/peers to bench mark. Get real data using social media analytics and make a timeline with actual numbers to hit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 21:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a solid social media following, and have you established yourself as an authority in your industry? 

If you have an engaged, sincere social media following, and you're engaged with influencer in your industry, you have a much higher chance of success. Launching a Kickstarter to just friends and family -- with no social media traction -- will be a lot tougher. 

I think it's against Kickstarter's terms and conditions to pay yourself. That would get your campaign cancelled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 20:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you using Google Analytics to create traceable links, which you use in your ads? 

You should also be able to, in Google Analytics, see conversions when your site is visited directly from social. Configure specific goals for conversion / sales, then you should be able to see them in all of your GA tables. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Social Media Analytics: Crowdbabble and/or Hootsuite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you liked it!

I'm a freelance social media strategist if you need help building an audience for your agency. Would you like me to run a free report on one of your accounts? 

For new clients, I usually start with a free report followed by a more detailed audit of your social strategy, SEO, and website.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 16:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you done analytics on his account, figuring out what works and what doesn't? Has he been regularly engaging with influencers?

Crowdbabble has a great free app for Hootsuite that could help him out. 

PM me if you want a more in depth free report on his most engaging hashtags and filters, as well as best time to post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 16:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of these metrics could be useful: https://www.crowdbabble.com/facebook-metrics-glossary/

People reached is key, possibly more than likes, comments, and shares. Negative Feedback is also important: that measures the number of blocks/reports/unlikes your page got. Crowdbabble measures all of these for multiple accounts from one dashboard, but it would be hard to calculate manually. Engagement is easy to calculate manually and if you want to do it yourself, then that would save you money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 16:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hootsuite has analytics apps that you can use, if you want an all-in-one solution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 23:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do your high paying job, but at a non-profit that you care about or in an industry that you want to move into.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was Instagram </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need an indication on the splash screen that I'm supposed to scroll.

The font and overall treatment of the scroll navigation menu on the left looks glitchy and doesn't match your site. 

Other than that, looks great! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the three main menu items (work, resume) need to be in a different font weight than your bio/name in the bottom left. There also needs to be more space between your bio/name and the menu items -- they're a little too cozy and it's a bit confusing.

the rest of the site looks great. I would just break up the text into columns. It's a UX best practice to break text into columns for ease of readability, rather than have the text drag all the way across the screen on desktop (or almost across the screen as is your case). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not obvious to me when the page is loaded that I'm on the work tab. Usually when you're within a menu item, the menu item is changed somehow (bolded, faded, highlighted, something).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The get started call to action isn't big enough. I didn't  know I was meant to click it.

When I initially loaded the page, I was focused on the interface in the middle. It wasn't obvious to me that this was a sample of what your product looked like -- it's like a product within a product within a product. My eye first went to the Add+ button within the test app. Maybe have the screenshot more obvious as a screenshot - give it a shadow, fade it, whatever. 

I don't like the double Get Started, one in the side navigation and one as a button. That's confusing. If the side navigation is meant to be steps, it needs to be more differentiated -- all caps, fainter font, whatever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I searched #toronto -- it might have just returned too many results </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> English language and literature is mostly male? My classes were 99% female.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rank all of your Facebook posts by reaction [new feature] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys! Facebook reactions, in terms of social media marketing, is like a very blunt form of sentiment analysis. Reactions tell you how your content makes your Page fans feel. 

Sorting your content by reactions gives you important insight: you can see which content themes elicit which emotions, and the amount of engagement overall they get. You can do this manually, or with a social media analytics tool. Depending on how often you post on your page, you could easily jot down the reactions manually in Excel and then use the Sort function to rank your posts by reaction. Make a row for each post and a column for each reaction type, then use the Data-- Sort -- Sort By -- [choose a column] to sort your posts. 

To automate this process, you can use a social media analytics tool. Below, I walk through how to use Crowdbabble to sort all of your content for any time period by reaction. So, for example you can see what posts make your fans the happiest or angriest, and which ones drew the most likes/reactions overall.

First, login to your account and from your dashboard add a Facebook page (you can make an account here: http://www.crowdbabble.com/app/signup_trial). You can add a Facebook Insights report if you have admin access to the page, or a Public report if you do not (if it's a competitor, for example).

Once your data has loaded, click on the report and choose your date range. For a huge (proto-)sentiment analysis of all your posts, choose February 26 as your start date. That's the day Facebook Reactions launched globally.

Next, navigate to the Content tab. In the Content tab, click All Posts. You'll then see All Posts by the page during that time range. Scroll down and load them all, then click the individual reactions to sort the table by reactions. You can also sort by comments, shares, and total engagement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks good to me.

When I opened the CSV I downloaded, it was blank. But the UI is great! It just doesn't seem to work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your competitors doing?

First, figure out your audience. Then, figure out who else is trying to sell the same thing to them (aka competitors). 

I'd get some social media analytics (or just do it manually) and look into what your biggest competitors are doing and what best in class is doing. What are their content themes? How often do they post?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 02:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also provides some background on her character (pretty much left out of Suicide Squad).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some fun tweets I put together -- if Harley Quinn were on social media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 02:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 22:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahoy! I've written a couple of case studies about this. As an agency, your social media presence can act as an important test for potential clients -- they'll check to see if you're able to build an audience through your own channels. 

Pinch Social in Toronto has done well by establishing itself as an authority in marketing through Twitter and Facebook. I do a write up about them and another Toronto agency in the post below. 

Establishing yourself as an authority: http://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/how-to-don-draper-your-social-media-a-guide-for-agencies/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Benchmark using your competitors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to my current strategy, I'd bribe credible influencers to use it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 17:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it looks cheap, but it depends on how you use them. Ideally, they'd be partially integrated into the tweet itself, not all dangling off the end. And you really shouldn't use more than 3 or 4 -- that does get spammy. If you don't use any hashtags or links, your tweets will appear less spammy. But if you're already trying to get people to click a link, you might as well include some hashtags. 

Good hashtag use: Anyone else dig this new #design? http://www.thedesign.com I really love the use of blue here. #ui #webchat

Bad hashtag use: Anyone else dig this new design? I really love the use of blue here. http://www.thedesign.com #webchat #ui #ux #web #design #chat #ifollowback 

You can use social media analytics to find the most engaging number of hashtags for you. Crowdbabble tells you your most engaging and least engaging hashtags, and engagement per number of hashtags used. It could be that after 5 hashtags, your engagement radically drops -- or maybe your followers like that. It really depends on your audience and the communities of the hashtags you use. What's your Twitter username? I'll load up the graph for you and post it here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 16:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you also post non-paid content, like page updates -- links, videos, photos, etc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 18:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What benefit does your product offer? That should be the button.

Beautify Your Site! Clear My Skin! Get That Shirt! Beat My Score! Look Cool At Work! Minus the exclamation points, but you get the idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 16:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research, strategy, execution </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 21:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did a write up on his messaging here: http://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/trump-vs-clinton-vs-sanders-who-is-winning-the-election-on-social-media/

His messaging is intensely shareable, because it's so outrageous and so simple. Basically, most of what he says can be chanted by an angry mob. This doesn't hold true for Hillary or Bernie. 

He's also much more harsh. He makes simple, hardline statements -- his confidence is part of what draws people to him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 17:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your competitors doing? Or your peers in other towns? Start there, and come up with content themes, a content strategy, and a content calendar. Get some analytics (I recommend Crowdbabble, but you can also manually track the posts) so you can see what works and what doesn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 23:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your competitors doing? Get some analytics on their most engaging content, then refine your content strategy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 22:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a good social media analytics platform, so you know what works and what doesn't. Add your competitors + best in class in your vertical and see what their top posts are.

Hire a good user experience designer to make sure that your site converts. 

You might also spend some time learning how to write Google ads for keywords that convert, and how to do great Facebook targeting. 

Do some growth hacking prizes for your winners, perhaps where you send them actual gift boxes with fun stuff (betking winner tshirt, betking winner crown, etc). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 21:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me know if you have any questions!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 21:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your competitors doing?

I'd load up their social accounts on an analytics platform like Crowdbabble (or just look into them manually), and see what their top posts are. Should help you determine a strategy on different platforms.

Pinterest is also awesome, if your demographic is suburban and rural women.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 20:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Crowdbabble, you can export all your social data to CSV or Excel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 18:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a good list of metrics (some with calculations): https://www.crowdbabble.com/facebook-metrics-glossary/

Post virality is a good one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 18:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any way you can avoid flying in and out of Instanbul? I'm probably just paranoid, but they're in the midst of a foreigner/educated person/elite round up right now and the country seems on the brink of a huge crisis. 

Split in Croatia and Tuscany are not too far off your itinerary -- if you like beautiful scenery and good wine, could be a good place to visit. 

Have you walked around with your backpack fully packed for 2 hours? 

One thing you didn't bring is laundry powder -- I'd toss in a few pellets/pods in a ziplocked bag. 

I don't think you need slippers. Just flip flops for the shower, ideally comfortable ones that you can wear outside too. 

With all that tech, I wouldn't bring a laptop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 18:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd suggest Pew.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 17:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried an analytics service like Crowdbabble to track your organic vs paid engagement breakdowns? It could be that your pages aren't preforming well in one area, but are doing better in another.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 17:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out your competitors and see what they're doing. I suggest Crowdbabble for this -- do the 14 day free trial, then add competitor accounts, and see what their most engaging posts are. That should give you some idea of how to use Instagram for marketing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 17:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crowdbabble does all those networks except Pinterest. I'd suggest adding your competitors to get their analytics, then using them to benchmark. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 17:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should check out Crowdbabble -- the free trial is pretty awesome, and you can get all the engagement data for each post. You can also sort all of your posts by likes, shares, comments, reactions, etc. Pretty handy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 17:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At Crowdbabble, we saw a huge increase in sign ups when it was on a different page than Pricing. We funnel everyone to this new sign up page: https://www.crowdbabble.com/start-free-trial/

Before, everyone would have to go through pricing. Seeing numbers made people balk, even though they had access to a free 14 day trial: https://www.crowdbabble.com/pricing/

Both had the same conversion rates, so the Start Free Trial page is the clear winner for us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 16:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look for problems in other peoples' lives. In your community, what products are people missing? What frustrates people? What do they need, but don't have?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 21:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google is a great source for programming courses. You can learn with free courses like MIT's Open Coursewear: http://ocw.mit.edu/courses/electrical-engineering-and-computer-science/6-00sc-introduction-to-computer-science-and-programming-spring-2011/

Online courses have low success rates because people lose motivation. Your school is another great opportunity to learn programming. Email the computer science department to ask about auditing or taking courses.

The problem with waiting until you're out of school is that once you're out of school, you'll need to make money immediately. And since you don't know how to program, you'll have to hire a developer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 20:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to benchmark based on your vertical and on your competitors. 

How much, in %, did your competitors gain last year? What about the best in class brands in your vertical? Start with that and do the math for your own audience size. 

Crowdbabble lets you get all the data for your competitors and you could also do this manually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to the close daycare, and spend 40 minutes before and after playing with your kids in the park.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 18:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am terrible at naming things :(

I think one thing that's missing from your plan is looking into competitors. I think this could potentially be a blue ocean idea, but there are a lot of retrofitting companies out there who do similar things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 18:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should start building your businesses while you're in school. Start small, while you have accommodation and food paid for. Don't spend your loans on your businesses and get a small part-time job. 

Unless Hillary wins (and then keep her campaign promises), there won't be debt relief for graduates who start businesses. You need to avoid debt at school. Go to a state school, get a research assistant job, whatever you have to do. Go to your office hours and ask your profs about RA opportunities as early as you can (emailing them about it over the summer is also a good idea -- find ones whose work you admire and get in touch). It would be great to start in September with a part-time job to minimize your debt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 18:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this commitment to market research is great -- it's going to be a tough process, but you're going to get good data.

You need to tell people how much money the'll save. Luckily, there are a lot of window insulation / lightbulb producers who have already done studies on this -- see if you can get that information. 

Just make sure your name is good for SEO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 05:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does this cake have a hole in it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 01:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sciences are very much dependent on politics, though. Research funding, the military especially, academic funding, NASA, etc. Not to mention government regulations that can stamp out innovation or ban stem cells, just as an example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 00:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to ask -- why do STEM majors not vote?

Do they think laws affect them less, because they will have higher income (I don't need to rely on public schools / public transit)? 

What is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Student Turnout in US Federal Elections, By Major </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 22:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 22:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A library for both images and text, ideally showing useful metrics from past uses, such as engagement rate and click through.

Crowdbabble does past posts with engagement data, but not click through :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Case Study] Pinterest users and conservative voters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 19:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 16:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubling conversions by tweaking the landing page

Increasing traffic driven to site from social, which in turn increased conversions on that landing page

I think your achievements are great -- can you link them to other things within the business? Increased social media following -- sales increased </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 16:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait for the analytics API to be out for this. Right now you can't track them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 16:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they deliberately went after the poor and told them to raise their credit card limits to pay for the courses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 04:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lawsuits have mostly been from veterans and the poor. http://www.cnbc.com/2016/08/02/donald-trump-loses-bid-for-pretrial-win-in-trump-university-lawsuit.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 04:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were mostly poor and included many veterans, being worked over by highly trained sales people promising to save them from poverty. Not morons. If you were desperate for your next rent cheque and a trained salesperson worked you over, you'd probably fall for the same thing. 

The real estate classes weren't the main sell. The university promised advisors and mentors who would help them navigate purchases, which never materialized -- that's why he's being sued (that and the predatory sales practices). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 04:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot scams -- he also makes a lot of money from scams. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 04:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America's best interest can be interpreted many ways, and Trump would interpret it as protecting big business (not workers). He'd protect the GDP at all costs and would further hollow out the middle class, a trend which in the end, will destroy the American economy.

Clinton, on the other hand, has co-sponsored many bills that protect small businesses and workers -- like a bill that offered tax credits to small businesses that provided health insurance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 04:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with the efficiency bit, but I don't think any outsider can just ride in on a white horse and start cutting red tape. You need someone who understands the system. 

We disagree on almost everything else -- gun control is a big one -- so we won't agree. But I think Hillary has protected workers well, whereas Trump could not care less about most Americans. This is my impression of Trump (he's Lucille): https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/564x/41/5b/d0/415bd0232265dbde5d22a54f5ce01267.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 03:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many companies choose not to bring in temporary foreign workers, instead choosing to hire American workers. Hiring people on short term contracts is good in the short term, but actually destroys productivity in the long term. Companies that only have quarterly earnings in their sight, rather than long-term strategy, often fail spectacularly (see Dell in the mid 2000s). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 03:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has a brain and a track record of progressive, useful bills that protect workers. I think she's an infinitely better choice than a corrupt reality TV star. https://www.govtrack.us/congress/bills/browse?sponsor=300022#current_status[]=2

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 03:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes me think he would do that?

Because he does it with his own businesses. Hundreds of foreign workers to save money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 03:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary has co-sponsored many bills that hurt big companies and support workers. https://www.govtrack.us/congress/bills/browse?sponsor=300022#current_status[]=2

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 03:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it pales -- it's a sales process that targeted poor people and told them to raise their credit card limits so they could earn a living (aka pay for more Trump 'courses' that never materialized). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 02:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He does what's best for his business in the short term, and leaves a trail of lawsuits behind him.

You really want him to take the same approach with the US? Bring in temporary foreign workers to fill positions, not pay debts, etc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 02:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, the ones that she stored on the server that were released? The vast majority were pretty mundane, and in 2011 she even emailed that she thought she should disclose the private server email (https://foia.state.gov/searchapp/DOCUMENTS/HRCEmail_SeptemberWeb/O-2015-08632-170/DOC_0C05780317/C05780317.pdf)

She wanted to disclose the private emails, and it was her staff that dissuaded her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 02:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...

So, scamming veterans just screams President of the United States to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unpaid bills: http://www.wsj.com/articles/donald-trumps-business-plan-left-a-trail-of-unpaid-bills-1465504454

Hundreds of temporary foreign workers: http://www.politifact.com/florida/statements/2016/may/06/ted-cruz/donald-trump-attacked-bringing-hundreds-foreign-wo/

Trump University elder abuse lawsuit: http://fortune.com/2016/03/08/trump-university-financial-elder-abuse-charges/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree totally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whereas, running the most corrupt businesses in the private sector is better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read some of the legislation that she's created? Are you familiar with her actual work?

Dig into some of the bills she's co-sponsored: https://www.govtrack.us/congress/bills/107/s429

If you look through those bills, you will see dedication to protecting US workers. Many of the bills incentivize companies to create jobs and provide benefits and even housing. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find that people who hate Hillary actually know almost nothing about the legislation she's created (you know, her actual work).

Read some of the bills that Hillary Clinton has cosponsored and see the real benefits that she's already given American workers: https://www.govtrack.us/congress/bills/browse?sponsor=300022 subject=6328#terms=6235

This one, in particular, might interest you. Throughout her career, Hillary has expanded funding for small businesses and manufacturing in the US (while Trump gets his t-shirts made in China): https://www.govtrack.us/congress/bills/107/s429/summary

She banned lead in children's toys. She got 9/11 first responders adequate health care. She regularly sponsors bills that up funding for struggling veterans. She sponsors tax credits for small businesses. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump University doesn't hand out degrees. It takes your money, gives you an advisor, and literally does nothing else. That's why Trump is currently being sued.

Encouraging poor people to get real university degrees may or may not be a bad idea. It's bad advice in some cases, but it isn't theft.

Stealing from poor people in a get rich quick scheme that gives no degrees, has no classroom time, and no teachers, is an actual scam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He does ship jobs overseas. Most of his goods are made overseas, and he hires temporary foreign workers anytime he can. He doesn't hire Americans at his own businesses when he can get a temporary foreign worker visa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has a great record of protecting workers and skillfully negotiating foreign policy. Check out Iran, which could have been yet another addition to the war on terror. Instead, it's contained. She fought for first responders to 9/11 to get health care, she's fought for more funding for veterans.

If you actually read through some of  the bills she has sponsored, you might feel differently: https://www.govtrack.us/congress/bills/browse?sponsor=300022 subject=6328#terms=6235 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know he fills his jobs with temporary foreign workers every chance he gets, right? He doesn't hire American.

These are some of the bills Hillary has sponsored for American workers and veterans. You should read through them: https://www.govtrack.us/congress/bills/browse?sponsor=300022 subject=6328#terms=6235 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump University. 100% corrupt. 

Have you actually looked at Hillary's voting records and the bills that she's sponsored? Read through them. https://www.govtrack.us/congress/bills/browse?sponsor=300022 subject=6328#terms=__ALL__

Her work for First Responders, in particular, shows how she can unite both sides of congress to do good work. She might not be as idealistic as Bernie, but she does do good work. For children, she had lead banned in children's toys and limited the prescription of drugs not tested in children to children -- fighting big business to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He hasn't taken any money from wall street, but he kind of IS wall street? He is big business. He is from the private sector.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary Clinton has taken a lot of hits to her reputation for policies she believes in.

Check out her work in Child and Family Law, where she's fought big industries to add more regulation to protect workers. Banning high levels of lead in children's toys is just one example, but big business fought it tooth and nail. She sponsored that bill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're honestly going to vote for someone who lines his pockets with wages he's stolen from others and bills he hasn't paid? 

If he gets into the White House, Trump is going to make the US the most corrupt country in the world.

Hillary Clinton might be owned by Wall Street, but Donald Trump IS Wall Street. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump University

Hiring cheap foreign workers whenever he can to save his businesses' money, having all of his branded goods made overseas

Not paying contractors, destroying small businesses
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump doesn't pay his contractors, has committed fraud, won't release his tax records, build businesses that go bankrupt, and has created scams specifically to rob people. He hires cheap foreign workers every chance he gets to save his businesses money. Look up Trump University. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up the Trump University lawsuits. He founded a fake university specifically targeting the poor and vulnerable to steal thousands from them.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Trump University, the fake university he created to rob veterans and their families?

He lured in veterans and the poor, charged then tens of thousands of dollars, and gave them nothing. Huge scam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 06:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Social media is probably your best bet. Instagram and Snapchat would be huge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 06:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're describing RV lots.

Look into the financing for those before you start this venture. 

You'd need everything that a great RV park would have, but also with all of the organic / nature / indie stuff that tiny home owners want as well. Privacy, vegetable gardens, lots of mature trees, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 06:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are Dallas gamers? What communities do they hang out in IRL and online? What social networks? I'm thinking Reddit and Snapchat might be big.

Make inroads in local gaming groups and with local gaming shops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 19:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should throw in other green services as well, and make sure that you have a $ amount that you can save homeowners.

By adding window insulation, your windows will go from an R2 to an R5, leading to a heat loss reduction  of [REAL NUMBER]. With 16 LED light bulbs replacing 16 incandescent bulbs, I will save you $ per year on your energy. Your carbon footprint will be reduced by XYZ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 07:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't like Donald Trump either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 01:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take stats. Statistics is absolutely key to many areas of marketing, and it's essential to market researchers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 01:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your competitors doing on social?

Where is your audience?

For a lot of fitness brands, Instagram and Pinterest are huge -- they're aspirational, like fitness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 01:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your competitors doing?

Social media would be a huge help -- especially Instagram, where a lot of photographers are. 

How can you get influential photographers to start using your products?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 00:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unpaid internships are almost always a bad idea. If the company you're working for doesn't pay its interns, it's likely that they'll never hire you -- before committing to this internship, you should really ask them how many foreign workers they hire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 22:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/digitalnomad

Look for coworking hubs. 

Keeping east coast hours really limits you. If you can lift those limits, I highly recommend Hubud in Bali. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 21:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way too rushed -- 1 night / .5 days in  each place?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 21:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With $5,000, you don't have to stay in hostels. I'd suggest spending 4 nights in each city (3 full days), so you're not exhausted. Don't include your arrival and departure nights -- you'll just be dead. For all 4 cities, that's 16 nights. Check Google maps -- the distances by train and plane can be a full day of travel.

Any possibility of going in September? There won't be the crazy lines.

Search /r/travel for "europe itinerary" to get ideas. Book flights 3 months out -- you should be able to get round trip for $800 each if you find a sale. Put a flight alert on using kayak.com.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 22:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I profiled 4 startups who grew an organic following here: http://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/starting-at-0-social-media-for-new-businesses/

Basically, if you're launching a company, your followers want to hear about your milestones and your progress. That content theme performed well for all four new businesses I profiled. 

Other than that, you have to find content that your customers value.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 22:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When can you go? The season will really affect the places you should visit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 16:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree. Everyone I profiled seems to have found content themes that their audiences value. For most startups, at least one content theme that will do well is news about your team and milestones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 16:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reinventing Dell - how to build an entrepreneurial culture, then how to lose it

Hooked - Great UX book about building habit-forming products </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 18:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, what are your top performing hashtags and filters? What's your best posting time? What was your top performing post? 

Get some data so you can figure out how to move forward.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starting from 0: I looked at how 4 startups built small, sincere audiences on social media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 05:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, entrepreneurs! I looked at the social media strategies of four startups to try to find lessons for the rest of us. How do you build an audience when you're starting with 0 followers? 

This isn't a get-followers-fast post. I looked at 4 startups who are slowly building audiences, organically. 

Here's a link to the full article, with the images mentioned: http://www.crowdbabble.com/blog/starting-at-0-social-media-for-new-businesses/


**The Challenge**
Building a brand can be a challenge for small businesses on a shoestring budget. A creative approach to social media can have a huge impact, at a very low cost. But when you start with zero followers, how can you build an audience?

Many small businesses turn to either buying likes on Facebook or furiously following and unfollowing people on Twitter and Instagram to inflate their audiences, somewhat artificially. This approach can damage your brand at the outset: inauthentic growth will make potential customers question your brands authenticity in other areas. If your online audience is fake, your brand promises, reviews, and value might be fake as well. I looked around the new brands in my own social network and the incubator where Crowdbabble is based to find examples of real growth: of users finding and following brands not just for a #followback, but because they find value in the brand and the content it shares.

The small businesses below have successfully cleared the first hurdle of social media marketing: building a small, but real audience of fans online. How did they do it?

**Arti Designs Her Life: A Lifestyle Blog**
Arti Designs Her Life is an inspirational blog run by Arti Joshi, where she discusses her journey through the world of following your passions and who splits her time between London and far-flung locations like Australia and Indonesia. The blog launched in August 2015 and has experienced slow and steady growth to 500 WordPress followers and 110 very dedicated Facebook fans. On Facebook, Joshi has achieved what few other small businesses have: an almost equal proportion of shares to likes. Likes require less effort, and usually signal that fans are closer to the top of the funnel  less likely to convert. Because Facebook shares extend your reach to entirely new audiences (they push content onto your fans feeds for all of their friends to see), theyre much more powerful for increasing reach.

45% of fan engagement with Arti Designs Her Life on Facebook is shares. This indicates that her early adopter fans are brand advocates: though the page has a small audience, its very powerful. From March 2015 to March 2016, this highly engaged audience gave Joshis Facebook page an engagement rate of 152%.
Joshis ability to attract such a high proportion of shares might lie in her content strategy: her Facebook page is focused on videos with an inspirational lean.

When Joshi posted two interviews in quick succession, in early March, her Facebook Page Likes increased dramatically. By creating video content and interviewing with bloggers who have more Facebook fans, Arti engaged two active audiences: her own brand advocates, and those of her interviewees. With this approach, her Facebook fan base should continue to grow organically and she should be able to amass an even higher proportion of brand advocates.

**SlimCut Media: Tech Startup**
SlimCut Media is a Toronto-based startup that offers advertising solutions to online media, including news sites. Though its ad solutions boast more than 1 billion page views, translating those viewers into brand advocates on social media hasnt been easy. As a B2B startup, SlimCut faces a unique challenge on social media: its solutions arent aimed at most consumers and their audience is much narrower. On Twitter, SlimCut has successfully attracted followers interested in the companys progress. 

The companys most successful tweets arent about its industry, but about SlimCuts milestones as a startup. Photos and status updates, rather than industry news links, are the most engaging for @SlimCutMedias audience.

According to startup social media expert Brent Stirling, speaking as a person, rather than a faceless company, is the best way for new businesses to grow their audiences. SlimCuts focus on its progress as a team of people, rather than a company in a B2B industry, is aiding its follower growth.

**A Piece of the Party: Videography Company**
This new business delivers on the promise of fun in its name. Its CEO  London-based Lauren Garvey  has carefully built a trendy brand that delivers playful, authentic videos of important events. A Piece of the Partys brand is that its not your mothers wedding footage. Shareable content is built into the business model: who can resist footage of the first time the groom sees the bride, or a snapshot of the flower girl and ring bearer?

On Facebook, Garvey has leveraged this content to build an audience of potential customers. Garvey focuses on lush HD footage uploaded to Vimeo, and personalizes posts by mentioning the first names of the bride and groom. These short highlight reels will help her page continue to grow along with her business. Her engagement rate from 2015 to 2016, when she launched her business, was 109.8%. More recently, Garvey has focused on video content and photos  this strategy seems to be paying off. In May 2016 A Piece of the Party grew fast on Facebook, gaining 20 new fans in one day.

The graph above shows the sharp rise on May 16, when Garvey posted a feature highlighting her videos on a popular wedding site. By celebrating the feature with her followers, she is making early adopters part of her milestones. As with SlimCut media, sharing positive news about the company creates the biggest return for her new and growing audience.

**Climb Out of the Cubicle: Ecourses**
This brand delivers e-courses and organization tools to help you maximize your spare time, realizing your dreams around a 9 to 5. Founder Amber Monaco has created a second shift community on social media, where she organizes chats and shares her insights via blog posts. Social networks are drowning in self-help brands, from companies promising miracle cures in turmeric recipes to bloggers selling $800 conference tickets that promise to change your life. But the success of brands who promote content that only teases other products is often short-lived. Once social media users realize that value is never just one click away, they stop clicking. Customers have become wary of anyone peddling #lifehack solutions; building credibility and delivering real value up front is key to success in this area.

Climb Out of the Cubicle stands out with inspirational content available for free, in Monacos personable voice. Monaco has avoided the clickbait trap by frequently updating her Facebook page with blog posts that are self-contained stories, not behind a paywall.

The audience (and credibility) Monaco built on Twitter, along with her unique content strategy, allowed her to succeed on Facebook. Monacos steady growth on Facebook, where she posts her articles frequently, is a testament to the success of her strategy.

Another key factor in Monacos success? Posting as herself. As social media guru Brent Stirling said, new businesses can find success by posting as real people, so that users can identify with the person behind the brand. Monaco publishes in first person as the business owner, rather than in third person as the business, and this has been key to her success.

Starting at 0 in January, Monacos audience has grown on Facebook to almost 500 likes likes. That may seem small, but her engagement rate is high: an average of 147.5% since January. By giving away quality written content for free and not pushing other offerings hard in her posts, Monaco has avoided the spammy feel that turns off potential customers.

**Lessons for Small and New Businesses**
Slow and steady growth can be frustrating for small business owners growing their brands authentically by delivering real value on social media. Seeing just 5 new likes on a Facebook page or 10 new Twitter followers in a week seems, on its face, discouraging. But if you are growing authentically, those likes are valuable: they represent users who are genuinely interested in your content. 

New businesses do best when they recognize that their audiences are early adopters: users excited to share in the companys growth and be part of its important milestones. These fans and followers  the few, the enthusiastic  are more likely to become customers and then brand advocates. Another key feature is posting as the human behind the brand, not the brand itself. With engagement rates of more than 100% and a high proportion of shares and retweets, organic growth will likely continue for these new businesses.

When you start at 0, attracting 10 new likes or follows unlocks 10 potential new audiences: your brand is exposed to the networks of new fans genuinely interested in your content, and most likely to share it. Startups and small businesses that begin at 0 might grow slowly, but the early adopters who found real value in their brands will be more likely to convert. For new businesses, small gains are big victories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 22:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crowdbabble does a follower export in excel or csv for any Twitter or Instagram account, but it's an extra you have to pay for. 

Birdsong does this as well, but it's pricier. Overall, you're looking at .002 - 1 cent per follower for spreadsheet format for big accounts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 21:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not go out on your own, and develop social media strategies for indie games? Start at a local video game course if you have to -- find people who are building and releasing games, and develop campaigns for them. And execute them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 00:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone here read Made to Stick? It was written before social media, but I think a lot of the principles (like testable credentials) are even more useful now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can digital advertising agencies advertise themselves? Social media and testable credentials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 00:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 00:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, what are your competitors doing on social? What are you doing for analytics?

What do you offer that they don't?

Who can you partner with that they aren't partnered with?

Find your differences and pursue them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR: Your clients will use your agency's social media accounts to test your brand promises, from audience building to engagement. If you can't deliver on your own social accounts, your credentials will not be credible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 18:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did a few case studies on their social media campaigns.

Trump succeeds because he's sensationalist, and no matter what he says, he gets a high proportion of shares. This has allowed his follower base online to explode. 

Hillary always positioned herself as the anti-Trump, whereas Bernie positioned himself as the anti-Hillary -- I think that's why he didn't make it as the nominee. The core of  Hillary's campaign is that she can defeat Trump.

My latest case study on their campaigns is here: https://medium.com/@crowdbabble/trump-vs-clinton-vs-sanders-who-is-winning-the-election-on-social-media-62421a743298

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 17:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your competitors doing?

What are your goals?

What are your content themes and strategy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
