<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8180</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BF1] [Question] Trying very hard to help my team but I die too quickly to be of any use </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 23:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title says it all. I am not new to the Battlefield franchise, although I have never played it seriously, and since hopping into BF1 it feels completely different. I am shot at not a few seconds after spawning, and no matter how many corners I check or how slowly I move, someone always seems to be able to lock me down. 
As you can imagine, this makes for a difficult time for being anything other than cannon fodder on the battlefield, and I really enjoy helping my team. What am I doing wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 11:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, Ill shoot you a message in game tonight as Im currently at work. 
What is your IGN?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 10:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone sell me an early game Frame? I started a couple of days ago and have no idea which one would suit me. I have Exc at the moment, and I really enjoy the feel of him, if that helps... I tend to melee a lot more than I shoot though, but thats probably because I use a bow. 
Thanks in advance. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 12:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck this is exactly what I'm looking for, are spots still open? I will contribute in any way I can. 
Name is - damage3
If you need it, my steam is - http://steamcommunity.com/id/elipterohmygod/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 03:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @xMetriccv I'll add all of you! (ps: I'm lonely :( )  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for Unturned buddies to play whatever :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 03:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey!
Recently I just got back into Unturned and wow have I been missing out. The new update is incredible and the game has come far since I last played. But there's one small problem... I have noone to play with! :( 
I am 16/M/UK and would like to play with anyone with an interest in the game whether it is casual, competitive, PvE or PvE, whatever you would like :)
My steam is - http://steamcommunity.com/id/elipterohmygod/

Look forward to meeting some of you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 10:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet, see you soon :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dont usually eat lunch but did today, feeling very ill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 14:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone, Im not sure whether Im posting this in the right place but I thought some of you may be able to help me out.
Recently, I have stopped eating lunch simply because I didnt feel the need to, and have been doing so for about 3 weeks, if not longer. Today, though, I decided to have a small amount of food just to give me a bit more energy and now I am feeling very ill... My stomach feels really unsettled and sickly and it has been going on for a good while now :(

I would appreciate anyone letting me know whats going on, Im very confused... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 19:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, look forward to playing. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 14:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added you, see you there. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 14:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done, look forward to seeing you around. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 17:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I dont have Borderlands :( Are there any other games you play? Im free about the same time :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [16/M/UK] Looking for friendly PC gamers to play and chat with, most games :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 14:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently got a new PC that can handle pretty much whatever so I got a bunch of games and am now looking for people to play them with! At the moment Im playing a lot of Insurgency, CSGO, Dark Souls and H1Z1, but Im open to pretty much anything :) I dont mind if youre in a different timezone, Im free most days~
My steam is - https://steamcommunity.com/id/elipterohmygod/ and for communication, my skype is - reptil31066
Look forward to meeting some of you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 14:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, hmu - https://steamcommunity.com/id/elipterohmygod/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
