<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4332</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 17:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the pictures, these are inspiring!


A link with an address for each location would be awesome.  I'm going to be in NYC twice this summer and if I can swing it I will try to hit a few of these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 20:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard in an interview that Chip makes a big deal out of making sure players get enough sleep.  A year or two ago I made changes to my daily schedule to make sure I get no less than 7 hours of sleep a night.  It's made a huge difference in my overall health and fitness.

I'm guessing you are inferring that because Trent was going to sleep at 8:00pm in order to get the amount of sleep he needs that he was somehow off schedule due to the game being late.  Maybe, but I think it had more to do with him being over matched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 20:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is such a breath of fresh air after all those years of Andy.  Love the sarcasm, love the quick wit, the frank answers.  I imagine if he wins us a Superbowl he will be doing Blue Cross commercials from the grave.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 20:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the exact same thing when I heard about this.  The Phillies had a similar swagger right before their last run, let's all hope this is another sign of good things to come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 23:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me happy.  It will be nice for the front office to get another year with a consistent team in place making picks.  I guess being the head honcho isn't important to him yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 21:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He seems to be one of those players that knows where to be to make a play.  My wife and son tease me now because I yelled out I love you! after one of his game sealing interceptions.

As a whole this year has been such a joy to behold, from the on the field improvements of both the offense and defense to the general warm up the front office has experienced.  They may not always be right but at least they all seem willing to speak to the public now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 18:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really nice restore.  I loved this game as a kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 15:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you could have done is get the 4 top teeth on one hand and 4 bottom teeth on the other.  Then when you put your hands together it would make a set.  Or do them left to right across so you'd have the top of a smile.  I do like the look of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 22:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you consider doing these in the other direction?  They feel upside down to me for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 22:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a link to the original portrait?  I'm curious to see if his eyes are like that in the original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 22:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As others have stated, it looks crooked.  In particular the top looks like it is rolled forward - it should have lined up with your collarbone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 22:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scale of the on leaf at the bottom is jarring to me.  I understand it may be meant to appear closer than the others but it looks off to me.  If it were me I would have the branch going to the lower right maybe arc up towards my neck so I would have space for something below it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 22:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the Philly Metro area and the guy that does my tattoos was at the convention.  He linked to the following on his facebook page (possibly NSFW - I didn't look at every picture):

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vk6KRaSrJeQ

https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.388962507866586.86569.143789019050604 type=1

I wish I had gone down to see what it was all about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
