<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5227</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the altered title is actually reflecting what the article claims - which is where we should have discussion right? Like why or why not we agree or disagree with the article.

Here's the excerpt that matches the title:

And minutes prior to the final decision  in which FTC commissioners took the unusual step of overriding their staffs recommendation to sue, and voted to settle the case instead  the White House official even sought Googles talking points in the matter.

Edit: oh wow, I see what you're saying. Thanks for clarifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 16:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are countless examples ranging from spin of US drone strikes and spin of US torture programs to accusing Snowden of selling secrets to China. I'm glad the only three comments here said pretty much the same thing lol

Tho I guess they still have a ton of fans because the post has a 50% upvoted rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 15:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't we talking about The Intercept? The paper run by Glenn Greenwald?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 15:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Astroturfing is real.

[This thread](https://np.reddit.com/r/shills/comments/4kdq7n/astroturfing_information_megathread_revision_8/?st=irwpnkzm sh=115ca8a6) lists a long list of sources talking about the issue, from sites such as the Guardian.

Even tho the redditor you're talking to claims he's/she's in PR, it's pretty silly to instantly refute all the evidence we've seen of it based on that isn't?

Edit: using phone, had to fix formatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did The NY Times Give Up Its Journalism Standards The Second Facebook Threw A Few Million Its Way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emails Reveal Relationship Before Tech Antitrust Lawsuit Was Shelved </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 17:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mainly think it's [this](https://www.reddit.com/r/undelete/comments/4xuwxe/whenever_i_make_a_comment_about_how_slippery/d6j2dgg)

I might try to repost the story sometime because I think it's newsworthy   relevant. It also fits with a concerning theme that is slowly entering discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worse yet, unless youre an enterprise user, no matter what, you have to share at least some of this telemetry data with Microsoft and theres no way to opt-out of it.

Wow, didn't know that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House Official Cozied Up to Google Before Antitrust Lawsuit Was Shelved </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 17:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just going to say the same. The headline doesn't match the article at all, but I did find the short article interesting to read anyways.

Click bait headline (as it had nothing to do with the writing), but decent description of context for event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it will help "pay for groceries." /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Reddit Dead? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 23:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If nation-states are interested in what we are doing we must be doing something right. Right?

Funny times we live in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ed Snowden Explains Why Hackers Published NSA's Hacking Tools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 23:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assange said he timed the DNC leak to hurt the Clinton campaign and he has come out in favor of Trump.

Asked recently by Amy Goodman of Democracy Now if he does prefer Trump over Clinton, Assange replied, Youre asking me, do I prefer cholera or gonorrhea?

[Source](https://theintercept.com/2016/08/06/accusing-wikileaks-bias-beside-point/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't Greenwald time his journalism to have maximum impact? I don't see how that is an issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More reason to use tor. It's like giving them the finger in a way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article actually mentions that in the first paragraph and differentiates the two. This honestly looks much worse than that shift, especially from the possible inclusion of DRM. I recommend reading it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't see the part where he admits to having talked about overthrowing their gov. I may have just missed it though, could you show me where the article mentions that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 17:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's the basis of wikileaks, to use leaks to expose wrongful actions of powerful figures or organizations. It isn't really that sinister, however there are other concerns - like how well they will continue to be able to verify/make-corrections and remove irrelevant private information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 17:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, even Bruce Schneier is calling this a backdoor.

Source: https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2016/08/microsoft_accid.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secure Boot snafu: Microsoft leaks backdoor key, firmware flung wide open </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 17:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Possible Solution To Twitter's Difficult Problem Of Abusive Behavior: Let People Speak, Don't Force Everyone To Listen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick question, were you arguing that Facebook's program would counter the kind of state censorship in India the article talked about? That is what I was arguing against. That one gatekeeper would be no better than another, possibly worse - in the case Facebook might offer it globally.

Additionally, I don't think we're giving enough credit that there can be better solutions to a problem than this - that do not create bigger monsters to deal with. If the only way to better humanity is through undemocratic policies, if there are no alternatives, then humanity has a catastrophic problem on its hands. When tyranny is the only hope for improvement, things can only get worse.

Edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As social media centralized, blogging's core infrastructure has withered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you give that kind of power and influence to an entity, it becomes very hard to take it back. Short-term tradeoffs have repeatedly shown this, many we grapple with to this day - with continuing consequences into the foreseeable future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Talks Tough About Military Contractors, But Quietly Signals Friendship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 22:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 20:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook would have the choice of blocking access to websites they want as part of the limited service. If they were really not self-interested (and if there is even such a thing as a 'free lunch') they'd donate to public libraries to increase information access; not make themselves the gatekeepers to easy access information.

The long term danger to giving those policies any ground outweighs short term gains. If it is true that India's establishment forces opposed Facebook for their own self-interests, I'm glad to hear because in some places - corporations and governments often have the same interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only problem with VPNs is that it's often a "privacy by policy" type scenario. Although not as relevant to most of us, there have been some sad stories about VPNs that gave up logged traffic to authorities (Hidemyass was one)*. Many VPNs also log traffic for marketing reasons as well.

But your other points are definitely true, though I think Tor can be trusted in more ways than their alternatives. E.g., larger pool of users which increases anonymity.

*Some VPNs literally have blood on their hands for turning over activists. Can find sources later if wanted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi Insurgents Stymied the NSA and Other Highlights from 263 Internal Agency Reports </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure Verizon is known to read traffic for marketing reasons (not just law enforcement). There's been a few articles about it including concern that they're even reading traffic from other carriers that use their shared cell towers.

And I wouldn't put it past Comcast either. Can't offer sources right now, but they shouldnt be too hard to find. If you're not using Tor, you should assume your traffic is being tied to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corporate and state censorship are both serious problems and should equally be opposed, regardless of excuses offered like terrorism or good business. Controlling information flow is an easily abusable power, and one could simply look at the concerns regarding tech companies' involvement in politics as it is to see the dangers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Like The Rest Of The Internet Of Things, Most 'Smart' Locks Are Easily Hacked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malware Linked to Government of Kazakhstan Targets Journalists, Political Activists, Lawyers: EFF Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 21:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google is a company with billions in annual profit. [Src](http://www.businessinsider.com/alphabet-google-q4-2015-earnings-2016-2)

25k is a tiny amount for what was effectively scanning people's home networks and collecting information such as passwords, through the street view vans. That's like 0.000625% of their profit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Iranian Government Hacks Dissidents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 16:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 15:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, I don't think they liked Trump since the first debate where he said he'd run as a 3rd party candidate. Both parties are markedly divided.

It's been an awesome election that I don't think we'll get again for a long time.  I imagine both parties will be way more careful in vetting their candidates in the future, and return to their usual staging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It definitely revealed a whole slew of shady business. Most of all, I think it showed people something many of us knew, that parties pick their running candidates - not popularity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I think it describes them pretty fairly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The information presented in the article itself actually doesn't match the headline. There's more to Wikileaks than being anti-hillary, the article shows.

I actually have the same sentiment you do and likewise think you'd enjoy reading the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democratizing information has never been more vital, and @Wikileaks has helped. But their hostility to even modest curation is a mistake.


This article's main criticism of Wikileaks is the same as Snowden's (shown above). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Julian Assanges War on Hillary Clinton Says About WikiLeaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 21:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 01:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The label system was designed so users can filter though those subsets and not have-to see them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 01:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on what country you operate in, it can be pretty scary. Countless examples. And hopefully you're not entering for the money, because part of the reason there is so much bad journalism is that honest journalism isn't lucrative (speaking as an outsider, not a journalist myself). [This article](https://theintercept.com/2016/07/22/oil-lobby-paid-washington-post-and-atlantic-to-host-climate-change-deniers-at-rnc/) talks about it a bit.

E.g.  Brazil:

[+] https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/3g54c0/brazilian_radio_host_famous_for_exposing/

[+] https://www.theguardian.com/media/greenslade/2015/may/21/brazilian-journalist-beheaded-during-mystery-investigation

[And many more enemies of the truth.](http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2015/02/government-censorship-21st-century-internet/385528/) 

Truly, honest journalists are **heroes.**

What those who take shots at Tor forget that it literally keeps some of these people alive and able to continue their work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 00:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On wikipedia, the origin of the word *allegedly* comes from this quote:

How long is it going to take before lawyers realize that the simple act of trying to repress something they don't like online is likely to make it so that something that most people would never, ever see (like a photo of a urinal in some random beach resort) is now seen by many more people? Let's call it the Streisand Effect.

And I think that interpretation is shared by many people, as it's often cited alongside the line about the internet rerouting around censorship. But you're right in the sense the Wikipedia definition supports your point.

As sad as it is that the idealistic view of an internet that is self-correcting hasn't held up over the years, I do think many of us are willing to fight censorship when we find out about it, and that itself is pretty awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Security Researchers Hijack a Big Rig Trucks Accelerator and Brakes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 23:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 22:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I don't think a few comments on the story is the same thing as an internet lynch mob.

I also don't think there's a difference between defamation of 'your boss' if he is a public figure (Sheriff) and defamation of 'state and federal government.' In other words, the First Amendment defense (which usually holds in defamation cases in the US) should apply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 22:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because writing on paper isn't popular isn't an argument that this isn't technological issue. If internet of things became more popular than their counterparts, we wouldn't say coverage on issues relating to internet of things are not related to technology. 

They seized the electronics of the suspect to investigate defamation charges. They may not have succeeded at finding the right person, but they are clearly engaging in a criminal investigation of defamation from the website owner. Defamation charges are used to take down content, e.g. Jim Sterling's YT channel experienced a few well-known examples of it. Whether justified or not, it would still be a form of censorship.

I'm addition to how politics affects technology (ie the censorship part of the story), how technology affects politics (exposing corruption) is a topic relevant for technology discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 21:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference is if you received a pamphlet, you'll likely be able to keep it   make copies, but few people mirror obscure websites on the internet. And since online communications is a critical for previously mentioned reasons, news stories on how technology is affecting politics (alleged corruption exposing) and how politics affects technology (removal of online speech for defamation) is relevant here. To reiterate online censorship is a technological   political issue, not just legal. This particular story isn't groundbreaking but it is one tale in a long running issue that we're grabbling with - unique to the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 21:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately I don't have time to flesh out discussion on this topic right now but know this sparked a pretty big debate on /r/technology 3 years ago   a lot of mods were removed as a result. That's why you see there are different labels on the side, so you can filter out topics that are related to technology - but not what you're interested in. 

They weren't there before the controversy but after, it was confirmed that a less strict definition of "technology" (e.g., discussion on acts like SOPA and the CFAA) should be allowed on this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 20:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fundamentally none as civil liberties apply online and IRL. However the internet has been thought to be a technology to give visibility on issues unlike other mediums, but online censorship is in many ways easier than IRL censorship. 

Shutting down or blocking an obscure website will often effectively erase it on a level unique to online speech. It's actually much harder to completely destroy every copy of a book than to remove something online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 20:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, I think the Streisand effect is a myth nowadays. I've seen censorship in-general as often very effective. Still, when you realize it happened - I guess it makes many of us more motivated to try to keep it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 20:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish these messages provided a reason why the article posted doesn't match the rule. Figured a story talking in the context of online free speech would be relevant to technology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 20:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A techdirt article linked me to this reddit post. They provide a reason as to not only why the threat is credible but why the CFAA is so bad. Pretty sure this was the same one used to prosecute Aaron Swartz after JSTOR dropped the lawsuit, and many other examples exist.

Here's the article: https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20160804/17595935161/pokemon-company-threatens-pokemon-go-api-creator-with-cfaa-lawsuit.shtml </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 17:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or have deep enough pockets to afford it. Thinking of William Binney. (Trying to find a source, seems his Wikipedia article no longer mentions what I'm alluding to)

Edit: It was the other NSA whistleblower, Thomas Drake.

If you become a whistleblower, "You have to mortgage your house, you have to empty your bank accounts," Drake says.

Drake estimated that the charges had cost him over a million dollars in legal fees and lost work.

Source: ["These Whistleblowers Lost Almost Everything for Sharing the Truth" - Vice](https://motherboard.vice.com/read/information-isnt-free-how-whistleblowers-suffer-for-the-truth)

The judge also rejected the government's request for a large fine noting that Drake had been financially devastated, losing his $154,600 job at the NSA and his pension.

Source: [Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thomas_Andrews_Drake) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sheriff Raids House to Find Anonymous Blogger Who Called Him Corrupt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 16:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 16:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard people say everything is clickbait. I hope the word isn't so subjective so as to justify removing articles the way /r/technology did 3 years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 16:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the fact that it's being advertised as a trade deal (something way less controversial than it really is) speaks volumes about our media.

Worth reading or skimming:

https://theintercept.com/2016/07/05/despite-what-media-says-tpp-isnt-about-free-trade-its-about-helping-corporations/

https://theintercept.com/2016/08/01/cnn-and-fox-news-are-finally-covering-the-tpp-after-ignoring-it-for-two-years/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 15:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's only willingness. Globally, people are living in times of [increasing censorship and disinformation.](http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2015/02/government-censorship-21st-century-internet/385528/)

The most heavily consumed sources of information is either coming through literal state web filters or through media with conflicts of interests (state ownership, [corporate ownership](http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/gossip/confidential/walters-top-pick-edward-snowden-didn-fascinate-abc-article-1.1536685), [drying up sources of income](https://theintercept.com/2016/07/22/oil-lobby-paid-washington-post-and-atlantic-to-host-climate-change-deniers-at-rnc/)). And even looking for public discussion is bound to be contaminated by [astroturfing.](https://np.reddit.com/r/shills/comments/4kdq7n/astroturfing_information_megathread_revision_8/)

explaining all aspects of the TPP

Here's [an article on a study](https://theintercept.com/2016/08/01/cnn-and-fox-news-are-finally-covering-the-tpp-after-ignoring-it-for-two-years/) on how long US news media ignored it entirely. Also an article about [how it's been presented](https://theintercept.com/2016/07/05/despite-what-media-says-tpp-isnt-about-free-trade-its-about-helping-corporations/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 00:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only we all had Aiden Pierce's cap, which seemed to magically defeat facial recognition in Watch Dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 00:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd believe it. Microsoft seems like they were always one of those kinds of companies, for other reasons besides being the first one to participate in PRISM. Obviously no big tech company has the public interest at heart, but Microsoft usually seems to be more blatant about it.

I mean, it goes as far back as hilarious [_NSAKey.](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/NSAKEY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 21:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By contrast, a vote  for Nehlen was a vote for someone who would never sit in a board room with Goldman Sachs executives. Its a vote for every person who never got to go out for a steak dinner with lobbyists for the Chamber of Commerce, he said.

In June, Nehlen said that the TPP alone was enough reason to run against Ryan, saying it would cause the fundamental undoing of America.

This is some real fire and brimstone populism. We might be watching something interesting emerging in US politics. A lot of anger at the system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft Pitches Technology That Can Read Facial Expressions at Political Rallies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 21:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 22:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how I'm seeing it. Certain kinds of sudden activity for something as small as a comment strike me as sketch, especially on /r/technology - which doesn't usually get excited about trivial stories based entirely on one alleged comment.

For example on the politics subreddit, for a week all you saw was anger at the DNC email leak revelations, anger that a certain politician hired a Party member after resigning from the scandal in the emails, protests on the DNC floor (anti-war and anti-TPP), discussion of third parties, anger at moderator censorship and so-on.

However it currently has a very different narrative. Pretty much sole attention is on things Trump says or things Hillary says. Even outside of reddit, I see media personalities refer to the DNC as largely smooth   showed 'unity' (which if you look at what happened that week, you'd be scratching your head). It's jarring but I honestly think it's too late to undo the damage done in July. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 22:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the one which got snuck into the larger bill after public protest, right? Do we know who were responsible for that egregious action? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 22:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another redditor says this article was spinning something she said about children cell phone use into a strawman about WiFi. Don't have time to check but I wouldn't be surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 21:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol did he really try to bribe the Intercept reporter that blatantly?

Following that call, Tang telephoned Yu [the Intercept reporter in Hong Kong] directly in Hong Kong. Speaking with her in Cantonese, Tang was alternately threatening and cajoling, asking Yu to prevent The Intercept from referencing unverified claims on Chinese-language websites that he had been accused of smuggling, tax evasion, and bribery in Shantou. If she did, Tang said, when he came to Hong Kong the following week he would give her **a red packet of 200,000 dollars, so we can be friends, adding, I dont even know why you want to be a reporter, reporters make so little money.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 21:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't even about only one party or person. The article is talking about the bipartisan issue of money's influence in politics - including the money held by foreign actors. Heavy stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 21:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure how much party affiliation matters in this story. This type of influence in politics is scary.

I wonder in what ways APIC is different from AIPAC, besides the obvious surface layer differences (like APIC is specifically for Asia)?

Also, interesting highlight from the article:

The story of APIC captures the bizarre reality of the U.S. political system: George H.W. Bush and George W. Bush between them appointed three of the five members of the Supreme Courts Citizens United majority; this majority opened up a loophole allowing foreign money to flow into U.S. elections; and this loophole was used to grab foreign money in an attempt to make a third Bush president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 16:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It also captured a conversation between a San Mateo Superior Court judge and a county prosecutor who discussed "case loads, the quality of attorneys appearing before the judge, and a request from the judge that the prosecutor not blame his deputies for certain events."

I don't know what personal motivations were at play but it does seem at least one judge was recorded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 00:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She said this about the TPP

When The Intercept asked Lim if she thought Clinton would support the TPP, she said that was likely. Thats a great question. I know that she has changed her position a little bit recently on it, Lim said, but I think that she will go back towards the middle on TPP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 00:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the article mentions the background of the these people and the organization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 00:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) free trade is not about putting greater restrictions that only serve to benefit entrenched powers. That's protectionism and anticompetitive.

2) how is it fair and reasonable to sue democratic will for affecting corporate profits? From my understanding, there are no exit clauses or expiratory date.

3) 600 pages? I think you mean it's around [6,000 pages long](http://www.npr.org/2015/11/05/454907630/obama-lifts-veil-of-secrecy-on-tpp-and-its-a-whopper-of-a-trade-deal)

4) Actually no, you shouldn't trust a comment on the internet when they claim they're a lawyer. 

5) Well, it must suck to have all the answers to correct the erroneous record people keep putting forth on the internet. A thankless job I imagine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton Will Be Good for Business, Predicts Chamber of Commerce Lobbyist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 23:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Judge Rips Uber Apart Over Dirt-Digging Investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 23:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 18:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Vice President of Comcast](https://theintercept.com/2016/05/11/lobbyists-dnc-2016-convention/) is personally pushing agendas with both major parties.

David Cohen is the **special adviser to the [Democratic] Host Committee** and serves as the executive vice president of Comcast, overseeing the companys lobbying and regulatory strategy.

And despite **hosting fundraisers for Clinton at his home last summer,** Cohen has **spent heavily to help elect a Republican Congress**, including recent donations to the NRCC; Sen. Toomey; Sen. Scott; Sen. Kelly Ayotte, R-N.H.; as well as $33,400 to the NRSC, a committee for helping elect GOP members to the Senate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 18:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were founded on the investigative reporting of the NSA and opposition to msm coverage, and I think the quality of their work has remained above-average at worst. They publish only like a couple or few articles a day.

I only hope they continue to embody adversarial journalism at its finest. Good journalists are like heroes of this age where the truth is internationally under assault. Censorship (e.g. web filters, lawsuit threats, targeted violence, media conglomeration), surveillance, and financial conflicts of interest all attest to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 17:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're watching both parties openly act against our interests. It's sad, but it's also amazing seeing so many people understanding how the system has become a stacked deck against them.

Even usual claims of Republican vs Democrat and Left vs Right, that keep people divided and arguing non issues, isn't holding as much water in this environment. People are seeing the media spin, legal immunities, awkward improvisations from politicians not used to this environment, and political machines noticeably designed to serve a powerful   connected minority influence.

So many people of all backgrounds are seeing this that I doubt even an army of astroturfing can undo the damage done.

I know a lot of people are upset about this election, but for someone who has believed this was a worsening problem for years - it's been very satisfying to see the elites try to play their usual games unopposed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the Hillary Clinton Era, Democrats Welcome Lobbying Money Back Into the Convention </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 17:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 16:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I gave the wrong link. Here's the right one: https://youtube.com/watch?v=2oAWwno0Gw8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Famed Hacker Is Grading Thousands of Programs  and May Revolutionize Software in the Process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 16:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 16:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've heard stories of Google, Facebook, and Twitter affecting politics with new policies. Regardless of what you believe about them (tho can't imagine any defense for the Facebook one) Alan Rusbridger (Editor in Chief of the Guardian during the Snowden revelations) made a recent speech that includes a chilling warning of political democratic processes becoming affected by hidden corporate algorithms.

I think about halfway through: https://youtube.com/watch?v=2oAWwno0Gw8

Edit: fixed link, sorry about that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed that whenever the TPP comes up, a redditor will defend it with already debunked points. It's weird because it's been happening so long, I've noticed that the points often include:

[+]it's a free trade deal (if free trade means [corporate protections for existing large corporations](https://theintercept.com/2016/07/05/despite-what-media-says-tpp-isnt-about-free-trade-its-about-helping-corporations/)),

[+]ISDS allows to undo dumb laws (*cough* sue taxpayers for pushing for unprofitable laws *cough*),

[+]trust me or read it yourself (all 5,000+ pages)

[+]I'm a lawyer so I'm right (in juxtaposition to credible sources that aren't faceless reddit accounts, like [Doctors Without Borders](http://www.politico.com/agenda/story/2015/06/tpp-deal-leaked-pharma-000126)),

[+]it's only spreading existing US law to other countries (except when it's [not](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trans-Pacific_Partnership_Intellectual_Property_Provisions)),

[+]trade negotiations start off in secret (except for corporations involved and that secrecy [still continues](https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20160506/17281834365/european-parliament-orders-mep-to-take-down-video-about-his-attempt-to-visit-reading-room-trade-documents.shtml))

[+]start comment thread complaining reddit is biased/(insert reductionist label here). 

Considering how many obvious red flags there are, it's scary seeing the constant push - reciting the same points over and over again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germany had some glorious protests. Using Tor, I remember the German YT front-page had a video talking about the TPP (usually YT front pages around the world are sorta trashy, marketing, or clickbait).

If I remember correctly, their elites ignored the protests.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 06:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an [informative and compelling introduction video](https://youtube.com/watch?v=DnC1mqyAXmw) you can show people.

[EFF animation](https://youtube.com/watch?v=p3KlrfjcjV4) that goes slightly more into the tech side.

Intercept article [countering the claims it is some free trade deal](https://theintercept.com/2016/07/05/despite-what-media-says-tpp-isnt-about-free-trade-its-about-helping-corporations/)

Counter the claims it is merely extending US copyright law with this [Wikipedia article](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trans-Pacific_Partnership_Intellectual_Property_Provisions) largely based on a couple of studies that contrasts the TPP with US copyright law.

And the secrecy in the process *still* continues, as seen here in this [somewhat humorous situation](https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20160506/17281834365/european-parliament-orders-mep-to-take-down-video-about-his-attempt-to-visit-reading-room-trade-documents.shtml)

Remember there is way more than what is mentioned in these sources, likely due to the process it was negotiated in   their ambitions; but I hope sharing this helps with expanding your activist utility belt. Simply staying informed on this issue is opposing it, as it is evident that they have tried hard to prevent that (citing the article on secrecy and article on msm spin). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 06:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean push a popular issue into the Convention? Their goal is to pressure their party by voicing their concerns over it and modifying their party platform. If anything, those people are more optimistic about their party listening than the average person.

Distrust of both US parties is almost on par with their 'disunity,' and ignoring them isn't going to help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 06:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's what quality journalism is for. It's them who must do quality investigative reporting on leaked documents or citing financial conflicts of interests when talking about public servants. They are incredibly important to democracy, but often lacking or met with entrenched opposition. In countries including the US they face censorship, surveillance (e.g., Associated Press by DoJ), and mainstream media contempt.

E.g., Journalists had to do a lot of careful digging and studying to make sense of the raw NSA documents to explain to their readers. Glenn Greenwald's reporting (and fierce arguments with msm) is why I regularly read the Intercept, but it's up to us to figure out who to trust.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 05:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Secrecy concerning the TPP [continues](https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20160506/17281834365/european-parliament-orders-mep-to-take-down-video-about-his-attempt-to-visit-reading-room-trade-documents.shtml) to this day. There have been plenty of credible reporting (definitely more credible than establishment mouthpieces) on what the TPP really is. 

It isn't even a trade deal. The provisions inside go against even the ideals of free trade, it's just called that to sideline discussion away from the actual contents of the TPP.

In fact, the deals major impact would not come in the area of lowering tariffs, the most common trade barriers. The TPP is more focused on crafting regulatory regimes that benefit certain industries.

So the most consequential parts of the deal would actually undermine the free flow of goods and services by expanding some protectionist, anti-competitive policies sought by global corporations.

https://theintercept.com/2016/07/05/despite-what-media-says-tpp-isnt-about-free-trade-its-about-helping-corporations

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 05:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://theintercept.com/2016/07/05/despite-what-media-says-tpp-isnt-about-free-trade-its-about-helping-corporations/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 05:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did. /r/undelete tracked it for months and eventually a redditor aggregated statistics on what posts were removed to find the key words being censored (as the automoderator was hidden) and another redditor visualized the statistics - indicating the huge drop in activity over time.

This got the subreddit delisted and the mods removed, and the old mods made a huge stink about it for weeks (and verbally countering their petty complaints resulted in dozens of down votes in even obscure inactive threads).

Now main guy who aggregated the original statistics proving the censorship was occurring is a mod there, and they found a way to resolve the complaints the old mods had (that people upvote the same topics repeatedly) without censorship by starting a tag-filter system. So if you ever complain that the subreddit sucks, it's your own fault for not taking advantage of the topic filter buttons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 05:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know with /r/technology, the old mods defended their actions. They knew what they were doing when they added tons of words like NSA and TPP to their Automoderator list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 00:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to being antithetical to "free trade,"

"Something is antithetical when it is in **complete and utter opposition** to the character of something." [Source](https://www.vocabulary.com/dictionary/antithetical)

The redditor is rightly saying that the expanded IP protection is **completely against** free trade, because the TPP was never about free trade. 

In fact, the deals major impact would not come in the area of lowering tariffs, the most common trade barriers. The TPP is more focused on crafting regulatory regimes that benefit certain industries.

So the most consequential parts of the deal would actually undermine the free flow of goods and services by expanding some protectionist, anti-competitive policies sought by global corporations.

https://theintercept.com/2016/07/05/despite-what-media-says-tpp-isnt-about-free-trade-its-about-helping-corporations/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 00:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "fair" part is that he should be given a trial where we can make the whistleblower 'public interest' case. As it is, he would not be allowed to make those arguments. [See here](https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2016/feb/21/edward-snowden-willing-to-return-to-us-fair-trial) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 21:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainstream media is for elites. Many of us remember feeling disillusioned when they focused entirely on Edward Snowden and none of the revelations on the overreaching government mass surveillance (the kind that most thought only existed *in fiction*) and how foreign governments even help (e.g., Britain's Tempora program helped by wholly storing all traffic through the country for 3 days-to sift through). The New York Times even implied Snowden gave documents to China ([SRC](http://www.nytimes.com/2013/06/24/world/asia/china-said-to-have-made-call-to-let-leaker-depart.html).

They ignored a huge story, but Greenwald and Snowden knew how they would react and planned accordingly. They weren't just protecting Democrats but protecting the establishment itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 21:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems complaining about popular movements is much easier than introspection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 20:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good article showing both sides of the concern on how Kaine will act. Highlights:

Kaines record on energy is mixed. Hes been supportive of offshore drilling in the Atlantic and introduced legislation to speed up liquid natural gas exports. In 2012 he pushed for the construction of one of the nations last new coal plants. And he helped pressure the federal government to lower Virginias greenhouse gas emissions goals under the Clean Power Plan.

In Virginia, the Atlantic Coast Pipelines biggest investor, Dominion, was the largest single corporate contributor to local politicians between 1997 and 2016, and Kaine has accepted his share of the companys cash and gifts: more than $300,000 in total since 2001. When asked what he thought of Kaine, senior American Petroleum Institute lobbyist Louis Finkel told Intercept reporter Zaid Jilani, Hes the best we could have hoped for. Virginias governor and longtime friend of the Clintons Terry McAuliffe supports the pipeline.

Still, many environmentalists consider Kaine someone who can be swayed. After all, he was one of the earliest legislators to declare opposition to the Keystone XL pipeline, which would have transported carbon-intensive tar sands oil from Canada to the Gulf Coast.

Last week, Oil Change International, which is dedicated to revealing the societal costs of fossil fuels, released a report that shows how the 19 proposed Appalachian Basin pipeline projects could fail such a climate test. According to the study, the Energy Information Administration projections of fossil fuel consumption suggest that even if the U.S. reduced all coal and petroleum use to zero by 2040, the U.S. would still exceed its climate goals based on natural gas emissions alone. Since pipeline investments would incentivize the production and shipment of natural gas for decades, the report says, the pipelines are inconsistent with the 2-degree climate goal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 20:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this article's cathartic analysis applies to people all over right now. Both major parties are facing huge divisions as people express frustration over the how parties prioritize monied and established interests over their constituents. Part of what made Trump instantly stand out was his rhetoric about corruption and the status-quo. To clarify, I don't think rhetoric is a reliable indicator of policy (where political signalling like appointments is) - but it leads to the next point.

I honestly hope that the two parties do not get better at the deception that usually works for them. It's been amazing seeing people realize ways the system is stacked against them. Media spin, legal immunities, awkward improvisations from politicians not used to this environment, and political machines noticeably designed to serve a powerful   connected minority influence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 19:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea. Even though I don't identify as "left" or "right," because too often those labels serve to keep masses divided   arguing about non-issues, this article was really interesting to read. I was sorta guarded entering it expecting something worse but I'm glad I read it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Real-World Security and the Internet of Things - Bruce Schneier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 19:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 17:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good post! There's a lot of spin in these comments but your post was still interesting to read! Thanks for sharing!

Despite what reductionist comments claim, I think it's becoming abundantly clear to tons of people how money has shaped politics in the United States. People are seeing both major parties as not representing their interests.

I know this wasn't the main idea of your article, but I think the theme is there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 16:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah maybe, but making it harder for them feels worth it. Every bit of opposition and resistance to these powerful players feels worth it. Many issues that we face today will have huge ramifications, and those fighting this battle are on the right side of history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *It's only embarrassing if you still call yourself a public servant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely not. Supporting a deal that [continuously excludes the public](https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20160506/17281834365/european-parliament-orders-mep-to-take-down-video-about-his-attempt-to-visit-reading-room-trade-documents.shtml) while it includes powerful special interests is a major red flag. The provisions in the TPP are a huge deal.

In fact, the deals major impact would not come in the area of lowering tariffs, the most common trade barriers. The TPP is more focused on crafting regulatory regimes that benefit certain industries.

So the most consequential parts of the deal would actually undermine the free flow of goods and services by expanding some protectionist, anti-competitive policies sought by global corporations.

https://theintercept.com/2016/07/05/despite-what-media-says-tpp-isnt-about-free-trade-its-about-helping-corporations/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, neither party or candidate are particularly trustworthy. E.g., why should we believe Clinton when she says she's against the TPP when her VP is very pro TPP? There's a word for that in politics, it's called signalling. You say one thing to the voters, but appoint people with the views you want big financial/political backers to see.

By voting for Clinton, you are also supporting the "rigging of the DNC" shown in the leaked emails this week. In the next election, the Democratic Party will know that sufficiently demonizing an opponent will get enough people to vote for someone they didn't want in office.

And this isn't a defense of the Republican party either, but this is a reminder that both parties are not serving your interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I assume fracking will only be good for the environment huh?

The Global Shale Gas Initiative, Clintons program for promoting fracking, was announced on April 7, 2010, by David Goldwyn, the State Departments special envoy for energy affairs, at the United States Energy Association (USEA), whose members include Chevron, ExxonMobil, ConocoPhillips, and Shell.

[Source](https://theintercept.com/2016/05/23/hillary-clinton-fracking/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's becoming apparent that both parties aren't acting in the public interest. I mean this bit about the [Vice President of Comcast](https://theintercept.com/2016/05/11/lobbyists-dnc-2016-convention/) is pretty indicative.

David Cohen is the **special adviser to the [Democratic] Host Committee** and serves as the executive vice president of Comcast, overseeing the companys lobbying and regulatory strategy.

And despite **hosting fundraisers for Clinton at his home last summer,** Cohen has **spent heavily to help elect a Republican Congress**, including recent donations to the NRCC; Sen. Toomey; Sen. Scott; Sen. Kelly Ayotte, R-N.H.; as well as $33,400 to the NRSC, a committee for helping elect GOP members to the Senate.

People get stuck on their rhetoric but on many issues, both parties (and the candidates they pick) aren't hugely different from each other. Heck, we have emails showing Hillary trying to promote fracking in other countries. [Source1](http://motherjones.com/environment/2014/09/hillary-clinton-fracking-shale-state-department-chevron) [Source2](https://theintercept.com/2016/05/23/hillary-clinton-fracking/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 04:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be something like confirmation bias rather than memes bc I don't follow memes but still feel like I've reliably seen certain things in hardcore Sonic fans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 21:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another example yesterday: https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/4upvky/clinton_i_was_surprised_that_he_used_personal/d5s3lj4

Same reason given. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It [isn't even really about free trade.](https://theintercept.com/2016/07/05/despite-what-media-says-tpp-isnt-about-free-trade-its-about-helping-corporations/)

In fact, the deals major impact would not come in the area of lowering tariffs, the most common trade barriers. The TPP is more focused on crafting regulatory regimes that benefit certain industries.

So the most consequential parts of the deal would actually undermine the free flow of goods and services by expanding some protectionist, anti-competitive policies sought by global corporations.

Claims that it is [merely extending US law](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trans-Pacific_Partnership_Intellectual_Property_Provisions) or about free trade has been a part of a lot of misinformation on this [secretive](https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20160506/17281834365/european-parliament-orders-mep-to-take-down-video-about-his-attempt-to-visit-reading-room-trade-documents.shtml) agreement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 17:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resistance/activism isn't only about voting. It's about resisting these trends in whichever way we can. It might be informing ourselves of the injustices so that we can angrily cite long lists of transgressions (backed by credible sources). The people responsible for those acts want us to forget them, and merely remembering them and reminding ourselves is an act of defiance.

Resistance might mean finding allies who openly take up these causes - people you can root for and cheer as they face huge challenges. Journalists, whistleblowers, organizations, and speakers.

Resistance might even be as little as changing small habits, e.g. using Tor to make mass surveillance more difficult.

Activism and resistance is about finding carthasis in how we express our growing frustration, not popularity.

And no matter how terrible or hopeless things seem, there are always people who are fighting against it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 01:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check /r/undelete

They track removed posts. /r/longtail also does. Their algorithms slightly differ.

[This post](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/4upvky/clinton_i_was_surprised_that_he_used_personal/) was also removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton: "I was surprised that he used personal email account if he is at State" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 00:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 19:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current security   privacy trends (and their relevant political   business components) looks like they will make for a disastrous mix with IoT.

The one trend the article leaves out is DRM, which is how we are slowly losing control over the devices that we are becoming increasingly dependent on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Internet Of Things Is a Security And Privacy Dumpster Fire And The Check Is About To Come Due </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 19:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disclaimer: I'm not actually the owner of this blog.

Edit: Bunnie [links to the EFF post,](https://www.eff.org/press/releases/eff-lawsuit-takes-dmca-section-1201-research-and-technology-restrictions-violate) which might be more informative on the context. 

The EFF also includes a link to the complaint document. Hope this helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your reductive generalizations made any sense, wouldn't that make you part of the "stupid?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Privacy was important too, just not in every way.

E.g. the very high profile leak of celebrity private photos was likely a huge reason they moved towards encryption where users hold their own private keys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it can be. Making it impossible to comply with a court order is effectively doing that. That's where the phrase "privacy by design, not privacy by policy" comes from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mass surveillance is technically one example of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Im Suing the US Government [DMCA   DRM] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't think many people read the article. I got the same kind of responses in my post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like they are spending $425 million on a newer software they refuse to use. That's the basis of the case.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the [original article](http://www.theguardian.com/politics/2016/jul/16/justice-department-freedom-of-information-computer-system) this article is based on.

Shapiro told the Guardian that the reason the DoJ gave for **refusing to use its $425m Sentinel software to process Foia requests after ACS had failed to recover records** was that a Sentinel search would be needlessly duplicative of the FBIs default ACS UNI index-based searches and wasteful of Bureau resources.

To Shapiro, this is both disingenuous and evidence of the well-documented resistance to this law at the DoJ.

I don't think this is another meme about government incompetence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the [original article](http://www.theguardian.com/politics/2016/jul/16/justice-department-freedom-of-information-computer-system) this article is based on.

Shapiro told the Guardian that the reason the DoJ gave for **refusing to use its $425m Sentinel software to process Foia requests after ACS had failed to recover records** was that a Sentinel search would be needlessly duplicative of the FBIs default ACS UNI index-based searches and wasteful of Bureau resources.

To Shapiro, this is both disingenuous and evidence of the well-documented resistance to this law at the DoJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shapiro told the Guardian that the reason the DoJ gave for refusing to use its $425m Sentinel software to process Foia requests after ACS had failed to recover records was that a Sentinel search would be needlessly duplicative of the FBIs default ACS UNI index-based searches and wasteful of Bureau resources.

To Shapiro, this is both disingenuous and evidence of the well-documented resistance to this law at the DoJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there's a concern, to quote the article OP posted, "'that every mark of poverty serves as a risk factor.'"

Did you have any critiques of the study methodology ProPublica used? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 20:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The writer of this article has a funny sense of humor, e.g.,

He's also concerned a 12-month study from a Congressional committee won't address the issue fast enough.

Twelve months of taking testimony resulting in non-binding recommendations in a report will not adequately address the urgency of the problem that local law enforcement faces. Time is not a luxury that local law enforcement, crime victims, or communities can afford.

**With a nod to civil liberties:**

Our laws require **speedy trials.** Victims require justice. And criminals must be held accountable before they can reoffend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great article. In addition, they mention how many companies DO NOT share the source code of the software that is leading to convictions while Berk allegedly does share them. 

[Relevant study](https://www.propublica.org/article/what-algorithmic-injustice-looks-like-in-real-life)(which is mentioned in the article)

Courtrooms across the nation are using computer programs to predict who will be a future criminal. The programs help inform decisions on everything from bail to sentencing. They are meant to make the criminal justice system fairer  and to weed out human biases.

ProPublica tested one such program and found that its often wrong  and biased against blacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice department 'uses aged computer system to frustrate Foia requests' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
