<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1093</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WEIGH-IN WEDNESDAY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good Morning ketoers! o/

How are you doing today? Got a success you want to share? This is the place! Post your scale victories (SVs), non-scale victories (NSVs) and progress pics here, and spread the keto joy :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Daily Discussion] Wednesday, May 10th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Welcome to the /r/xmrtrader daily discussion thread!**

---

**Thread topics include, but are not limited to:**

* General discussion related to the day's events
* Technical analysis
* Trading ideas   strategies
* Questions that do not warrant a separate post

**Thread Guidelines**

* **Be excellent to each other.**
* Please do not create separate posts for the types of discussion mentioned above outside of the daily thread. **If you do, your post may be removed and/or heavily downvoted.**

* News that may have a big impact on the market may be posted as a separate thread.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The /r/Economy Open Chat, May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the open chat for /r/Economy, to discuss anything from things that don't quite fit as a post in the subreddit, or completely off topic!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wednesday SOTD Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Share your shave of the day for Wednesday!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MidWeek Check In </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your mid week check in to hold yourself accountable and stay on track. Post your stats, how you have done this week, what's been bothering you and anything else!

Good Luck! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Weekly] What would you like to know Wednesday? General Question Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not every question needs a backstory or long explanation but it is still a question that you would like answered. This is weekly thread is setup to allow a chance for people to ask general questions that they may not feel is worthy of a full post to the sub. 

Examples:

* What is the job market like in Birmingham, AL?
* Should I wear socks with sandals on an interview?
* Should I sign up for Networking 101 or Programming 101 next semester?

Please keep things civil and constructive! 

**MOD NOTE:** This will be a weekly post on every Wednesday and stickied for 24 hours.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird Wednesday. Share your off-base stories, glitches, images, and videos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All hail to our glorious leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that guy being me, the automod. yeah, robots are the best. chad's also cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radical Women Wednesday - Entertainment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Weekly Discussion Thread for Radical Women and Non-Binary People

This week's theme: **Entertainment**

Discuss what you do for fun. It could be movies, tv, games, books, music, hobbies, or anything else you do for entertainment.

*The theme is just a sugestion, radical women can talk about whatever they want in here.*

Next Wednesday's theme: Radical Women in History

---

Men are asked not to post in Radical Women Wednesday threads.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Daily Chat] - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please feel free to discuss anything here like memes, general discussions, makeup discussions, etc. Please remember to follow RAoM's rules when doing so. If you have any issues or feel a post is breaking the rules, please report it and message the moderators. Happy chatting!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hump Day - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Just in time for the hardest day of the week lets hear your COMPLAINTS AND STRUGGLES! 

Is that knee or hip still nagging you? Are your kids getting in the way of your streak? Did that other person awkwardly patch pace with you for a few blocks for the third time this week? Did they instead have audacity to pass you while looking smug?

If any of that or anything else happened this week here is the place to vent!! If your family and friends told you to shut up because your constant running talk is making them guilty this thread is for you!!!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Veterans are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scent of the Day - Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What scent(s) are you wearing today? Any special reason?

This thread repeats daily.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May 10, 2017 Pre-Game Discussion Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the pre-game discussion thread for May 10, 2017. Use this thread to discuss anything at all, post silly me-mes, photoshops, or whatever the hell you want.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's going on this weekend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weekends are made for getting out and exploring all that Savannah has to offer. What do you have planned? Are you doing anything interesting? Or are you hosting an event you'd like to promote? If so, please let us know here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whiny Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What stupid shit have people said to you regarding infertility lately? Does shit suck at work? Maybe your significant other was a jackass? We'd like to hear about it and commiserate.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [DATE] It is currently Mar/Apr </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BEEP BOOP
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly Store Thread! Use this thread for any and all TSM store related posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Welcome to the Weekly Store Thread. 
    
In an effort to stop the many personalized store questions and experiences, we are no longer allowing any more store related threads. 
However, we have created these weekly threads instead, to have everyone's store issues, experiences, and questions compiled into one place, to make things more organized. 

In these weekly threads, you can:

* Comment about your complaints, praises, and issues with the store

* Share your experiences and merchandise you have bought in the store

* Ask any questions regarding the store
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Purchase Help Thread (2017-05-10) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the Purchase Help Thread. This thread refreshes once every few days.

## Requesting purchase advice

This is the _only_ place in /r/audiophile where you can request purchase advice.  Since we don't want to arbitrarily discriminate, it doesn't matter if your budget is $50 or $50 000, or whether you're inquiring about vintage or new - your question goes here.

If you want to ask a gear purchase question, it's of help if you read [this guide](http://www.reddit.com/r/audiophile/wiki/purchaseadvice) first.

After asking a question, please have some patience as responders may not always be immediately available.

## Headphone-related question?

Please use /r/headphones/about/sticky instead (we won't remove your post, but you're more likely to get a good answer in that thread).

## Recording-related question?

While we won't remove questions about microphones or recording gear either, you'll be much better off asking in the [/r/audioengineering sticky thread](/r/audioengineering/about/sticky), after you've studied their [getting started guide](http://www.reddit.com/r/audioengineering/wiki/gettingstarted).

## Proposed systems

In an effort to cut down on some of the repetitive questions, here are the absolutely cheapest systems we are willing to recommend.

* **$120**:   [Micca PB42X](http://www.amazon.com/Micca-PB42X-Powered-Bookshelf-Speakers/dp/B00NXAEPDC/)  _or_  [Micca MB42X](http://www.amazon.com/Micca-MB42X-Bookshelf-Speakers-Tweeter/dp/B00E7H8GG2) + [SMSL SA-60](http://www.amazon.com/SMSL-SA-60-60WPC-Digital-Amplifier/dp/B00PA3ECGK/) if you prefer separate components.
* **$280**:   [JBL LSR305](http://www.amazon.com/JBL-LSR305-Professional-Studio-Monitor/dp/B00F1DEI8G/)


## Answering questions?

It would be helpful if you sort the thread by new.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you still subscribed here ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We changed our name to r/POTUSWatch a week ago, that was because we decided we're going to track President Donald Trump's successors too and because other subs have refused to help us due to our name containing the word "Trump" so we didn't really have much choice. We made an [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/Trump_Watch/comments/60psbm/were_moving_to_rpotuswatch_a_note_of_transparency) last week which apparently a lot of subscribers here didn't recieve, therefore we resorted to setting Automod to spam this sub until y'all move to r/POTUSWatch (we post there regularly now), so sorry for the inconvenience and see ya there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Pulls Megathread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
#Welcome!

Please post all your amazing or despair ridden pulls in this thread.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All Hail Elias, Our Supreme God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our glorious leader is a God among Kings and the Deity of all that is Holy. **Praise be to Elias. All Hail.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AskAuraxis - The weekly question thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello and welcome to **AskAuraxis** the weekly thread for any of your Planetside related questions. 

* Feel free to ask any question about anything to do with Planetside and **don't be scared if you think it may be stupid**.  

* The main aim of this is that: **no question should go unanswered** so if you know the answer to someone's question, speak up! 

* Try and keep questions somewhat serious, **this is not really the place for sarcastic or rhetorical questions**. 

* **We are not DGC**, we can't answer questions that should be directed to them.

* Remember if you're asking about guns etc. to say your faction and if you're asking about outfits to specify the server as well.

* Sorting by new helps the questions less likely to be seen get answered. You can now do this temporarily using [RES](http://redditenhancementsuite.com/).

* **Have fun!**

___
Special thanks to /u/flying_ferret who originally created this series.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your Week In Amateur Radio / New Licensees [05/10/2017] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Wednesday, what happened this week? 

This thread is also used for those who just passed their tests to introduce themselves. Welcome to the hobby!

Credit to /u/hobbycollector 
 
 
 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Dank Thread May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
JAPANESE TEXT! Have a happy Wednesday! Green Marth is king!


#[CLICK THIS LINK FOR A COLLECTION OF EVERY MELEE RELATED ARTICLE EVER MADE](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ)

Use the Comment

WWT Item

to send a submission to the Weekly Wrap-Up Thread.

Also comment

[Tournament] 'Name of tournament'

to give the big cheese stuff to put into the 2016 tournament list. Tournament must have at least 1 top 100 Green Marth attending

Lastly, here are a list of all the [DDTs](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/YuGiOh Pulls and Hauls Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought some product recently, pulled a nice card, or just completed a really sweet trade? Share it with the world in this thread!

Keep in mind that this is *not* the place to conduct trades or sales, but rather focused on personal collections, accomplishments, and so on.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Hangouts - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does that make you feel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May 10, 2017 - Dinner Recipes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ##Topic: Dinner

##Winner: ______

Dinner usually consists of one main dish and assorted sides.  Have a drink paring that goes well with your recipe? Throw it in there! Tips on how to properly cook this dish? Mention it!  

Pictures or albums of how to cook the dish are great if you have them, especially if it's a tried and true recipe.  If this is an experimental recipe, let us know!  

If you'll be posting in the How Was It? thread, make sure you write down what you did to personalize or change the recipe, this way we can try it again some time!

Reposts are acceptable, so long as it's never won before.

##Closing time: 12 PM est

##Points awarded to winning recipe: 1 point
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [DATE] May/June and Map </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DATE May/June and [Map](http://www.reddit.com/r/globalworldpowers/wiki/map)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wednesday at Bernies | Ask the /r/formula1 community anything! - 05/10/2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Ask any question you want in this weekly thread without any shame or hesitation.**](http://i.imgur.com/t7K41GR.jpg)

It doesn't matter if your question is very simple or if it is extremely complicated. Also try to answer any questions others ask as best as you can.

**Voting Etiquette**

Please do not post negative comments or vote in a way which hinders the interest of potential posters in this and future threads.

**Previous Threads**

[Archive](http://www.reddit.com/r/formula1/search?q=at+bernies sort=new restrict_sr=on t=all)

Please also consider sorting the comments in this thread by "new" so that the newest comments are at the top, since those are most likely to still need answers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Veterans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-rush posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [JPN] Login now to claim your 2 Boruto Pearls! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Rushers are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-rusher posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that veterans are losing this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans Rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's have a level exchange! - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The level exchange is an opportunity for users to share and play each others levels.   

What is proposed is that you take this post and sort it by "new" and try to play and leave comments on reddit for 2-4 levels that other people have posted. You don't have to star it if you don't want to, but there really is no reason to be stingy if you like the level.  Once you've done that, post your own level and a brief description of it. Preferably include what the theme of the level is, what style of Mario game you used, and about how difficult you think it is!

A new exchange thread is created every 48 hours.    

Use the exchange as an opportunity to get to know other makers and have fun.   


-----

Presentation Tip:  

Use
                                       
    *  Level ID: [B86F-0000-012A-0FE6](https://supermariomakerbookmark.nintendo.net/courses/B86F-0000-012A-0FE6)

to create a combined level code and bookmark 

*  Level ID: [B86F-0000-012A-0FE6](https://supermariomakerbookmark.nintendo.net/courses/B86F-0000-012A-0FE6)




-----

Please see our sidebar for events, challenges and other highlights 




* [](/#LOTW) ["**Level of the Week**" Contest](https://www.reddit.com/r/MarioMaker/search?q=flair%3Alow sort=new restrict_sr=on)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you still subscribed here ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We changed our name to r/POTUSWatch a week ago, that was because we decided we're going to track President Donald Trump's successors too and because other subs have refused to help us due to our name containing the word "Trump" so we didn't really have much choice. We made an [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/Trump_Watch/comments/60psbm/were_moving_to_rpotuswatch_a_note_of_transparency) last week which apparently a lot of subscribers here didn't recieve, therefore we resorted to setting Automod to spam this sub until y'all move to r/POTUSWatch (we post there regularly now), so sorry for the inconvenience and see ya there :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-vet posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/footballhighlights weekly spoiler free match ratings thread (Is that game worth watching?). 10-May-2017 / 17-May-2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example: Real Madrid vs Everton - 8/10

**Please participate.** If you seen a nice game please rate it here

***

Suggested ratings (not obligatory but you can use them as a guidance).

* **(0-4)** bad match, not worth your time

* **(5)** average/ok game

* **(6)** decent match, perhaps worth your attention

* **(7)** great match, worth watching

* **(8)** non-stop action and/or lots of goals

* **(9)** game of the year contender

* **(10)** instant classic

***

*PS : Ratings are totally subjective. Higher rating does not mean your and/or favorite team is winning. The game of Football loves upsets. Try not to forget the reddiquette while commenting.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Rushers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-vet posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> test </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome To Charlotte Wednesday! Visiting, recently moved here, or going to move here? Tell us and ask away. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the title says, ask away so we can help! Where to live, where to go, what to see, where to eat. What you have experienced thus far (culture shock)? Or just to introduce yourself and where you are coming from.

NOTE: This thread is also for relocation questions from folks already living in the area.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that rushers are losing this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Test scheduled post - May, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As mentioned in the [rules announcement](https://redd.it/48ia8a), we're giving out flair as rewards for good penpalling.
Please post below when you receive an email or letter in the following fashion:
/u/USERNAME - number of emails - number of letters 
So, if you got a letter from me, you'd post:
/u/subject1093 - 0 - 1
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers Rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PSA] Daily PSA Thread for May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **This thread is for all Public Service Announcements for today's date. Please post in this thread instead of posting separately with the [PSA] tag.**

*Note to users who are interested in opening their town to users from other regions for special events: we advise that you make a separate post and tag it [GIVEAWAY] rather than posting in this thread. You are likely to get a lot of interest, especially if you have a Japanese or Korean version of the game, and posting it in its own thread will be much less of a headache for everyone involved. Thank you for your generosity!*

A PSA is used to announce a service in your town that you would like to invite people to participate in, such as premiums at Re-Tail, Katrina's or Redd's tent in your plaza, and others along those lines; see [the rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/ACTrade/wiki/rules#wiki_permitted_posts_and_tagging_guidelines) for more examples. Please only post if you are available, and edit your original comment if your availability changes, including to "close" your thread, so to speak.

All posting guidelines still apply to the Daily PSA Thread. Posts in this thread **do not** count against the spamming rule. You may have an active PSA in this thread and a second active post outside this thread.

**NOTE TO HOSTS: WHEN YOU ARE FINISHED HOSTING/NO LONGER AVAILABLE,** ***DO NOT DELETE YOUR COMMENT.*** Simply edit it to say you have gone offline. Deleting the top comment makes it difficult to figure out what happened and so will invalidate any RMM reviews left for you.

**If you wish to review someone on /r/RateMyMayor for participating in this thread, please link to the host's original top comment for the event (click "permalink" under that comment to get the correct URL), to make the trade easier to find in the thread. Failure to do so may result in the review being removed if the trade cannot be found easily.**

**REMINDER:** If you are hosting a premium event, know that Bell Boom ordinance does not stack with Premium. Premium items will sell at the same price regardless of town ordinance.

 **HAPPY TRADING! GOOD LUCK!**
 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> !Clear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly Product Recommendation Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is for anyone looking to purchase an item who needs some suggestions on what to try next. Please let people know if you have any requirements (ingredient sensitivities, budget). And if you are replying, please do not link to any stores selling products you recommend.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Chat Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need some support or to get something off your chest? Want to talk about that grilled cheese you ate at lunch?  This is the spot for you!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/weedstocks Daily Discussion [May 10, 2017] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please use this thread for daily discussion.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TWIL (This Week I Learned) - Share something new that you have learned this week! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't matter if it's something trivial. As long as it's new information about machine learning you didn't know until this week, feel free to share!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hourly Buff Hydra Post - (May 10 07) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buff Hydra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] May 10, 2017 Questions, Deck-Building, and General Discussion Megathread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you need deck advice, have a basic question, or just need to get something off your chest, please post here. Basic questions outside of this thread will be removed. Please redirect new members here, and report posts that break the rules.

The [subreddit wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/DuelLinks/wiki/index) has a lot of great info - check there before you ask.

[Key Cards from each pack](https://www.reddit.com/r/DuelLinks/comments/66200o/the_key_cards_from_every_box_available_right_now/)

[Friend Code Megathread](https://www.reddit.com/r/DuelLinks/comments/655ljd/the_official_friend_code_megathread/)

You can also join our [discord server](http://discord.gg/DuelLinks) for help and general Duel Links discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily /r/rabbits theme: Workout Wednesday - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post pictures or videos of your bunny working out!  This includes general exercise, stretches, and any other active bunny posts.

This sticky post is meant as a suggestion for the /r/rabbits theme of the day. There are no hard rules about only submitting posts about this theme, and regular non-themed posts will be welcome as always.

This theme will repeat every week until further notice. Feel free to suggest new ideas for daily themes at http://goo.gl/forms/BmcJXsczCI

Current themes in the queue:

* Mouf Monday, Booplesnoot Monday
* Damage Control Tuesday, Teef Tuesday
* Wednesday Hay Day, Workout Wednesday
* Throwback Thursday, Thumping Thursday
* Floppy Friday, Bunny Butt Friday
* Selfie Saturday, Salad Saturday
* Lazy Bunday, Project Bunday, Loafing Bunday

If you have any questions or comments, please message the moderators.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FUCK TANYA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reminder to FUCK TANYA
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Discussion Thread 05/10/17 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the Daily Discussion Thread series on /r/smashbros! Inspired by /r/SSBM and /r/hiphopheads's DDTs, you can post here:

- General questions about Smash

- General discussion (tentatively allowing for some off-topic discussion)

- "Light" content that might not have been allowed as its own post (please keep it about Smash)

Other guidelines:

- Be good to one another.

- While DDT can be lax, please abide by our general rules. No linking to illegal/pirated stuff, no flaming, game debates, etc.

- Please keep your [meme spam](https://www.reddit.com/r/smashbros/comments/4apm63/the_melee_copypasta_collective_1/) contained to the sticky comment provided below.

If you have any suggestions about future DDTs or anything else subreddit related, please [send them our way](https://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2Fsmashbros)! Thanks in advance!

Also, if you want to chat with other /r/smashbros users you can do so via our [Discord](https://discord.gg/0ScJzLh4bmHciUIF) channel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The /r/Economy Open Chat, May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the open chat for /r/Economy, to discuss anything from things that don't quite fit as a post in the subreddit, or completely off topic!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bi-Weekly Welcome Wednesday May 10, 2017 - Come say hey! Any questions you want to ask or help you need? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *****
#Bi-Weekly Welcome Wednesday - Come say hey! Any questions you want to ask or help you need?
*****
  

  
###Hello r/fastmealprep!
  

  
We thought we'd try a few different fortnightly threads to get you guys talking and sharing ideas! Don't like these threads? Prefer to see something else? No problem, this is a growing sub-reddit so feel free to [make suggestions](https://www.reddit.com/r/fastmealprep/comments/4yhosb/fellow_redditor_what_type_of_content_do_you_want/)!
  

    
Today is **Bi-Weekly Welcome Wednesday!** This sub is /r/fastmealprep, a new community so lets get talking! This is the place to ask for any basic advice, help or just tell us how things are going!
  
  

      

######Bonus points for:
  
- Images
- Self-post recipes
- Links to recipes.
  

      
######Upcoming threads:
  
- **Bi-Weekly Fast Friday** - What fast meals or snacks have you made this past fortnight?
- **Bi-Weekly Welcome Wednesday** - Come say hey! Any questions you want to ask or help you need?


  

    
*****
*^1. ^Thanks ^to ^/u/danieltobey [^for ^the ^suggestion.](https://www.reddit.com/r/fastmealprep/comments/4yhosb/fellow_redditor_what_type_of_content_do_you_want/d6nzox9)*
  
*^2. ^Any ^suggestions ^for ^improvement ^or ^different ^weekly ^threads? ^Then [^message ^the ^mods.](https://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2Ffastmealprep subject= message=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2Ffastmealprep%2F)*
*****
[*^^Welcome* *^^Wednesday* *^^archive*](https://www.reddit.com/r/fastmealprep/search?q=title%3A%22welcome+wednesday%22 restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Chat - May 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything, within the rules, goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Chat May 10, 2017: Bump Day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone's favorite- show us that bump, no matter how tiny. We love to see progress comparisons! (All bump pics should always be posted in this thread each week, thanks!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/mturk Daily Discussion - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please use this thread to discuss HITs, quals, daily goals, and other day to day turker topics. As usual, please don't reveal survey or qualification content and no MTurk/Reddit TOS breaking posts. Be sure to search the subreddit and/or check the sidebar for answers to common questions/topics.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Are You Watching? (May 10, 2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please refrain from writing spoilers in the comments. If you *really* want to do so, we've implemented the new spoilers tag:

    [Insert spoiler here](#spoiler)

This will appear as [/r/taiwandramas](#spoiler). However, this will only work on desktop.

Talk about what dramas you have been watching lately! Doesn't need to be limited to Taiwanese dramas. Be nice, please!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Discussion for May 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be Excellent to each other! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Club Rugby gush talk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All Clubs / All Age Groups / All Sexes / All Species

No Pro-Team news!

Recent results   

Upcoming games   

Looking for players   

Goings on down the road   


Club Event ads encouraged!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /ttcafterloss WTT Wednesday Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **This weekly Wednesday thread is for members who are specifically WTT (or waiting to decide if they are ever trying again).  How are you doing today? What's new?**

Off-topic discussion is allowed. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /ttcafterloss Challenge Weekly Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **This thread is for members who are participating in the "30" Day Challenge (yes, yes we know each month isn't always 30). What's working? What's not going well? Share your success so that others can learn from you.**

 **Note**: Please refrain from discussing positive tests (and beyond) in this thread...and mostly avoid TTC topics at all.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /ttcafterloss Alumni Daily Discussion Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **This thread is for members who are currently pregnant. How are you doing today? What's new?**

 Off-topic discussion is allowed :)

**[Due Date List](https://www.reddit.com/r/ttcafterloss/wiki/duedatelist)** 

**[Rainbow babies sub](https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow_Babies/)** - for those who have had their babies.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /ttcafterloss TTC Daily Discussion Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **This thread is for members who are TTC or waiting to try. How are you doing today? What's new?**

Off-topic discussion is allowed :)

**Note**: Please refrain from discussing positive tests (and beyond) in this thread - those topics are better suited for the "Alumni" daily thread or the Weekly Results thread. Thank you!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NC/NP Trade/Sell   Pet UFA/UFT Thread! (May 10, 2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> # Daily NC/NP Trade/Sell   Pet UFA/UFT Thread! (May 10, 2017)

Welcome to the Daily NC/NP Trade/Sell   Pet UFA/UFT thread. A new thread will be made every day at midnight NST. Please refrain from posting individual threads and use this thread for your trading purposes!

# Items

**Remember that you can use Ctrl + F to help you find items you might be interested in!**
**Please use the following specific formats to make it easier for people searching for either NC or NP items.**
## Format - NP

Please use this format when buying or selling items:

**Buying:**

item

**Selling:**

item - price (or link to your shop/trades/auctions)

## Format - NC

**Seeking:**

item(s) or link to wishlist

**Offering:**

item(s) or link to trade list

## Neocash Trading
Please keep in mind that you can ONLY trade Neocash items for other Neocash items and cannot buy them with neopoints.

To trade an NC item you need a gift box that you receive when redeeming NC cards, opening Gift Box Capsules or other events. To read more about trading Neocash items check out the [Jellyneo guide](http://www.jellyneo.net/?go=ncmall#trading).

*If you're trading NC items, here are a couple guides to help you out with values and avoid being scammed:* **ALWAYS KEEP AN EYE OUT FOR WHEN THESE WERE LAST UPDATED AS THEY MAY BE OUTDATED.**

* http://www.neopets.com/~lyl
* http://www.neopets.com/~loosi
* http://www.neopets.com/~korolie
* http://www.neopets.com/~saphronn

# Pets

This also is the place to post all your pets that you are seeking new homes for, whether you're trading or adopting out.

Please post the pet or pets you currently have up for adoption, that you are zapping to adopt out, or that you wish to trade.

You do not *have to* post the name of the pet or the name of your account if you do not wish, but remember to check your reddit PMs if this is the only means of communication you are allowing!

**Please update or edit your comments once you have found a new home for your pets.**

If you want a pet, or are trying to adopt a pet out _but want to give redditors first dibs_, the [/r/neopets Dream Pet List](https://r-neopets-dream-pets.herokuapp.com/) may be of some use! [](/clap)

# Rules

0. **DO NOT** mention /r/neopets or reddit on Neopets in any way.
0. Be excellent to each other, as always.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All hail to our glorious leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that guy being me, the automod. yeah, robots are the best. chad's also cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Check-in Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the /r/quittingkratom daily check-in thread. Feel free to post as many updates as you'd like :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Veterans are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Chat Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please use this thread to chat, have casual discussions, and ask casual questions. Moderation will be light, but don't be a jerk.

This thread is posted **every day at midnight PST**. Previous Daily Chat Threads can be found [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/cscareerquestions/search?q=Daily+Chat+Thread restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big 4 Discussion - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please use this thread to have discussions about the Big 4 and questions related to the Big 4, such as which one offers the best doggy benefits, or how many companies are in the Big 4 *really*? Posts focusing solely on Big 4 created outside of this thread will probably be removed.

Abide by the rules, don't be a jerk.

This thread is posted each **Sunday and Wednesday at midnight PST**. Previous Big 4 Discussion threads can be found [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/cscareerquestions/search?q=Big+4+Discussion restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> W[h]ine Wednesdays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You made it half way through the week! Let it all hang out, folks. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/Whole30 Daily Update Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is share your updates! Where are you in your Whole30? What successes or struggles have you had so far? How are you feeling? Found any good recipes? How can we help you with accountability? Share it all here and be sure to show some encouragement to others by replying!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Daily Discussion] - 10/May/2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the **/r/Digitrader** Daily Discussion thread. The thread guidelines are as follows:
***

-  Discussion topics include, but are not limited to, general discussion, details related to events of the day, technical analysis, and minor questions.  
-  Important content should be posted as a separate thread.
-  Be excellent to each other. 

***

Thank you in advance for your participation. Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you still subscribed here ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We changed our name to r/POTUSWatch a week ago, that was because we decided we're going to track President Donald Trump's successors too and because other subs have refused to help us due to our name containing the word "Trump" so we didn't really have much choice. We made an [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/Trump_Watch/comments/60psbm/were_moving_to_rpotuswatch_a_note_of_transparency) last week which apparently a lot of subscribers here didn't recieve, therefore we resorted to setting Automod to spam this sub until y'all move to r/POTUSWatch (we post there regularly now), so sorry for the inconvenience and see ya there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bi-Weekly VR Discussions Thread (May 10) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [(Previous bi-weekly threads)](http://www.reddit.com/r/HTC_Vive/search?q=flair%3Aweekly sort=new restrict_sr=on t=all)



Want to talk about Virtual Reality? Have questions about the Vive ask them, and we will try to answer you.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All Hail Elias, Our Supreme God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our glorious leader is a God among Kings and the Deity of all that is Holy. **Praise be to Elias. All Hail.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly New Rider Thread for May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need help choosing a bike, finding a place to ride, or just want advice on technique, gear, or cycling etiquette? This threads for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly /r/Nanny Discusson - Can't Take it Wednesday! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy Wednesday Nannies!  It's Can't Take it Wednesday! Please use this thread to rant, complain, vent, and let it all out.

Keep in mind that other nannies will be offering advice, comments, similar experience, and perhaps even criticism and countering viewpoints.  Remember to be kind.  We are here to support each other.

Please remember to not to use any real names or identifying details.  This is still the internet after all.  Using the first letter of a charge's name is strongly discouraged.  If you would like a generic name feel free to use the names MomBoss, DadBoss, Susie, and Billy.  (or for sillies, feel free to substitute whatever fake name you like.  We look forward to hearing about the adventures of little Batman, and his sister Princess Leia)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wishlist Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's on your wishlist? Let's talk about it! Someone else might have used it and can let you know if it is a worthwhile investment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TEST] Thread for lysdexicllama - 01 02 - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###**Welcome to /r/longboarding Daily General Thread!**

***
You can view yesterday's previous daily discussion thread [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/longboarding/search?q=daily+discussion+author%3Alongboardingbot restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all)!

###Discussions

Use this thread for any and all types of discussions. (ie: X Company just released Y board, what are your thoughts?)

####**Rules:** Please keep it civil and respect the opinions of others. If you're going to downvote someone, do it only if they are wrong and explain why.


***
###Asking for help

There is no question too stupid for you to ask. We are all here to help you. If you have anything in mind, **ASK IT!**

####**Rules:** Do not threadjack. This means don't post your question in a higher upvoted post to get responses. Your question will be deleted.

Do not downvote someone if they ask stupid questions. Only downvote someone if they are giving out bad advice and explain why in the comments to warn others.

***
###Anything else

Use this space to shoot the shit if you'd like. Share your latest skate accomplishments, tell a story, anything goes.

***

####**SUGGESTION:** If you are coming into the thread later in the day, please sort by **new** so **new** questions and discussions can get love too.
***
###Remember to follow [Reddiquette](http://www.reddit.com/wiki/reddiquette) and our [rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/longboarding/wiki/rules)!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA Wednesdays (May 10, 2017) - Share your tips and ideas with others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Welcome to /r/ArcheAge's PSA Wednesdays scheduled sticky discussion thread!**

Do you have any gamer tips to fellow adventurers? Or a new cool class that you may have have tried that could be a "main class" for others to try out? Or what about a new gaming strategy for naval or land based combat? Anything you want to discuss and get your chest off about, this is the thread to post them for others to see and discuss about!

To look back at previous tips and public service announcements, click [here!](https://www.reddit.com/r/archeage/search?q=%22PSA+Wednesdays%22+OR+author%3Asubject1093 restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Veterans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly Questions Thread for May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **This thread is for you to ask all basic game questions. Questions about when certain things unlock or how do perform basic functions in game should be asked here only. **
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/FireEmblemHeroes Daily Question Thread (05/10/2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###/r/FireEmblemHeroes Daily Question Thread

Welcome to the /r/FireEmblemHeroes daily question thread! Before asking your question, we suggest that you try using [Google](https://www.google.com/) or the [subreddit search bar](https://www.reddit.com/r/FireEmblemHeroes/search?q= restrict_sr=on) to see if your question has already been answered. If you don't find an answer, try taking a look at the official [Fire Emblem Heroes wiki](http://feheroes.wiki/Main_Page). /r/FireEmblem is also another great resource.

All questions on /r/FireEmblemHeroes should be limited to this thread. If you notice that someone has made a post asking a question outside of this thread, please politely direct them here and report their post to the moderators. Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-rush posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stable servers are down for scheduled maintenance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Rushers are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-rusher posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 Hourly, Today's date is - 05/10/17 00:46:26 -0600 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Testing auto-mod schedule. though this stuff isn't updating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that veterans are losing this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans Rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Support Question Megathread (May 10, 2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ##Daily Support Thread

Hello! Welcome to today's **Daily Support Thread**

This thread is to help answer all of your simple questions, and keep /r/AppleWatch's front page clean! Got a simple question? Get a simple answer. It's as simple as that. The thread's been set to sort posts randomly to push all sorts of questions to the top.

####Before you ask, please make sure you've checked out our wiki's [**troubleshooting guide**](https://www.reddit.com/r/AppleWatch/wiki/guide/troubleshooting), searched it on **Google**, or used our [**subreddit search**](https://www.reddit.com/r/NintendoSwitch/search?q= restrict_sr=on) feature *(wow, who knew that was a thing)*! If you can't find an answer, you want some further insight, or you're just lazy, feel free to post your question here. 

*****

###What can I ask?
If you've been asked to post your question here, then go ahead! Otherwise, if your question is one or two sentences long, and is pretty simple (such as asking for recommendations, apps, troubleshooting, app issues, etc), go ahead. If you need a lot more investigation, or you're asking for many opinions, go ahead and post it elsewhere (it may be removed if it's too simple, or it's deemed to be more suitable for here).

###See all the other threads
[For your viewing enjoyment!](https://www.reddit.com/r/AppleWatch/search?q=Daily+Support+Question+Megathread+subreddit%3AAppleWatch+author%3Asubject1093 restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all)

*****

Please remember our rules. Have a nice day :) Also, sorry for the strik- I mean, rest yesterday. Yeah, rest. I was... uh, *reads script* very tired and sick. Please don't hurt me. Smile aga--- oh, that's a part of the scrip-, I mean: no script! No script at all. I am treated so nicely; How was your day, by thE way... Loving life as Per usual!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you still subscribed here ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We changed our name to r/POTUSWatch a week ago, that was because we decided we're going to track President Donald Trump's successors too and because other subs have refused to help us due to our name containing the word "Trump" so we didn't really have much choice. We made an [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/Trump_Watch/comments/60psbm/were_moving_to_rpotuswatch_a_note_of_transparency) last week which apparently a lot of subscribers here didn't recieve, therefore we resorted to setting Automod to spam this sub until y'all move to r/POTUSWatch (we post there regularly now), so sorry for the inconvenience and see ya there :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-vet posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Show Thread - Wednesday, May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Wild Card Wednesday people! Make sure to tweet your questions to the show with #ASKSTUGOTZ. Billy is getting sad since no one is playing his game anymore...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/footballhighlights weekly spoiler free match ratings thread (Is that game worth watching?). 10-May-2017 / 17-May-2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example: Real Madrid vs Everton - 8/10

**Please participate.** If you seen a nice game please rate it here

***

Suggested ratings (not obligatory but you can use them as a guidance).

* **(0-4)** bad match, not worth your time

* **(5)** average/ok game

* **(6)** decent match, perhaps worth your attention

* **(7)** great match, worth watching

* **(8)** non-stop action and/or lots of goals

* **(9)** game of the year contender

* **(10)** instant classic

***

*PS : Ratings are totally subjective. Higher rating does not mean your and/or favorite team is winning. The game of Football loves upsets. Try not to forget the reddiquette while commenting.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Rushers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-vet posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> test </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> General Chat May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is our daily chat thread, anything within the rules goes.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that rushers are losing this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers Rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ETH Daily Discussion] - 10/May/2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the **/r/EthTrader** Daily Discussion thread. The thread guidelines are as follows:

***

-  Follow the Golden Rule. All other rules apply as well. Follow [this link](https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/about/rules) to view the rest of them. The rules page is also linked in the announcement bar above.
-  General discussion topics include, but are not limited to, events of the day, technical analysis, alternative Ethereum projects, or minor questions.  
-  Breaking news or other important content should be submitted as a separate post.
-  In-depth altcoin discussions should be referred to the /r/CryptoCurrency discussion thread. To view the thread, [follow this link](https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/search?q=%5BMonthly+General+Discussion%5D restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all) and choose the latest entry on the search page. 
-  Pumping, venting, trolling, or any other similar behavior should be redirected to the /r/CryptoMarkets trollbox thread. To view the thread, [follow this link](https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoMarkets/search?q=Trollbox+Thread sort=new restrict_sr=on t=all) and choose the latest entry on the search page.

***

Thank you in advance for your participation. Enjoy!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winning Wednesday - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was something you did this past week that you were proud of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [DATE] It is now March/April </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is now March/April.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quattro chiacchiere all'Autogrill... [Settimana 19/2017] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cazzeggiamo un po' mentre aspettiamo il nostro Camogli!

Spazio per la libera discussione su tutto, macchine, moto, sport, domande e consigli! Forza, a ruota libera!

...e ricordate che ogni momento  buono per un bel **rant**, qui vi capiamo. Volete lamentarvi di quello davanti a voi questa mattina? Volete insultare chi guida una Mercedes? Ora  il momento giusto!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly Wednesday Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck everyone! May the odds be ever in your favor. Please be a fair AP and don't ruin it for all of us. Make sure you watch what information you give out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge my accent - Record your voice and get opinions - May 10, 2017" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the JudgeMyAccent thread. Each week on Wednesday at 06:00 UTC, I, your faithful Automoderator, will be hosting a thread where in users can record their voice and get opinions from native speakers. Also check out /r/JudgeMyAccent. 

Here's how it will work:

* Go to http://vocaroo.com/ or http://soundcloud.com/ or https://clyp.it/ and record your voice. (No other recording service will be allowed).

* 1 comment should contain only 1 language. Format should be as follows: LANGUAGE - LINK + TEXT (OPTIONAL). Eg. French - http://vocaroo.com/------- Text:  J'ai voyag  travers le monde pendant un an et je me suis senti perdu seulement quand je suis rentr chez moi.

* Native or Fluent speakers can give their opinion by replying to the comment and are allowed to criticize positively. (Tip: Use CTRL+F to find the languages)

Consider sorting by new.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> !Clear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcoming Wednesday - Community Questions   Answers for Newbies   Pros Alike! - (May 10) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to [/r/PUBATTLEGROUNDS'](https://www.reddit.com/r/PUBATTLEGROUNDS) **Welcoming Wednesday**. This post is for anyone (whether you have 1 or 1000 hours) to ask any question about the 
game that you may have. This can be as simple as keybindings or as advanced as 4 man breach   clear tactics... as long as it is relevant to the game - ask away! 

If you are new, feel free to introduce yourself here as well!  Don't forget that we have a [Discord Server](https://discordapp.com/invite/pubgreddit) with over 11,000 other players, a help channel,         region 
specific LFG channels, and constant game discussion at all times of the day! Lastly - our [FAQ](https://www.reddit.com/r/PUBATTLEGROUNDS/wiki/faq)   [Community Guide List]
(https://www.reddit.com//r/PUBATTLEGROUNDS/wiki/guides) is ever growing, so feel free to check there as well for additional tips   common questions/bugs. 

[Click this link to find our previous Welcoming Wednesday threads!](https://www.reddit.com/r/PUBATTLEGROUNDS/wiki/weekly#wiki_welcoming_wednesday)   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hourly Buff Hydra Post - (May 10 06) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buff Hydra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FUCK TANYA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reminder to FUCK TANYA
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Write Up Wednesday Mega Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Click here to see the WVW Archive (soon-to-be WUW Archive)!](https://www.reddit.com/r/stunfisk/wiki/wvw)

**What is this?**

This is the day where we encourage users to write up analyses of pokemon, do an article on anything competitive pokemon related and ect. Of course it doesn't have to be today but it is encouraged today to have a few posts up on a consistent day.

**Who can write?**

Anyone! If you don't feel confident with your article feel free to get feedback from our [discord server](https://discord.gg/aYgMFZw)  

**What should I write about?**

Anything! Although it is encouraged to check the [pokemon analysis archive](Link to archive) and the [analysis archive](Different link, will put a few articles in there)

**What should be done here**

Ask for requests, say what you're writing about, ect.

"GL HF"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Discussion Thread - Wednesday 10/5/17 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the Daily Discussion Thread! 

This thread is a place to post any minor topics that do not quite deserve their own submission. The daily post should be utilized for questions, requests, track ID's   general discussion, as well as being a place to have some casual banter with your fellow users.

**or**, feel free to join our [Discord Channel](https://discord.gg/skrillex) for casual chat with other people


Please keep the discussion civil and be sure to follow the subreddit rules at all times.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The /r/Economy Open Chat, May 09, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the open chat for /r/Economy, to discuss anything from things that don't quite fit as a post in the subreddit, or completely off topic!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friend and Club Recruitment Thread (May 10, 2017) - I get by with a little help from my friends... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Post your in game UserName, Level, and Ace.

Feel free to advertise your club or request a club to contact you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opt Out Thread - [May 12, 2017] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Veterans are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anarhija srijedom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rasprava o vaninstitucionalnoj politici srijedom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BWF Daily Discussion and Beginner/RR Questions Thread for 2017-05-10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Welcome to the /r/bodyweightfitness daily discussion thread!**

* Feel free to post beginner questions or just about anything that's on your mind related to fitness!

**Reminders:**  

* Read the [FAQ](http://www.reddit.com/r/bodyweightfitness/wiki/faq) as your question may be answered there already.
* If you're unsure how to start training, check out our [recommended routine.](https://www.reddit.com/r/bodyweightfitness/wiki/kb/recommended_routine)
* Even though the rules are relaxed here, asking for medical advice is still not allowed.

**For your reference we also have these weekly threads:**

* [Motivation Mondays](http://www.reddit.com/r/bodyweightfitness/search?q=motivation+monday+author%3Aautomoderator restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all)
* [Training Tuesdays](http://www.reddit.com/r/bodyweightfitness/search?q=training+tuesday+author%3Am092+OR+author%3Aautomoderator sort=new restrict_sr=on)
* [Concept Wednesdays](http://www.reddit.com/r/bodyweightfitness/wiki/weekly/conceptwednesday)
* [Technique Thursdays](http://www.reddit.com/r/bodyweightfitness/wiki/weekly/techniquethursday)
* [Form Check Fridays](https://www.reddit.com/r/bodyweightfitness/search?q=form+check+friday+author%3Am092+OR+author%3Aautomoderator restrict_sr=on sort=new t=all)
* [Slip Up Saturdays](http://www.reddit.com/r/bodyweightfitness/search?q=I+SUCK+SATURDAY+author%3Asolfire sort=new restrict_sr=on t=all)
* [Progress Sundays](http://www.reddit.com/r/bodyweightfitness/search?q=progress+sunday+author%3Am092+OR+author%3Asolfire sort=new restrict_sr=on)

**Notable Threads and Going-Ons:**

* We recently unveiled our newest routine: [Move](https://www.reddit.com/r/bodyweightfitness/wiki/move). It's similar to our Recommended Routine with a larger emphasis on mobility and handstand work!

Feel free to join us on on the #bodyweightfitness channel on SnooNet! You can find the web client by clicking this link, [here](https://kiwiirc.com/client/irc.snoonet.org/bodyweightfitness). For information on connecting to Snoonet via desktop client or mobile, click [here](https://snoonet.org/help#using-a-desktop-irc-client).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Discussion Thread 05/10/17 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the official daily discussion thread of /r/gzcl post your GZCL program questions, tips, workouts, and everything else relating to the method and your training </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reasons Our Kids Are Crying (weekly megathread) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
It's Whiny Wednesday, so share which insipid bullshit reasons your kids are squirting water from their face this week. Their favorite cup is still blue? Pepe the stuffed cat won't stop staring at them? Their hands are dirty but they're terrified of soap? Comisserate here. And remember: `AUTOMODERATOR IS MOTHER TO US ALL.`
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All hail to our glorious leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that guy being me, the automod. yeah, robots are the best. chad's also cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Community Post | Guild Recruitment | 05/10/2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Well, it is Hump Day and that means its time for the Guild Registrar to open up his bulletin board for Guild Recruitment. The purpose of this post is to allow for guilds to recruit players and for players that are looking for a guild to see what different guilds have to offer.

Please observe the following rules when using this bulletin board to allow for all guilds to have an equal chance to be seen:

* "Looking for Guild" posts are **not** allowed here. If you cannot find a guild you like below, use /r/SWTORGuilds.
* Make sure to mention the **name** of your guild, what **server** you are on, and what **faction or factions** you are part of within the first sentence of your post.
* Only **one** post per guild per week.
* Please keep all posts to **less than 250 words.** If you wish to post a longer post, make one in /r/SWTORGuilds and link it here with a shorter summary.
* It is suggested that you make a similar post in /r/SWTORGuilds and post a link of it here with your recruitment post.
* Please keep this area clear of all posts responding to a Guild Recruitment. Instead, message the person who made the post or respond to their post on /r/SWTORGuilds if they have one.
* Please do not downvote guilds that do not interest you. Someone else may be looking for that type of gameplay.

If you have any questions or comments, you can [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2Fswtor).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Are You Watching? - [2017/05/10] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
[Here are the shows we've been watching](https://www.reddit.com/r/KDRAMA/search?q=flair%3A%22on-air%22 sort=relevance restrict_sr=on t=week) this week on /r/kdrama.

[Here](https://www.reddit.com/r/KDRAMA/search?q=flair%3A%22on-air%22 restrict_sr=on sort=relevance t=all) are the shows we've been watching overall on /r/kdrama.

Check out our neighbor subreddits:

* [/r/asiandrama](http://www.reddit.com/r/asiandrama)
* [/r/asianfilms](http://www.reddit.com/r/asianfilms)
* [/r/ChineseTV](http://www.reddit.com/ChineseTV)
* [/r/HKdramas](http://www.reddit.com/r/HKdramas)
* [/r/jdorama](http://www.reddit.com/r/jdorama)
* [/r/kpop](http://www.reddit.com/r/kpop)
* [/r/korea](http://www.reddit.com/r/korea)
* [/r/korean](http://www.reddit.com/r/korean)
* [/r/koreanrock](http://reddit.com/r/koreanrock)
* [/r/koreanvariety](http://reddit.com/r/koreanvariety)
* [/r/runningman](http://reddit.com/r/runningman)
* [/r/taiwandramas](http://reddit.com/r/taiwandramas)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what is this place? just got here from /r/random and i'm really confused right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sticky stacky licky dicky licky licky daddio dicky

le fugg~~~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you still subscribed here ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We changed our name to r/POTUSWatch a week ago, that was because we decided we're going to track President Donald Trump's successors too and because other subs have refused to help us due to our name containing the word "Trump" so we didn't really have much choice. We made an [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/Trump_Watch/comments/60psbm/were_moving_to_rpotuswatch_a_note_of_transparency) last week which apparently a lot of subscribers here didn't recieve, therefore we resorted to setting Automod to spam this sub until y'all move to r/POTUSWatch (we post there regularly now), so sorry for the inconvenience and see ya there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wednesday Weigh-ins - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, thinspo lovers!

Post how much you weigh today compared to how much it was last week.

It will also be helpful to post your gender, height, and BMI.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Food Journal - Wednesday, May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post what foods and drinks you have consumed already and plan on consuming for the rest of the day.

Include the calorie count, if known.

Also post your exercise for the day if you feel it is relevant.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily /r/Poker Discussion Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything and everything that you feel might not need its own thread!  For example, a screenshot of your recent MTT score, a bad beat story, a picture of your live 1/2 chip stack after a heater or royal flush, noob friendly questions, etc.  Mainly up to user discretion.  Be respectful and kind to one another! 

If you're new, welcome!  Check out the [FAQ section](https://www.reddit.com/r/poker/wiki/faq) if you're looking for a great place to start!  

*This thread will be refreshed every 23 hours to accommodate different time zones being able to participate.*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All Hail Elias, Our Supreme God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our glorious leader is a God among Kings and the Deity of all that is Holy. **Praise be to Elias. All Hail.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily RMT/Advice Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is for ***all*** RMT/Advice posts, any posted outside of this thread will be removed. Please include a screenshot of your team and upvote those who are helping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anarhija srijedom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anarhija srijedom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forum libre Aix-Marseille / Aix-Marseille open discussion 10 May 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ce sujet de discussion est ouvert  tout, rien n'y est hors-sujet ! 

This is an open discussion, please discuss or ask anything you'd like!

Ce sujet est post automatiquement tous les mercredis  8h et reste en premire position du subreddit pour une semaine.

This thread is posted every Wednesday at 8 AM and stays stickied for a week
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Veterans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TRASH TALK THREAD - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
#CAPS ON

#FLAIR UP

#DON'T HOLD BACK. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily free talk thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
A thread to talk about anything, related or not to Albania. You may discuss whatever you want, just please keep it civilized.

Subreddit rules are active in this thread too.

Go and chat!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 09 May 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bump Picture Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Please feel free to post your not showing bumps as well. It helps others see it can be normal and give you a starting point!*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly Support Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
/r/ENFP has always been and will always be a place that lends an ear. Large or small, get it all off your chest. In this corner of the internet, you will be heard. We are here to support one another. We are all we have.

This doesn't replace the individual posts; it's just another avenue to start talking, MBTI related or not. Sometimes you need to check in more than once before you feel restored. That's what we're here for.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-rush posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that the Rushers are going to win this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-rusher posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that veterans are losing this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Help/Advice Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use this thread if you have any questions about the game or need advice. Post here if you need help with tactics, don't know what team to pick, require technical support... you get the idea.

Also please remember that this thread will only work if you also answer questions as well as ask them. A good rule of thumb to follow is if you ask a question, then try and answer one or two questions as "payment". This keeps the thread moving quickly and ensures that everyone's questions get answered.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video playthroughs and stories thread (renewed every 3 days) - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Share your Football Manager stories and videos here.

You took Potter's Bar all the way up to the Prem? Win the World Cup with Vanuatu? Did you raise that 2-star winger from a pup and now he's killing it     everywhere? Or maybe it was something less heroic (like winning La Liga with Real Madrid 2037) and you feel the need to share? Welcome to ~~Alcoholics Anonymous~~ /r/footballmanagergames' Story Saturday!

Tell us about the journey, the life, the ups, the downs.

We have also decided to allow people to post their videos in this thread as well. Originally the videos had their own daily thread, but due to subreddits only being able to use 2 stickies at any one times, all of our stickies were used up. This meant that if important updates were made to the subreddit, or awesome user-submitted content was made, we would not be able to sticky them without removing the sticky thread in slot 2. By combining the two threads in to one, we now have a free slot to do whatever we please and give us more flexibility with sticky posts.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans Rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you still subscribed here ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We changed our name to r/POTUSWatch a week ago, that was because we decided we're going to track President Donald Trump's successors too and because other subs have refused to help us due to our name containing the word "Trump" so we didn't really have much choice. We made an [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/Trump_Watch/comments/60psbm/were_moving_to_rpotuswatch_a_note_of_transparency) last week which apparently a lot of subscribers here didn't recieve, therefore we resorted to setting Automod to spam this sub until y'all move to r/POTUSWatch (we post there regularly now), so sorry for the inconvenience and see ya there :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-vet posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> League Application and Recruitment Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post all your league advertisements here. If you are looking for a league, advertise here too! Please make sure to sort by NEW to get the latest/ newest posts. 
 Any posts regarding this topic outside this thread will be removed.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/footballhighlights weekly spoiler free match ratings thread (Is that game worth watching?). 10-May-2017 / 17-May-2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example: Real Madrid vs Everton - 8/10

**Please participate.** If you seen a nice game please rate it here

***

Suggested ratings (not obligatory but you can use them as a guidance).

* **(0-4)** bad match, not worth your time

* **(5)** average/ok game

* **(6)** decent match, perhaps worth your attention

* **(7)** great match, worth watching

* **(8)** non-stop action and/or lots of goals

* **(9)** game of the year contender

* **(10)** instant classic

***

*PS : Ratings are totally subjective. Higher rating does not mean your and/or favorite team is winning. The game of Football loves upsets. Try not to forget the reddiquette while commenting.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JudgeMyAccent - Record your voice and get opinions - May 10, 2017" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the JudgeMyAccent thread. Each week on Wednesday at 06:00 UTC, I, your faithful Automoderator, will be hosting a thread where in users can record their voice and get opinions from native speakers. Also check out /r/JudgeMyAccent. Don't forget to upvote this thread because it will not be stickied.

Here's how it will work:

* Go to http://vocaroo.com/ or http://soundcloud.com/ and record your voice. (No other recording service will be allowed).

* 1 comment should contain only 1 language. Format should be as follows: LANGUAGE - LINK + TEXT (OPTIONAL). Eg. French - http://vocaroo.com/------- Text:  Hsdkxvc sdfkjlxv sdklfjlxc.

* Native or Fluent speakers can give their opinion by replying to the comment and are allowed to criticise positively. (Tip: Use CTRL+F to find the languages)

Consider sorting by new.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck the Rushers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly /r/UdyrMains Discussion (May 09) - Builds, Tips, and More </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please use this thread to discuss builds, tips, and the current state of Udyr. 

--

Some things to discuss:

* What are the most effective builds this patch?

* What runes/masteries are the most effective?

* Which jungle clear offers which strengths and weaknesses?

* What is the state of Udyr in the current patch. What buffs could help Udyr?

* Pheonix vs. Tiger? Which one and why?

* How is Udyr fairing in NA, KR, EU, etc, vs other meta champs?



Here are some helpful links regarding Udyr: 

* [Udyr's Wiki](http://leagueoflegends.wikia.com/wiki/Udyr)

* [Udyr on LolKing](http://www.lolking.net/champions/udyr#/overview)

* [Champion.gg - Udyr](http://champion.gg/champion/Udyr/Jungle)

You can find more discussion and anything else at our [Discord server](https://discord.gg/UmDph4A).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video playthroughs and stories thread (renewed every 3 days) - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans are not allowed on this Subreddit! Please report any pro-vet posts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> test </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder that rushers are losing this war! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rushers Rule! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Help/Advice Thread - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video playthroughs and stories thread (renewed every 3 days) - May 10, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flicks Change My View Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much like /r/changemyview, this /r/Flicks CMV thread is for you to post viewpoints you hold about movies, directors, trends, genres, etc, and learn and discuss reasons for dissent. Your CMV topic *does not* have to be a long comment/question, but try and give some short insight to avoid **rule 5.** Have fun and remember **rule 1.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May 10 Daily Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should post here for:

* PRs
* General discussion or questions
* Community conversation
* Routine critiques
* Form checks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekly SUBJECT 1 Discussion - SUBJECT 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SUBJECT 1'S POST

YAaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaas
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wednesday Workouts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your workouts going strong? 

Or still looking for some? 

Tried something new and want to share?

Tell us all about it!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder to log your Inter-Team Challenge steps/minutes/water intake, etc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget to log your steps, workout minutes, water intake,  etc.  Deadline is until Thursday evening every week until the challenge finishes.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
