<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7081</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 05:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vagina. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 01:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want this printed on cards to hand out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 00:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hand on the Cha-Cha is so comforting, especially when trying to get to sleep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 08:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. I start to get really anxious if I can't feel the air from the fan. It started with just the fan noise being enough, now I have to feel it blowing toward me.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 07:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's glorious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-29 00:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tootles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 18:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> love it! Will be doing this when we build our place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 05:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I found Wicca and paganism in general it was such a natural fit that I had no real "coping ". I have always described my conversion as coming home. As far as my friends and family, I was always "the weird one " so no one was shocked. At this point, I think both my sisters are puzzled that I am still pagan 16ish years on but no real friction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 00:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could never win at Hide-and-Seek because my dog was like fucking Lassie and would lead the other kids to where I was hiding. True story, her name was Trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 06:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, Tom, don't shoot anyone with the black hipster beanie. Got it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 05:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> an excellent point.If you give cannon fodder a uniform, they might not realize they are cannon fodder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 05:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to put some thought in my potential Henchmen attire! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 05:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> interesting. So it's more of a military indoctrination than a booklet in the new hire packet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Action movie fans of Reddit:Who enforces the Henchmen Dress Code? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 05:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, I was re-watching Blade and in the final fight scene every one of those fuckers were dressed alike down to the black, knitted, hipster beanies. If you are a psychotic crime boss/monster/terrorist bent on taking over the world, are you really taking the time to enforce the dress code?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 02:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> was he pregnant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 02:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOVE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 02:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is something that we all need to hear! thank you so much for sharing it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 19:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband is a truck driver and when our youngest was breastfeeding I let him sleep so he would not drive tired. On his weekends home he would give her a bottle and let me sleep in and give me the chance to take naps. As long as there is give and take,I don't know why it would be a big deal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-10 20:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that he is smirking! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-10 03:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am originally from Elwood Indiana where the Fairy episode is set. We had a big laugh about how nice "Elwood" was on the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-10 03:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is that a nightmare light? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $1 at a church rummage sale and now I feel safe from ghosts! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-10 02:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 17:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are bigoted against white trash? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 17:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did, but again M. Dixon as in Merle Dixon. Daryl Dixon's brother on The Walking Dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 05:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> M. Dixon as in Merle Dixon. They didn't get it on r/thewalkingdead either and removed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My daughter's karate studio is safe from Walkers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 04:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look who goes to my daughter's karate studio! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 02:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh, the pain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 23:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a customer at a drugstore that does not have green walls yesterday. I was in the very long line of the sole open register waiting patiently to buy oragel and ibuprofen for my daughter who was crying inconsolably with a toothache out in the car with my Mom.

 The older man behind me told me he needed to go in front of me because his hip hurt. Normally I would always let some someone, especially an older person, go in front of me in line but my daughter was really in pain and he had several items to my 2 items. I politely told him no and explained why, then turned back around. 

He started muttering about his hip, and I was actually about to just let him in front of me because i was feeling guilty when a clerk came up and said she could take him on the other register.  He said "Oh, no. I want to pick out some of these candy bars."

Yeah, you were really hurting. I payed for my items and got out before I bit my tongue in half trying not to pop off a smart off comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 06:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always trust your penis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 06:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This absolutely sounds like my stepdaughters mom. We could buy that bitch a gold plated BMW and she would scream to the world that it wasn't platinum. Keep your chin up, your kids know you are awesome and that's all that counts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 22:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We might be white trash, but we have a hell of a [view!](http://imgur.com/gvruNov.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 03:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doing it right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 03:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10,000 internets to the one who makes this happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 17:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> like a boss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 17:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You win as a Daddy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 01:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Nice!](http://i.imgur.com/FSGvo.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 16:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually advice I have seen on a site about getting your house uncluttered and organized. Flylady.com. I forgot until I saw this. She says to get up and dressed with shoes every morning to motivate yourself . 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 04:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't had a toon that level in a while, but that used to be a quest to track down a lost Dwarven caravan. That was pre LK, so it might be nerfed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For all the talk from the right of not allowing abortions in cases of rape, have any of them proposed a means of support for the child that results? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 00:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen a lot of splashy headlines about the far right wanting to abolish abortion under any circumstance. I have not seen any talk of putting a support structure in place for the mothers denied abortions to raise these kids. 

Do they propose to impose child support on the rapists? Will the state step in to raise the children left motherless because Mommy died due to pregnancy complications with their little brother or sister? Am I just not getting this side of the story, or do these politicians only care about the fetus and once it comes out of Mommy and is a child they lose interest?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 00:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm giving up the Downey Bar for lint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 23:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, for one, welcome our robot overlords </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 23:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what a waste of fine whittling craftsmanship... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 23:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's like buying a porn for a pimp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 23:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is there no beer in there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 22:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a scene in Dragon: The Bruce Lee Story about Bruce watching it in a theater and just seething
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 04:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in. Urban Fantasy/Fantasy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am deep in the Mean Reds today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 02:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 06:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have read it maybe 6 times and it creeps me the fuck out every time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 17:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> squee!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 00:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We looked into that, but my SO asked an associate we know if it was a good deal and she warned us off doing it. She had one and said it was a nightmare. We just stuck with what we had </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 00:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That might be the most purely WTF thing I've ever seen.[Bravo]
(http://i.imgur.com/lueEW89.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 23:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what your situation is, but you are on this sub, so you know you're not alone. Take as good of care of yourself as possible because you can't expect anyone else to do it for you. Internet hugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 23:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am caring for two kids and a Dad with stage 7 Alzheimer's, every minute of my day someone needs something from me. There are a lot of times I just want to lay in bed, but I have shit to do all day/every day. When I do get time to myself, my anxiety and depression take it from me. It is often more than I can take, but I can't expect two small kids or a man with dementia to give a shit. It's hard not to be annoyed with expectations, even when they are motivated by love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 22:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this on my card, and I always thank the clerk/server for asking. I have been on the other side of that transaction, and people are assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 21:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very shiny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For everyone who was so sweet to me yesterday, I present my Dad with our dog, Malcolm Reynolds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 21:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 17:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it! Congrats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 14:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I'm pretty? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 01:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love you and, we're I unwed, would have your internet babies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 00:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the physical care is, although gross at times,(he has a Foley catheter and wears adult diapers) is the easy part. The psychological damage is the hard part, especially since I have my own anxiety and depression issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 00:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's more of an Andy Griffith man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 00:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a daughter, but thank you so much! We had the new Home Health nurse in today, and between her the awesome Browncoat response, today was a good day. We are all my Dad has, and as much as it hurts to watch the part that's 'him' slip away, he is much happier here with us and is healthy enough at the moment to be here. My girls especially love having Papaw here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 23:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As is your right, and it is my right that, as the daughter of a Master Cosmetologist, I find mullets hilarious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 23:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 23:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a genius! I will be thinking of it this way from now on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 23:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! Cause it's one thing to make fun of retards, but people who make questionable hair styling choices are sacred! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 22:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of me feels like I am making fun of him, but the bigger part just needs a laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 21:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feels accepted and returned
http://i.imgur.com/lueEW89.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 21:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have help with a home health care agency. The nurse was ny today in fact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 21:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have carefully reviewed his meds for the word pax </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 21:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for that. I actually have tears in my eyes reading it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 17:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He does go to sleep... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I might be a terrible person for this, but... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 17:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am the primary caregiver for my Dad, who has Alzheimer's with periods of dementia. My SO and I have begun to refer to his dementia as "River Tam". He can get pretty belligerent, especially when we have no idea what he is talking about, and it can be pretty upsetting. We use it as a way to lighten up the situation for ourselves, as it's a 'laugh or cry' type of situation. My SO has even started saying "Eta Kooram Nah Smech" when we put my Dad in bed.

EDIT: Browncoats FTW! You guys have just made my month with the awesome love I'm getting! Keep flying and stay shiny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks! I was starting to feel parched. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 22:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 03:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, more exactly like [this!](http://www.caneloproject.com/projects/canelo-buildings-2/don-juans-compound/?basic=true iframe=true width=800 height=500) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-03 23:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are planning to build a "compound" of small strawbale buildings to live in when we get a nice piece of land. One main one, a"bedroom" for us and each of the kids, and a bath house. That is the long term plan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-03 21:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this order:
emergency fund
car/van
piece of land
our strawbale project </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-02 04:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly my barometer for that situation. My toy poodle, Bruno, goes into T-Rex attack mode at the least hint someone might be in a 2-block radius. Therefore is he is not yapping, I am not worried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is more than our electric bill alone would be for January in Indiana! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 21:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 04:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted just last week about my family of 4 moving onto a 1979 Allegro. We are in process of remodeling it and plan to be in it until we buy land and build a strawbale house. I really like it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-28 02:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually hold my girl-junk (or Cha-Cha, as we call it in my family) when trying to fall asleep. Have most of my life. It's also a given that I touch my own boobs as well. Boobs make everyone happy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 20:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beautiful and practical 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 16:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love my Diva cup! It took me about 2 cycles to get used to it and know when I had it inserted properly with a good seal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 16:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 18:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we could have gotten a school bus, that would have rocked! Love it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 18:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is not seasonal, and the management could not be nicer! I can pm you the website if you want </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 18:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never been to Burning Man, but maybe in a few years. We are originally from the Midwest so there are a lot of places around here we need to check out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 18:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I plan to take loads of pics of both the RV remodel and the strawbale construction. Luckily, we went to visit the [Canelo Project](http://www.caneloproject.com/) last month and we might host a workshop to get us started...whenever that may be! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 15:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We plan to be in the RV for 6-9 months, then it will be used for camping trips. Our plan is to get land in this area and build a strawbale house </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 15:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $316 includes water, electric, cable, WiFi,and the clubhouse has a pool, hot tub, 3 private shower areas, pool table, ping pong table, and a family room with a tv.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 04:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 03:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't plan on moving it until we buy a piece of land to park it on, then possibly trips to Cochise Stronghold and Roper Lake, which are fairly close </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 03:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will check it out, but we are not traveling in it, living in it at an RV resort </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 03:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We set up at our site yesterday and it took all day to drive it there and get set. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 03:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our kids are 3 and 8 and we will all be in it full time by May. Right now we are split between Hereford AZ and Graham County AZ until our older girl finishes school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 adults, 2 kids, 2 dogs, 1 29ft RV. Our adventure begins! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 23:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 23:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! How dare poor people want tips to get through a rough patch! Boo, hiss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 17:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this exact problem. It takes me 30-60 minutes of self-talk to get to a place where I can try to sleep, and that's after my meds. Do everything you can to make your bed a safe place. I am 37, and it might sound childish, but stuffed animals always help me, and making a "nest" with the pillows and blankets. I have been working to convince myself I am safe in bed and will be safe while I'm asleep. Internet hugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
