<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5867</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 05:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably posted it because it's a funny image, and didn't think that people would look that closely at a naked baby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 07:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen The Matrix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 07:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it works the same way as activating a game on Steam, you wouldn't get another copy, unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 20:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that people are being hipsters about it, I think they just love the old consoles because one of those consoles were one of their first consoles. 

And you never forget about your first console, even when you view it with nostalgia goggles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 07:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The second movie was okay, three is one of my favorite movies, 4   5... not so much. 6 was pretty good though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 22:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed it, the plot was a bit odd, but I still enjoyed it. Mostly for the fanservice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 08:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, that's not it either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 08:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, that's not it. Although, I have been trying to find that webcomic, thanks for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 08:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, that's not it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [Webcomic] Sci-fi webcomic that was very fanservice-y </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 03:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading a webcomic, a few years back, about a guy, a girl, and I think a robot flying around in space.

It also had pretty much every female character in a skintight and/or skimpy outfit.

I know it's not much to go on, but if anyone knows the name of it, it would be very much appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 17:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, I liked Spy Fox as well. Even though, I could only find the first game to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 04:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't look too bad, although I didn't see very much gameplay in the trailer. I just wish that they could turn down the insanity a bit, but maybe it's just me not liking this version of Deadpool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
