<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4083</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, and the various Mustang logos are all pretty nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ford.  Especially sticks out like a sore thumb on the new GT.

Which the Kia logo resembles.  

I also really dislike the Lexus swoosh.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They get 40 million unique views monthly, their EIC works for the President.

That's mainstream.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats the KBB on the Mazda?  Do you have another vehicle to act as another daily in case the Porsche is OOC... or you need to haul something more than a laptop bag? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the PPI looks good and I could afford an extra 5k over what he's asking for the required maintenance, I'd be leaning towards a buy myself.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 21:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was written by someone who has only seen Asian women on TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lel no u </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm tired of being ruled, I as an American deserve to be served by out elected officials.

If you don't want to be ruled then stop vesting power in the political caste.

 MSM went with pizzagate or Obama is a muslim.

Breitbart and FOX are part of the MSM.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their job isn't to be "true journalists".  It's an entertainment industry 100%.

Not saying that in their defense.  Just people shouldn't expect anything but high adrenaline "news" "reporting" to keep you glued to the channel during commercial breaks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's why I mentioned to check mileage.  High mileage 986 gen can largely avoid IMS issues.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We just went through 8 years of "Obama is a secret Muslim" and #pizzagate and people seemed to be pretty cool with that.  Conversely, Obama said "if you like your insurance you can keep your insurance" and that was "reported" constantly and we know how that turned out. 

News agencies pick and chose whatever story fits their political narrative all the time and have been doing so for the past 30 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pre Purchase Inspection

They'll catch things he didn't notice/know to care about/etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your IMS replacement seems to have come in a bit on the cheaper side.  

Still though, an extra 3k on top won't break the bank if you went in expecting it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That certainly killed my boner for this car.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something that everyone else with a Tesla, GroPro, and an Apple is currently doing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you estimate those costs to be?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your thoughts on it?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get CarFax if available.  PPI.  Check mileage and ask if he's had the IMS fix if not then see if his maintenance schedule is very prompt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes we just need to double check. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking of the 718 Spyder, which is stripped down and NA.  

Also, the GTS does have a few things done to it to get a bit more HP out, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 06:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, I was thinking of the Spyder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 04:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that what the upcoming GTS is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand why people would be turned off by the changes.  People were turned off by the 997 as well.  Some people like certain things.  I like turbos a bunch, but I also like the predictability of an NA engine.

Something like 80% of Porches are still on the roads, so people who like a certain engine will generally have access to what they want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the specific example given was Mincraft.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> German car problem, not necessarily an MB problem.

Interiors are great, outside styling got rid of the more conservative look they've been sticking with, drive much better than the mid 2000s models.

The downsides are downsides you see in other brands as well.  Run flats standard is probably the worst.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I no longer have my beater, but it was a mid 2000s Dodge Magnum Hemi.  I put over 200k miles on it and treated her worse than she ever treated me.

I'd still have her today if she weren't taken from me by a drunk driver in 2015.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Imagine if Mercedes didn't have E classes for almost half the year.

I just bought a C43 and cross shopped plenty of different cars.  There was no dearth of new 5 series.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait another year.  They'll be rolling out new engines that should cut down on all the minute differences.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Sir I don't like it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wife had one.  Internal issues.  Had to take it in and have the "CPU Reset" all the time.  Center console would freeze up.  Tire PSI low warning light wouldn't turn off after airing up.  Drove terribly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 05:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like a bus in that you're back is straight up and you're punching down on the pedals.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has a phone number pad on it.

You can't get more mid 90s than that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a Renegade as a rental a few months back and it was like driving a fucking bus.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The C300?  Even if you put it in S+ mode it still behaves like it does in C until you start giving it gas and driving it hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a rebadged GLA250. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Average lease is 3 years so it kinda makes sense in the long run.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Volvo or the new C?

New C300 2.0 liter had some quality issues with wrist pins but that is long since fixed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  because BMW is too focused on complicated infotainment systems

MB's infotainment is pretty complicated to use, really.  BMW's is a bit easier.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google says this is a 2006 330i interior.

http://www.1addicts.com/forums/e90garageimg/11019/P1010392.jpg

https://preview2.netcarshow.com/BMW-330i-2006-1600-17.jpg

2006 325i

https://files.graphiq.com/4315/media/images/t2/2005_BMW_3_Series_325Ci_Rwd_2dr_Coupe_25L_6cyl_5M_3784263.jpg





Other than gear shifter, the new cars look pretty much **exactly the same**.  

This is the same reason I waited until 2015 to buy a Merc.  [The 2014 C Class interior was ugly... it looked like BMWs](http://images.newcars.com/images/car-pictures/original/2013-Mercedes-Benz-C-Class-Coupe-Hatchback-Base-C250-2dr-Coupe-Photo-14.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  4 years

I think it's 3 years now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was the GLK a shared platform?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And Ram trucks. They've been having record sales and they're vastly improved since Fiat took over. I own one and love it.

I had a late 90s 1500 for a while.  Was a great truck.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fiat seem to be making a reasonable go of it

The 500 is a bad car but I see them *everywhere*.  

 Jeep especially are having a bit of a revival under the Italians. Who'd of think it.

Another strange situation.  Really bad quality vehicles, but the "Jeep Culture" has bolstered alot lately.  I've even seen Wrangler grill tattoo's become a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be nice.  I'd like to see an XC90 like interior to make it's way down to the S/V60 and XC60.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interior has stagnated, MB's has gotten significantly better.  The 2014 C300 compared to the 2015 C300 is mind blowing.

Another similar update in scope was the Volvo XC90.  2015 - 2016 almost like it's a completely new vehicle.  Volvo's selling the new ones pretty well too from what I hear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mercedes-Benz overtakes BMW to become largest premium carmaker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fixing their name scheme probably helps a bit, as does the introduction of the GLA250.

Every Infiniti QX30 sale is basically a sale for MB as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't feel bad.  All the insiders on Twitter are starting to pipe up and saying that it is specifically an MS issue as MS wants to focus on "live service" titles.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She should get different kids.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C300, yeah.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interior without a question.  Handling seems to be fairly equal between the two.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's pretty fantastic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, just get a Targa and a Cayenne.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're splitting hairs at that point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For all Macans, correct?  All Panameras after 2017 as well, IIRC.

What about Cayenne?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the engine performs a bit better but the 7 speed tranny is really lazy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 991.2 Targa GTS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "it doesn't smell"

I can smell their Grape Pomegranate bullshit for sure.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The vast improvements MB has been making over the past few years is certainly paying off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does this Stinger GT.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant!

Wife really wants an SUV and between the two Porsche offerings we're also looking at an XC90.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is an insert for the center console storage box for sale on Amazon, buy it

Link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I've experienced the Turbo lag on the base is similar to turbo lag on my C300.

Manageable, not great.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tiny Heist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what I was thinking, but their website doesn't present all the info very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just absolute laziness.  You can legally toss it in the trash if you a stick it in the fridge to let it congeal or b put it in a bottle that can be capped.

This was a five gallon bucket so I guess they didn't have the space in the fridge and didn't have enough two liter bottles so they decided to fuck up our neighborhood plumbing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently lease deals on them are ridiculous as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the 2015 S equipped with a turbo or is only the base 2.0 and the Turbo model sporting them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 911 if you want the space to put shit that a daily would benefit from.

Targa if you got the money, since that is the defacto "I have money for a Porsche as a daily".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the comments:

 Not confirmed, but a UK site had an anticipated list price of 43k pounds/$52,000 US.

You can get a 400hp Infiniti Red Sport at that price.  A 340i isn't gonna be much higher either.  A new Audi S5 Sportback is right around the corner as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new Kia sports car has a very familiar looking interior... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would gladly give up a Merc for this.  That interior looks A+.  Also looks like my Mercedes interior! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda.

Least they could have done was use their local PD's phone app to report it.  I've only done this for someone pouring a gigantic bucket of grease into a drain in our neighborhood.  Took a pic, sent via app, and they were there in less than 5 minutes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the Sportwagen a great car?  Thinking of swapping the Prius out for one.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gets a 2018 refresh IIRC!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 03:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still available as a coupe as well.

https://www.mbusa.com/mercedes/vehicles/model/class-E/model-E400C </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first 2/3 and big reveal are great.  The last 1/3 is awful.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alpha Protocol.  

I'd even take something paired down, graphics wise.  The actual systems of the game, especially dialog and branching story, is what matters.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 23:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> E400 is coming back as a Wagon this summer.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 20:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Motortrend also thinks the new MB C series design language is ugly.

I don't even know what they're smoking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 19:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same reason most US executives don't face repercussions for when they break the law.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well OP?  How'd it turn out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 17:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a big fat ugly American car, so yes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 04:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here.  I have a Pro 3 and, while good, the kickstand/keyboard cover ends up requiring too much desk real estate, which is a hassle on planes and small hotel desks.

Prolly gonna get a refurb Air or MacBook for quick and easy stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 01:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  E350 and the AMG version.

The E43 is either out or about to.  E400 is coming out soon as well.

The C300 is the analog to the 330i.  C43 to 340i.  C63 to M3.  Etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 01:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was taking advantage of the traffic clearing for the ambulance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's largely why I went with what I got.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  are out of warranty

And yet they're still 10 years younger than the car you're trying to get a free repair on.  

Your issue isn't a safety issue, your issue is a "my car is old as fuck" issue.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Takata airbag scandal

Affects cars still under warranty or around 4 years old.

This BMW is well out of warranty and parts are failing.  This is not surprising at all.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a Half Priced Books here that is absolutely and constantly packed.

Kinda shit selection for my tastes, but oh well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And call the actual brand HQ as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whichever car you look into, make sure that it's AWD is rear biased.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen many monies before.  This is definitely a money.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% this.

Lawyer up, OP.  If you have copies of the previous contracts, take them to the bank that holds the loan for your previous car and let them know.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC he was drummed out of his political party and had his license taken away. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to park in two spaces then park in the very back.  Otherwise don't get upset if someone keys your shit.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  C43 4matic Cab

Ugh I think I made the wrong choice.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone link us to that video from a few weeks back from Europe where the Merc driver purposefully kept getting in the way of the Ambulance.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And you are taught to do that in driving school

You're taught to do that in America as well... but you know us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I send you my used games or console?

We cannot accept used items. If you or someone you know would like to donate used games or game equipment, please consider an alternate game charity or selling your items on eBay with 100% of the proceeds going to Childs Play.

Health reasons.


I don't think hospitals accept used consoles either for similar reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 07:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least double the cost of your Nissan.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 07:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Austin here, go back to family in MS a few times.  Basically outside of I10 and I55 in LA/MS it's pointless.

But I spend maybe 1% of my life on those roads so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 23:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Probably because they tend to use the same cheap plastic interiors as their more economical stable mates. As an example, back in the 90's, the Viper used the same junk radio that came in the Dodge Caravan.

This is the same problem with Maserati.  They were using the interior of a Chrysler 200 on their Ghibli and Quatroporte </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 22:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just use Waze.  Alerts me to speed traps all the time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China and the US film industry are working on getting a nice, cozy, relationship going.  That's why we have that Great Wall movie coming out.  US films make more in China than they do the US sometimes, big revenue buff for both countries.  If China didn't make the film industry happy there isn't much of a reason for the US to keep China in mind when it comes to exporting films.

That and 200k is a drop in the bucket compared to what movies make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should, yes.  :(   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 07:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess this is why they didn't ask you for your opinion.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 01:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The level of noise in a theater like that is thousands of times higher than what you'd see on a public street. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much the only thing Communist about them now days.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The VV guys earned that dough themselves?  Good on them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
