<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3508</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're spot on about Maddow. I likely agree with most of her arguments, but y'know - I really don't know because I can barely stand to listen to her and avoid her unless there is some big todo about one of her episodes on reddit and I decide to watch it out of curiousity.

But damn, between her and Maher I don't understand how there is enough condescension and smarminess left over for anyone else in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the beauty here being that the invisible hand of linguistics will find the solution. 

makes one wonder if there were a bunch of language nerds arguing over how to pronouce knife and knight during the middle ages. 

"Well, I talked to an actual knight and he said it is pronounced Kuh-Ni-Ghe-T. And he would know, don't you think?"

"Yeah, well, my uncle is a knight. and he said the King said "NITE" when he, you know, "NITED" him. And he's the fucking KING!"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tweet, which echoes something Herman Cain said **on Fox News' Fox   Friends an hour before**, doesn't make sense for a few reasons. 

goddamit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> y'know, I just rewatched this today and in fact, Julie cups her hand behind his head after he kisses her hand. And kissing her hand seemed like exactly what his character would do in the show.

So, on rewatching it, I'd actually have to take back my above comment. I probably would have preferred them to not kiss on the lips and his laying his head on her chest/breast was a bit odd even on the second watching.

But damn, in terms of that entire scene, which was so good, I can overlook it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hello. We are calling simply to confirm your reservation at London's Ye Olde Wonderfull Inn. (pause) Great, so nice to serve people like you in our great hotels. A valet will pick you up at Heathrow airport and take you from terminal 1 to terminal 2 where you will board for the final leg of your journey. Flight time ill be approximately 9 hours. When you arrive at the hotel, a fresh mint will be on your pillow". (pause) Yes, that is correct, sir. (Pause) "Yes, but the upside to oursourcing our hotels to India is the authetic Indian cusine!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. But you're forgetting the context of my comment to which you replied.

That comment (mine) was: "Or really? So whom do you consult?"

And was pointed directly at /u/MittensSlowpaw , who said:

if you are smart you don't consult CNN, Fox or most mainstream news outlets for your news anyways.

So, if he does not consult them, which ones *does* he consult?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck, do I really have to spell this out?

"I go online and read various sources to put a picture together" means nothing at all! 

I ASK *WHOM* DO YOU CONSULT NOT *WHERE*.

Godammit some people are dense. Not necessarily you, of course!

But do you go on-line to read the New York Times, or WaPo or Brietbart or Le Monde or whom?

ANSWER THE QUESTION OR STAY OUT OF IT.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There you have it - there are parts of Sweden which are no longer "Swedish". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh, tell us about norway and denmark! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 13:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ridiculous to get news from Stewart, Colbert and Oliver. It's hilarious to watch them dissect the news of the day, and sometimes they may have turned my attention to something I missed in the you know, actual news, and that may serve as a jumping off point for me if I want to learn more about that particular subject.

But yeah, as far as opinions of mine go concerning anyone on the left who "always admitted to getting their news from people like..." - they are dumbos and probably have very preconceived notions of how the world works and/or should work. I'd probably have to pummel them in many debates. But I would not go so far as to pulverize them unless they were really beyond "the pale". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 13:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 13:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shit goes in, shit comes out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 13:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yours is an answer to a different question, however. 

In fact, you are saying "consult the news and then look deeper and form your own opinion".

The fellow I was replying to, is saying to avoid the MSM. I asked, if not the NYT, WaPo, or any number of "mainstream news outlets", then whom shoud one consult? In your answer, you did not narrow that down at all. You said "use the news" when the entire point is *whose news*?

I appreciate your trying to offer an honest answer, and hope you don't take this personally (because I ceratinly don't mean it personally, but in the context of the larger discussion), but at the same time, I hope you can see you did not answer the question at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 13:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That rings a bell. But what is she doing *right now*? Just staying out of the limelight? That would be no surprise, But it would also be no surprise if she were foung speaking up somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or really? So whom do you consult? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is, for most of America the lines *do* blur and hence you have great swaths of core Trump voters believing the *opinions* of the *pundits* are in fact *the news.*

I mean, does Fox even want the Trump faithful to be able to tell the difference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does "the small portion of Fox dedicated to journalism" include anyone besides Shepard and Wallace? Serious question.

Also, where is Megan Kelly now? Still under non-compete, or travelling the world with her kid or what? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 09:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is "hacking" in the same way as the term is used in "lifehacks". No-one is rewriting or explointing actual computer code, people are simply finding unorthodox ways of doing normal things. 

The meanings of words change and I know it's always uncomfortable to those behind the curve, but it is what it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can say that aga...

oh, you did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say a lot of the people who *did not vote* in the past election are just as dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ties to Russia and ties from China! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, no that's exactly why he should have run in NY. He'd have lost handily) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do Trump supporters hate Carlin, too? I am just wondering aloud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we are comparing the contents of the e-mail leaks to the contents of leaks about the FBI's investigtion of Trump, I'd sure say the latter are way more alarming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reagan was governor of Califorinia first, right?

I think we'd all be better off if Trump had run for governor of NY first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 08:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats in districts represented by Republicans where the elected Republican is avoiding town halls, need to begin hosting ther own town halls there.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, the kiss was a definitely out of place. He got comfortable far too fast.

But I guess he knew it was going to be over pretty quick and he'd never get another chance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think aobut how long she has been lost. No real contact with other humans. And then this man comes in and connects with her, of course she treated him like a long lost lover. Well, she didn't actually. 

She treated him like the only human she has talked to in a long, long time and she has been yearing for human contact. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your comma at the end was amost superfluous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they should just trade places with all those people in kentucky who are also supposed to just move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, too, have a holodeck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 04:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> apparently 1 in 5 Americans at least belong to this category.

and 4 out of 5 Republicans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 04:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   her skill at bullshit is no longer needed. And since it was her only skill ...

Boom, the heart of the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kellyanne, I'm just going to be upfront with you.

There are two facts:

1) You are easily replaceable.

2) We don't even have to replace you, we just don't need you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> invisible hand, free market, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honest question - what do you think of articles like this?

https://foreignpolicy.com/2017/02/21/the-worst-and-the-dimmest/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my point being that one might feel some sympathy for the minority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 12:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no. The idea is to have Clooney, not Trump, at the top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 11:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Clooney should have run for president?

And his cabinet should have 9 people in it. 

Nine + Pres + Veep = 11.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 11:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, the case for his extradition is allegedly bribing some Indian lawmakers. 

It's a hook.

Just like Al Capone was caught "merely for tax evasion".

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you should look at the maps here:

Briefly, yes, the state is overwhelmingly red. But between 15 and 30 per cent of people in all those red counties did in fact vote for Clinton.

http://www.nytimes.com/elections/results/kentucky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why couldn't they jsut read those parts to and replace Sessions's name with "The miscreant"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> degrees, degrees .. but who did they vote for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the big question is  - do vets still vote for the GOP anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally, I would have skipped a submission with this title, but I noticed it was from teenvogue.com and then knew it was worth reading.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, the indirect reference to "fake news".

Blanket statements like this do not help, you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they'd probably fuckng hang you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn libruls! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, that in fact proves he was in Latvia somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you please explain why this mod-bot comment is there? 

    []JoyousCacophony[M] [score hidden] 2 hours ago 

    Hi facemelt. Thank you for participating in /r/Politics. However, your submission has been removed for the following reason(s):

    Off-Topic: All submissions to /r/politics need to be explicitly about current US politics.

    If you have any questions about this removal, please feel free to message the moderators.


It this submission visible or not? It's extremely confusing when I can see it, but I also read this comment from "the mods". If the submission is in fact "live", can you please delete that comment?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found this posted on /r/politics where in fact it belongs as well as belonging here.

As far as I can tell, the FBI will soon have its hands on Firtash. 

Remember, this guy was arrested in Austria on an FBI warrant but due to his deep pockets being able to afford really good lawyers, it is only now that Austria has decided his case is in fact not political.

It's amazing to think what the FBI might learn from him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austria grants US request to extradite Ukrainian mogul Dmytro Firtash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking no shit they're watching him closely. This guy probably knows a hell of a lot about what really happened in Crimea in 2014.

This news really needs to his the top of /r/politics. It is even bigger than the Trump aide's deals that one guy left on Flynn's desk, becuase frankly, there is so much room for denial on Trump's part (what plan? I don't know nothing about no plan!). And that pro-Russia Ukrainian politician that is kind of sorta behind it is not a really big fish, he's a wanna be. 

Firtash is the real thing. He will know everythign about Manafort. He will know a lot of shit about any shady Russian or Ukrainian businessmen Trump has been dealing with. A FUCKING LOT. 

And he's a guy with a fuck ton of resources, so you can't just take him out that easily. If he dies anytime soon, that's a high level special op, if you ask me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Oh my god.**

**This is huge. Nay, yuuuuugomungous!**

Read [this Reuters article](http://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-austria-firtash-idUSBREA2C14V20140313) dated March 13, 2014 - weeks after Russia took over Crimea. See, Firtash was arrested in Austria on an **FBI Warrant**.

FTA: "It (Firtash's arrest) sends a strong message to Russia that the west is willing to go down the financial sanctions route unless it backtracks over Crimea and over broader policy towards Ukraine," said Timothy Ash of Standard Bank.

For a long time, Firtash fought very hard against Austria extraditing him to the US. He has deep pockets and can afford the best of lawyers. 

So, this news that NOW (what timing!!!) Austria is going to let the FBI have him is - just wow!

If you read the submitted article here, you will see that Firtash is caught for bribing Indian officials, but that's the hook. 

I can only imagine the songs he is going to start singing to the FBI because this dude is steeped fucking deep in Ukrainian-Russian corruption - especially anything to do with natural gas. And people in gas know people in oil.

He has conncetions at the VERY TOP. He knows everything about Russian gas deals (did I mention that already?). I DON'T KNOW THAT HE KNOWS ANYTHING ABOUT THE 19.5% ROSNEFT DEAL, BUT I WOULD NOT FUCKING BE SURPRISED. 1000% SURE HE KNOWS PEOPLE WHO KNOW. 

I mean, I guess you can tell from how i'm going on and on that this is Really. Big. News.

OMG, reddit. Follow this one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I guess everyone has their red line? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on now, you know he's going to go for the first ever presidential golf course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are not a male of the species, are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and ordered dijon mustard on his "people's hamburder"! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Zealand controls mega.nz? wow, i did not know that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd go with 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait to come back to /r/askhistorians in 20 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Alpa Chinco

I really wanna see some more movies now with the guy in it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, Trump and Tillerson get almost 1/5 of Rosneft. 

 **SPICY IS AS SPICY DOES!!!** 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like this?? 


NOTE: I've been bannd from T_D (for a comment on Common Core that did not even mention Trump, fwiw!), but I can copy paste from there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not very true. The Nord Stream gas pipeline for example goes from Russia's north to the Baltic sea and on to Germany.  Map: https://gdb.rferl.org/C34C78F9-E7B2-496D-AD54-10CFDA62DF26_mw1024_mh1024_s.jpg

Furthermore, *nothing* is being sent across Crimea. And in an age of sophisticated missiles, Crimea itself is not very important militarily (You'll have to read about that somewhere else, but the gist of things I read was that Crimea is good for projecting some naval force in the Black Sea, but not good for much else and that projecting force in the Black Sea is actually kind of weak in the big picture). 

Taking Crimea does however give Russia all the oil and gas fields in the sea surrounding it. Oil and gas deposits that were Ukraine's by right to develop and now Ukraine - which really needs more hydrocarbons had that stolen from them. 

Here's a map of what Ukraine lost de facto: http://www.platts.com/IM.Platts.Content/InsightAnalysis/NewsFeature/2014/NaturalGas/Ukraine-Crisis-Energy-Implications/images/crimea-oil-gas-assets.jpg

Here is a map of gas pipelines via Ukraine. You'll notice nothing traverses Crimea, just some branches go there to supply it:

https://www.zerich.com/images/articles/Ukrainyi.jpg

So, I personally think Putin took Crimea knowing full well it comes with offshore oil and gas fields (and that makes him even righer, though to be fair I think they are not devleoping those fields now as it is a legal minefield - International law recognizes the fields as Ukraine's and any company trying to devleop them would be hit with sanctions) and also he did it to bolster his declining popularity in Russia itself.

Ondoklassniki - an early Facebook socil media site like vKontakte, was really jumping on the Putin's failures meme parade in 2012-2013. That stopped when the war with Ukraine started and all those people upset with Putin suddenly became his fans. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Russians themselves know they don't have all the tech they need:

http://rbth.com/business/2015/09/28/russia_admits_lack_of_technologies_for_offshore_oil_production_49605.html

And it has caused delays:

http://upnorth.eu/the-impact-of-western-sanctions-on-the-russian-oil-sector/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, my overview was overcourse superficial, of course they can do some off-shore drilling, but here is Russia itself saying they don't have the tech:

http://rbth.com/business/2015/09/28/russia_admits_lack_of_technologies_for_offshore_oil_production_49605.html

And it's caused serious delays:

http://upnorth.eu/the-impact-of-western-sanctions-on-the-russian-oil-sector/

Here are some other analysts:

http://www.offshore-technology.com/features/featurewhat-next-for-russias-offshore-oil-and-gas-4627639/

Andrew Neff, principal analyst at IHS Energy's petroleum sector risk group says: "Companies are not allowed under the sanctions to participate in projects and the Russians do not have the technological expertise [to do it themselves] and now they do not have the access to financing either, so for longer-term projects the time line is going to be extended even further.

"Russia would need to develop its own technology, which is doable but it is going to take a longer time. Western companies will enable Russia to proceed with these projects in a 10 - 15 year horizon and without that Western investment you are pushing that down another five years at least."

Both US and European Union (EU) sanctions will restrict Gazprom and Rosneft's access to world-leading offshore technology suppliers such Schlumberger and Halliburton.

and RPI, probably the leading indepedent oil gas research institute in Russia:

https://rogtecmagazine.com/rpi-offshore-field-development-in-russia-are-the-sanctions-an-opportunity-for-russian-companies-to-fill-the-void/

While in the drilling segment for relatively small depths there are drilling companies such as EDC or Gazprom Burenie, **the situation in terms of quality support of offshore drilling is very alarming**.

This article (from 21 September 2015) shows how much Russia relied on imported equipment before the sanctions:

http://www.rcinet.ca/eye-on-the-arctic/2015/09/21/sanctions-menace-offshore-oil-security-russia/

According to the newspaper, **68 percent of the technical equipment needed by the industry is now subjected to sanctions and consequently out of reach for the Russian drillmen**.

and also:

When it comes to shelf exploration, **Russia produces less than one percent of the equipment needed**, Kommersant [a heavyweight Russian business newspaper - my note] writes.

**Ha, I just realized you linked to a photo, too. (Hadn't looked at it first)** So, the Prirazlomnaya, eh? So funny, you'll have to read this:

http://barentsobserver.com/en/energy/2014/08/sanctions-could-jeopardize-security-russian-arctic-platform-26-08

The Prirazlomnaya platform is **packed with Norwegian technology** and is likely to soon feel the consequences of the western export ban on oil and gas equipment.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is exactly it.

A little background. Russia's land-based oil fields are rapidly depleting. They have been producing on oil them since the Soviet days and they have the technology down pat. Tey are good at it, but the oil is running out. At least the oil they can access.  

But Russia has jillions of tons of oil (and gas) locked away off-shore in especially in the Arctic. They do not have the technology to drill for this oil. They just don't. They rely on western companies like NOV, Schlumberger, Halliburton - oil field service companies that DO have this technology. And they like to team up with huge Western companies that know how to use this technology.

Just before 2014 and all the shit Russia pulled in Ukraine, they were setting up big huge deals with companies like ... Exxon (ta-da!). Exxon would set up a joint venture with say Rosneft to drill for oil in the arctic.

These deals are - as you know - worth billions. 

Well, Russia fucked them up by annexing Crimea and the West asked "How can we really punish Russia for threatening the peaceful world order we have had since WWII?" *That* is the huge thing Russia did not get. Just how much the Europeans are willing to sacrifice to ensure the continent does not go to war again. And the rules state: "No annexing parts of other countries, just because you feel like you can get away with it when the opportunity arises". 

The answer was (after smaller sanctions at the beginning directed at individuals involved): "We will deny them access to our deep sea off shore drilling technologies and fracking technologies so they cannot make money off of selling oil. And of course, we must ban our companies from doing deals with Russia on these types of projects".

So, it's not even that Arctic drilling is not profitable for Russia, it's simply that they do not have the expertise to drill in those conditions. They do not make the equipment necessary and they can't really get it anywhere else, because it's almost a strictly Western expertise. India and China are trying, but they are years behind. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 17:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> better call the coppers!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but it's going to make for some awesome campaign attack ads in 2018.

Just video of Trump doing whatever it is and a voice over - in Trump's own voice - complaining about Obama doing that same thing.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For every new regulation, get rid of two! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> now i need a tl;dr of art therapy. or an eli5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> art therpy sounds liberal as fuck. i don't know how they will eplain it to trump's core. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (we won't) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also wonder if it is going to convince him that in fact, yeah, everything is okay. and by getting complacent, he'll make further, bigger fuck-ups that will hopefully have impeachment not far behind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You missed the part where Clinton was there *herself* literally giving them cash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 12:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> puppet, meet strings... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 09:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a very good explanation. I would just add that in addition to "moron from the Urals", there would also be "businessman from St. Petersburg" trying to letigimize his taking over ABC factory, too. 

Also, I think the comment you were replying to was just confused by the English as someone might see the word "recognizing" more in the context of "I did not recognize you when you came in wearing that big hat".

But you very good comment should probably be a top level comment, actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 08:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and even that doesn't keep it from leaking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also how a place like this lures dumb Westerners and murders them for their wallets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I know they are exempted. The point is having proof they take advantage of that exception could be damning to their reelection bids.

It would truly piss people off. 

And some rep will just need to make *all* his constituents his staffers. That would be fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, your teachers should not have failed you for that. they should have helped you put your thoughts into words. 

anyhow, you're able to do it now, so that's good ! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grammar nazi here. ~~it~~ It works better as "Jesus holy fucking shit sandwich".

EDIT: I am clearly a junior officer grammar Nazi, as I failed to capitalize "It". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you telling me that Washington was 1? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, are you open carry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can report on it without making it look like  big deal. But also without hiding the numbers of people present or they'll just get called out on that with comprisons of phone videos of the event to their news videos of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wonder how the Republicans primaries are going to go down.

Either Trump goes down before them or he doesn't. Either way, his rabid supporters are going to still be around. So, how will they affect the primaries?

If they overrun the primaries and get lots of their rabid pro-Trump candidates on the ballot, how will that hurt/help the Democrts running against them?

Were I runnng the RNC, I'd making damn sure to rig the primaries so establishment friendly candidates get nominated as they *should* have  far easier time beating Dems in the election. 

But even if they are on the ballots, will ther be enough of a Dem/liberal uprising to swing the close gerrymandered districts?

Somewhere, there must be a bunch of scientists watching this experiment in their petri-dish named Earth, taking non-stop notes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's stupid. An intelligent person should in fact be able to explain in words a simple thing like how he did a math problem. 

NOT because that math problem need sto be explained, but because CRITICAL THINKING skills need to be developed.

The same thing applies to people who complain about "my kid has to draw inside the lines, but why are they stifling his freedom to draw outside the lines!"

Kids are supposed to draw inside the lines because it helps them develop fine motor skills. NOT because anyone is trying to stifle their imagination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 14:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are apparently one and the same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 14:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump mde some remark recently about how he had been told how devastating nuclear war is. 

I suspect those who told him were seriously worried he might not underdtand the implications because he is that stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 13:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant](http://i.imgur.com/BvSpd5q.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 13:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even rocks hate him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 09:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because you have to entertain the possibility that you are wrong and that trump will stick around and therefore that his cabinet will in fact destroy things. 

or, if you don't care that they destroy things or even agree with their vision of destroying things, by all means, vote for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 09:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you mean lose his reelection or lose his primary?

because if he'd lost his election, wouldn't there be another Dem in the senate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 09:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when they don't move and you won't budge, that's how a civil war begins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 08:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmmm, after you put it that way - maybe that has already happened? anyone noticed any backwoods hicks missing lately? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully, Trump is the last of the other alternatives and they can finally get around to doing the right thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll have 9 if he can get rid of the first one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's labelled "To my dear love Schrodinger. Kisses, your Pandora". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And i mentoned this in another thread, but it's easy to imagine very damning stuff in RNC e-mails. Like a congressman telling his broker to buy some stock the same day as he has a committee meeting on something related to it. And the next day the stock rockets up to a new high. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will come out eventually, but the very fact that people *suspect* the Russians hacked the RNC every single dam R senator and house member if wracking his brain wondering "fuck, what have i said in an e-mail that could come back to haunt me?" 

So, why would they want to press forward on an investigation that could be their end? it not only that they want to avoid an investigation to keep trump and the party alive, it's that they damn well know they've forwarded an e-mail where Michelle Obama is drawn as a monkey, or they replied to an aide that their adie's write up of some policy is perfect and the aide's policy paper is so not wha the R is know for publicly, or they wrote an e-mail telling their broker to buy whatever stock and that e-mail was sent during a hearing on some company whose stock rocketed the next day.

Marco Rubio was 100% right when he plead with Rs to stay away from this stuff.

And now is the perfect time for some Democrat to take the floor and flat out say "There needs to be an investigation into the possible Russian hacking of RNC e-mails. Now my esteemed colleagues have long been tough on digital security, arguing in favour of the government to be able to view electronic correspondence to secure the nation from threats. And that argument has long been 'if you have nothing to hide, you have nothing to fear'. So, I ask my esteemed colleagues, what do you have to fear from an investigation? Why are you hiding from this?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/politics needs to add a rule about how to format a real donald trump quote so we don't have to ask tese questions anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 06:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cannibas friendly horse! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the relevant quote (emphasis mine):

I refuse to accept that our values are morally equivalent to those of our adversaries, he said. I am a proud, unapologetic believer in the West, and I believe we must always, always stand up for it. **For if we do not, who will**?

Well, that remains to be seen, since clearly YOU, Mr McCain, apart from running your mouth, are unwilling to take an actual stand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe and Mika said that morning
linky? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, everything is perfectly lined up to do this right now.

If you want to really push Net Neutrality, frame it in terms Trump's most ardent supporters can embrace.  

Why them? Because they hate the main stream media right now. Put together a few stories that can FW:FW:FW:FW across e-mail and Facebook letting them know that the "Deep State" wants to limit people's right to balanced news. Tell them that the deep state is pushing congressmen and senators - especially democrats (not true, but this will probably work better with a dash of "fake news")...

Like I was saying, tell them via chain e-mails and Facebook that the Democrats in cahoots with Hollywood nd the MSM want to limit what they can read on their Internets. 

These stories should point out that the evil libruls are infiltrating ISPs and when Net Neutrality is lost, the ISPs can begin offering "packages" of news where NYT, WaPo and CNN might be free, but you'll have to pay extra to read InfoWars or FoxNews.

Now you've got their attention and you can ELI5 on what Net Neutrality means for them. 

Next, get them (and others, we're not forgetting anyone else) firmly convinced that "No, the main stream media CANNOT be allowed to choose what "real Americans" hear and read and see on the Internet.

Finally, get them to plead on Twitter with realDonaldTrump to save them from this terrible possibility and BOOM Net Neutrality is a done deal - enshrined as a way for Real America to ensure that libruls don't brainwash the People of the USA. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The horse is not dead. That's why everyone is kicking it. So it dies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in, instead of Seth leaking to Wikileaks, he leaked them to a Russian spy who then picked what to give to wikileaks and then the Russian spy, rather than Clinton's 'secret pizza-fed abduction crew', is who took him out of the picture?

Is that what you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That get's me wondering - what is Germany's answer to Breitbart?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A man who must say his machine in running 'fine-tuned' has no machine at all"

- Tywin Bannister

^((Bannon owns the machine)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and it plays well into the jason bourne movies and Enemy of the State.

Breitbart appears to be pushing this really hard now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're conflating doing a specific thing - make a cake with homophobic slogans - to not serving someone based on his protected class.

if a person feels it is immoral to serve cake to gays, he needs to find another job. 

if he finds it immoral to make cakes shaped like vaginas, he is free to not make them. but he cannot make them for white people only and refuse to make them for asians.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, if the gay couple demanded that their wedding cake be shaped like a giant erect schlong modelled on one of their own - with pictures for reference - the cake shop could refuse them!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, to be fair, they'd be happy if no one paid taxes or fees for anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so, basically, if a couple of black guys asked you to make kkk hoods you could deny them and if a bunch of old white anglo-saxon protestants started cussing like sailors and throwing chairs around in your bar, you could kick them out, right?

makes sense to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
