<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7051</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 02:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A great example to set for our children, too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 02:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 02:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are making a difference in that dog's life. Nobody could ask any more of you. You're good people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 02:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The man that assaulted my husband 11 months ago was sentenced this week. He will be serving jail time, and we are relieved that the whole ordeal is over with. My husband was injured so severely he had to have surgery to repair fractures in his face. We had to move because the man that assaulted him was our next door neighbor and did so while our ten year old son watched. It's just such a relief to have it all done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 02:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just going to second this community, fantastic. My family is batshit crazy, I'm positively sane in comparison, but it takes work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 02:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You can trust me, I'm not like everyone else". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 00:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surface to Air missiles. We DO have a military, contrary to popular belief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 23:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MMMMMMMM. Pizzaaaaaa. Canadian, too!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 23:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 23:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad poutine is still better than good anything else you would eat, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 23:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some Canadians gloated a little to much after the girls won, Some Americans had some sour grapes. I think coming within 55 secs of a gold medal only to have Canada storm back really sucked and some people were kinda angry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 23:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but we'll just refuse him at the border. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 23:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, he was basically a kid a few years ago and he has grown-up a lot. Is he overrated? Maybe. Does everyone like him, HELL NO. IS he a GREAT hockey player, OH YEAH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 23:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I'm pretty sure we're going to name holidays in Carey Price's honor. Regardless of what happens.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 23:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like exactly how they used to describe Gretzky.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 21:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was on in our lunch room and I streamed it in my office and everyone knew. Even my kid's schools showed the games in class yesterday and today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 20:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not quite family! She was my Christmas Greeting Card match :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 05:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure it was The Daily Mash, and my Facebook exploded with idiots on that one. Might be time to cull the herd. (I believe they said he fell on a bunch of knives, too).

Edit: [It was The Daily Currant.](http://dailycurrant.com/2014/02/08/man-responsible-for-olympic-ring-mishap-found-dead-in-sochi/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 05:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you HAVE to have them close together. So they get along!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 05:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Small freaking world! Um, Reddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 04:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had lingering doubts before that. NOT ANYMORE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 04:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O...M...G!! Hey hun!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 02:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget bobsleigh yesterday!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 00:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sportsmanship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 23:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You betcha! Hopefully my ticker can handle another game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 23:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We wouldn't have it any other way! Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 23:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like your optimism went a looooong way, friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good game, though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone with a great sense of humor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry some are being jerks. Thanks for the great game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some are, most aren't. We're horribly patriotic (and I don't doubt there are some drunk Canadians amongst us ;) ). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Collective strokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately a few will spoil the reputation of the whole. I appreciate the great hockey that was played. Great game, USA! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a few of those, but there are also the opposite. Great game USA! See you in four years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a woman, I screamed it for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great game. That's what hockey supposed to be! Thanks guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you hug your co-worker for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OHHHHHH CANADAAAAAAA!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's almost better than gold. Almost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We love you meeps! -All of Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, man. Thanks for a great game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was so preeeeetty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 22:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a frigging ulcer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 15:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Healing time isn't SO bad. I had an impacted wisdom tooth (I believe?) that they had to take out from the side. The healing is MUCH better than having a "traditionally" pulled tooth because the "wound" isn't really in the way when you eat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 03:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Truck nuts](http://imgur.com/sWkAjha). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 03:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hubby weighs a buck forty and looks fat next to this guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 03:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And an appropriate username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 03:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you apprehend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 03:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 11 year old has this problem. Hmmmmmmmmmmm. 

Before you yell at me, it's a joke. He doesn't even like booze. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 05:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're really creative, in fact. If they could channel that into books or movies they could probably do well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 02:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confidence in yourself is the best defense you have in life. I think Dita Von Teese said "You can be the juiciest, ripest peach, but somebody is still going to hate peaches".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 02:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you have all the more reason to succeed!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 23:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't seen him for awhile, I was concerned! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 23:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not with Dw!! He's EVERYONE'S favorite troll.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 06:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow!! Those are some awesome looking guys and gals! I noticed the rescue is from Ontario! You're Canadian? I'm from Alberta! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 05:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG. That poor baby. WTF is WRONG with people? These are living things! They feel pain! They have emotions (sorry, firm believer in that, if you don't believe a turtle has emotions, watch them get mad when they don't get food when they beg). It's so sick the lack of empathy. Like I said, I felt sick to my stomach when Chuck got soft shell. We scrubbed him, dry docked him, kept a close eye on him and AGONIZED. I was so scared he would die, even though he remained feisty. Eventually he healed very well, but I keep a very close eye on his tank and shell, lesson learned!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 05:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my buddy, [Chuck](http://imgur.com/LSomfbl). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 05:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have ours in a 100 gallon fish tank. He's 6" in diameter and came to us in a 30 gallon tank at about 5". It was too small! We got a great deal on this tank used and he is very happy. Most of the pictures on that page made me cringe!! Poor turtles :'(. And the green tank water!!! Ugh!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 05:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cop put me and my husband in a snowy ditch and kept right on truckin'. Huge piss-off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 05:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're a parent it's like watching it live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 05:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ginger tomcat literally outweighs your pup. Sweetie pie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 04:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me, this is true, had a few counselors tell me that it is possible to be a great parent by having a role model show EVERYTHING NOT to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 04:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turtles are not for the faint hearted pet owner. They require room, a clean tank and time! When my red-eared slider developed soft shell I felt like the most neglectful awful owner ever. We were able to clear it up by tripling his tank size and quadrupling the filter capacity, but most owners don't dedicate that much time of money to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 22:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's got you confused, sport? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 11:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband says every time he thinks he should text me, I text him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 11:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/yUELoH1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 06:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, you know, windshield wipers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 05:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hug her tight for a while, she'll need it. Glad you got her out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 05:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truck nuts. End of story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 18:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no. I literally meant that they butchered him in the literal sense (cut him up) for meat for the lions. Like you would a cow. Totally backfired on me. Duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The view from my office window is strangely arousing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 18:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 05:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I meant to say dissection. My bad. Looking for the wrong word and I failed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 05:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my knee jerk reaction before I read it, but they made it clear that this is a natural process in the wild and it is something they are doing to preserve the integrity of the species as a whole. As they said, it was likely as a young giraffe he would not have seen older years as many fall to natural predators such as, well, Lions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 05:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant butchering as a butcher shop butchering, not a horror movie butchering. Dissection was the word I should've used.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 05:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant it as a dissection with the end purpose of the meat going to the lions. Like a butcher shop butchers, not like Jack the Ripper butchers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 19:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you read their official statement it WAS a last resort. His genes were far over-represented and they needed the space for a giraffe with rarer genes to perpetuate the species in a healthy manner. They know what they are doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 19:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that from just running 5K's! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 19:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a word, YES! I feel great after I run. Even if it was a crappy run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 19:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just found out mine died (NC for 12 years). It's a great feeling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 19:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm counting the months until winter is over. Here in Edmonton I MIGHT get to ride by June! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 14:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took a course and I really recommend it. As for maintenance, my hubby does most of it, but really it's mostly winterization here. Storing your battery in a warm place, gas preservative, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 14:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you live in a big city with the option of public transportation that's the way to go. I live in a forest where I'm more likely to see deer or elk than people. It's perfect, but you REALLY need a car! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 08:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you do what your Mommy told you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 08:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I truly believe that your love for her did a lot for her, too. I'm sorry for your loss. *hugs* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 03:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good! College is tough for some young adults when they aren't used to making decisions for themselves. For the record, I'm not a teenage girl hater. Most of the reason I'm relieved I had boys is I had a terrible mother and I was worried that I would continue the cycle. I'm also not incredibly feminine and don't do bullshit or drama, so a teenage girl would have been a nightmare. I hope college is going well for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 02:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to hear that. If you ever need to talk, I'm here for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 02:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. And raising teenaged boys and teenaged girls is MOST DEFINITELY not the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 02:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you feel better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 02:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a more responsible 39 year old now. He wasn't a dumb kid, but he liked his bikes! Still does. He got me on my own a few years back and I love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 01:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I do. Luckily, I don't have to deal with the fallout of their bad decisions on an everyday level. Just societal. My mother was a severe narcissist who doted on my brother so I was lucky enough to have to become a very dependent woman. He is incredibly dependent person, so it does go the other way. I'm not saying these kinds of statements are always from young girls, but so many of them are. My son had a young woman in Grade 11 ask what the Holocaust was. I was absolutely incredulous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 01:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if you're supporting me or not. I love the song however because I'm Canadian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 01:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also am not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 23:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full or empty? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 23:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sneeze and you've crossed a province. JESUS. I honestly thought it was a typo at first. My hubby used to get his Suzuki GSR600 up to over 200km/hr on back country roads when we were first dating (twenty years ago). I yelled at him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 23:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live 15 min from civilization. No car, no work, no money, no food, die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 23:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To clarify, I'm Mom. I just see this girl and I'm reminded of all the drama that my friends have gone through with their teenage girls. If it isn't the girls themselves, it's other girls creating drama FOR them. We are a dramatic sex, aren't we? My biggest fight with my boys is getting my 11 year old to empty the dishwasher and my 17 year old to clean the litterbox. Like, seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 23:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also enjoy my knuckles and the things around me and don't want to destroy them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 23:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have friends with teenage girls and the sense of entitlement is much worse in girls. I'm Mom, by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 21:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 350? Fuuuuuuuuu.....
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 21:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came to the comments first. I can't even watch it. I fear I'll facepalm too hard and trigger a migraine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 20:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are also SEXY at work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 20:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son who's graduating this year and I "carpool" because we live twenty minutes from his school and thirty from my work. I drive right past his school. Why would we waste the extra $250-$300 a month on gas driving separately? Makes no sense. This girl is a spoiled, entitled little brat. Jesus I'm glad I had two boys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 20:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the opposite. It wasn't until I started exercising that my depression stabilized significantly and I was able to reduce my meds to their lowest levels ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 20:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've made several posts lamenting the fact that women go to Europe and sleep with men. Yet no mention of the reverse happening. I'm going to go ahead and deduce that you find it an issue. 

And no. I like my trash right where it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 18:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear the trouser snakes are the deadliest.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 18:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it were a guy bagging European women would it be an issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 18:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scott, you're a dork. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 18:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy lives in Mundy, Michigan. I doubt there is much in the way of Affluenza going around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
