<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4673</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which celebrity did you use to like but not anymore and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 11:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you think Trump will go in the next four years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 11:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who should more people know about and what do they do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 08:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If i was a teenager in the seventies or eighties, i probably would have taken drugs, had sex, hooked up and did some crazy stuff. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 14:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which celebrity was a late bloomer in hollywood? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 14:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the worst number one player? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 07:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do the kiwis have to do, to win the world cup next year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 06:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the most perfect person you know and what makes them perfect? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Million Dollar Baby is a masterpiece! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clint eastwood always delivers. He is a great storyteller and phenomenal director. The cast is world class and the story is amazing. Hilary swank became a boxer. She was believable and i felt her every breath and touch. I also liked the narration by the great morgan freeman. I am not a fan of female boxing but it made me interested in female boxing. It was a powerful movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes you weird? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 06:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relatives/parents of strippers/adult performers: what is it like and how has it affected your life? (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 05:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many more grand slams will novak djokovic win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 04:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the sexiest ads with links too? (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 04:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your fave wes craven movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 13:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed the scream movies. They weren't scary but i like the characters and the origin of sidney prescott. I like thinking about who the killer is. I guess in a way it is scary because there are psychopaths out there killing people. At least i will be prepared. I thought he directed more movies but they are all quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miss March Terrible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 09:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched it a few years ago because it sounded funny and sexy. I was bitterly disappointed because it was just terrible. You don't care about the characters at all. The acting is horrid and the storyline is terrible. The only redeemable qualities are all the hot playmates and actresses. I knew it had lots of bad reviews but i thought it was a decent raunchy comedy. Boy was i wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who have premonitions that come true: what did you see and how has it affected your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 08:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if your wildest dreams did come true? That would be so amazing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 08:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That maybe some girls were interested in me but i was too dumb to realise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 04:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which celebs do you think are secretly friends but they seem to hate each other? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 04:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who has played for australia that was a shock selection? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 03:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you start up your own movie production company? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 13:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been a fan of movies. How it is all put together. I enjoy all the elements of film making and the outcome. I've always wanted to be a director but it is a long shot. I have some story ideas but hollywood is pretty much impossible to crack. I know you probably need a lot of money to start your movie company and lots of connections. I was hoping someone who knows a thing or two about the movie industry would help me out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you start up your own movie production company? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 07:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the cheapest thing you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 14:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have come to the sad realisation that no one cares about me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 13:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie should be remade? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know hollywood is remaking a lot of movies lately and most of them are pretty bad. I can't believe they are remaking scarface, the mummy, the crow, big trouble in little china and so on. There have been some awful remakes like fantastic 4, ghostbusters, the wicker man, point break and some others. They should really come up with some new ideas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What popular movie haven't you seen yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 15:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never watched the godfather movies, star wars, lord of the rings, blade runner, alien movies, inception, avengers movies, good will hunting, the bourne movies, dirty harry movies, schindler's list, jaws, casablanca, gone with the wind, wizard of oz, citizen kane, the scream movies, the original halloween movies, original nightmare on elm st, footloose, the rocky horror show, priscilla queen of the desert, life of pi, star trek, the karate kid movies, gremlins, the goonies, the lost boys and that is all i can think of. I have seen heaps of movies though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did you find out someone you knew was homosexual and how did it change your relationship with them? (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 05:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie is a must watch but it is a hard sell? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 11:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've watched heaps of movies and try not to recommend them to people because they would think i'm depraved and a total weirdo. I like movies with interesting characters and storylines. I have a weird taste in movies i guess. I like anything from ps i love you to martyrs. The people i know don't like gore and think i am messed up. I try to keep that part of me a secret but on the internet i can talk to people with similar tastes and it makes me feel better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone tell me what this movie is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 14:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has sammo hung in it. Jackie chan's best friend. It is a chinese horror movie if i remember correctly. I only watched a scene where a creepy doll comes alive. I checked wiki but i couldn't find the movie. It was on tv when i was a kid. I was too scared so i didn't watch all of it. I want to watch it now because i like horror movies. I think it was in the late nineties but i'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good revenge movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 14:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like revenge movies because they have meaning and are intriguing. I only know a few revenge movies. The long kiss goodnight, i spit on your grave, american mary, farewell, my love were good. I just want to want to watch more and expand my movie knowledge. Those smart and violent revenge movies, that really build the suspense and are unexpected is what I am looking for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good revenge movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 13:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good revenge movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 12:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which character do you hate with a passion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 10:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who have sex with inanimate objects: when did you find out you like it and how has it affected your life? (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 07:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What cool stuff have you ever found? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 14:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the biggest hypocrite you know and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 13:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which past player do you think deserved a million a year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 08:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddittors who have been to those exclusive high end sex parties: What is it like and how did you become a member? (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 05:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What weird stuff do you have sex with? (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 15:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is hotter: monica belluci or elizabeth hurley? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 08:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do your parents or friends do, that is so hypocritical? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 14:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you rather live without technology or sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 13:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you rather live without technology or sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 13:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you know if you have a connection with someone online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 11:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the most inconsistent tennis player? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 11:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What actor/actress should be in a superhero movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When is scott going to get a love interest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 09:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He deserves some love in his life. His devotion to cosima and the clones is really nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spinoff of the tooth fairy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 09:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does no one respect cyril? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 14:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know he is a cocky know it all but he seems like a caring person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the best player not to win grand slam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 09:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if trump and clinton are on the same side? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 08:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it safe to assume dr kieger is a virgin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 05:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know he had an animated girlfriend but he is always in his lab and we never see him out on dates or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it safe to assume that dr krieger is a virgin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 05:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you witness, that restored your faith in humanity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 12:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How could dan just end his friendship with vanessa, after everything they have been through? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spin off of brian moser, hannah mckay, doakes, daniel vogel, isaak sirko, special agent matthews, laguerta or lundy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does Tracy look like Lily? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 14:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which celebrity rips off their fans and please explain why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 08:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who was the creepiest person you have ever known and what did they do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 16:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you know if you are homosexual? (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 10:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which player has the hottest partner? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 05:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the best player not to play representative football or win a premiership? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 08:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you spice up your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 08:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is hotter: raquel welch or sophia loren? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 07:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is hotter: sandra bullock or jennifer lopez? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 07:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which celebrity has a hotter sister? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 16:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your horror roommate story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 14:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best gangster movie that not a lot of people know about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What don't people care about but they should? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 14:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What always makes you happy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 14:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vigilantes of reddit: when did you start taking justice in your own hands and how has it affected your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 08:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which celebrity are you weirdly attracted to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 14:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the seediest person you have ever met? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 07:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was unexpectedly good that you thought was crap? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 04:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When have you been certain that someone was doing something illegal and what did you do about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 14:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the opinion on the women's league? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 14:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which player had so much potential to be one of the best but threw it all away? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 05:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is semi radradra going to the broncos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 14:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stalkers of reddit: when did it all begin and how has it affected your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 06:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your favourite show growing up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 15:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are the hottest actresses? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 15:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the unspoken rules of meeting celebs in public? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 11:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which celeb would be an awesome rapper but they are too clean cut? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 09:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who were adopted: when did you find out and how has it affected your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 04:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie doesn't make sense even after watching it a few times? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 10:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] Lana Del Rey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 15:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do you think raped corey haim? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 15:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the biggest rip off out there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 11:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What shouldn't you eat but everyone eats it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 15:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you do, that was so stupid that you can't believe you did it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 13:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did you totally lose it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 08:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Necrophiliacs of reddit: when did you find out you were interested in that kink/fetish and how has it affected your life? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 16:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who was the hottest actress on nip tuck? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 15:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes a man/woman cute and what makes them hot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 06:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What scares you but everyone thinks is normal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 16:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you use gofundme effectively? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 07:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your crazy craigslist story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 14:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who have you met that was pure evil? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 14:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are the hottest horror actresses? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 14:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did you have a violent outburst? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 06:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your crazy burglar stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 15:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the craziest way you have met someone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 09:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which celeb is so messed up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 15:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do you think is alive but everyone thinks is dead? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 09:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do you buy so much clothes, shoes and accessories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 07:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the pros and cons of being a nurse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 05:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the easiest decent paying jobs, you could get without a degree? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 15:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who have you had sex with, that you immediately regretted and why? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 16:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddittors who have had cosmetic surgery: why did you have surgery and how has it affected your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 07:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What advice do you have for people going under the knife? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 16:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are the hottest swimmers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 07:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are the hottest female athletes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 07:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some cheap and easy vegetarian dishes to make? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 15:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some cheap and easy seafood dishes to make? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 15:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which celebrity gets the most action? (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 12:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the biggest womaniser or the female equivalent in hollywood? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 16:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you sell old clothes and stuff at a decent price? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 13:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most evil act you have ever witnessed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 14:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which celebrity have you met, that you thought were mean but they were nice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 05:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you get celebrities to reply to you online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 16:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which actors/actresses should work together in a movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 06:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swingers of reddit: what is it like and how did you get into it? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 11:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is the weirdest place you met someone special and please elaborate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 08:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When have you turned the table on a robber? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 11:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie has actors/actresses you don't like in it, but it turned out to be a solid movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 08:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddittors who have tattoos of celebrities: why did you get it and how has it affected your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 11:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do you hold a grudge against and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 07:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddittors who collect autographs: what is the coolest autograph in your collection? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 16:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best celebrity feud ever? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 09:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddittors with extremely religious parents: what is it like and how has it affected your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 14:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who was the hottest bond woman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 16:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something that is surprisingly cheap but it seems like it should be more expensive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 08:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most random thing, you bought online by accident? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 08:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When have you witnessed sexual harassment at your workplace and what happened? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 05:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is you celebrity obsession? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 06:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your weird job interview stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 17:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What random thing should everyone buy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 16:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do you think is attractive even though they have gone off the rails? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 05:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is weirdest thing you've seen on recorded film? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 14:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most random thing you own? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 14:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What good cheap stuff is on ebay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 10:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should we collect, that will be a good investment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 05:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where would a guy find a sugar mama? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 11:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What exclusive club are you a part of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 09:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What secret club or society are you a part of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 05:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your number one rule to surviving in a post apocalyptic world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 15:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is hard to believe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 15:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which celebrity do you love but you are not sure why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 09:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which movie did you watch with your parents, had unexpected sex scenes and nudity, and how awkward was it? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 08:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What turns you on? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 07:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What weird stuff do you do in the shower? [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 06:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your weird skill? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 15:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddittors who work in the casino: any crazy stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 14:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debt collectors of reddit: what are some of your crazy stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 10:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which urban legend freaks you out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 15:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who like to cross dress: when did you know you were different and how has it affected your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 04:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favourite gory movie and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 16:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who was the hottest actress on Weeds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who have dated pornstars: what was it like? (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 14:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the most hypocritical person, you have ever met and what are they like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 11:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your horror public transport stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 07:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you do if someone you trusted, betrayed you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 14:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What weird stuff have you seen at concerts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 23:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good virus free online games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 07:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the weirdest way you became friends with someone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 08:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When have you seen someone with so much potential, throw their life away? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 11:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys who have donated sperm: What is it like, how has it affected your life and have you been in contact with your offsprings? (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 04:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
