<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6945</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 00:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree not because I think it's going to be bad, but because everyone has HUGE expectations for it that are seemingly unreachable. I'm going to buy and play the shit out of it either way, but I'm definitely going to avoid any discussions as soon as it comes out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 22:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burn it to the Ground by Nickelback was actually written for the St Louis Rams. 

http://youtu.be/iSf_cs4-E-I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 16:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't watch my porn in a cinema though. 

Although...I sure would like to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 16:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh if anything I would put a comma in between with and with. Taking one away doesn't sound right. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 16:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not him but I can only assume he's been gaming for a long time. I think DOS was a system or computer for gaming IIRC. MS-DOS?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 14:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao it's all good man. I don't think it'll NEVER be broken. There's always a chance. But I think this record along with Emmitt Smiths career rushing yards record will never be broken (see my post) and Jerry Rices career receiving yards record (just on pure obscenity) simply because it take more than skill to break career records. If I'm sounding incoherent it's because I've been up for about 28 hours or so. So. Yeah. I should get off Reddit. 

EDIT: I listed running backs that I feel are the focal point of the offense. Charles and Peterson (Foster when he's healthy) are the only BIG names I could think of. Gurley might end up being the whole offense in Los Angeles, but it's only been one season so I want to wait a bit. I like what I've seen though. He's definitely going to be a good player.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 13:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah so I never ended up going to bed but basically the reason I think it'll never be broken is two things:

1) Running backs don't last very long. The average length of a running backs career is only 3.11 years. There's a lot of wear and tear involved in the position. Now I get that there are some running backs that have long steady careers such as Steven Jackson and Frank Gore that just make it over 10k yards (and then you have the superstars like LDT or AD that go above and beyond). LDT finished his career 5th in rushing (13,684) and AD is currently 17th (11,675). AD is 30 and is showing no signs of slowing down anytime soon, he seems like his body can take the punishment. Let's say he doesn't slow down. He had 1,485 yards this year and led the league. Even if he gets 1,485 yards every year until he hypothetically breaks the record he would need to keep up that pace or better for over four seasons. That is highly unlikely. However, in my opinion if anyone can do it its AD. 

2) Running backs aren't really the focal point of the offense anymore. I did a bit of research and found that the number of 1,000 yard rushers has fallen off since 2005, along with the season high:

2005: 16 1,000 yard rushers. Shaun Alexander led the league with a whopping 1,880. 

2010: 17 1,000 yard rushers. Arian Foster led the league with 1,616 yards. 

Now that doesn't seem too bad. It really isn't honestly, but when considering the 2005 season had three backs that out gained Fosters yards in 2010 it shows that there is either a drop off in use, talent or possibly even luck. 

But when you look at this season it becomes clear. 

2015: ONLY 7 1,000 yard rushers. Adrian Peterson led the league with 1,485 yards. Not only is 1,485 yards another drop off but losing ten 1,000 yard rushers in five years is crazy. 

Now in 2010 only Foster out gained ADs total from this past year, but in 2005 had five rushers that out gained him. 

The pure running back is on a decline, I don't think it's dying but I think it's stagnant for now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 12:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bell isn't the focal point of his offense. 

Gurley literally just finished his rookie year, let's give him a bit before we think he breaks Barry's record. 

I really don't know who Adams is off the top of my head. 

I'm not even going to comment on Ingram. 

Johnson. Which Johnson? Chris is too old to handle the work load and I don't see David doing it either. 

I should have phrased my comment better. I meant to put Generational/Hall of Fame RB (AD, LDT, Barry, Sweetness, Faulk, or Smith) but decided not to because IIRC Demarco Murray came close to breaking the record in the 2014 season. I think he had 7 straight and he isn't even a top 5 running back in the league, he just so happened to fit perfectly with Dallas' gameplan last year and played way better than expected. He's definitely not a generational talent or top 3 back, if he was he wouldn't have laid an egg this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 10:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/60fpsporn because be honest, that's all we ever watch anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 10:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Petrucci from Dream Theater. Everything he plays is magical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 10:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emmitt Smiths career rushing yards record.

I'm getting ready to go to bed so I'll be back to explain why when I wake up in the morning. 

Edit: Yeah so I never ended up going to bed but basically the reason I think it'll never be broken is two things:

1) Running backs don't last very long. The average length of a running backs career is only 3.11 years. There's a lot of wear and tear involved in the position. Now I get that there are some running backs that have long steady careers such as Steven Jackson and Frank Gore that just make it over 10k yards (and then you have the superstars like LDT or AD that go above and beyond). LDT finished his career 5th in rushing (13,684) and AD is currently 17th (11,675). AD is 30 and is showing no signs of slowing down anytime soon, he seems like his body can take the punishment. Let's say he doesn't slow down. He had 1,485 yards this year and led the league. Even if he gets 1,485 yards every year until he hypothetically breaks the record he would need to keep up that pace or better for over four seasons. That is highly unlikely. However, in my opinion if anyone can do it its AD. 

2) Running backs aren't really the focal point of the offense anymore. I did a bit of research and found that the number of 1,000 yard rushers has fallen off since 2005, along with the season high:

2005: 16 1,000 yard rushers. Shaun Alexander led the league with a whopping 1,880. 

2010: 17 1,000 yard rushers. Arian Foster led the league with 1,616 yards. 

Now that doesn't seem too bad. It really isn't honestly, but when considering the 2005 season had three backs that out gained Fosters yards in 2010 it shows that there is either a drop off in use, talent or possibly even luck. 

But when you look at this season it becomes clear. 

2015: ONLY 7 1,000 yard rushers. Adrian Peterson led the league with 1,485 yards. Not only is 1,485 yards another drop off but losing ten 1,000 yard rushers in five years is crazy. 

Now in 2010 only Foster out gained ADs total from this past year, but in 2005 had five rushers that out gained him. 

The pure running back is on a decline, I don't think it's dying but I think it's stagnant for now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 10:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially when you consider how running the ball isn't really the focal point of the offense anymore (yeah there's still AD, Foster and Charles), it's going to take IMO a combination of: a top 3 (possibly top 1) RB, a really good Oline and some luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 10:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit that's impressive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 10:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dude hangs dong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 22:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Care to explain why? :p  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 20:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all good. It should be one of the first ratings you can scout. Next to Overall and Awareness and such.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 09:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you play as a coach or an owner you can scout players and two of the ratings you can scout are intangibles and physical rather than speed or catching or whatever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 04:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would LOVE to get Shaq Lawson in the first. After the NC game he looks like the best LB in the class.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 04:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play madden 15 all the time and can give my two cents. I just drafted a WR in th 5th out of Harvard and he was an 83 OVR, highest rating for a WR out of everyone else drafted. 

Basically, when scouting, ONLY scout Intangibles and Physical. If a player has an A in one and an A or B in another, he's gonna be a superstar. If he has two Bs he's gonna be good. Has a B and a C he's going to be decent but could also be a wild card, I've drafted a B/C player and had him start as an 80 which is really good for a rookie. Two C's and your looking at a little work but not too much. And anything worse than that I don't even bother drafting. 

I don't have to worry about the cap and resigning guys as much as much because I can keep drafting guys to replace them. After his first year the 83 WR I drafted is already an 89. Evince Powers is his name. 

(I'm pretty sure it's all random in 15 though so the names don't matter)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 11:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 years old. First grade. For Christmas I got a teal gameboy color with Pokemon Red and Yellow. And then my cousin got Crystal and gave me his copy of Silver. Been hooked ever since. I've beaten one game from each generation minus Gen IV. Currently running through Black 2 again, having a fun time. :) 

EDIT: Teal not Real  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 12:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Rangers winning the cup wouldn't be THAT bad. If the Blackhawks win it again I'll be upset.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 23:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want to see? 

Cards v Chiefs

Don't want to see?

Anything with the Panthers or Broncos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 01:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rob and Glenn have both stated that the original title of the show was "Jerks." Then they went to "Its Always Sunny in TV." They got the inspiration for the title from a song by a-ha. Source: iMDB.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 01:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did this actually happen? I'm dying lmao  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 13:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Drew Bledsoe Pro Bowl jersey and that confused a few of the guys I went to school with. My dad has a Darren Woodson jersey and one of his friends thought that it was a Charles Woodson jersey but custom made for Dallas, which is dumb because they didn't even wear the same number.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 07:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yeah man if you're gonna ride in the back of this thing you gotta do it with your mouth closed." 

Lmao literally just watched that episode. On the wedding massacre now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 15:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Endboss by Marteria. Or anything off of the album that song is on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 10:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. It's honestly hard to tell who's who.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently performed a cold water extraction, have a few questions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 23:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So last night I performed the extraction shown in this post 

https://www.reddit.com/r/LSA/comments/ynwbv/simple_nausea_free_lsa_extraction_technique/

I have a few questions:

1) Do I have to take it right away? I plan on saving it for the National Championship game next Monday and I'm worried it won't be as potent.

2) Adding on to that, will the lemon juice affect the product in any way? As far as affecting the potency.

3) Can I mix LSA with other psychedelics? Or is it a waste of one or the other. (I was thinking of mixing it with DXM)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 10:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but it's the Browns so it cancels out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every player on every team over the age of 30 is on their prime, who are the best teams and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 10:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a thought I had earlier. I was thinking about Woodsons retirement and other great players that are either way out of there prime (Fjax, Stevem Jackson, Andre Johnson,  Wilkfork, Jared Allen and the like. So what do you think happen if I'll those players (and any others you choose to add were playing at  ability of their prime?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 22:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wanna go down to the quad later?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 22:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember you! You're mello Mike! 

'Sup mello </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 04:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you friend 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 04:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was kind of like mushrooms almost. My body felt like it was vibrating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 04:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The extra stuff was just because. The morning glorys are a very nice happy buzz. I only took 250 seeds. A lot of people 600 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 04:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's going very very well. It's my first time doing these and it's very nice. LSA and LSD rather. I've been just I'm. I did a method I read on Erowid where the OP ground the seeds up and mixed them with water to make a paste and then took it sublingual lt. So I did that from 7-745 and I've been feeling great. I started really feeling the effects at around 8.  around 830 I smoked a bowl and at around 9pp I railed 10 OxyCodone. My sister bought me The Last of Us Remastered and I've just been grinding through it. I have headphones on and the game makes me feel like I'm really Joel. I love the last of us 

Edit. 10mg OxyCodone not 10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 23:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 23:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if I have a coffee grinder. Would a mortar and pestle work fine?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gonna try to trip on Morning Glory seeds tonight, just have a few questions on managing the nausea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 22:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been doing a bit of research on here and on Erowid the past few days on LSA and Morning Glory seeds. People say the trip is incredible but the nausea is similar to vertigo or food poisoning. 

What do you recommend I take to keep that from happening? I have Omeprazole, TUMs, Pepto and a little bit of weed. 

Will these be enough to keep me from feeling like shit? 

Also, would LSA mix well with weed? How about opiates? 

I'm really eager to try these out, and input is appreciated! Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. But my uncle is a big Skins fan and I like to see him happy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 21:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the NFC: Carolina, Arizona, Seattle, Minnesota, Green Bay. 

For the AFC: New England, Cincinatti, Kansas City, the Jets, Houston.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 04:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pillars of Eternity. 

Final Fantasy 7 but it was my 8th time so I'm not sure if it counts. 

Gears of War 1 Remaster Campaign. 

All of the Master Chief Collection campaigns. 

REmake HD.

There's probably a few more but those ones are the ones I remember of the top of my head.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 09:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "At the end of the day." Sounds like it was pulled straight from an 80s sports movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 09:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd honestly love to see it happen. The 2011 and 2007 runs by the Giants were fucking great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 15:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That only works on goats...and after badger attacks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 03:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No chance. A lot of people talk about how blessed we've been post 2000 with the QBs we've been able to see play (Manning, Brady, Rodgers, Brees) but I think we're also blessed to see the TEs as well Tony G, Gates, Witten and Gronk (if he stays relatively healthy the rest of his career) are probably all in the top 10 tight ends to ever play the game. Hell, I'd go as far as to say that they're all in the top five, with the 5th spot going to Sharpe. Gates is definitely in the Hall. Unless he kills someone before his induction. Twice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 23:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romo is on the IR? Man, stick a fork in us, no playoffs now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 11:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This actually happened to me when I was younger, except with PS3 and 360. I asked for a 360, got a PS3 instead. I was...upset? I wasn't satisfied that's for sure. What I did was just suck it up. I got a few sports games, and saved up for a 360 and got it a few months down the road. Everybody wins. I have both next gen consoles and my PC currently. PS4 is for Bloodborne and Madden. Xbone is for Witcher 3, Forza and Gears, and my PC is for cRPGS and old games. If suggest you do something like that. I prefer third person RPGs on console so I might be a bit different. Good luck friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 21:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dishonored 2, easily. The first is still one of my favorites. I think I do a ghost run every other month.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 11:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scratch that.

Ancient Secrets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 11:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Final Fantasy 7

Secrets of the Ancients.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 10:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happens to me and my friend sporadically. Usually we either look it up on our phones or just remember what the word was eg Will, Dexterity, Draining etc. and look it up in the in game encyclopedia thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 09:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put da team on his back doe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 09:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that the only reason the Cowboys exist is because the guy that created them held a copyright or a patent or something for the Redskins fight song and wouldn't let them use the song unless he let the Cowboys become a team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 08:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One that I've been hearing as of late is that Dez is overrated. "Oh, but Pamela, he's one of the highest paid receivers and he hasn't done jack this year." Okay. He fucked up his foot in the beginning of the season, came back before it was 100% healed and got the ball thrown to him by Brandon Weeden and Matt Cassel. Yeah, I realize he hasn't done great this season, but people are ignoring the fact that when he got paid he was leading the league in TDs since he started playing. "Oh, well touchdowns don't matter as much as yards." And to that I say fuck off. If you would rather have a guy get 1500 yards and 5 TDs over a guy getting 1000 yards and 15 TDs you can be my guest, I'll take the extra points any day of the week. It would make since if the passing attack was all that Dallas has, but ever since I've been a cowboys fan it seems like it's short passes and rushing to get down the field and passing to score the points. Sure, Dez isn't the best receiver in the league, but he's worth the money and easily one of the best playmakers. Now if you'll excuse me I'm going to go wait until April 28th.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 21:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put about 15 hours in the first and 10 in the second. The stories in both are really really really good but the combat was the big thing that made me put it down. It feels like an MMO, not to say it isn't great, but I got bored of the combat after a while. I'd say give it a shot. Both games pick up fast after the first hour or so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 21:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Go fuck yourself Meghan. :'(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 05:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say it was obvious, but that's why I picked them to win that game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 23:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad says not to worry about the horrible season because at least now we'll have a good first round pick, but I'm worried that it's going to be a terrible pick in typical Cowboys fashion (Morris Claiborne). Granted we've hit a decent amount of solid picks (Smith, Martin, Frederick, Jones) it makes me feel like we're due for a bust.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 21:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I've heard. Thanks for the warning. Just saved me $60.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 21:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why, you're welcome!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 03:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played through this a few months ago. It was pretty fun. Doesn't hold your hand at all which is really nice. I'd recommend it to anyone with NV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 02:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna start trying that then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 22:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not exactly sure. If GTAV gets low enough I'll probably pick it up, it'll be the third system I've bought it for but it'll be worth it I think. I'm just worried how it'll run on my computer. 

Other than that, maybe MGSV, anyone know if the port for that was decent? 

I kind of want more RPGs, if Scholar of the First Sin is cheap enough I'll probably get that too. Realistically I'll just keep playing Pillars of Eternity either way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 21:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was worth a play through. I beat it once, uninstalled and haven't looked back. It feels like Frictional has lost their mojo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 21:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you taking yours? And how much? I've been taking about 8 grams and mixing it with my protein shake but I feel like it's a bit inconsistent. Like it isn't as potent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 21:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm staying away from this one until there's a price drop. It's really fun, don't get me wrong. But before everybody and their mother asks me why, here's my answer:

I don't like multiplayer anymore. I'm burnt out on it. Shit, that's all I've ever really played was MP shooters. I started with R6 Vegas actually. Then CoD and BF and then TF2 and then CSGO and I'm just done. I'm not confident I'd get my money's worth. I get frustrated easily and am always playing three or four games at once and I wouldn't have time to actually learn and get better...which would then lead to me getting more frustrated. Tis a vicious cycle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 21:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy friend! I was skeptical at first but Kratom is pretty legit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 21:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to get some shrooms for NYE, then getting MDA for a party on the second. Until then? Just gonna chill and blaze. Might get some Xanax and Hyrdos, not sure yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 14:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you explore every area thoroughly and do as many side quests as you can you can get the gear early. My highest level character is only level 4. I literally just got to defiance bay. And as far as chants I prefer come soft winds, some thing else, come soft winds. I usually just have his chants set to AI though. I mostly manage Aloth, Durance and my monk with my rogue and Eder on AI and Kana 50% control 50% AI.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 14:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Weapon and Shield talent
- Resolution (for draining) and a Fine Large shield (12 def -8 acc)
- Fine Mail Armor iirc
- cape of Deflection
- minor ring of protection
- potions and food for endurance boost

You can also swap the cape of deflection for a necklace with the max endurance boost, I've done that before and it's worked fine. I should let you know that I use him as a summoner, so by the time he gets a phantom or the skeletons off most of the heat is taken off of him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 14:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer running Kana as an offtank simply because he can chant while he attacks where durance has to cast-attack-cast-attack. I'm sure there's a way for it to work with Durance but I've found its better with Kana.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 11:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Al Michaels, Jim Nantz and Gruden.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 09:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really liked the first three episodes, really didn't like the Tweek X Craig one, and thought the rest of them were ok. 

Best running gag was either Shi Tpa Town or Caitlyn Jenner, the whole ad thing was a bit annoying. 

Rating? Low tier. Probably not gonna watch some of these episodes again. 

I liked the continuity last year but now it's kind of meh. I really just didn't like the plot this year. 

Season 20? I'd like little to no continuity, but I don't see that happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 05:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd try and hire an adventurer to be a tank or build kana to be an offtank. It seems like you need more on the front line, if you get another tank it'll help take pressure off of Durance and Kana too because you're gonna want those guys to most if not all of the fight. 

EDIT: I saw you want more damage, I'd hire a rogue if you're confident that your frontline can hold mobs back long enough. I have a rogue just for ranged weapons and it's working out pretty well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 00:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most if not all HoF running backs. Marino, Joe Cool, and Steve Young would be really good. LT and Derrick Thomas. Jerry Rice, Michael Irvin and I want to say Largent but I haven't really seen much of his play. Lou Groza and Ray Guy would probably still be great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 03:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see:

Pillars of Eternity: HOLY SHIT THIS GAME! It's the first cRPG I've ever played and it is already one of my favorite games ever. I bought it during the last steam sale when it was only $23 and I've already put in 85 hours (while working 50-60 hours a week). The combat is fun but very tough to get used to, the characters and the storyline are amazing and the side quests OH MY GOD the side quests are seemingly endless. I finished my first run at 75 hours and did about 20 side quests, my second play through is only 10 hours deep and I've found 7 other side quests in the first act alone that I never found before! I don't have many complaints, I know the game isn't perfect, but it's pretty close in my opinion. If you've had any thoughts of getting this game, DO IT! You won't regret it. And this is coming from a guy that really only plays Madden :p

Wolfenstein The New Order: This game is just badass. Idk why it took me so long to play it, it's been in my steam library for a few months. Last week I decided to boot it up and I've been having a blast. Just mindless nazi killing. It's a good blend of classic Wolfenstein and modern FPS. 

Forza 6: My first racing game since Gran Turismo 3, and I'm having fun. The graphics are really nice and the dynamic driver AI is very cool. Need to play more honestly. 

Borderlands Handsome Collection: I've only just started BL2 but it's uh, alright I guess. I think I'm just burnt out on Borderlands. And it just seems like they tried too hard? Maybe? I really don't know. It just isn't gripping me like the first one did. The gunplay and the mechanics are great and it's more challenging than the first one, but I feel like something is missing. 

I just picked up Final Fantasy Type-0 today and I'm eager to play that as well. Happy gaming all!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 22:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not extremely experienced, I've only gone through the game once and I'm still learning but I've been using Kana as a summoner for both of my playthroughs and its working pretty well. It doesn't seem like it works much in the beginning but when he gets the wurm summon it starts being helpful. Even the skeleton summon helps out because of the chance of distracting enemies and the damage they can do actually adds up. Once you get the ogre and drake summons its game over. If you're gonna be creating you're own I would advise in high constitution and dexterity so he can last long enough in fights to get all of his summons off quickly. Again, a more experienced player would probably help more but that's what I've found works. Good luck! It's a really fun dynamic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 19:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coach: Jim Harbaugh

Owner: Packers fans

5: Watt, T. Smith, L.Bell, D. Carr, OBJ. 

EDIT: OBJ, not Dez.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 18:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright then, how many hard boiled eggs will ya eat?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 04:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For someone looking to get into Dwarf Fortress, what would you recommend they do to learn the game? I've heard it's extremely complex but massively fun and even addicting once one figures the game out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 20:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely RPGs. My first one was Fallout 2. I think the one that got me hooked though was definitely FF7. Right now I'm back on the cRPG grind with Pillars of Eternity. It's one of the best games I've played in years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I accidentally posted it before added the link. It's edited now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I accidentally posted it before added the link. It's edited now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I accidentally posted it before added the link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello all, just had a quick question about buying jerseys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, as you can see from my flair, my favorite team is the Cowboys, unfortunately I can't have two teams otherwise I would have it set to Cowboys/Raiders. For Christmas this year I am looking to get a jersey for my favorite defensive player of all time: Charles Woodson. Now, I also wanted to eventually get a jersey of one of my favorite Cowboys players, Darren Woodson. I figured it would be cool to represent both of these all time great safeties with one jersey. I've scoured google and other forums looking for a solution but cam away with nothing. Would anybody on r/NFL know if this is possible? If not it isn't too much of a problem. Thanks in advance everyone, and to the mods, if I violated any rules please let me know. 

EDIT: I'm looking to get a jersey similar to this one:

http://imgur.com/8yROVNZ

But replace Manning with Woodson and have it half Dallas half Oakland. 

I realize they aren't the same player , Bt they have the same last name and I thought it'd be pretty cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 18:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got me, I'm being completely sarcastic. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question for experienced users </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 05:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all. I just have a few questions to ask you. And if there is a post on the sidebar or a popular post that can answer these for me It'd be greatly appreciated. 

This past weekend I ordered a starter kit of Kratom, I'll post the link if asked but I'm not sure if it'll help that much. 

First, a bit of a backstory. I first heard of Kratom while lurking on r/Drugs and started lurking here as well and I became interested. I'm an on and off user of Oxy and other painkillers and I want to try Kratom because I've read it gives the same effects and is safer. So enough about me. On to the questions. 

1) What should my dosages start as? I ask because I worry that if I start too low I wouldn't end up feeling anything and if I go to high I would end up having a bad time. Normally I would rail 2 oxy 10mgs a day if that gives any help as far as my recommended starter dose. 

2) What should I exactly be expecting from the buzz/high of Kratom. 

3) How should I go about doing it? I've read that some people just mix it with juice or even use a shaker bottle to mix it with other beverages. I dont really want to try and make tea off the bat because I fear my roommates would end up drinking some without expecting what would happen. 

That's about it really, if i broke any subreddit rules or could have gone deeeper into the sidebar posts just let me know and I'll delete this post.

Again, thanks for any and all advice. I'm eager to experience this product.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 04:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that seals it for me. OBJ is on his way to being a top receiver in the league for years to come. Even though he's on the Giants, I'm really excited to see how his career unfolds. Hell of a player and really fun to watch. 

For the record, I'm being 100% serious. I don't want any comments assuming I'm being sarcastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 19:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first jersey was a Rocket Ismail jersey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 04:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty satisfied with Gamepad support. I use an Xbox One Elite controller and it is phenomenal. The games that don't offer support that I play I wouldn't use a pad for even if I could so it's not a problem for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 10:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a Bucs fan but one of my co workers is. He's satisfied with Lovie. And from what I've seen this year (not as much to have a strong case for this opinion)  but to me the team seems to trust him more. And you can tell that between this season and last season that he has the love of his players. And the Bucs post game locker room videos are some of my favorites to watch. I'm trying to watch their games whenever I can, it seems like they've definitely progressed over last year. They're gonna be a fun team to watch for the rest of this season and the next few seasons to come.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 00:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dads a Cowboys fan. So I'm a Cowboys fan. Second team is the Raiders because that was my Grandfathers favorite team and he passed away this September. He didn't get to see AC/DC light it up this year. :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 23:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does BDD stand for?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 18:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize to all of the other people enjoying this single player RPG that I use the console. I didn't realize it affected other players. 

~ "ninjacapo" disable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 17:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My personal Pros and Cons:

Pros: 

It's fallout, my favorite games series. 
Weapon and armor modding. 
Companions and their quests are a lot better IMO 
Legendary enemies weapons and armor are cool
I really like the side quests. 

Neutral:

Base building, I don't use it so I have no opinion. 
The perk tree is hit or miss, it's okay. 
The new armor system is okay as well, just tough to get used to I guess. 

Cons:

Main story is abysmal. I struggled to really care about anybody in the Commonwealth. I sided with the Institute just because they seem like the most evil faction and my first character in a Fallout game is usually evil. 
Dialogue choices kind of suck. 
It's extremely hard to create an evil character, and there seems to be a lack of choice when it comes to the main story. Similar to FO3, I feel like it's too black and white. 

All in all its a great game, I'm level 41 with my main and I'm starting a second guy this weekend. It's a solid 7.5/10, can't wait for DLC. 

EDIT: replaced grey with black and white, got my phrases mixed up. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 17:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My courier and SS would probably get along. They both sided with the technological powerhouses in their respective games (House and Institute), they're both addicted to Chems, love sniping and travel with a red headed badass (Cass and Cait). I feel if they were going to fight however the Courier would crush the SS. He's way more versatile than the Survivor. My survivor sucks at close range combat and my couriers Arsenal prepares him for any and every situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Underrated/Sleeper defensive players? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 14:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm starting a new Fantasy CFM when I get home.  I'm looking to spend my first five picks on offense. Who are some underrated defensive players? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 13:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm basing this off of what my dad and Uncle would (attempt to) do: 

- We trade our entire 2016 draft for AP

- We trade Romo for Manziel 

- We cut Claiborne and sign Champ Bailey

- After Manziels first game we give him an extension through 2025

- I become a Raiders fan
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 15:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at work so I'll go in depth later but I honestly have Lucien taking this 9/10. The 1/10 being if Burke can one shot him with his pistol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 05:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I don't think I've ever had someone refer to one of my answers as great before. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 04:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had:

Georgia

Clemson

Notre Dame

TCU

1/4 isn't bad...right? Right!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 04:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if this has been asked before but where does Hanson rank as an all time kicker? I never really saw him play much but from what I've seen and read he seemed to be pretty good throughout his career.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 06:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jason Brody from Far Cry 3. He's adept at stealth, tracking and using a bow. If he can practically solo a large pirate faction and a military force if say he can 10/10 the Hunger Games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 16:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure it's Thomas Davis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 02:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anybody have Ahmed's number?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 01:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have an iPhone download PlayTube. It's what I use. You can make playlists and play them in the background.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 01:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to agree. I started off with El Camino and Turn Blue, then after a while I dive into their old stuff. I think Brothers is my favorite followed closely by The Big Come Up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
