<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4049</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 06:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Gf used my phone as a flashlight...I still had my phone on /r/nsfw...she's my ex-gf now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 06:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gone through this before and the way I gained confidence was just by talking to people; men and women. But I didnt pick the women that I liked because I knew I wouldn't even be confident enough to speak one word to them. Talking with people gained my confidence but that doesn't mean I still didn't get nervous. Women notice confidence in a guy by the way he looks, his posture, eye contact and the way he talks. So when I asked a girl out, I dressed casually but made sure I stood out from the crowd, walked up to her with my back straight, I made eye contact with her and asked, "Hey - im going to -. Do you want to be my date? (This was a girl that I talked to before) Now if it isn't soneone you don't know try to introduce yourself the same way that I asked the girl out, good posture, eye contact, strong voice, and make sure to dress casual, you don't need expensive clothing but you do need clothing that isn't torn or dirty. I hope this helped a bit.

Also make sure to have a good hygiene, you don't want to smell bad when asking a girl out.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 04:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. Looking forward to hearing an update. If you ever get to make one... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 03:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of The Stanley Parable. Good job OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 03:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend read this and started to do th1s t0 m3. Needless to say, im sleeping with the lights on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 03:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im afraid of the dark, especially very old places that are dark...it gives me an uneasy feeling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 20:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a short story and a couple of questions.

My little brother was molested when he was three if I remembered correctly. He was in his father's house when it happened but it wasn't his dad who molested him, it was one of his dad's friends. Apparently, from what I heard from my mom, him and his friends were smoking weed and when my brother's dad fell asleep, one of his friends went upstairs and proceeded to molest him. I don't know all the details. My brother is 14 now and he gets into fights and he yells at everyone, but when someone talks to him about him acting out, he puts his guard up and stays isolated from everyone else. When he does act nice to people, he hates when people give him compliments or give him things and I keep wondering, Does he act like this because of being molested at a young age? Or is he used to being put down because all of the trouble he has caused?

Also, I hope I didnt sound like a jerk to you or to anyone else, I just want to know why he acts the way he does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 02:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not a scumbag, it's just his clothes and hat and the.....smug face. Fuck it. I want to hit him soooo bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 01:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I messed up my comment.....a lot, but I did an Edit 2 just to tell you what it was supposed to look like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 01:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh well, there should be plenty of comparisons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 21:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Danzo is the most influential person.  and that wouldn't of fueled Sasuke's rage to get revenge...which leads me to, like you said, Orochimaru.

Edit: Also, correct me if I got the whole "Without Danzo's orders Itachi wouldn't have gone on a killing spree" comment wrong. I'm a little fuzzy on the details but I'm for certain he is the reason why itachi did what he did.

Edit 2: I kinda fucked up my comment, was originally trying to say, "I think Danzo is the most influential person. Without Danzo's orders, itachi wouldn't have gone on a killing spree and that wouldn't of fueled Sasuke's rage to get revenge....which leads me to your answer Orochimaru. " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 21:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's my #1 funniest fight. But my #3 best fight I've seen from Rock Lee. Any Rock lee fight always reminds me of classic anime fighting.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 20:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you feel about DBZ and Naruto? Do you think they have parallel stories? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 20:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say Rock Lee since he's one of my favorite characters, but I feel like he would always want me to be positive and active all the time and I can't tolerate that shit for too long. So I pick Choji, he seems like an all around good guy that knows how to have a good time.

Edit: if not Choji then Pervy-sage all the way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 20:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a quick question, How important do you think node.js is to web development? I'm an intern working under my godfather and he says it's "very important to the industry" but I never see him use it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 12:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question still stands whether they be heroes or villains. No inconveniences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 12:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think all of us can agree we are all just genuine fans of anime.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 02:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never asked this but....someone please give me a golden shower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 02:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit! I'm always late to these parties! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 01:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 21:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I just meant that the 10th member didn't necessarily need a role. If you look back on thriller bark luffy tried to get a few zombies to join just because they looked cool. Us viewers knew they weren't going to be part of his crew, but seeing as all roles have been filled, getting a 10th member with no role seems logical. Oh and I also knew Kin'emon and Momonosuke were just getting a ride to dressrosa not joining the crew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 04:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 04:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has a lot of great books, but they aren't all that great. Tell me, did you like "Rose Madder", "Cell", and " The Tommyknockers"? Do you think "lisey's story" is a bit dragged out? Because I do. Either way, this is my opinion. If you like all of his books good for you but I think ill stick to what I said earlier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 03:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2012. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 03:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say it's cheap literature.  I would say however that he is a bit overrated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 02:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you expect? That's how they remember you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 02:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope she didn't try to fit that thing in her mouth, she'll get paper cuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 02:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't until I looked down to your chest that I realized you weren't a woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 02:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would send them a calendar that went *passed* December 21, 2012. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 01:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, they already had a calendar that ended on December 21, 2012. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 01:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's suprising, that's the first thing I thought of. Not technology or books. Nope just a big dildo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 22:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get a shamwow guy vibe from you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 17:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Step 4) Get virus there.

Step 5) Die
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 21:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh the reason why he looks like a rogue ninja is just because of the eyebrows and just the face mask. The eyes are fine the eyebrows make him look angry. Either way, the picture looks great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 07:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had to be completely honest. I like the picture. I get this feeling this character would end up being a rogue ninja (just from personal perspective) definitely keep it up you're doing great.

Edit: I also forgot to add that he kind of looks like nagato. And also don't mind the insults just keep doing what you do, just make sure to draw it a little smaller so viewers like me could see everything, other than that good job :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 06:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 03:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See I had problems we my friend about this. Just tell him to try to watch more and eventually he'll get into it. Basically what I'm trying to say is dont jump the gun on Op. If you do then I would pick luffy's fight with Arlong it's a good fight and it doesn't reveal to many things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 02:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a problem with me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 02:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ok I didn't remember that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 02:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watch OP. Just because I don't remember EVERY episodes details doesn't mean I don't watch OP. Read my comments. I was part of the discussion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 01:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont really think all of his crew needs to have specific role. I mean take thriller bark arc for example or punk hazard arc luffy just picked random people that looked cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 22:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he even meet her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 22:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or ace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 22:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I was thinking law, but jinbei is a fishman so I wouldn't expect him to fall for her. So I guess there is only a few people that can resist her temptations. Also I liked the fact luffy was the only person to make Boa....horny? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 22:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who else didn't fall in love besides Zoro and Luffy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 22:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I think he did stab himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 22:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's staring into my soul...I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 22:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anal sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 21:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I NEED JUST A LITTLE MORE AND THAT'S IT...I SWEAR! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 21:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit...I think so? Are you talking about the vice admiral with the Mohawk like I am? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
