<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4153</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 03:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comfort, complacency, and function don't exactly equal love. You can be a good partner to some one and not love them the way that you deserve. They deserve genuine love and if you can't provide that then maybe it's time to change things up despite the difficulty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 03:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hobbies, maybe airsoft in cool countries like Russia and Japan. Make friends hiking and back packing through cool areas of washington and canada. Hunting trips through mexico and oregon. Maybe build up a high end pc and play the stuff I can't afford on the VR spectrum  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 03:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non Playable Characters in video games are where your soul goes if your a piece of shit. Imagine dying a 40 year old man and being damned to GTAV prostitute duty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What's something that you think on a regular basis that's just offensive enough to not share ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 02:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ten bucks saved adds up. Especially to an average sized family and money is tight. Could have bought some kids an ice cream cone or maybe a bargain bin movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure it made their day. Decent sushi is kind of a luxury not a lot of a people can afford.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is nice of you, if they were driving like a douche I would have pitched the thing out my window and headed home after the third or fourth light.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still a good act to randomly show kindness to some one like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Dark for your service, also Yea some times a you get dealt a bad hand at this whole life thing, be glad you're so fortunate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job, I'm sure it meant the world to them. The school systems need all the help they can get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was heading back home and decided to take a scenic highway back because the shorter route was gridlocked with traffic. an SUV had flipped over in some kind of accident and my self and two other cars had stopped to see what had happened. We were the first to call emergency services but the car was smoking and starting to catch. There was only a woman driving but caught on her belt and beaten pretty badly.

One of the guys was fearless and jumped onto the car that was on it's side and was scrambling to get her out. You could barely see the woman in the smoke. He tried to kick in the window, I scrambled and gave him my knife. It had a pike on the handle meant for just the thing, he shattered the window and cut her seat belt. He pulled her out and handed her to me and checked for more injured. I know the other driver has a lot of credit to be given but I still feel proud of that day. Others had stopped and were scared that the car was going to catch on fire and watched. But that other driver and I helped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What is the nicest thing you've ever done for a stranger ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 01:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 18:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blaire Witch, It shat on the key fundamentals of the first one by trying to make everything more xtreme. It was an overall fine scary movie but a shit reboot of the original, Much like Total Recall, World War Z, Ghost Busters, and lets not forget Point Break. Fine C or D grade movies to kill time but awful homages to the original.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst thing you've ever been caught doing ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 23:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 23:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the situation doesn't call for it I agree. But I wont let street walking scum make a victim out of me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 03:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kershaw driver combo, and an old Rat 2. I forget the steel but once you run it under the wet stones properly it holds an edge for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 02:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep the largest knife legally possible in california in my back pocket and sharp. If no gun is present "Hey dude, listen. I've got $200 dollars in my wallet, Let me just give you that I need my ID for work," Deploy knife and cut either or the hands, neck, eye, fore arm, or brandish the knife in a loud manner to get attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 02:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darwinism balancing out the gift of the knowledge the internet provides with addiction. Weeds out the idiots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 02:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found people I could stand to be around. Became comfortable with hobbies that did and did not involve people so that I am comfortable in my own skin and with others. 

And above all else came to the conclusion that not all people that I appreciate want or need to bee in my life. Study acceptable behavior and mimic till a personality sticks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 02:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cubone bone bone, Cubone Cubone Bone. Cubone bone Cubone... Bone Bone Cubone ....  ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 02:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baby sitter, boys will give you a high five when you tell them that your baby sitter showed off boobs and took advantage. But if I was a little girl and she was 17 year old dude I would be a victim. People are untrustworthy monsters and I'm going to make sure my kid keeps me informed.

Guess this doubles as my confession as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 02:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If some one wants to identify as a man or woman or anything in between that I am not aware of. Can we at least draw the line at age and species ? I shouldn't have to respect that you're now a fox, or a 12 year old girl when you were just a 22 year old man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Should people be able to change their age and species identities the way they change their gender ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 02:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What's your favorite tattoo that you wear personally ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What is something you should care about more than you do ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The indifference of good people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother was heavily medicated due to a serious medical condition. We didn't live in the same house hold so for over a year we played with friends Red Dead Redemption on the Xbox360.  

My brother was out of it but still game for another hour or two. We were in the mexican portion of the map and we started saying that Rockstar was playing Return of the Jedi for May 4th at the Blackwater theater on the other side of the map. My brother discounted it but one of my other friends in the party put himself at the theater on the map and without missing a beat started playing the theme over the mic. He hopped on a zebra donkey and we road after him as best as we could XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most humans, until I get to know a person I can't be certain that their intentions are good. Humans are the scariest thing on this rock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 03:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America is doomed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a score somewhere i've lost track of. I've saved and damned my soul so many times that I guess I'll have to face the tally when the time comes. every now and again I'll play in all honesty. and even more honestly little things that are simple to win.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> particles floating in existence before we were made into dad fluids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vote green party. Both republicans and democrats recruited the worst candidates possible to run. I wouldn't be comfortable having either represent my country at the worlds stage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh, I misread. Apologies. But nine times out of ten it's misinformed sheep bahhing at the thunder of mass media. Scare the masses and they'll push you, there's not much you can do to stop it either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, this is kind of one of the only times I've shared this aloud, or publicly I should say. Most of the time it was something I was confident i could do easily. Almost like getting the devil's attention just to tease. But I distinctly remember an occasion where there was a door that closed automatically at school. I bet that I could put both straps of my back pack on and make it to the door handle before it closed completely. I tripped, I was torn up all day and was too embarrassed to tell my mom why.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll come eventually. No need to rush.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said a thing about a dead body. Happy hunting local redditors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Violence is more natural than most would like to admit. Push anyone and they've fight or run. Good thing you maintain your composure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to play a game with my soul when I was little. I'd bounce a ball or do something time sensitive and have to do a task before the time was up or my soul was damned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dig here. There's a pile of rocks near a burnt tree.past the dry river bed. Only about three feet deep. I was tired. 

https://www.google.com/maps/dir/34.7103725,-119.3977246/34.7092999,-119.4004558/@34.733501,-119.4192552,11z </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we all have a touch of that. No one will dislike you more than you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That blows, my heart goes out to you. I hope you find something less harmful to help your situation . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the definition of an "assault weapon" has been broadened to include weapons that flat out don't fit the definition. Laws are passed by idiots that don't know anything about the items they are prohibiting. 

As a Californian it is illegal for me to purchase a bean bag round for my shot gun. A non lethal round that can stop an intruder or hostile individual with a minimal chance of lethally wounding them. But I guess bird shot "wich is essentially metal sand" that can definitely mortally wound an intruder is fair game.  

Laws should be made by people who understand what they're talking about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck no, woman have the dating scene pretty wrapped up. I feel the general population of men get shot down so much in their early dating life rejection feels like an old friend you awkwardly make small talk with. 

A chick taking some initiative has been and always will be awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Large social groups, I hate trying to pretend that I get any kind of substance out of meeting +20 in one place. I forget names and don't really invest enough to really get to know anyone well enough to lay down ground work for any kind of substantial report.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What else might kill you ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously ? or that same odd fleeting suicidal tick you get when you pass by a semi truck or stand near a high ledge ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought an cheap masquerade styled mask at a Halloween shop today. I have a Pancho made out of cammo net made by a friend. I'm going to hang stained burlap from the pancho and glue stained burlap to the mask to create kind of a woods monster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some times I hear my name when no one called, and I imagine people staring at me when they're not. I don't know if it's a common thing but I have to square that thought away all of the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What's the most insane thing that crosses your mind regularly ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rain, I think this drought is making a lot of people appreciate it. It rarely ever gets cold enough here to make the rain uncomfortable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 19:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I close the door every time out of force of habit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 19:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't bring up the fact that other first world countries are in a better standing regarding health, education, and economics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grilled cheese crab sandwiches  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I drive by a large cemetery every day for work. I wonder which loved one will make me dawn the black next from time to time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst thing you've put yourself through for the sake of someone else ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my mac book and non prescription nerd glasses tilt my man bun in such a way that leads me to believe that this is a more ironic way to reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use to hundred to buy us some ingredients for a killer dinner. a feast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ellen Page, I feel like we can work the Lesbian thing down to Bi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend of my father came home early to find his wife on top of a man in their bed. He didn't interrupt them and they didn't notice he was home. We pulled a six shooter out of the garage, put two in her back and four in his face. Called the cops and watched Mr. Rogers on the tube till they showed up. He went quietly. 

I can't cheat because of it, they baby sat me when I was younger and I always thought they were in love. He was a caring, loving man. I was in disbelief.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> frothy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Dip  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20,000 to the American cancer society and the rest towards owning land and property and a solid education. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The internet needs to be hard wired to the brain with a site that is illegal to post misinformation on. No one needs to waste time on school if we already know all of humanities discoveries and base knowledge instinctively. A new species of human geniuses could make or break earth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not my favorite one, but a well used one would be to know whether a person wants a hug, hand shake, fist bump, wave, or head nod as a motion for saying goodbye.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Projected self loathing mostly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once witnessed a man push on a door clearly labeled pull with the bar and everything for a clean two minutes. Used the door next to him and he followed after without a word, didn't seem drunk or anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 06:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> star citizen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 00:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they are the worst, head phones are so cheap and readily available that there is no reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 13:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a number that's large enough to be upset about. I've been put in situations where submitting to police bullshit is the answer. And I did it out of fear for my life, why the hell is that the current meta ? "Officer Porkchops is clearly out of line, but let me keep quiet so he doesn't kill me out of negligence" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 00:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the same way, she's got more psychological strength. She keeps anchored so that I second think driving an idiot into the ground and landing my self in rap sheet. Keeps me goal oriented and successful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 00:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're too content with this mediocrity. If things don't get devastatingly bad we don't change. For what ever reason as a country we are perfectly content being shown up by our first world rivals. Bush was a good start, but I think the US needs another good imbecile to push us over the edge. Once we've checked with reality we can prioritize and become a respectable country again. 

I wont vote for the glorified orange, but I sure hope enough idiots do.  :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 00:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had the time, energy, and was in the mood to get depressed as fuck sifting through the police shootings of innocent civilians. I bet it wouldn't take long for me to find a dozen examples showing otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> student debt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A well prepared cheese cake and as much beans as I can handle before throwing up. After I die some one will need to clean up the mess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha ! yea, there is always one or two racers in a lobby being a cunt on the turns and knocking you from 1st to 14th.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he realized that the people and electoral college would rather choose between two idiots than an actual qualified official. Yeaup, that's what happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is one of the most toxic games you can play if you hate shitty gamers. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Told a cop once that searched me for "suspicion of possession of an illegal substance" while I was in an outdoor seated area of a restaurant with friends. Which by the way, I had none and had given neither the officer nor anyone around me any reason to believe I was in possession of anything illegal.  "Officer brownfield, I'll remember that. Been thinking about buying a pig for a pet, that's what i'll name it. Officer Brownfield," </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go on youtube and type. Cop shoots unarmed civilian. The fact that there are multiple pages of videos proves this point wrong. The fact that those are just the ones captured \on video is depressing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what games ? I have a coworker that is the most rational person you'll ever meet, but if he's loosing at Smite and i give him shit about it. He's visibly angry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up with tempers flaring between my folks. I have a really low tolerance for that kind of thing. I like coming home to a place of peace.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they there regularly ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The system is broken sir, those complaining about Mr. Sanders being a socialist don't realize that the way our country is currently run isn't truly a democracy by definition. This presidency has shown us that the system in place is there not for the people, but for those in power to stay in power.

Donald is just the kind of idiot that can run us right into the ground. From there we can start fresh and rebuild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What is one thing you would change about your SO ? and why ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just out of curiosity, how do you two work ? Or, why ? I should say. Sometimes i look at my gf and I don't understand where the love comes from, are interests and hobbies wouldn't tell you that we're a good fit.

But i've dated others that are more in line with that life style and they didn't work half as well as my current gf.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 00:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> both ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 20:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very true. She's got a nice can of mace that should do fine with similar instructions now. I wouldn't trade her for the world, I've had exes that would make killer battle buddies. But none of them make me as happy as she does. So there in-lies the issue. 

Is your SO aware of how you feel ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 20:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was this prick that hurt my sister in an irreparable way. He got off Scott free due to technicalities so he ran into some bad luck. He did end up getting what was coming to him but not before the car he was driving some how blew four tires at once. The car belonged to his sister, she let him borrow the damn thing on a regular basis. He's the kind of person that wouldn't pay for the damages and from what I can gather she's a decent person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 20:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend and I are pretty good contenders for this. She's a well established administrator at a university. Blonde, clean cut, outgoing, and super friendly. I'm work quality assurance for a shipping company, and spend spare time fixing, selling, and trading airsoft and paintball equipment as a side gig. I'm a lot more rough around the edges, very private with my personal life, and find great joy from bashing faces at metal shows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 20:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet, I've met some northerners in Washington and they were super mellow. I might wait for late fall or early winter, I'm a californian and I miss the snow so bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 20:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a guy is OP in almost every way, I wouldn't trade. But being able to get knocked up and cop-out of progressing your career is kinda cool, and climaxing as a guy is great, but chicks seem to go nuts when you get them going just right. Maybe i'd swap over for a day just to see what this whole vibrator business is about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A solid knife, I've got a four inch back pocket blade that had a built in window smasher, bottle opener, and a fold out screwdriver tool with four Phillip and flat head bits to swap out on the sides. It has saved my ass so many times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
