<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7030</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [A smart Bluetooth rectal thermometer. No more fumbling with awkward wires tracking your core temperature while running.](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/3tkemy/what_is_a_sub100_gadget_that_everyone_needs_but/cx6zr0h/?context=3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a mirror in your back pocket? Cause I wanna fuck you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["If your a racist, I'll attack you with the North." - Abe Lincoln](http://cdn0.dailydot.com/uploaded/images/original/2014/2/16/tumblr_lnh45mh5QM1qdci9xo1_500.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 20:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like they changed their registration after it was impounded. New info as follows: 
INAI MERAH SUPER
IMO:  8669747
MMSI:  457054000
Call Sign:  JVML5
Flag:  Mongolia [MN]
AIS Vessel Type:  Dredger
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 20:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAI WEI GONG 889, current tracking the known historical positions of this vessel (not having much luck, they seem to fly under the radar for obvious reasons). I'm using AIS, if someone else has access to another service (with history) look for lingering vessels at 06.11 S - 112.08 E.

https://www.reddit.com/r/WarshipPorn/comments/26b3rq/plundered_remains_of_the_wreck_of_the_ijn_light/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Welcome Veronica Yeast!, and remember: "If it's a itchin', don't go a scrachin', Get Vagisil instead!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^"Not ^as ^much ^as ^I'll ^'member ^dat ^ass...hmmmp...when ^she ^walked ^be ^like ^two ^moist ^Georgia ^peaches ^wrestlen."

"Kara will be remembered as a kind always giving person to the community..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Open your pop-up history books to page 64. Today we'll be covering slavery in the US. Pulling on the tab makes them pick the cotton." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "MAAAALIIIIAAAAA!!" "Yes daddy?" "What I tell you about dating boys?!" "Sorry daddy, but Baron..." "Baron??? Baron TRUMP?...oh no no no." Que Laugh track, que cheesy 90's family sitcom music, fade to outside panning shot of suburban home, slice in 4th wall breaking cuts of all the main characters in a surprise and smile shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Where do yall keep your scripts?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hey there, I'm an attractive female and I'm speaking to you." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I need an orderly in room 343, Mr. Dadabo is having flashbacks again. He is muttering something about 30 frames per second and the peasants of the console ward." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "These three contestants will compete today on...Jeopardy! And now here is the host of Jeopardy!, Mr. Gilbert Gottfried"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a poorly placed loading door on the second floor. The rail is for keeping idiots from taking a 2 story dive. It's not used a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 09:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was kinda hoping he would have said "Clinton called to concede, I told her "don't worry...I'll make sure they don't put the cuffs on too tight." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 05:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah I'm gonna listen to polls. They were sooo accurate the first time around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This you should help yall visualize exactly what a T-rex-a-roo would look like in the wild.](http://imgur.com/gallery/UF1Kr9p) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hearthstone Stonewalled, hilarious last two cards drawn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 15:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 21:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That guy looks suspiciously like the guy from Lost who was stuck pushing that button thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have been euthanized, not the dog, the reposter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 02:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's supposed to be Chock Full O' Nuts. Folgers? I didn't watch my buddies die in the mud on hill 49 for you to fuck up the coffee brand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes be bold, creative. And when you succeed...we will tax the ever living fuck out of you! No go butterfly, spread your wings. Daddy needs to buy some more bombs to kill brown people with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 06:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I was that guy that paid $39.35 to have an extra person in the delivery room. But since insurance companies like to pay as little as possible the hospital only made $27.55. That is less than the average nurse makes per hour. No wonder the hospital charges to have the extra person there to make sure that your child and wife were safe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had one that traumatized me. Dream started out great. Was getting ready to make sweet sweet love to Julia Roberts. We started making out and her mouth just kept getting bigger and bigger and her teeth were the size of tombstones and I just fell into the abyss that was her mouth the the sound of her signature laugh echoing in the wind rushing by. I woke up in cold sweats. To this day I can't watch a Julia Roberts film or hear her laugh without my hair standing up. TLDR: Traumatized by Julia Robert's mouth dream.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last one in vid is impossible to pass correct? 1x2 square solution and the given set was 3x3 wide in one direction and 2x3 wide in another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 06:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't plan on having children, so fuck it. BURN it to the ground! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real talk time. There is no point. People would figure out the "best" spec and as it rises in popularity everyone that fly's that ship would have nearly the same or identical load out. EVE online, WOW, you name it same pattern of behavior. I'd rather the ships be all the same, and winning factor is teamwork, skill, and timing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afterward we both grabbed our fedoras and hit the town, but not before holding the door open for some m'ladies. They both appreciated our sense of style.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 15:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non fisherman here. Umm where the eyes at?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the heavy lander landing gear...that is not attached to the engine there is no snap point on the foot end..
[Here is the lading strut in the intended usage](http://wiki.kerbalspaceprogram.com/images/thumb/c/c9/LandingStrutNonDeployable.png/300px-LandingStrutNonDeployable.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah Gamma. This is the time my team has won the most quick matches. At Gamma II. If we see the entire enemy team FF on Gamma we send in one heavy or fast ship to fuck with them while we quick cap and move on their base. We have won SOOO MANY matches this way. Gamma is the "shiny" in this game that makes for a great misdirection for a quick cap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Ability: Container Chaff. This ability launches freight containers filled with scrap and explosives. Upon detonation they create a 8000m debris field scrambling all enemy missiles for your team within the sphere of influence. The effect remains for 1 minute and has a 3 minute cool-down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mars totally looks like Hitler](http://imgur.com/gallery/TpLfYPK) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Busta Rhymes would be the best debater of all time. He could get all the facts in and still have enough time left for a zinger and mic drop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 17:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd take a Battlestar Galactica point of view on this. In a world with AI and war do you really want interconnected systems?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 16:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as I get a sex robot between then and now I don't give a shit. Take the Earth. Place is a shithole. I'll move to Mars with Elon and my sexbot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 16:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a time when Kings and Aristocrats alike would save their best cutlery for only the finest guests. It was made from aluminum. The rest ate from gold or silver dinner wear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 22:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.google.com/maps/place/1%C2%B004'23.7%22N+43%C2%B059'04.8%22E/@1.073261,43.9840937,287m/data=!3m2!1e3!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x0:0x0!8m2!3d1.073261!4d43.984662

Perhaps you are looking for this U-boot? It's just south of Barwe on the beach. Consistent with the length of a u-boat at being ~234 feet long, being scuttled the bow and stern would have been blown off accounting for the blunted ends and the slightly short length. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I made It. I am a dead sculpter. My secrets out bitches! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 23:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks took like 10 tries to get to that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yall should check any grassy knolls for shell casings and shit. That bang sounded like McMillan Alias Super Short 308 firing subsonic munitions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [looks just like mine!](http://images.akamai.steamusercontent.com/ugc/258218890828685364/AF46162E76B54471B502819A03FB06B575579BB1/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Re-title post: "HIV cure close after disease brexit's from blood of British man" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Or this?](http://g03.a.alicdn.com/kf/HTB1y4bsIFXXXXcxXVXXq6xXFXXX5/-6-Western-Art-Decor-Copper-Bronze-Sculpture-Persian-cat-Marble-Base-Statue-Figur-.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Like this?](http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-_Et2QjDlJWY/UTlY2bPYFHI/AAAAAAAAZ8Y/PqJF5lGWGe4/s1600/DSC_0019.JPG) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard if you take $10K US dollars in 100 dollar bills, blend it with water and rub it on your skin that it makes you $10K poorer and look like an idiot trying to paper mache themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a fat bird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 00:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would make for one interesting engineering paper to try and prove or disprove if this was possible given the materials/engineering available to humanity. I highly doubt even a latticed carbon fiber lever of appropriate size would be structurally sound enough to be able to move a planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
