<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7582</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, 2 million? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There must be 2 million people in that crowd! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! Let's ban em all!  
*sees Amazon.*  
  
oooh, that's gonna be a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tradition Vapes has done the same thing.  
I placed an order on Jan. 13 through Paypal (thankfully). I e-mailed their customer service directly twice, and twice through paypal over the past 10 days. Haven't heard a peep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Trumps immigration ban threatens health care, in 3 charts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can the Democrats Be as Stubborn as Mitch McConnell? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the same story with The Young Turks. They predicted Trump would win the election much earlier than anyone else, and the predicted accurately exactly how he'd win the election. TYT and Olbermann have gotten a terrible wrap, even from the left, but they've been accurate so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TrumpBeat: Three Lessons From The Travel Ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been watching West Wing for the past 4 months. I like to pretend that President Bartlett is our President so I can sleep at night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..."Dong is the biggest..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vladimir Krull.  
He just sounds like an evil supervillain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I was in the front row, cheering Snoopy on. And I was *hammered* drunk! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump picks Colo. appeals court judge Neil Gorsuch for Supreme Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grand Plans vs. Reality: White House Veterans Recall Their First 100 Days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Immigrants From Banned Nations Live in the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they could also fire her and put someone they want in her place until Sessions is confirmed, but that would never happen...OH SHIT! That. Just. Happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aldous Huxley interview on Brave New World, the changing face of democracy, advertising and the media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Katrina Pierson or Steve Bannon. Or Kelly Anne Conway. I just can't stand her with the smug smile, lying through her teeth with doublespeak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I set up a monthly $15.00 gift after the inauguration. It ain't much, but $15 bucks in individual donations can do a lot of good with enough people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you lie to yourself. He has a TON of support, but that support is not growing, it is shrinking. However, his core is getting more fired up than ever. There is opposition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, now I've seen everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This explains why I hate hiking for long periods of time with both men and women. Huh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say "stay" like they've been active before. Like, ever before.  
We're in deep shit if people don't figure out how to leave their computers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what a real Tea Party looks like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do the people you know understand that most U.S. citizens don't support this "Muslim ban" Trump and Steve Bannon have initiated? How is the mood? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats won the most votes. Why arent they acting like it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget to dry hump is face after stabbing him in the back with an energy sword. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Train Plows Through Trees After Huge Snow Storm in British Columbia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, Trumpettes. We gave him a chance. Now what?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't like this one, I'll suggest another. I bet you just haven't heard enough of his catalog.  
[Bob Dylan - It's Alright Ma (I'm Only Bleeding)]
(https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mYajHZ4QUVM]) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was 3 days away from turning 18, sitting in 1st period calculus when I found out. I distinctly remember a girl in my class asking "what's the world trade center?" We said "twin towers" and she got it. It was a really odd day, no one could focus in class. Most of the classes that day, we just watched the news on television.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. Very true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch planets orbit a star 129 light-years away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Litvinenko inquiry verdict could reignite the Cold War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps trade agenda is on a collision course with his rural voters economic interests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How nuclear war could break out in 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 13:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said it since the day I'm Wide Awake It's Morning/Digital Ash in a Digital Urn came out and I discovered Conor Oberst/Bright Eyes: He is Bob Dylan of our generation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Arrest of a U.S. Spy Working as a Russian Intelligence Officer Could Tell Us a Lot About Trump and Putin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mexico doesn't seem very happy with us either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve "Goebbels" Bannon.  
I always wondered what it would have been like for Germans in 1932. This has to be as close as we could in the U.S. come to knowing what they went through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but *most* of the time, being a dropout shows that a person is *not* a hardworking person, not willing to finish what they started. When I graduated college in 2008 I was told in an interview that's all they (a bank) viewed a degree as, a person's willingness to finish what they start. As for whether it was required to perform the job? Nah. Not really. No, I didn't get the job. They thought I'd leave within 6 months if I could find something better than a teller job. Fun fact, I didn't. Not for another year or so. Good times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R/the_Donald has arrived. They hate facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Sean Spicer said the President believes that because of studies people have sent him. I have to believe that's credible enough evidence of voter fraud. Why would Donald lie or allow himself to be deceived?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's winter? -A Northeasterner begrudgingly relocated to Texas for work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Trump nominated Merrick Garland, as a sign of respect President Obama, I would gain a good bit more respect for Trump. But I don't see that happening. If he nominates his sister or one of her friends, I won't be surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one cares about Tiffany. Especially The Donald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 21:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Better angle](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yxPJgMrjAJ4) from his own channel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the streak began on or just after grocery day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? That's why we're all here, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it would be really irresponsible to have kids right now. In a couple generations food and resources could get awfully tight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 05:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Texas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A semi truck burns about 1 gallon of diesel/hr when idling. If you burned 8+ gallons of gasoline (assuming small 16 gallon tank), something must be wrong with your vehicle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NEA makes up .003% of the budget, to be specific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump reportedly planning to kill National Endowment for the Arts, privatize PBS and NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 01:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, when I was 6-10, Milo and Otis was on of my favorite movies to watch with my little sister. I mean, we still sing "Here comes the dog" when we visit each other and play with our dogs.  
Trump is President, and Milo and Otis were abused/killed to make me laugh as a child. Fuck this planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 01:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ, is that what they mean when they say "no animal was harmed in the making of this film?"  
This video is going to be a game changer in Hollywood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great example of history being written by the winners.  
It'd be interesting to see in 200 years how the history of Crimea is written, if it is shown as being part of Russia the whole time, or if the invasion is documented as it actually went down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Homegrown powdered cheddar. Just add homegrown water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is math. Fucking statisticians and their liberal bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Reference](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=66ZKngvgkU4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So random. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, tit for tit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That Cowboys-Packers Game Was As Great As It Seemed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. That's not true. It's just not, because facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not all Trump supporters are racists, but most racists are Donald Trump supporters. That cannot be denied. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
