<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7668</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 06:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 21! Literally hating life! Because! I! Just! Binged!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 21:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful illustrations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 21:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I totally also wanna be light and cute for my boyfriend too but it makes him sad when he sees me restricting and cooking different meals from him when we used to do pasta nights and steak nights and all sorts of awesome dinners a few times a week. From your posts, your boyfriend sounds supportive of you and like a very caring individual, so I would try to be a little easier on yourself! He loves you no matter what your weight bb 


I hope when I get down to at least 112, I'll just maintain it and eat like a normal person again. I feel Like a "wannarexic" too because I'm EDNOS but too fat to be considered anorexic. I'm at a "healthy weight".. Whatever that means :| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 00:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recipe for the meal pls? It looks great!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 22:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg same with the Halloween costume. I keep thinking how much better I'll look at my UGW and how its motivation to get there before late October so I can look cute in a costume :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 22:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry guys I posted this in a fit of rage when my skinny friend was telling me she just downed almost a whole pizza. I just felt really jealous and envied her for being able to eat to her delight and not gain much weight. Now I understand that she probably Isn't eating much else throughout the day and that there's no real "secret". If only!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmfao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 00:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry before I replied on my main and had to delete it -_- but also I agree this reminds me so much of my relationship with my boyfriend and how I'm experiencing my ED wile living with him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 00:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take biotin daily but my hair is falling out a bit and has been brittle and dry and breaking easier. What can I do to prevent this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hunger hurts, but starving works, when it costs too much to love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 06:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 22:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a person with anorexia, a loss of control and eating beyond feeling full feels like a binge to me, though other people may not consider it one. Technically it may be considered "overeating" rather than a binge, but it's that extreme "unable to control myself" behavior that makes me feel like it's more so a binge rather than just eating a bit more past my comfort zone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 21:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ewwwww nope leave pls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 20:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you do it! I binge when I smoke so I stopped smoking a few months ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 08:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg HUGE fan of him. He's incredible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 08:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The smaller you get, the quicker you'll get drunk :D maybe try to focus on your calories as a whole rather than food and then booze. I stay at around 900 a day and if I know I'll be drinking I leave 300-400 for vodka and diet soda so I don't go over. So I guess planning out your day with your drinks included could help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 07:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That super helpful, thanks sooo much! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 04:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I want to be thin for him" I can totally relate omg. My boyfriend makes it seem like he doesn't like the weight I lost but now he's suddenly way more into sex than he used to be lol. The things we do to feel worthy of love :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 04:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of related but I'm constantly biting the skin off of my cheeks and lips. Seriously, constantly. People point it out all the time. It makes my jaw hurt so bad but I cannot seem to stop doing it. I only realized this isn't normal like this year and have yet to bring it up to my therapist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 04:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 04:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's amazing! I visit it every day! I should actually post some thinspo I've collected on there if that's ok (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 03:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome back! I have been on and off binging so I can totally relate. I'm sure it's mostly water weight! Try drinking a lot of tea and water the next few days and you'll see the water weight will shed right off of you. (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 03:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's very kind, I appreciate that a lot :,) I think you're right about the insta models thing. In real life they probably look way less "curvy" and not as perfect as they edit their photos to be lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 03:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! Thanks (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 03:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks beautiful thanks! What weight did you start to have a true thigh gap? I only wanna get to 110 but I'm dying to have a thigh gap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 19:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Glitter_Cunt is this what your thigh gap is like? Her legs touch at her knees as well  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 19:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for you input! that really makes me feel better, i appreciate it. i feel like perhaps im in the middle? i gain weight quickest on my thighs but also do definitely gain relatively fast on my bust. For example, when i was 115 i still had a bubble butt and around a 34 B chest, and a tiny waist. I gained weight to about 132-136 and my ass was huge and my chest grew to a 34 C, an entire cup size. Im totally cool with being pear shaped as well, i just got worried because my friend told me i have a "boyish" body and it made me feel so un-feminine and self conscious. Im not sure why she said that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 18:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much!!!! I feel like I can't see myself clearly and it's helpful having someone else's objective input (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could cry tears of joy... My friend (who isn't the brightest bulb) recently told me I have a boyish figure and a straight body... Like no defined waistline like those insta models. But I always thought that maybe I was hourglass because my proportions do match up with what an hourglass body typically is! Thank you for helping me out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone please tell me what body type/shape I have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/a/IJz9o

I have never been sure what shape I am. I'm 5'6 and 118 pounds, and have full 34 b bust, and have been known to have a bubble butt all my life but the weight seems to be coming off of it (if any of that helps). Am I more of like a boyish body???? HELP  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup! I kind of stash it away "just in case" I need it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow thanks!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 06:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinspiration really helped me out. When I felt like binging I looked at thinspo... Especially photos of people I know who are underweight and beautiful. 

Also, I'm not sure what the biggest reason you want to lose weight is for, but for me I just wanna feel like I'm good enough for my boyfriend and for myself. So I remind myself that when I feel like eating a ton. I try not to reward myself with food as well when I restricted really well for the day because I think about how light I'll feel in the morning (-: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 05:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/a/IJz9o I know I'm kinda late but I'm posting here for accountability as well! I'm about 118 pounds at 5'6 and am glad I'm carrying that weight relatively OK, considering I'm not even underweight yet :| haven't lost much in the past week but my body is looking a tad different which is cool! I will prob be removing this later. 



EDIT:
ALSO!!!!! Can someone please tell me what body type I have? My chest is a pretty full 34 b. I've been trying to figure this out for the past year and I'm clueless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shit out an entire brick of shirataki noodles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 22:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only had half of a portion of my shirataki noodles but I shit out what looks like the entire packet.. Should I add an extra 200 calories to yesterday's log in MFP just to be safe? PLEASE HELP!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 21:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm starving enough, even cardboard tastes like heaven -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 21:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiiii ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 18:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the same way and I have an eating disorder. I stay under 1000 and am usually eating 800 a day. This is incredibly unhealthy and will cause you future health problems!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 06:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love this so much. Also, hello stat buddy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 06:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A very weird shaped body with really chunky thighs and fat hips and huge belly pooch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 05:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 05:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would save most of your calories for the night time and go out to the dining hall with them! In the mornings you could leave wrappers around before they wake up so it looks like you ate or maybe dirty up some dishes. I know it's so extra but this is a tough situation :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately this sounds more like the diet of someone with en eating disorder. You may want to up it to 1200 and continue working out. You'll lose the weight as long as you're weighing everything and logging it correctly. If you're still not losing, you may wanna see a doctor/nutritionist to see what's up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 02:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 17:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Originally I was allowing myself to finally get my belly button pierced at 120 but still at 119 I look pretty big and my stomach isn't completely flat so now when I hit underweight at 114 I'll get one! When I get to 110, I'm finally going clothes shopping because all of my jeans don't fit and I want cute fall clothes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 17:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I had my first real binge in awhile ... And I DIDNT PURGE IT !!!  I just kinda dealt with feeling bloated and even went out with a few friends and took photos and didn't look like a complete whale! But those last ten pounds def still need to come off ASAP  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 00:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just binged the hardest ive ever binged. i needed this 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 22:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup I lost around 17 pounds and don't think my boyfriend noticed much at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow thank you!! im definitely gonna start taking care of my hair more because im worried its going to start thinning out. ill look into those products you linked (:
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what product do you use? my natural hair is kind of stringy and frizzy. it looks unhealthy when its not straightened but it looks shiny and smooth when it is -_-  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you !!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you, this seriously just made me feel ten times better. im just gonna try to be patient and relax. im just sooo antsy waiting for these last 9-10 pounds to shed off! so close yet so farrrrr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaining on 1000 cal a day?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So for the past few days ive tried upping my intake to 900-1000 cal a day so i dont feel so sluggish (and so my boyfriend kind of gets off  my case) but my weight has been going up instead! i messed up a few days ago and had 1300 but the last few days ive been at 1000 or under. My TDEE is somewhere around 1500-1600 cal if im a potato, but ive been biking a bit to places around campus so i thought that should help.

I was around 118 when i was weighed on thursday and ive ballooned up to 121ish. Is this all water weight or what?! SOMEONE HELP! ive kinda been panicking but i keep trying to remind myself that with the amount im eating, i HAVE to be losing weight still..right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my problem is probably that i straighten it almost every single day :/ also mines pretty thin to begin with. i guess i just need a lot of patience! but thanks for the info :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 02:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how long did it take you to grow it to your waist!? i wanna grow mine so bad but i had to get it trimmed and not its only a couple inches below my shoulders  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 23:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i usually update mine to a pound more than my most recent lowest weigh in. i got weighed last week at the doctors and was 118.7 but put 119.4 (arbitrary, i know) because i was paranoid it just was a super good day with no water weight. im glad i did though, becauce ive been 120-121 these past few days -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes pls update on kitty!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 17:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG!!!! This is exactly how I wish my body looked! You have incredible proportions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 04:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait help I tried to make this the other day and maybe I didn't make the crust thin enough but the ends were crispy and crust like but the middle was an soggy and a little mushy :/ what do you think I did wrong?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 04:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry ): we're here for you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
