<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1258</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 07:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU GO GLEN COCO!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 17:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the hormones (HCG) that make the pregnancy test positive do go down after 3 months of pregnancy. So it SHOULD test negative at some point around there or upcoming! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 06:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all 3 together?
Pretty, fucking effective if I do say so myself. As long as you use the methods correctly
Individually in order from most safe to least safe: Oral contraceptives, condoms, pulling out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 21:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an American who was grew up in Australia and had tons of people try to imitate my accent and end up sounding british...I don't understand how it happens. They are completely different!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 18:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really need a huge *hug* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 18:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like you. Let's be friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phase change problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 00:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assume 12,500 J of energy is added to 2.0 moles (36 grams) of H2O as an ice sample at 0 degrees C...

A. Only Ice
B. Ice ans water
C. Only water
D. Water and water vapor

Hi guys, I don't understand what I even need to know for this problem. I've looked in my books and notes and everywhere and I can't find anything. What do I even start with? What values do I need to know/memorize?
E. Only water vapor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 01:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an understandable feeling frankly, It's hard to connect when you're not on the same page or close to the same page intelligence wise. If it's a small difference, you can get over it, if there is a such a huge difference in your "intelligence level" I think you're just going to continue to get more and more frustrated. Either except her as is or break up with her. That's not something you can ask her to change for you. It also isn't something that is in your power to control or change. Sorry :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-17 05:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd def be down for this. I like to drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 00:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My while world has turned  upsidedowl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 20:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This outrages me. BMI is not a good indicator of health. There are a lot of  other factors like genetics and body adaptations.

I am a 22 year old female 5'2" and I way 88 pounds.  I am not unhealthy, I am not anorexic and I don't diet. I eat as much as I want and eat pretty healthy. I love eating. I"m a foodie. I just don't put on weight. At all. Like ever. In fact, if I'm not constantly eating and stuffing my face- I lose more weight. Most of my efforts go to at least maintaining my weight. And no, I don't have any parasitic worms. My doctors have checked multiple times. Also, I don't over exercise, hec, I've barely exercised at all this year. I am super healthy.  Yale needs to STFU. 
-end rant- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 01:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's fantastic. Like really great news. I didn't know you could probably take it the summer before. I thought it had to be ALL well and done before you applied so I just FREAKED OUT. Now i have some leeway.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 22:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alright! I guess i'll have to find a way SOMEWAY somehow to make it happen! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Switching to PT- pre-req help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 19:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a nursing student switching to PT because honestly it seems to be  more of my niche that nursing is.
Anyway, with that said, I think I can do all the pre-reqs required but doing a second semester of physics is proving to be really really difficult with my schedule. What are the chances of me actually getting into any PT school if I don't take a second semester  of physics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 00:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a sticky situation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 02:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It honestly sounds like you are just a very sympathetic and empathetic person. It's not a bad thing, but it's hard to deal with isn't it --when you are too nice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 03:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> lovely PAs of reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 23:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm a nursing student and just quit my  major because I really didn't enjoy it, does having 3 years of patient experience in NURSING through school count for the  patient care hours highly recommended when applying to PA programs? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 16:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks so much! I think I'm going to book an appointment for next week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 12:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The police will DEFINITELY side with the father.

I've been to india multiple times and seen enough child abuse there to know that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 11:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's easy at all! 
I mean bipolar is extremely dependent on whether or not she has Manic episodes. OP has described anything of the sort, only volatile and unstable relationships/ behavior.  But then again, none of us would really know. It'd be better to ask her therapist/pychiatrist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I drink coffee at this point? I'm exhausted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 11:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,
The day before yesterday I started a new prescribed stimulant. I used to have pretty bad insomnia up until high school, but I guess I grew out of it. Anyway, I've been wide awake for the past 2 nights. I've managed to get may an 2 hours the night before last, and 45 minutes-ish just now...I have an exam today....is it worth drinking coffee to keep me going for the day? Or will even one cup make it worse? You guys are the experts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 07:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me it sounds a bit like. Borderline personality disorder!   You should def talk to her therapist and brig up personality disorders!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 02:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT IS THIS MAGIC? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 00:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go Blue indeed!
Leaders and Best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 19:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Doctors!!
Junior year nursing student here at U of M hospital!! I'm so incredibly excited you are doing this AMA! What was the most difficult setback to overcome in the process of designing this new splint?
AND- does the splint being absorbed have any future adverse effects that you are aware of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 19:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I didn't know that!! Thanks for the citation! I'm going to look it up!! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 17:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it just goes to show, that children aren't the problem. It's the adults who have the problem. If we force no gender stereotype onto them, they probably wouldn't have one. I think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 04:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't think it's bad or unnatural that everyone has days where everyone thinks guys are ________ girls are ___________

parents are so _____________. I think that's honestly human nature. Do i think guys are douche bags everyday? No. Do i think they are when a group pushes a girl around at a bar and laugh. Yea. Did this well written post just remind me that hey, there are some really great guy out there? OP is such a wonderful guy! It totally did. I don't think I'm in the wrong at all and I don't care if this is downvoted because I KNOW all of you reading this have had thoughts like that before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monday Cheer! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 01:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ponies don't trigger bullying, It's gender stereotypes that do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 01:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 01:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just as I was thinking "wow, guys are douche bags..."

Faith in men restored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 01:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just sit and look at posts like this on /r/baking and drool and wonder why the hell everything I bake turns out burned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 01:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mothers who are proud of their daughters for being a virgin.

Seriously, no one cares and that probably just means they are more pent up and sexually frustrated. WHO WANTS THAT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 01:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of how many college classes they skip and still manage to pass their courses.

I don't care. You just sound lazy to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 01:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> since I don't have kids...I'm totally doing this to my roommate next year.
Fuck her if she doesn't believe it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 01:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to say City Hunter. sigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 01:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this guy sounds like an eat-and-run type of fella. 

It is NOT fair that he expects you to do all the housework. This is not the 1800s or the early 1900s. Me message to him is get of yo ass.

On a side note, when my father married my mother (arranged marriage) he demanded she do all the housework and cook and take care of the kids. She completely stopped cooking and cleaning. He threatened to divorce her. She called bullshit.
Conclusion: My dad is pretty much a housewife now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 01:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> may all her bags break on her way to her car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 02:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jokes, too big -_- 
Thanks though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 00:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How big is it!? I have a regular car but would love this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 02:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In answer to this, I give you this article I conveniently read about and hour ago?
http://www.tickld.com/x/9-crucial-tips-written-by-a-cop-this-might-save-someones-life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 23:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe a stupid question, but for 2, how am I finding the mass of the electron? Is that the only mistake you saw for 2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gen chem - photons, wavelength, velocity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 20:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done all the problems, this is more for confirmation on whether I've done the equations right or whether I'm using the right equations. ALSO, I have no clue if I did answer number 6 right, so I've given you all the problems and answers, and how I've done them because you may need them to figure out number 6? Thanks for you help!!

(1.)  Suppose 33 g of water is irradiated with photons of wavelength 5.00E-4 m. Assume that the radiation is absorbed  and then converted to heat. How many photons will be required  to raise the temperature of 33.0 g of water by 13.1 degree C. 

My Answer:  4.55E24 photons
How I did it: Delta H of water (33 g) x 4.184 J/gc x 13. 1 C = 1808.7 J

Energy of photon: hc/ wavelength : 6.626e-34 x 3.00e8 / 5.0e-4 = 3.975ee-22 J

1808.7 x (1 photon/ 3.975e-22 J)  = ANSWER: 4.55e24 photons


(2. )The photoelectric work function ( energy threshold) for calcium is 4.34e-19 J. Light of wavelength 405 nm shines on a piece of calcium metal. If one photon can eject an electron, what is the speed of the electron? ( assume that the electron's mass is equal to its rest mass.) phi = work function

ANSWER: 6.51e-38 m/s

HOW
 V =c/wavelength    (1) 
E= hv - phi    (2)
Kinetic Energy= 1/2mv^2  (3)


V = 3.0e8 / 4.05e-7 m = 7.41e14 

E = 6.626e-34  x 7.41e14  minus 4.34e-19 = 5.70e-20 J

Kinetic energy = 1/2 (40.08 = calcium mass) x (5.70e-20)^2 = ANSWER: 6.51e-38 m/s


(3. )What color will this photon be?
ANSWER: Violet?????

(4.) What energy will the photon be? (wavelength =  405 nm -- 4.05e-7 m)
ANSWER: E = hc/wavelength = 4.91 J ?

(5. )What would teh energy of a moe of these photons be?

ANSWER 2.96e24 J

HOW: (6.022e23 photons/ 1 mole  of photons) x (4.91 J/photons) - 2.96e24 J

(6. )What is the wavelength of the emitted electron?

E = hv/ wavelength.      v = velocity

ANSWER:1.32E51 m

HOW:  5.70E-20 J / (6.626E-24 x 6.51e-38) = 1.32E51 m



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 18:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good on you mate, good on you. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frosting recipe for an amateur </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 07:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi r/baking! I pretty much never bake unless it's out of a box, but I've decided to give it a shot, because what can I really lose? 

Does anyone know a good fluffy frosting recipe? nothing super duper sweet? It would be going over a yellow cake. Nothing super difficult please!

Thanks!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 04:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can i just tell you as a female to female, thank you? No  one ever wants to hear about it from us, but sometimes, you just gotta let it rip and let someone know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
