<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject374</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome! That is the single story I've written that inspires me to not forget that I have five in progress c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 19 and female, been reading here since I was ~16. 

I don't mind the simple stories, but I prefer the super engaging ones that keep you wondering until the very end, whether it be in a single long post, or a series of well thought out and well put together posts. 

Either way, if the story is relatively original, as well as interesting, I'll read it regardless of how simple or complicated the plot is, but I prefer the complicated ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment chain made my day c: Glad you liked it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So glad this is back up, unsure if you'll be able to update, or if you'll be dead by tonight. 

I wonder what the timeframe is between blood on drawing and drawing becoming real. This post fills me with happiness, even though OP is kinda fucked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 09:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When George put his blood on his picture of the slugs, they became real. Also, after the little confrontation, it becomes clear that he saw his father being "rough" with his mother, and likely caused his death. George is making monsters to hurt to people that he thinks "hurt" his mother.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/crappydesign 

Perverted as I am, I first misread "Jazz" as "Jizz", then I noticed the boobs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 06:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google Docs, a notebook at times when  my ideas are too scattered for me to feel okay typing them up. 

I once wrote an entire story for nosleep in the submission box. It wasn't well received, but it didn't suck. 

I don't use anything to check my grammar or spelling, I just reread 79 times. Could be why I'm not a super great writer as of yet. I should really use a grammar checker, because I doubt I'm doing perfectly in that area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 06:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew this girl in high school who always had the *nicest* smart phones. She'd end up with a new one every time she got bored of the current one, not because she'd whine, but because she'd purposely destroy her phones several times a month. 

I witnessed her smash brand new phonew against brick walls, stomp one into the cement, and toss one into the road to get run over. 

She was never without a perfectly in tact phone for more than 48 hours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 10:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screamed internally when I saw that more stories from Griffin Drive were coming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happened to me with Population Control, people compared it to the recent show "Between" and that movie "The Happening" 

Honestly didn't intend to have it derive from those, though I've seen them both.  I just wanted to create a bioweapon type pandemic that caused disturbing/gruesome deaths and such. 

Was a little sad to see it compared with them because of how extremely grotesque I felt I was going with my symptoms/deaths/murders/suicides. 

Edit: For some reason I feel like I said the wrong show and movie, but at the same time I'm pretty sure those are correct.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me have a smoke and make some food, then I'll let you know if I've figured it out. 

I have the same issue at times, just find something that at least sparks the motivation to do it bit by bit. Like "hey this sentence sounds great!" And then build around one sentence. 

I just find a part of the story that pops, and focus on getting the story to that part, then think of how to make another part shine, and work towards it next.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once a story has hit the point where the bad grammar and such ruins the flow or confuses me, I just move on without voting. 

Unless I'm told it's *amazing* or otherwise have found some hope deep within to make me continue  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh yea, that makes a lot of sense. Thank you, I like knowing these things about our mods ^-^ 

But oh well, at least the majority of the community isn't part of the crappy downvote-for-no-legit-reason train.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have no idea why this is so awful. But I'm probably not a really well adjusted person. 

Currently writing something about a cannibal, and it doesn't really freak me out. The act of obtaining the human meat is what I find to be kind of.. Messed up? 

It doesn't really scare me, but I have this internal sense that it's wrong for a human being to rip apart another living person with their teeth. Also, the aspect of preserving a body so that it can be eaten in regular portions seems kind of wrong, there's not really instructions on how well human meat will taste after being frozen, and how long it takes for said meat to spoil. 

I guess that it's only taboo because people are repulsed by it, I personally wouldn't eat a human because I'm a picky eater. 

I have no moral reason why I wouldn't eat a person, I just don't think they'd taste good, and am not great at trying new things. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that could damage the voting process, but that there should be some way of stopping bots from downvoting. 

If it's a bot doing it, that's just cruel. 

Maybe they should create a thing where if you've only ever downvoted things from a certain sub, you're no longer allowed to downvote there. 

Also, possibly put in a limit to how many times you can downvote within a certain time frame, so people can't go and downvote every story on the "new" page, or mass downvote every post by one person. 

Another cool idea, if an estimated reading time was calculated based on post length, you shouldn't be able to downvote a story if it hasn't been posted for that length of time yet. 

Or, no downvoting without opening the story, so you can't just vote based off the title/author without at least getting a glimpse of what was written.  

All decent ideas, but I think they'd be super hard for mods to attempt to put in place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened to me not too long ago, I had posted a story at the pretty much the exact same time as someone else, saw that they were down voted, up voted them, checked and saw that I was upvoted once but already had a few downvotes, which had to be random or spiteful because my stories are pretty damn long. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've downvoted stories for incredibly poor grammar, but only when the story itself is also poorly put together. I can get over spelling errors, using the wrong "there" and whatnot, but if the story makes zero sense in addition, I'll usually downvote it 

However, I rarely downvote, and won't downvote a story on the "new" page unless it's absolute garbage. If I don't like it, but don't think it's the worst thing ever, I just don't vote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's usually how I go along, but I end up having so many ideas and such long posts that I feel bad for the spacing of posts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never intend to make things a series, but I end up with 6000+ word posts and still have ideas, and love a twist ending, and twice now my twist has turned into,  "I'm gonna need a second part, this is such a great idea." 

And then I get excited making the second part, and fizzle out during it, or after it, and never think ahead about the length of time between posts. 

With the new one, I wasn't exactly out of ideas or hating the story yet, but the timing didn't give me a lot of time to get things down the way I wanted, and after not updating for a week I felt pressured to put it out faster because I was messing with the timeline of the story by not actually having the real time to put into it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually decided to do this with my old series, I recently put up the rewritten second part that I had taken down before for personal reasons, but I only decided on continuing with it because of the anthology piece I began writing, and I needed the second part back up to kind of put it out there that something new is coming. 

This is actually the best idea, because though my second part was never well received, I decided to overlook it because the part I'm working on has a lot of potential and I'm happy that I don't have to directly continue on a story line that I lost hope in, but still get to use the base idea of the first post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy to hear! 

Best wishes for you and your health c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well damn, I didn't realize this was a trend but my most recent series is doing this. Woops o.o

Not in the sex trade though, that would have been too easy. Hate my second part though. 

I haven't been reading a lot lately though, mine unintentionally follows the trend because I based the beginning off my childhood and my 14 year old friend being taken away was a really plausible happening in that lifestyle. 

Time to creep through nosleep and see how poorly mine stacks up against similar stories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 03:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Late but, saying the word "breakfast" 

For the first fifteen years of my life I was not told I was saying it wrong, now I'm 19 and sound like a four year old because I can't help but say "bref-tuss"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 03:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hearing and vision blurred as I became increasingly overwhelmed. *What the fuck did I sign?* Why didn't the attendant give me whatever form contained the part with the safe word? They couldn't actually kill my family anyways, right? This is just another test to scare me shitless, and make me try to quit. *It's just a game.* 


I was broken out of my trance with a sharp smack to the back of the head. The fuck are you waiting for, who dies? Sharkman looked at me with a smile of glee on his face. The back of my head throbbed from the fresh contact with my previous wound. 


I groaned as I ran my hand over the spot, and thought quickly over my options. Treating this as the game it was would be the best option, not giving this sadistic shark freak the satisfaction of freaking me out. Fake or not, Claire would be pissed if I let her die. I looked at them both on the table, and saw my father nod at me with tear filled eyes. It tugged at my heartstrings, either he was playing along really well, or he honestly thought he was going to die here. 


I was once again conflicted about what was real here, but the Sharkman began counting down from three. As he reached one the gun stopped on my fianc, and I impulsively yelled, Not her! 


**BANG** 


She screamed through the gag as the shot rang out, and suddenly the inside of my father's skull was strewn across the table. *It's not real, it's not real.* I tried to convince myself as my stomach rolled at the incredibly real looking scene in front of me. I felt hot metal press into my neck as the Sharkman leaned in close to me. 


Let's sit for the show, why don't we? He gave me a sharp toothed grin as he led me to the head of the table and strapped me into a chair. He walked back to the other end of the table and bent down to speak quietly to the Behemoth. He stood back up and held my fiancs face down into the gore on the table. I sat completely stunned as I noticed the headless body begin to rock against the table. 


What the fuck are you doing! I screamed in disgust. I was met with a sharp pain in my shoulder, which I registered as a gunshot wound a minute later. The Sharkman sneered at me, gun still raised. 


Shut the fuck up. And watch. The. SHOW! He laughed hysterically at that, and pressed the gun against Claire's temple. Moments later she began screaming as the Behemoth took his turn on her, I couldn't convince myself that this part was fake, and couldn't stop myself from throwing up directly into my lap. I was filled with disgust and anguish, Claire looked directly at me as she tried to scream for it to end. 


My vision started to blur from both the shock of scene and the blood loss from my new wound. I blacked out. 


I was awoken by the screaming again, but I couldn't see. They had blindfolded me. I could tell I was outside, everything smelled like grass and there was a cool breeze. My hands were bound behind me, and my wounds ached. Claire's screaming was distant, and I had no idea what was happening. I heard footsteps approach, and then the voice of the Sharkman. 


You're nearly done, bitch. Things just need to get a little more interesting if you want us to actually let you go at the end of the night.


((Wasn't 100% sure where to go to bring it closer to the end while still keeping up with everyone's additions, but hopefully most of this is decent)) 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 01:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually drew him three different versions of one this favorite TV show characters for Christmas c: 

These are good ideas, thank you!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I risk the wrath of my mother by sitting on reddit for 20+ minutes before doing any task I am told to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fixing the internet and doing dishes... Woops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this so gross though?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 22:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a beautiful post. 

Thanks for the link, awesome c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 12:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm slightly confused by the end, was she just standing behind you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missing Post, Population Control (Part 2) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 12:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **We have worked hard to cover this all up, but I can no longer be a part of this. She wasn't crazy, everything she told you was true. They removed this, but I found it. I've been working here for a while now, and I recently realized that I needed to learn more about what I was working on. That's a later story though. You may have read [this](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/545jly/population_control/) account of events some time ago, below lies the rest of the information our patient could learn and share. I'm sorry for all of this, I'll explain more later, but this really needs to stop being covered up. Here was the update we never wanted you to see:**



The past few days have been eye-opening, to say the least. I know more than I want to, I know too much about myself now, and I know more than I can tell you, even though I still cant find key information about the people who did this. I can say this will likely be the only update you will receive from me, I dont expect to be able to come back after today, or for any of you to want me to. The last time I was able to access one of the computers to update you all was just before the last round of testing. For those of you who didnt see my smaller updates and background information that I left in the comments, heres a bit of that for you before I go into detail about what Ive learned over the past few days. 



The town was in the Yukon Territory of Canada, very near the border of Alaska. I honestly dont know a lot about it or its location in relation to other places. Small town, small school, and a pretty small world for those of us in the town. Ive never been anywhere outside of it, except perhaps this lab. It really isnt important now that I know how large this operation is. I still have no idea where this facility is. As I said in comments, I cant locate a single window in the facility. I have no sense of time here, everything is on their set schedule which may not even be following regular daylight patterns. 



As far as the testing goes, Im not entirely sure what it was all about. Until the past few days, I had never seen any of the 8 other survivors. I still havent figured out who exactly is running this operation, but I know its been running for far longer than Id imagined. In the beginning months of the testing, they seemed to be just checking vitals. I was in bed for days at a time with an IV attached to me, and they took a lot of blood samples. I thought at that point they were just making sure I was clear of any signs of infection. After that, every few weeks I would receive an injection or several, and then I would sleep while they observed whatever those injections did. After the testing I felt sick for days, like there were insects burrowing in my stomach and bones. The most recent ones were more blood tests and injections, but this time I was awake, and I really dont think theyre happy about that. Ill tell you about that after the more important things.



Here we go, I hope you dont blame me after all this. There are things my body physically wont allow me to write. I didnt see until after posting that when writing out certain telltale information in the file I saw, I censored myself. Ive tried to go back and edit it, but whether it is my brain or my hands, my body will absolutely not fill in those blanks with real information. I know why now, but youll find out yourself as I tell you what Ive discovered. 




Through memorizing the passwords of different computers Ive been able to get access to in the facility, Ive found out that the event which happened in E.S (my town) started long before the three weeks of hell I experienced there. Obviously due to the computers and my own bodys restrictions I cannot disclose exact specifics, or show you the files, but I promise to do my best. Ill tell it to you chronologically, as well as I could piece it together. Other than E.S I couldnt find specific locations, but I can guarantee this has happened or will occur in at least 19 other places. I wish I knew where they were. 



As far as I could find this began thirty years ago. The scientists working here had completed an outline for how to control the population in the years to come. They knew it was a growing problem, that the world would eventually begin to die from the lack of resources in an exponentially growing population. I really apologize for being unable to go into the specifics of this, but maybe someone can figure out the science to it all. They created some type of genome, or at least I think thats what it was called in the files. My mind gets so foggy when I try to think of the details. Anyways, they used this in some type of solution so that it could be implanted, Ill refer to it as the Crystal serum for the sake of clarity. 



The implantations occurred every five years, the first set being given in 1986. In five different locations, which were not listed in the files, they injected ten newborn infants with the crystal serum. This would have been the first of their trials, all of which were 100% failures. According to the data I found, each child died without infecting anyone else. The results were disgusting. None of the mothers were aware that their children had been injected with anything, it had all seemed like routine post-labour checkups and blood tests. Within 24-hours of injection symptoms began to show, small crystallizations formed in a film over the skin of each child. By the 48-hour mark the entire epidermis of each child was made of a putrid green crystal, but that was as far as the symptoms went. They were not infectious, they did not have violent outbursts, but they did die. Every time one of the children were touched, the crystals flaked away and revealed raw muscle and tissue, each movement of the children caused cracks along the crystals which bled with no way to stop them without tearing away more of the crystallized skin. 




Each child from that trial died. According to the research all those children suffered greatly. Their crystallized skin was painfully detached from their bodies, by accident and as other doctors tried to save them. Every attempt at grafting new skin became more crystallizations. Their small bodies couldnt take it, some died of heart failure, organ failure, and major immune issues due to the crystal serum, others died due to blood loss. They were unable to do anything to save those children, they couldnt even identify what was wrong. The data says that the serum is untraceable through any medical technology, so no one ever knew what had happened those two days in any of those locations. I dont know how a story like that was covered up, all I know is that the mothers were told that an infectious disease spread through newborns specifically and took those fifty lives. Trial 1: 100% failure, noninfectious, 100% host death rate. 




The second trial was 1991. The research didnt specify as to whether or not they change the formula for the crystal serum, but they decided to try a different host subject. This round of injections was given to mothers a month before they were due to give birth. Passed off as a simple prenatal injection to assure the health of the child during the last stage of pregnancy, once again these women were clueless to being experimented on. Those women all fell ill and died within a week of their implantations. They were said to show minor symptoms of crystallizations around their eyes, and their fetuses had no chance of survival. The wombs of the women in the second trial were filled with disgusting masses of flesh and green crystal protrusions, not enough to pierce the mother, but to such an extent that they werent even discernable as human. The file called this positive progress, and said that they were close to developing a serum with correct results. Trial 2: 100% failure, noninfectious, promising results in post mortem tests, 100% host death rate, attributes similar to expectations for Beta stage of implanted hosts.




The third trial occurred in 1996 with results better than ever expected with only minor tweaks to the serum and implantation method. My town was one of five to be impacted by this set of research. They implanted the serum in pregnant women during the first trimester of pregnancy, in a smaller dose, and more directed at the fetus. There were no side effects on any of the mothers. Most of the children made it full term, and those who didnt were naturally miscarried and showed no signs of the side effects the serum could cause. Each child was born seemingly normal, each mother was fine, it was as though the crystal serum had never entered their lives. The file suggests about the same success rates in every location, between 95%-100% fatality in non-host subjects. Im unable to say how many host-subjects survived due to my limitations. 




Trial number three was described as a time released serum that would meld into the DNA of the host subjects, with zero side effects to host. Hosts would have a predisposition to be secretive and wary of others, an advanced sense of danger, and above average intelligence compared to their peers. The hosts would be unable to divulge class-A confidential information when exposed to such, and have generally heightened immune system responses. They will be immune to toxins, airborne or otherwise. The Alpha stage occurs at the time when every host reaches full maturity they will simultaneously release undetectable airborne toxins into a 100 mile radius, at which point any exposed person(s) will also become infectious. The release of toxins should last for approximately two weeks, with up to two additional weeks for the the airborne virus to dissipate. 




The Beta stage would be what I described in my original account of events. The infections, crystallizations, gruesome deaths and all. They cleaned out the bodies in the town for further testing. I never had a chance of dying, I am not even entirely human. I dont know what I am. I am part of the cause of all this death. There were only nine hosts in my town, but it was more than enough to kill over 400 people. Since learning all this Ive realized more about the testing being done on me and the others. Ive also been unable to locate more specific files on what is currently going on. I can definitely say that somewhere out there, theres four other locations that had or will have their hosts become fully mature and release the crystal serum infection sometime this year. I dont know what they consider fully mature, but obviously it can be as young as 19-years-old, but it seems its just about 20 years after the initial implantation. Perhaps its the serum that is maturing.



I also know that there was at least a fourth trial in 2001, but the means of implantation and results were not listed in any of the files I found. I dont doubt that theyll continue this research, or that they have and I just havent located the files yet. As for the files on my town, I cant find the detailed ones that would tell what exactly their objective is with the Beta stage. I feel like were well past that part now and theyre working on something even worse with us.




The tests they were doing on us initially were to see if we were still releasing toxins. They were checking the levels of whatever chemicals the crystal serum had left in us. They were checking to see if wed suddenly develop symptoms, and then if we could be provoked to develop symptoms. I think theyre trying to see if we can be made into weapons, more so than we already are. Four of my fellow hosts have died during the testing, I have no idea what these so-called scientists did to cause that. I only saw the others briefly after I woke up during my testing. Ill get to that now.



Usually when they take me in for testing, its a blood draw, followed by some type of sedation and then everything is black. That last time the sedation didnt work though, whether Im developing a tolerance to it, or they made a mistake in dosage I do not know. I know that when I opened my eyes to a brightly lit room, I found myself squinting in confusion. I had no fingers for a moment, only jagged, green, crystalline claws. They didnt notice I was awake until I screamed, and then they ran for me. Its a hazy memory of half sedation, but I know I had sharp enough crystal protrusions along my arms that I ripped through restraints. All I saw was green glass, and blood. My skin was being torn open where the jagged green malformations were piercing through. The more confused and scared I became, the worse they got. My blurry vision began to have a tint of green, and as a scientist came towards me I lashed out with my hand to ward them off. My panicked movement caused my jagged claw to elongate, and I severed the hand that was reaching before me. I was screaming in horror once again, when I felt a pinch and began to lay back and calm down. 



I felt the jagged crystals recede beneath my skin, it felt like glass cutting through me, and then maggots writhing deep through my tissue and into my bones. They restrained me again and I was being rolled through the blank white halls on a bed, I passed by several rooms where I saw some other people my age from my town through observation glass, they were all asleep and in various stages of crystallization as the researchers monitored and took notes at their bedside. In one room I passed I saw an entirely crystallized person laying misshapen on the floor. There were several obvious bullet holes in what was once a normal person's body. And so much blood, so much more blood than Id seen since the event was in full force. I saw that there were several researchers tending to wounds in the room, and someone else was being rolled out on a bed covered in a blood soaked sheet. The sedation made me fall into slumber at that point.



Apparently if we get too out of hand in testing, were done with. The crystalline person I saw while being rushed out of my observation room was the fourth to be terminated according to the files. I was lucky I didnt cause lethal damage or Id be gone too. I need to get out of here, I dont want to become the thing I saw one of my fellow hosts become. It feels like a constant fire is under my skin, my blood is full of shattered glass that may burst through at any moment. Im not safe here. Im a monster hidden in human skin, and I dont know how many of me are out there unknowing yet. Remember the characteristics, think about yourself. Think about your life, think about your age and the tests. Keep yourself far away from others if you might be one of us, because were dangerous. Were more than population control, I dont know what these tests are, but theyre going to make us more lethal. Theyre going to make the future hosts even worse. 



I am not human. I never was. I dont know what I am, but a host for something deadly. I dont know if these tests have made it so I will be infectious again. I know that I cant control the crystallizations when they appear. I know my emotions can trigger terrifyingly deadly reactions from them. I know they hurt. I dont know if I can escape. But one way or another, tonight Im going to find the medication that provokes the transformations, or learn how to trigger them on my own. Tonight Im getting rid of the other hosts in this facility. Tonight this place is going to be done with, I will be gone one way or another. I will find the other facilities somehow. They may have created me so that I cant focus on the information I need to find them, but Ill be looking. I know too much to let this go on. Im sorry if I spread this on my way to stopping it. Im sorry if youre a host. Im sorry that they turned us into monsters. Im sorry Ill never be what I expected, but I am more now.



The population needs to be controlled, and right now Im going to start with ones trying to do it themselves. 


**I don't know how far she got with her plan, I did hear of some major damage in one sector a few months back, but I'm unsure at this time if that is related to her. My name is Madison, and I'll be back to tell you the truth.**


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 12:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured I was in front of the three people once again when the quiet whimpers of the wounded female sounded to be just a few feet in front of me. I tried to recall what the other two looked like, but I had only gotten a glimpse of them before the lights went out. A male to the left, and another girl to the right. The fake bullet wound had kept my attention too long to really look them over. They were all bare anyways, so I doubted I missed any important details. 

I knew what the people running this little show wanted, I was basically playing a character in a horror movie. I wouldn't be a damn bit surprised if this was recorded and posted somewhere afterwards. See how the main character flinches at the unspeakable acts that his tormentors forced him to commit. Fucking lame.


I didn't really feel like playing *directly* into their bullshit though. Normally, the main character, being a good guy, would go for the already wounded person. Be all merciful and stay as innocent as possible. But where's the thrill in that? This was supposed to be scary, not some cliche movie plot. I sidestepped to the left, until I was in front of where I assumed the guy was. I was going to throw them off, to whatever extent I could. I paid for some high quality terrifying enjoyment.


Not gonna give me a look at my choice? I yelled aloud into the room. I was met with only increased sobbing coming from the girl again. It was getting on my nerves. Do you want a fucking gold star? Jesus, quit it already, you're not impressing anyone! 


She was a little more silent after that, but I could still hear her. Whatever, I took an aggravated step forward and leaned towards my victim's face. I could feel his heavy breathing, and was slightly disgusted and the stench of his breath. I guess I might have made a displeased noise, because from the darkness in front of me I heard, Fuck you.


Well then, With irritation rolling through me, I raised my arm and quickly slammed the knife into roughly where his shoulder should be. An aggressive yell from the man was quickly cut short by my own scream of pain. The dirty bastard bit my arm. This sparked newfound rage in me, so I ripped the knife out from whatever padding and blood pouches I had punctured, and drove it forcefully into where I figured his gut was. I had definitely hit more blood pouches, but the bite had pissed me off, so I was hoping the force of my blows could be felt through whatever protective padding he had on. 


Suddenly my forehead was bursting with pain, and I was falling backwards off a ledge that I was fairly sure I hadn't climbed up to get here. It felt like a long drop, but instead of thinking about that as I fell, I was thinking about how that actor was *such a dick.* 


Suddenly my back hit concrete, followed closely by the back of my skull. I reached back to feel the point of impact, and was met with a warm, sticky sensation. I found myself getting angry, but also slightly worried. I was *actually* bleeding, and probably had a concussion. I looked up to see how far I had fallen. A light flickered on from far above as I squinted upwards, I appeared to have fallen at least sixty feet down a square shaped hole. There's no possible way I fell that far though, I didn't hit the ground hard enough or fall for a long enough period of time to travel that distance. Must have been a wicked optical illusion. 


The light above flickered off then on again, and I could see the robed figures standing around the edge of the hole looking down towards me. As the light blinked in and out they disappeared and reappeared, then suddenly the flickering stopped, and I watched as something came barreling down towards me. I pressed my body tightly to the wall, and instinctively squeezed my eyes shut as the large object hit the ground with a sickening crack. When I reopened my eyes it was pitch dark once again. 


Annoyed as ever, I felt along the walls and found my initial observation was correct. 8 by 8 square room with no doors. How creative. Wow, dark room with no doors! Haven't seen this one yet, I yelled up the hole. The sound didn't echo though, as though the shaft I had fallen down was now closed. I sighed and got down on my knees to feel about the floor and discover what my robed friends had tossed me. It was a body, of course. I couldn't tell much about the fake body, except that I could feel skin, and I was kneeling in fake blood. The skin felt really realistic though. 


That's when the light flicked back on, but this time much closer. The hole above was gone, and a ceiling with a small light fixture was now in it's place. I looked over the body, and it appeared to be my victim. The body had landed face up, a stab wound was in the shoulder as well as several to the abdomen. They looked really realistic, and so did the bones which were broken and out of place from the fall. This was some hell of a prop. The bag tied around the head was leaking fake blood, so I decided to remove it. I was met with an extremely human looking face, half of which was crushed.


It made me feel a little uneasy, but I laughed anyways, Think you can fool me? 


I wavered a bit at the end, as I glanced back at the almost too-lifelike dead man. Of course the lights turned out again, but this time I was met with deafeningly loud eerie laughter from all sides. 


((Edit me like crazy if you wish, for anything that helps it flow better with everything else, not the greatest at dialogue. Also, sorry that I write so fast, couldn't sleep and had ideas in advance.)) 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 09:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a lot of concern and reasoning for her sleepwalking in these comments, but really.. What is it she's looking for? Who is this "he" that is going to get you of this thing is not found? Why now? 2017 is gonna be a hell of a year for you. Maybe you should help her dig? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 08:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sounds of my unfinished stories screaming and crying from my documents folder 

But if I actually have the thought to put something on it's usually alternative rock/punk rock/metal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 09:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw I read this when it was first posted, human beings are fucking vile. I've yet step into similar childhood experiences of mine, but things like that are part of the truest evil in this world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 04:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have friends who drive for Uber and I have always joked when they were going to get someone "Don't get stabbed." 

Maybe this is why he was never stabbed. 

Daniel? O.o  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 03:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was great! Thanks for reading it, and glad you liked it c: 

Edit: Oh, and I should have mentioned before, but for future reference, my user sounds like "Hi-lee-anne-fay" c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 22:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, loved it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 06:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only posted a few on this account, but if any of them fit with style of reading for you, go ahead and read it! This sounds wonderful. I honestly think I've only posted two so far, I'll have to check

*Edit:* I've posted three, check out "My Children Never Lied". I think it would sound great in this format, because I wrote it in a very slow and calm tone. (At least that's how it sounds to me).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 06:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes Gravy, yes! 

I had fun with this last time, even though we didn't win. 

It's a fun ride seeing what we can all come up with. .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 01:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if your children are no longer your children, and if that Toby kid is now actually Max, who had been trapped under the ice for so long. Who or what was inside Max all this time? And who or what may be inside your children now, if they too are trapped under the ice.. 

Maybe dip them again to retrieve their souls. 

But then, who knows? Hopefully they stay the same kids they were before going under the ice, and you can just put this all behind you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 22:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm, I'm really a man in a 19 y/o female body.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 22:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really messed up, you don't really see anything, can't see the ghost and whatnot, but you can definitely tell what's happening :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 09:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are really interesting. Having dealt with seeing severe trauma firsthand I don't find them scary, but fascinating. 

It'd be awesome if you could ask your dad for more background information on the cases that you know of, so that you could give a longer story for each patient. I zoomed right through reading this, so if you could ask for more information about what happened to them, how they were fixed, what caused their injuries, how long they were there, and any other information you can receive without going into specifics about the identity of patients, then you could put in less stories per post, and slow down how quickly your posts are read all the way through. If you update this post with additional information, or make another post, let me know! I'd love to hear more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 09:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That moment when r/no sleep gives you a heavy case of the feels. 

Kinda creepy of her, but so sad..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 09:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 06:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if I'm just a total moron, but what did you mean by they "optioned" your story? 

Congratulations though, top ten and all sounds amazing, and whatever this option thing is must be great! I loved that story when I read it. :) 

Edit: I did a bad at English.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 04:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things I saw on Netflix that I actually liked, even though I'm that little shit that laughs in the horror movie, comments on how "If that was real blood all over your car windows at night in the dark, it wouldn't glow red inside, it'd be pitch dark" and calls the characters dumbasses consistently, :

* REC (all three were good, not sure of they're still on because this was a few years ago) 

* V/H/S 1 2 (hated 3) 

* Shrooms

* Silent Hill: Revelations (I think? Second silent hill movie though) 

Can't think of others that I actually enjoyed at the moment, though I found a Google search of "found footage horror movies" turns up some of the best and worst of that specific horror genre c: 

Oh edit:
I recently watched these on a *totally legal* site . 

Ouija: Origin of Evil (prequel to Ouija that came out sometime in the past two years? Not bad, but I'd recommend watching it BEFORE Ouija, as it is slow for a majority but provides interesting background to the first movie, which IMO was the better film of the two) 

Don't Breathe (Some young adults break in to rob a blind war vet, who happens to end up being very sinister) I found it more thriller than horror, but it was pretty decent. 

Speaking of Sinister, I recall that I didn't hate that movie when I saw it, though for the life of me I can't remember what it was about since I watch horror quite often. Think there's a second one to that, but haven't seen it. 

Older, but there was a remake of The Amityville Horror sometime between 2004-2006 that was actually quite good. Scared the shit outta me when I was 6.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 03:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The REC movies (not sure if all of them)  were made into the Quarantine movies, so instead of Spanish or whatever it is, it's English. I don't remember if they're intentional remakes or just coincidentally exactly alike, but they're good. REC 3 was great, never checked if they made a Quarantine 3, but the first two were good c: Last time I checked REC 3 is on Netflix, wedding turned zombie apocalypse!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds similar to a movie I saw, Ghost something. Film crew trying to fake a paranormal investigation TV show go to this abandoned hospital? Asylum perhaps? Can't recall. But they were going to rig up fake scares for the show, and end up being murdered by ghosts and such. Including a ghost on human rape scene. 

Can't remember it all, or the actual name. But it's a similar premise with the whole "Fake paranormal hunting turned into actual death". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Ontario, Canada, where everyone I know calls it pop. Now in Michigan, where a majority of people I know also call it pop, including my grandparents, who are from Florida.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 09:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to drink 5 or 6 a day, two or three in the morning, take a couple hour nap, then a couple more cups, but also pop and tea in the evenings, plus a Monster when extra money is around to get fancy like that. 

Now I've cut it down to where I can have one or two cups in the morning, take a nap, maybe have another one after, and then pop and/or tea for the rest of the day. Just general desire for caffeine constantly. 

Though my daily schedule is odd, go to sleep between 1-4am to be awake at 5am, depending on what I have to do during the day, I could nap between 8-12 but I usually am up til 10 and awake again in under two hours.

My sleep schedule is all sorts of odd, to the point that caffeine doesn't really cut it, I have fallen asleep before on the floor with a quarter can of Monster in my hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 08:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate birds. 

Started reading this, and was like "Hey, birds could earn me money. They're not evil, vicious sky-villians!"

Then the ending came, fucking evil little teeth stealing sky-villians.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 07:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find this specifically with things I post on Reddit. I write horror stories now and then, everything in Google docs, run it through a spelling and grammar check, reread it six times before copying it over, submit. Reread immediately after posting, finding the stupidest spelling errors and words auto corrected like "were" into "we're". Then every time I get a comment I reread and yet again, stupid mistakes I missed the first twelve times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 07:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had an ex who joked about injecting me with caffeine due to the excessive amounts of coffee I drink on a daily basis to avoid becoming a zombie. 

Please mail these needles, running low on coffee and the will to live.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
