<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1856</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Effective communication </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, it drives me nuts when Reddit posts a bunch of cat pictures.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo boy, how you doin'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cats, I can't even look at them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I was fat and attempted to starve myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 11:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we be friends? Please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 22:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always see 2 sides of a story or problem, makes for quite a bit of indecisiveness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 03:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, now I know how to shower properly. I've been doing it all wrong :(.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 03:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like plants and stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 03:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When people feel the need to talk about how important they are and how important their job is. I'm like, bitch please, grab a chair and sit down somewhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 20:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can hold 10 verbal conversations at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 01:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wearing these huge Cinderella dresses made with tulle netting that my mom brought back from vacation. Those things were so itchy even   aloe vera didn't help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 01:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The latter because there is more room to tumble about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 00:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks for the Grand Tetons suggestions! 

My friends and I went to RMNP back in September, we split up and they went to Emerald Lake while I went to Lake Haiyaha (sp?). I was so jealous afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 00:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I've been to Palo Duro and Garden of the Gods (both aren't my thing to be honest, too dry!), but am highly considering the great Sandy Dunes to go sand surfing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any trails to recommend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 22:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greetings /r/hiking!

I will be moving to Oregon from Texas in May. I'm planning to squeeze in some camping and hiking along the way, with an estimate of 10-14 days for the entire trip. 
[Map!] (https://www.google.com/maps/dir/Dallas,+TX/Rocky+Mountain+National+Park/Yellowstone+National+Park,+WY/Grand+Teton+National+Park,+Teton+County,+WY/Portland,+OR/@38.9173664,-119.2393563,5z/am=t/data=!3m1!4b1!4m32!4m31!1m5!1m1!1s0x864c19f77b45974b:0xb9ec9ba4f647678f!2m2!1d-96.7969879!2d32.7766642!1m5!1m1!1s0x876979e4455903e9:0xfa27ee43a78e8217!2m2!1d-105.683639!2d40.342793!1m5!1m1!1s0x5351e55555555555:0xaca8f930348fe1bb!2m2!1d-110.588455!2d44.427963!1m5!1m1!1s0x5352519ec95d1ba9:0xa5a0b88ecc91a337!2m2!1d-110.681763!2d43.790428!1m5!1m1!1s0x54950b0b7da97427:0x1c36b9e6f6d18591!2m2!1d-122.6764816!2d45.5230622!3e0)

I have a few national parks I want to go to along the way, but welcome any suggestions on other places I need to stop at. I would also love to hear any tips you may have for solo hiking and camping (I'll be camping at campsites to ease the anxiety of my parents), especially food suggestions. My car will probably be stuffed so I will not be cooking anything while camping, just looking for quick things to put together to replenish the burned calories. 

A little more information about me: 24 year old in decent shape, I probably can't run a marathon, but have no trouble hiking a few miles uphill. I will be driving a Toyota Camry loaded with my life belongings so any insight regarding being me being able to make it through certain areas will be greatly appreciated. Thank you in advance guys!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 21:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Antidepressants typically take 4-6 weeks to work. Also, never discontinue taking antidepressants abruptly without talking to your doctor first. 

And lastly, please keep in mind all antidepressants carry the risk of suicide (especially during the early stages).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 21:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of these would work I suppose 
http://www.reddit.com/r/pharmacy/comments/22vi27/pun_timebest_pharmacy_pickup_lines/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 20:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone can reduce, reuse, and recycle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 19:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I camped at Elkmont campsite in GSMNP in May, you could hear the fast creek in the morning. I went in May and the water was cold, but still bearable for a short dip.

There's Kisatchie National Forest in central LA (might not be on the way though) that was decent to camp in. Not too many scenic hikes in my opinion, but it's not crowded and a nice place to get away to for a few days. 

Most of Louisiana itself will not be cold during that time of year, so pack shorts and tshirts to roam about in. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 19:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically a technician can check another technician's dispensing work (provided they get proper training and pass an assessment put together by the institution). This is only applicable to cart refills and things like that, technicians can't check a new antibiotic prescribed for Baby Grey in the NICU.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 05:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree about people being nicer to you, to a certain extent. Guys are nicer to you, but girls can be somewhat bitchy or condescending. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 05:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second the pajamas point. I have ON pajama pants from 5 years ago and they still look and fit great. I don't recommend their tshirts, get's all linty and worn after 1-2 washes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 05:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Land's End, the cost:quality ratio is pretty good!
A lot of people associate them with clothes for older people but it's so not true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 04:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a half glass full kind of gal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 04:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark chocolate, 70% cocoa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 04:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fried chicken all the way! 
I'm from Louisiana, can't help it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And ever will be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is what it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't get people to take me seriously. I've tried to keep a straight face and assure them 18937 times I'm really not kidding, but my mouth always defaults into a smile and people always think I'm kidding when I'm really not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I don't know" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been to the park to hike, but never camped (live about 2 hours away). A few of my friends have camped at one of the campsites and really enjoyed it, they're both pretty inexperienced. There's also Palo Duro Canyon State Park that might be a bit more of a drive but has better landscape views in my opinion. 

Out in the canyon, the stars are pretty amazing. It's a nice park with buffalos and a pond, but in terms of hiking trails, there wasn't much. I think 1-2 nights will be sufficient. Just remember to wash your shoes off after you get back because if you don't, the red dirt stains. Hope that helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 05:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't do the same now unfortunately, everything just sticks around a lot longer :/.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 06:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I had 2 big mac meals when I was like 8, complete with smoothies as the beverage of choice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 06:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "tips fedora"
who wears those anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 06:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> textured slanted ceiling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 06:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or your coworkers, that's a red flag that you're probably not a team player. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 05:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> skyscrapersnships </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
