<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3387</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 19:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Europe 3 or 4 times a year and stay with friends; just a week or long weekend. I don't consider these a holiday at this point it happens so often.

1 big holiday a year usual to Asia. Big soft spot for Japan and Korea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 13:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good example. 

Funny you mention it, I'm working on a piece at the moment which took inspiration from this. It's much darker as it's slower. Again, I think tempo has a lot to do with making a minor piece sound sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 13:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really great tracks, thanks for sharing. They both sound very positive but in different ways for me.

Major: carefree, fun, youthful energy, "sound of the summer" vibe.

Minor: nostalgic, a journey or sorts was completed, sense of pride.  

I guess this is a good lesson on using music to express different forms of happiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 10:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any examples of pieces, classical or otherwise, in a minor key but perceived as happy? Or vice versa - major key but perceived as sad. 

I'm guessing tempo also plays a big part. We associate minor with slow and sombre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 10:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I'm not. But you may very well be. "I could care less" doesn't make any sense at all in this context. None. The phrase you want is "I couldn't care less." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sit in the middle of the bus to prevent travel sickness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 09:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cahir - Cork is the same. Or should I say "was". They changed the timetable. The bus was frequently 1 hour late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to be clear, what you're saying is that you do in fact care about the companies? If even just a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This song is utter shite. In fact, a lot of their songs are utter shite. 

They do put on a good show though, I'll give them that.  Pretty entertaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like the Cahir -Cork route to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 14:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *couldn't* care less you mean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 16:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good advice here. I'm am European and most PhD's here take 3 - 4 years for completion. The time investment is probably the biggest factor in my decision making right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 16:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say slightly, I'd say very different! For the less advanced (certainly when I was an intermediate speaker), getting the correct one out of my mouth in natural speech took a bit of practice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 12:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Off topic, but now that you mentioned it, can I just say that the amount of "...' phrases is pretty tricky! 



Etc  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 21:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kurt Cobain never wanted to do more than one take. His bandmates got around this by saying "John Lennon always did two takes". His response was usually "ok FINE, ill do two takes." If he is adamant on not doing two takes, you can copy the first vocal take on another track and move it slightly left or right on the tracking window by a hair. It'll give a double vocal-esque effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 13:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big thank you to all who replied. I've taken all your comments on board and it's made me rethink my position. Thanks for the input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 13:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my research online, Australian PhD students seem to be very happy. You guys must have a great system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 13:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for that link. Very interesting about students being treated like employees. It's can look similar here in Ireland if one looks from the outside. However you are still indeed a student. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 13:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love this. The B52 style vocals are great and the lyrics are fantastic. I especially loved the "beyond a shadow of doubt" line. The dual vocals work really well and good use of panning. 
The acoustic, bass, and solo guitar play off each other nicely in the solo section. 

The backing vocals at 2:00 are perfect. Very subtle - good use of reverb. I would like to hear a touch more backing vocals to go along with the dual vocals at the end to spice things up further. Maybe just some "ahhhs" to bring climax to the song. 

Good song. The quality of the song pardons any issues in mixing and mastering I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 12:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the kind words. Happy to hear this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 12:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the kind words. Also my favourite part! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there anything good about a PhD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 22:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was considering going down the PhD route as research has always been something that interested me. While browsing the Internet for advice, I found this subreddit. All the information, tales and stories, posts etc. regarding PhDs seem totally negative. Is there any positives to the life of a PhD student? I suddenly feel mad for even considering it as an option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 11:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did biology in CIT myself followed by a course in the arts department in UCC (not history). Though I acknowledge they were different departments, the level of education I got in CIT was much better than UCC. More interaction with the lecturers too. 

I've been in Corl on and off for about 10 years now. It's a bit small and sometimes has a village-y feel and mentality to it but on the whole I'd recommend it. 

Get on the sharing section on Daft.ie and you might get looking with a house who's rent hasn't jumped up yet. Although I'm not sure of your chances being a first year student.  Generally it's professionals only.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 22:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kimoi is indeed the short form of kimochi warui. It's a little rougher. More rude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there, I'm coproducer in a new multi-genre electronic group called ERRA Project. Things have been going well since we started this year with aome good radio time. We're currently branching out into hiphop and are looking for some vocalists. Find us on all the usual social media sites (youtube, soundcloud, Facebook etc.) and get in touch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look for antipruritic spray or cream. It's costly but it takes the itch away completely. Ibuprofen for the pain then. You'll feel totally fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
