<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4227</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sessions is actively trying to Gaslight a community who is now painfully aware of the facts..... Good luck dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if you say you're for open borders but live in the inner city? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you support these budget changes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering the huge amount of resources that have been spent trying to get one big dirty thing on the Clintons for decades... I'm inclined to believe she's likely less corrupt than most people at the level of power in government.

THIS. This is exactly why Trump dropped it once he got into the WH. There was literally nothing to see.

We needed Lisa Simpson, and we got Cartman.. on a bad day.

That's Hilariously true.

IMO both he and Obama should have come out swinging hard for HRC as soon a the primaries were over.

Honestly Obama couldn't of done more cause he was sitting president and Bernie did support her, Bernie's voters just weren't happy about it.


We absolutely can have a third party president. We just need an actual candidate. Stein and Johnson had a dream opportunity for a third party presidency just sucks that they were both terribly incompetent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary's scandals were complete nonsense the biggest thing they found was that she was using a private server to discuss govt business. A private server mind you that was set up during Bill Clinton's presidency for him to use as an email server. I'd be willing to bet that half of our govt officials use private email servers for govt business most of which have not been set up by the secret service.

Hillary was an un-likable candidate that's exactly what i was saying. The DNC thought that they could beat and rep candidate with either Hillary or Bernie so they chose the one that would work with them more. OFC Hillary is not around any more. She got embarrassed, she would have no say with any voters anymore; hence, shes no longer useful. Bernie is still around cause he attracts people with what he says, Hillary doesn't know how to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for a serious discussion... How would cutting govt funding help the people relying on govt funding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary's scandals were nonsense. I think that if he jumped on her platform he could of got more people out to vote. That's the only reason Hillary lost. There was no group of people who were whole heatedly for Hillary. She didn't attract people in the same way that Bernie did.

Well if you read the article above Trump is planning on cutting funding to most of those committees that Bernie chairs... I don't think Hillary would of taken the same approach. + If Hillary did win Bernie probably would of had a more powerful position in Govt. just as Hillary got from Obama when he won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can! And i can tell you that a good portion of them are basically fundamental in keeping the rich from turning the middle / lower class into slave labor.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well when it came to the national scene Bernie did support Hillary for president...

Once primaries were over Bernie had no chance of winning. Too many people right now just vote on party lines for us to elect an independent candidate. He already had attention from the primaries and if he completely joined Hillary's team he could of been put into a position where he could make some change happen.

If you voted for Bernie when it came to national elections (which would have to be a write in since he removed his name from the ballots) you threw your vote away.

(i think u/lastcookies is referring to after the primaries) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he was trying to say that Bernie would of had a higher position under a Hillary Clinton Presidency rather than a Trump presidency..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Issue is China backs North Korea whole heatedly. Who knows what they are willing to do. I don't trust Trump enough to say that he would diplomatically solve an issue with North Korea if a serious one were to arise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Higher than senator....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah Bush wanted to finish the war his father started. He started putting troops back into the middle east at the start of his presidency (before 9/11) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well thank God he split it up into 3 separate tweets all in which he used some form of the phrase "wire taps". He should be able to clearly display a thought in 420 characters right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like corporate executives with the power of presidents. The irony is unreal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but that wasn't in his plan... he only wanted the Muslims to stay out.... *facepalm* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well as of right now hes only blocking Muslim majority countries and he probably doesn't want Muslims staying at his hotels anyway. The same way he didn't want black people in his hotels in the 70's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I'm not saying hes doing it for a good reason. Not at all. I'm just saying he has a very tough job. I mean spinning as much bull shit that this white house puts out on a daily basis!? How does he still have time to spend with his kids? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gotta look out for that sneaky "/s" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really gotta give it up to Sean Spicer. This dude has the most difficult job I've ever seen and he just takes it in strides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot twist: Republicans brainwash people into supporting them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all honesty I don't think Trump supporters understand what globalism entails. I was talking to a trump supporter the other day who said that under globalism we would have a ruling elite of a handful of people who would control every decision you make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally North Korea-level lies. Trump supporters are so terrified of globalism that they are ready to slide right into fascism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cancer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tea party slowly took over. Now the republican party is full of young republicans who don't actually have experience governing only obstructing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strongest part of his argument </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
