<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1459</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 23:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, Trump is killing it so much it's almost scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 23:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Me right now](http://i.imgur.com/KaAGNZu.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 22:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When is he scheduled to speak? It's very low energy right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 22:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it isn't the empathy that is the issue, but a failure to see the consequences of the actions they decided to use to fulfill that empathic urge.

What if the "empathic urge" *is* the reason you fail to see the long-term consequences of your actions. Intense emotions can often make it harder to think clearly and reason through our actions (think about the things you say when you're in a heated argument). If the "empathic urge" gets credit for sparking the good deeds, it should be equally responsible when it sparks the bad deeds.

I'm sure we have no problem admitting that "anger" - however natural and justified - can still be destructive in high doses. I don't see why we can't extend that same sense of balance to "empathy."

But I think we agree on one thing, which is most important: Reason is the intermediate factor here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 22:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gave an example of [animal hoarders](https://www.reddit.com/r/psychology/comments/4bd24y/against_empathy_while_weve_been_taught_that/d18bhuo) in an above comment.  Another popular example would be government legislation designed to help people that ends up having unintended consequences. 

"The road to hell is paved with good intentions" is a popular iteration of this idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 22:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not *just* that feelings can't replace action.

I'd argue that empathy in high doses can actually steer you down a wrong (and less moral) path. And sometimes it's smarter to dim those feelings or even ignore them entirely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 21:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If people can suffer from too little empathy, is it possible you can also suffer from too much empathy? Animal hoarders, for example, are sometimes described as [pathological altruists](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pathological_Altruism). While their hoarding comes from a deep desire to take care of animals in need, they actually end up hurting themselves (and the animals) by not having a sense of limitations and ultimately creating a dirty and toxic environment that harms all parties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 21:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I wouldn't say I'm "against empathy" like Paul Bloom. I just think there are limitations, and that it can also sometimes steer us in a bad direction if we follow our feelings unchecked. Empathy is a gut reaction. It's natural, but like all gut reactions, it can be prone to error too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 20:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really looking forward to Paul Bloom's new book. I remember his article [The Case Against Empathy](http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2013/05/20/the-baby-in-the-well) from a few years ago which I found really insightful and interesting.

I think empathy is clearly a very valuable tool, but like all tools it can be misused and abused. Empathy without a leash can be unintentionally destructive and short-sighted, sometimes you actually need to curb your feelings and act from a more rational standpoint.

One thing to consider is that as groups get larger, you need to think about them in more abstract terms. When we talk about 320 million people in the United States, we can't possibly empathize with all those people (your brain can't possibly do it, ie "Dunbar's Number"). To make intelligent decisions about large groups of people, you often have to weigh statistics over feelings.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 20:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Bernie" and "energy" should never be in the same sentence unless there's a "very low" in there.

He might have even less energy than Benzo Carson.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 01:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please spare me. The left can't shut the fuck up about how Trump is KKK Hitler Nazi Fascist. Those are literally the only words they know anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 01:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree it's wrong, but 10/10 for high energy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 01:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't a KKK supporter. He was a leftist trying to be cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 23:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's up with the millenials in the back just staring at their phones and giggling to each other? GTFO.

EDIT: One of them has a Trump sign but very low energy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 23:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We want to love our protestors...alright, get 'em out!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 17:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Deputy arrives and tells protesters to leave, they're not listening. Deputy calling for backup.](https://twitter.com/Jacobnbc/status/711230770421981184) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 16:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The left has been getting increasingly uglier and more desperate lately. This makes it all the more important not to stoop to their level - we have all the momentum, we can afford to take the high road - let them continue digging their own grave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 14:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be interesting. I bet there's a correlation between far North and far South (colder regions) vs. places closes to equator (hotter regions).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 13:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, it's a pattern or a tendency, but not a steadfast rule.

There's actually some research in the book on Asian Americans and they tend to be more moderate in these effects. And bilingual Asians from Hong Kong could actually be primed to think in both ways (depending on if they are exposed to Western stimuli vs. Eastern stimuli before an experiment).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 23:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The book mostly focuses on psychology experiments, several of which are mentioned in the article.

Of course the West isn't solely responsible for science and technology, but it does seem to be the biggest contributor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 03:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is actually a really likable person when you don't just get your information from Occupy Democrat memes and Huffington Post articles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 16:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #AMERICA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 02:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, definitely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 02:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's not completely true, but partially true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 02:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking it to yourself is often a lot different than hearing it from someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 02:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shared! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 23:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talking points. He hasn't released anything with details. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 23:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is highly unlikely considering Trump hasn't released his plan yet. In fact, it seems the majority of those 21 million people losing insurance comes from what they calculate from the "repeal of Obamacare."

These numbers are extremely rough, in part because Trump's "plan" is more like a set of talking points than a detailed proposal from which analysts could make a firm projection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 20:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TAMPA CUCKS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 20:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SLEEP IS FOR LOSERS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 19:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The honor of being told "GET 'EM OUT" from the almighty Trump. Your friends will be blessed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 17:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  LOVE FEST  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 16:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GET 'EM OUT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 16:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #MONDAYMOTIVATION #HIGHENERGY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 00:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DRUNK FOR AMERICA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 23:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh good, another Trump rally, my energy almost went down for a second there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 17:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the smell of kicking out Sanders supporters in the morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 16:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who needs coffee when you have Trump rallies in the morning. Wew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 01:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's three "Get 'em outs" in a row. Bingo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 01:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throwing out protestors is my new favorite hobby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 20:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who was it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 20:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. There's always something to be insecure about that we can't change, but cleaning yourself up and presenting yourself at your best helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 15:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why would you do that -_-

Because even though social anxiety is painful, I think we all want healthy social interaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 21:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mods already took the post down. Relax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 20:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Context when talking about something Trump said? Mind blown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 19:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand introversion and social anxiety aren't the same thing, but there actually is a correlation.

[Social anxiety and the big 5 personality traits](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/25705989):

It is well established that social anxiety (SA) has a positive relationship with neuroticism and a negative relationship with extraversion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 19:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I share to many reddits, yes, but I don't care about karma - I just like sharing information (and getting people's feedback).

Yes, the article is about social anxiety, but as someone who is both very introverted and has social anxiety, I thought there was a relevant amount of overlap. 

I'm sure there is a significant percentage of people here who also suffer from social anxiety, yes?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 22:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're kind of embarrassing yourself here, talking about how smart and confident and attractive you and all your friends are.

Well, I did say we were narcissists. :)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I say "speak my mind" it's usually not about criticizing a person's character. We argue about things we're passionate about (politics/religion/philosophy/music/etc.). And yes, sometimes things get very heated and sometimes egos may even be bruised (but we get over it quickly).

I understand what you're saying though. My friends are more narcissistic than the average person, but they are also smarter and more accomplished than the average person. They may not be your "typical" narcissist who is more impulsive or superficial. High IQ narcissists are probably more entertaining for me than low IQ narcissists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. Narcissists think they are better than others. That can lead them to treat people poorly, but it can also motivate them to pursue goals that other people wouldn't normally think they are worthy of.

For example, some of my favorite artists and musicians - Frank Zappa, Mike Patton, Kanye West - are all fairly narcissistic. It's a trait I tend to admire in the right doses (though it can certainly go over-board). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Overinflated sense of self-worth
- Thinking you're better than others
- Seeking validation/satus

I know what it means.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, narcissism as a personality trait isn't the same thing as NPD. The original article appears to measure it as a personality trait (on a spectrum). So no, I'm not talking about it as a mental disorder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #FeelTheBern </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We do clash a lot, but we can handle it. Also, I like arguing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 16:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who is fairly narcissistic and has a big ego (though probably doesn't have NPD), I can attest that I do like hanging out with other people who are narcissistic and have big egos.

The reason? I generally don't have to tip-toe around big egos. We both say whatever we want, we can tolerate arguing and debating, and there's less "beating around the bush" when it comes to sharing our thoughts and opinions.

In fact, I tend to admire my more narcissistic friends. They are generally more goal-oriented, ambitious, and confident - they are more likely to have drive and purpose.  And I'd rather be with someone like that than someone who is kind but spineless (and boring). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 21:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, this definitely covers the very basics. I too sometimes get annoyed by the over-saying of "correlation doesn't equal causation," as if to completely dismiss the study, but correlations are still important to find.

Another pet peeve of mine is when people outright dismiss sample sizes when it comes to fMRI studies, which are generally very expensive to conduct and that's why sample sizes tend to be smaller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 19:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you might be onto something there. Are fitness levels correlated with testosterone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 18:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going out on a limb here, but it may be related to measures of psychopathy. Those with high psychopathy tend to be really calm and cool under pressure, and I remember reading that when their bodies go into "fight or flight" mode their heart rates actually *decrease*. In general, they are better able to handle threatening stimuli and thus engage in it with a clear head - while most of us may back away if we were put in the same situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 21:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Evonomics has a lot of interesting authors and good topics covered, but the full articles don't *quite* hit the mark for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 21:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, thanks. I share a lot of stuff in a lot of places, but it all comes from sites and feeds I actually like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 18:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listening to it right now -  really great mix of warm, digital, glitchy soundscapes that groove. It makes me want to get the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 16:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop, my penis can only get so erekt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 18:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually misinterpreting this as "pinching" - I sometimes pinch my skin when I have a severe headache and it seems to distract me from the pain a little bit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 16:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump would've taken her sweater before he kicked her out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 02:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, being shamed can sometimes have a backfire effect, causing the person to just rationalize their behavior more and be even less willing to change in face of social pressure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 19:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interestingly "Nonviolent Communication" is next on my reading list!

Another related good read is "Crucial Conversations." (I wrote an article about it [here](http://www.theemotionmachine.com/how-to-defuse-heated-arguments-before-they-spiral-out-of-control) on how it applies to conflict resolution and defusing heating arguments). The diagram in the middle is a particularly helpful way of looking at communication. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 02:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once an hour seems a little excessive to me, but if you are going to practice a [STOP Meditation](http://www.theemotionmachine.com/stop-daily-injections-of-mindfulness-1) the general protocol is:

**How to Practice STOP Meditation**

- STOP what youre doing.

- TAKE a few deep breaths, focusing on the sensations of your breathing. This helps reconnect you with the present moment and also creates a buffer between your thoughts and your actions.

- OBSERVE what is going on. Ask yourself:

 -What am I thinking?

 -What am I feeling?

 -What am I doing?

 -What are my intentions?

- PROCEED with your day with this new sense of mindful awareness (based on how you answered the questions above).

It's not complicated. Just a few seconds to step back, breathe, and reflect on what you're doing. 

After this short meditation, you may find that you should be doing something "better" with your time (for example, you caught yourself searching Facebook while at work) - or you may just proceed with exactly what you were doing before.

Hope this helps a bit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 21:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Full Paper](http://faculty.haas.berkeley.edu/srivastava/papers/Virtues%20and%20Vices%2009122015%20FINAL%20REVISION.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 21:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Full Paper](http://faculty.haas.berkeley.edu/srivastava/papers/Virtues%20and%20Vices%2009122015%20FINAL%20REVISION.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 21:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Full Paper](http://faculty.haas.berkeley.edu/srivastava/papers/Virtues%20and%20Vices%2009122015%20FINAL%20REVISION.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 18:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of my longer (and more informative) articles, yet it doesn't seem to be getting the attention I think it deserves. 

I'm guessing a lot of people find the headline a little cheesy or cliche - can any of you think of a better title?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 15:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy this release a lot, but it *feels* like a collection of B-sides from previous albums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 19:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where these biases really come into play - and hurt the social sciences - is when it comes to seeking research grants on certain topics and getting published in peer reviewed journals when getting results that don't fit a certain narrative. That's why it matters that liberals make up 80-90% of the academics in social sciences. There's an inherit group bias there, especially in fields that are already very politically-motivated. (It's pretty ironic that the same people who preach skin-level diversity have such an intellectual monoculture, and don't see how their own biases have become systematic and self-reinforcing). We see this most notably in sociology, which consistently undermines biological influences and favors theories of social constructivism (essentially, as a rule). It's an actual problem. Diversity in ideas should be a primary goal at colleges. E.O. Wilson had the right idea bringing biology and evolutionary theory more into the social sciences, Steven Pinker has been carrying that torch now too, but there's still a lot more work to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 18:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Distributed cognition." Never heard that term, but I really like it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 18:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually found it to be a really nice moment of comic relief in an otherwise very tense and high strung episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 15:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This distinction is also why, as a former libertarian, I'm very sympathetic toward nationalism. 

I believe in the principle of *decentralization.* I have a strong individualist mentality (always have, it's in my biology), but I still see the value in siding with the local community over the state government, or the state government over the federal government, or the nation-state over globalism.

As groups get bigger, it's harder to manage them (see Hayek). There's a value in decentralizing power, the use of knowledge, and giving people the power to make decisions that affect them personally (or their "local sphere").

Applying this to nationalism, American people are allowed to side with themselves, they don't need to save the whole world.* This desire also brings out our imperialistic tendencies - it's why we make "bad deals" all over the world. But we are *allowed* to choose America over "world government." (and I don't mean that in a conspiratorial way)

Honestly, it comes down to respecting differences in how people govern themselves. Progressives are globalists though, they think their idea of "rights" is just true, and that's that. They can't recognize that other people may want to live under different moral codes.

*P.S. - We don't actually have the knowledge or capabilities to save the whole world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 01:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ctrl+F'd this and 1905. Glad one of them came up - *amazing* album! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 01:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **1905** - *Voice* 

Really great political screamo/anarcho punk band from Washington. Album was released in 2004.

**Gospel** - *The Moon Is A Dead World*

Another post-hardcore band from 2004/2005. But lots of southern rock and progressive rock influence here. Really unique flavor of rock. The drumming on this album is *insane*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 02:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Treating professional servers with respect

Yes. Too many people think "It's me who is paying you, so I get to treat you like shit if you aren't satisfactory." The truth is, even with most bad waiters, it isn't worth it to call them out. Keeping the peace is more important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 01:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [She actually is bipolar](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_people_with_bipolar_disorder#B), apparently. Not surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 18:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. Thanks for the analysis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 18:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's back up! Got an unexpected spike in traffic this morning and it crashed me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 16:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 50% of my submissions here are from this domain. Yes, it's my website.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 05:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm fine with leaning more offbeat rather than gorey. I remember liking Carnage, I should rewatch it. Thanks for the recommendations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 00:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Cheap Thrills" has a similar theme too. David Koechner is a hilarious madman in it, he's basically some rich psychopath who makes 2 random people he met at a bar compete for his money. Very suspenseful. Kinda similar to "Funny Games" too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 16:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the article isn't about Kahneman. That's just a picture from the sidebar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 16:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 19:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. It's interesting because I liked this article, even though I'm not a socialist, because I see this same conflation made from the opposite angle. "You hate socialism? I guess you're not using those roads or police or schools."

The word has become completely muddled from both sides. I actually blame libertarians for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 19:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the recommendation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 19:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't recommend consciously trying to inject emotion into your speech when in an actual social interaction. This is an exercise to do on your own, just to become more aware of different vocal attributes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 19:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you liked it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 16:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good suggestion! I need to add some video game soundtracks to my playlist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 15:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Why is /r/ZenHabits not just about Zen?](http://www.reddit.com/r/ZenHabits/comments/zo9n8/why_is_rzenhabits_not_just_about_zen/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 21:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you liked it! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 21:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most Americans aren't poor though. The majority of Americans are doing quite well, especially compared to the rest of the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 17:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was super depressed, I used to listen to a lot of avant-garde and harsh noise music. Just something that completely broke down my mental constructs and helped me tap into a more primitive state of being. It was cathartic. I needed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 16:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it a little subjective though?

**Acquaintance**:

a person one knows slightly, but who is not a close friend.

What about a friend who isn't a "close friend?"

The people I'm talking about I consider to be a friend and they consider me to be a friend too. We are not super close, where we have deep conversations every night, but yeah, we are friends.

**Friend:**

 a person who you like and enjoy being with

By this definition, we are most definitely friends. Seems like a lot of room between these two definitions.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 15:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I clearly said, you can keep in contact with them on Facebook, and even meet up with them again potentially. 

That is a different type of relationship than just someone I talked to in the stores once and literally have no way to get back in contact with.

There are some people who I haven't seen off Facebook in years, but I've been to a few shows with them and I chat with them every now and then. That's a little more than an acquaintance to me.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 03:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last of the Mohicans

Thanks, adding it to my playlist! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 02:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would consider an acquaintance someone I run into once at a store or bar and never see or hear from again. But if I'm friends with you on Facebook, there's always new opportunities to interact, even if it's just sharing new music or meeting up for another show. I would consider these people friends of mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 21:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's true that people's ability to have meaningful relationships is limited ([Dunbar's Number](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dunbar%27s_number)). Though I also think that social media has increased this number slightly, giving us more opportunity to maintain "weak ties" with a greater amount of people. 

I have over 600 friends on Facebook, and I recognize most of them by name along with a couple personality traits. ("Oh John likes the same type of metal as me" + "We went to that one show together, that was fun.")  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 17:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very true, although this article focuses more on music for motivation.

However, when I think about more intense emotional drama, *The Fountain* by Clint Mansell is a fantastic soundtrack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 19:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, game over already? Panthers aren't fucking around one bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 05:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DUDE OMFG IM WEARING CHEESE ON MY HEAD WOT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 05:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 03:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 01:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Onside kick time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 18:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm amazing. Where's my gold sticker?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are a general self improvement subreddit.

Please see our sidebar: [Why is /r/ZenHabits not just about "Zen?"](http://www.reddit.com/r/ZenHabits/comments/zo9n8/why_is_rzenhabits_not_just_about_zen/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 17:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have setlist?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 00:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Visiting" is a good way of putting it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 16:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interestingly enough, James does argue in favor of a belief in "God" or "Oneness" from a pragmatic viewpoint (providing feelings of comfort and security), as long as the belief doesn't get in the way of pursuing other forms of truth. This is why one big component of pragmatism is the notion of "pluralistic truth." 

As a soft atheist, I've come to a similar conclusion myself. I think the concept of "God" *works* for some people, and there's nothing wrong with that, as long as it doesn't get in the way of understanding science, or other philosophies and scopes of truth, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 00:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Though the study mentioned looked at perceived competence, and even asking basic questions seemed to improve that appearance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 19:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you not following? 

There's a difference between saying "Boycott the 2022 Olympics" and "Guys, slavery is bad, am I rite?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 19:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slavery is practiced today in the middle east. And by one of the US's major allies there, Saudi Arabia. Will you be supporting the 2022 Olympics in Qatar built with slave labor? Qatar's World Cup 'slaves'. Do you feel moved to express your disgust and disapproval over Qatar's treatment of it's Nepalese workers? I sure as hell do.

This is *exactly* why I started by asking you, "Where are you fighting against slavery?" I *realize* slavery still exists in parts of the world, but now we're getting somewhere more concrete than mere virtue signaling: boycotting the 2022 Olympics. Now you're not just expressing disgust, you're also providing a means to make a concrete difference.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 18:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So do you believe it is wrong to express disgust about slavery?

No, I don't believe it's "wrong." It's just kind-of pointless since the majority of people are disgusted by slavery already. It's not like you're really sticking your neck out to change public opinion. So I don't think it's a signal that really needs to be *boosted* in most of today's world.

Do you never indicate you favor certain ideas?

I do. I definitely signal, everyone does. And I'm certainly signaling right now.

But usually I signal when I have something unpopular that needs to be said, because I believe it needs to be said. I'm trying to *boost* signals that I feel need *boosting*. 

Signaling for obvious truths that literally everyone is taught non-stop in schools is not my idea of a good use of signaling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 18:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's super brave of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 18:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you actively fighting against slavery? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 20:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this album is fucking amazing.

Didn't they also do a split with Merzbow?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 20:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's on my sidebar. You probably don't see it on mobile or tablet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 20:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I explained why in my original post. The short answer is: because markets are shaped by cultural values. 

For example, a "free market" that values science, technology, hard work, and education is going to look radically different than a "free market" that values nothing but drug abuse, sex, and temporary highs - even if in both cases all market actors are interacting voluntarily.

**Please note:** Before you jump the gun, I'm not saying "Use force on all the drug addicts and lock them up!" I'm saying, "Culture matters to markets, so shouldn't libertarians be more interested in spreading certain social values beyond *just* freedom?"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 19:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  By "tell them" he means "force with violence," not talk to them peacefully and try to change their minds.


That's not what I said though. Anarchocapitalists taking a more active stance on cultural issues (discussing them, pushing certain cultural or social values - besides just "economic freedom") doesn't require forcing with violence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 17:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  1) If that's really what the vast majority wants, how can you (the minority) tell them "they're wrong" or "they should want something else"?

You mean, what anarchocapitalists do all the time when they tell people they should want free markets and are wrong for liking governments?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 19:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm definitely not denying the usefulness of skepticism or epistemology (or philosophy). I'm a habitual devil's advocate - I think strongly challenging and testing beliefs plays an important role in discovering where a belief fits in our "scope of truth." 

However, when I mention the Matrix, I'm thinking specifically about the [brain in a vat](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brain_in_a_vat) problem ("We're all in a simulation!"). It's an interesting idea that plays off of an "obvious" truth (we can't step outside of our minds), but it doesn't provide much practical value beyond intellectual fancying (which is fine, but it's nothing more than that). I feel a similar way about David Chalmers [philosophical zombies](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Philosophical_zombie) too. 

Don't get me wrong, I think thought experiments *can* be valuable (I like many of the ones Daniel Dennett describes in his book [Intuition Pumps And Other Tools for Thinking](http://amzn.to/1JQ4Kgr)), but they also have a tendency to come off more insightful than they really are. 

I recognize philosophy as very important and very practical to know (in general), but some philosophy is definitely *more* practical than others. That's the lesson I gain from pragmatism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 17:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 17:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full disclosure: I wrote the article and I've always had an affinity for pragmatism.

I do think there are some limitations to pragmatism, however:

- According to James, if a belief makes us "feel good" it could be considered pragmatically valid. I'm generally OK with this, I don't get super upset if people believe in "God" or "Oneness" as long as it doesn't get in the way of them pursuing other truths.

- Technically, telling a lie may bring you a desired result, even though you are telling a lie. So if a parent tries their child's broccoli and says out-loud, "Mmm..this is really good!" - it is a subtle form of lying, even though it may eventually lead to the child eating their broccoli. The pragmatic value of "lying" is probably one of the better arguments against the truth of pragmatism.

However, overall I think pragmatism is a mindset we have to keep in mind whenever we philosophize. I don't mind diving into abstract ideas, thought experiments, and intellectual curiosities, but I think getting *too* caught up in these things without recognizing any practical consequences can be a trap.

Curious to hear your guys thoughts. This post got a little beat up on [/r/decidingtobebetter](https://www.reddit.com/r/DecidingToBeBetter/comments/3yxevz/when_philosophy_cant_be_applied_to_our_real_world/) and [/r/zenhabits](https://www.reddit.com/r/ZenHabits/comments/3z2baq/when_philosophy_cant_be_applied_to_our_real_world/), though I think a big part of it is that I used a badly worded quote for the headline of the submission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 17:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet, I'm struggling to really think of an example of a non-"practical" part of philosophy.

The article mentions a couple examples. One that I commonly think about is the "we are all just living in a brain simulation" hypothesis. It's technically unprovable, but it's something people spend a lot of time philosophizing about (see "The Matrix"). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 17:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This article is stupidly judgmental and more pointless than any philosophical argument I've ever heard. Judgement is the most un-zen thing I can think of and it has no place in our lives.

This sounds kinda judgmental to me. Perhaps pragmatism isn't the best answer to everything, but certainly you can see some value in the perspective? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 04:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. And James acknowledges that beliefs like "God" and "Oneness" can be valid from a pragmatic standpoint if they provide feelings of love, comfort and security.

That being said, I think the overall philosophy of pragmatism is pretty insightful and I recommend checking out some of the other quotes in the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 00:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm using philosophy/belief system/"mental framework" all interchangeably here.

But certainly you'd admit that some belief systems are more practical than others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 20:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My reply is the same as the other one. [See here](https://www.reddit.com/r/DecidingToBeBetter/comments/3yxevz/when_philosophy_cant_be_applied_to_our_real_world/cyhiw5s).

Perception and reality are interdependent, but that is *not* the same thing as saying "perception creates reality." The causation goes both ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 20:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, thanks for the feedback, I will try my best to address some of your points.

It talks about how useless conjecturing about abstract ideas is as it conjectures about abstract ideas.

I don't think James (nor I) reject the use of abstract ideas. We just feel that, at the end of the day, those abstract ideas ultimately need to be recognized in concrete and experiential terms.

It also makes the assumption that unless we directly experience these 'real' benefits and identify them, they don't exist. Meaning in order to actually benefit from a thing you have to be conscious of the benefit it has on your life.

No, I don't assume that at all. I think most people aren't aware of the benefits (or costs) of their beliefs, except on maybe a surface level. 

Pragmatism certainly *recommends* trying to be more aware of the consequences of your beliefs, but it doesn't assume that is automatically the case. 

 I prefer to side with Kant on this topic wherein I believe that philosophy provides a mental model through which we experience the universe and make decisions. If you think about the human mind and thought in terms of an energetic system, it requires energy to make decisions, energy to apply judgements, energy to know which judgements to apply. Mental frameworks reduce this energy. You don't have to think about the afterlife if your framework has an answer for you. You don't have to go through the effort of finding out what the goal of existence is if your framework says there's no goal in existence. These frameworks make thought more efficient, giving us more energy to make more decisions.

I agree with all of this. 

Frameworks ("belief systems") provide utility, and yes, I think a big part of that utility is saving mental effort from having to consciously think out every situation we encounter in our lives. 

In general, we don't need our frameworks to be right all the time (they aren't, and probably never will be) - we just need them to be right *enough* to not cause us any serious problems. Most of the time, it's only when we get a real "shock" from life where we are motivated to change our existing framework in a big way. 

I'm not sure James' thoughts on Kant exactly.

Thanks for the reply. It's helping me think out these ideas more thoroughly.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 20:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I don't know quantum mechanics well at all. And neither do most people who use it to promote the "consciousness creates reality" idea.

What I do know - however - is that laws which are true at one scale of reality aren't necessarily true for other scales of reality. Newtonian mechanics is true for a lot of our everyday experiences, but those physical laws don't necessarily translate to quantum mechanics.

I find the idea that the behavior of particles is representative of the whole of reality tends to be an overly reductionist approach that ignores these different "scales" of reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 19:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> William James would probably say perception and reality are interdependent.

It's true that your mind adds, subtracts, and distorts reality to fit a certain point-of-view. But it's also true that reality has a component that isn't completely subjective. We know this because we can observe the same phenomenon across different minds (gravity isn't a creation of your mind, everyone experiences it).

There was actually a relevant quote about this from James I was going to include in the article but didn't:

"Does the river make its banks, or do the banks make the river? Does a man walk with his right leg or with his left leg more essentially? Just as impossible may it be to separate the real from the human factors in the growth of our cognitive experience."

So this quote acknowledges that mind and matter are entangled phenomenon, but it does *not* imply that mind is the sole creator of reality. 

Buddhism has a similar view on interdependent origination.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 19:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a good point. William James actually does entertain the argument that beliefs in God or "Oneness" can be pragmatically valid because they make people "feel good." 

I guess the real kicker is getting lost in these abstractions when they *don't* make us feel good, but instead make us worry and endlessly contemplate. "Is there really a God?" / "Am I just living in a simulation?" / etc.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 18:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perception creates reality.

Not exactly. And you're actually committing an error that is talked about in the article - you're taking the "observer effect" in quantum mechanics and then generalizing it as an over-arching theory of reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, eye contact is really intense for me too, I often have to look away when talking to people. It's not even a "shy" thing necessarily, it's just an overload of information I get when looking at people's faces (reading emotions, microexpressions, etc.)

I do think this study is mimicking a meditative-like effect, but I think the social aspect of it is relevant to why the effect is so quick and strong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, I do find there to be a different quality when staring into the eyes of another living being vs. just staring at any old object to meditate on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 16:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you pick up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 19:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also want to thank this subreddit for supporting a lot of the articles I post here. You guys give a lot of love, and I appreciate it immensely.

Are there any topics you'd like me to write about more in 2016? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 20:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Cruz is correct that people convicted of a violent crime are more likely to identify as Democrats than as Republicans. But people convicted of violent crimes arent more likely to identify as Democratic than non-violent offenders.

Um, that doesn't make him wrong. All that means is both violent AND non-violent criminals tend to identify as Democrats.

What a misleading load of bull. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 17:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This effect also reminded me of: [mean world syndrome](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mean_world_syndrome). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 05:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's popular in some circles to hate Rand, but I stand by this choice wholeheartedly. I find there is a lot that is compatible between Rand's writings and self improvement. And in many ways her philosophy embodies the whole "man is his own hero" ideal. 

If you want a direct example of the connections between self help and Ayn Rand, check out the classic "Six Pillars of Self Esteem" by Nathaniel Branden, who was a long time associate of Rands and was very influenced by Objectivism.

I also recommend checking out Anthem before jumping to conclusions, it's only 50 pages. It's all about the dangers of conformity and celebrating mediocrity and ignorance (it takes place in a future "dark ages" where everyone uses candles and the protagonist rediscovers electricity).

Rand's not perfect, and say whatever you want about her politics, but not being able to see *any* connection between her ideas and self improvement sounds a bit shortsighted and dismissive to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 03:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of good writings from Stoicism on death and grieving. I just finished Epictetus' *The Enchiridion* which has some good passages.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 02:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that one too but I'd consider it too long for this article. Everything mentioned is 100 pages or less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 18:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the paper is supposed to be tongue-in-cheek.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 00:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very fair reporting from what I can tell, though I don't sense that much "fear and loathing" from the rally attendees...in fact, their responses seemed surprisingly cool and "matter of fact" in their tone. I'm actually shocked they couldn't find a few real nutcases (I'm sure they were there, as with any big group of people). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 15:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  #10 jazz foty meme for pop culture critics to pretend like they care about jazz (the white colin stetson) (matana roberts but not good)

This was the most triggering for me. Isn't Kamasi black and Stetson white? Also, none of those 3 albums (Kamasi Washington, Colin Stetson, or Matana Roberts) sound alike to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 05:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's a picture from the sidebar, a book about cognitive psychology and decision-making called "Thinking, Fast and Slow." Highly recommended! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 18:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mentioned children because it's an obvious (and undeniable) example of living vicariously through other people's success. But my point was to take that principle and extend it further out to family, community, and nation. 

(Also, it's arguable that parents overestimate the impact they have on their children's successes and failures - consider genes, socioeconomic status, education/school, random chance, etc. - but that's a whole other conversation). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 18:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about your brother or sister? Or nephew? 

What about your neighbor? Or coworker?

You can be proud of things and enjoy people's success even though you didn't play a direct role in it, simply because you feel connected to them and you know them and you like to see them do well.

I think it's a really natural impulse actually. Nationalism is a bit bigger and more abstract, but it's the same principle (just applied toward a bigger "tribe").

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 17:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this any different than having pride for your family or community? Sure, your connection to them isn't by choice, but you still feel that you're a part of it and that it's a part of you.

If a parent is proud that their child gets a successful job and is happily married, is that wrong because the parent is taking pride in someone else's accomplishment? Are we not allowed to feel connected to other people's success? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 15:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're genuinely interested in why someone might want a "small dose" of psychopathy, I recommend checking out the book "The Wisdom of Psychopaths." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 15:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's not the definition. That's the reframe, so yeah, it's changing the meaning. 

Keep in mind, narcissism doesn't just refer to "narcissistic personality disorder" (NPD). Narcissism is also recognized as a personality trait that everyone has to some degree. Studies show that scoring moderately high on this personality trait can lead to certain positive outcomes.

Also related: [healthy narcissism](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Healthy_narcissism), though this term originated from Freud and psychoanalysis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 00:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, though I *do* find it funny how Deafheaven is literally the only metal band indie rockers seem to talk about.

Kinda interesting, but I saw them open for Russian Circles in support of "Roads to Judah" awhile back. I remember being surprised at a black metal band opening for RC, but I enjoyed it. It provided an excellent contrast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 00:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their last album Sunbather was a big hit with the Pitchfork/hipster crowd, lots of people thought it was a unique blend of black metal/shoegaze/post-rock. 

I actually liked Sunbather too. Though the highlights for me were the post-rock interludes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 20:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every list is biased. What's your point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 19:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was pleasantly surprised by this list (though I would've put VHOL, Mgla, Misyrming a bit higher). My only real complaint is no "Sigh" - I find their new album super fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 18:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odd, the link works fine for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 23:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This a great band and album to know. 

Also, the song [Man from Manhattan](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zz-9VPA1duM) off their second album has a very post-rocky build that is another must-listen and way ahead of its time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 18:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't. A lot of other people do. That's why Trump is doing so well.

It is what it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 18:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think whatever you want about Trump, but the point is he has caused the left to go into full panic mode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's the thing. The right is sick and tired of being shamed and ridiculed by the left. There's a left-bias in most news, media, academia, and entertainment. Trump has single-handedly undermined all of that, and that's why the right sees him as a type of "hero." 

Basically, Trump is a symptom of a cultural war more-so than a political war - and that's a war that the left started. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 20:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I did](https://www.reddit.com/r/psychology/comments/3vhi7q/how_a_rebellious_scientist_uncovered_the/), it didn't get much attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 18:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the claim is pretty easy to corroborate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 19:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's definitely not what I'm saying. It's still possible to do your own research and learn more about a subject through articles, books, documentaries, videos, etc.  You don't have to just take "science man" at his word. 

Dogmatism means believing in something without looking at the evidence. You don't have to be a scientist or expert to not be dogmatic, but you should actually care about the facts and not just regurgitate something because popular science guy on TV says so and that's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 17:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dogmatism doesn't necessarily mean you're wrong. Perhaps that's where there is some confusion. 

However, you're right that there are much better topics to choose from when testing liberal dogmatism.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 17:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say "you have to read all the scientific studies." Of course it's perfectly reasonable to err with the experts when it comes to a subject you don't know much about. I don't have a problem with that.

However, the type of liberal I'm thinking about probably can't even name a single expert in climate science. All they do is "like" and "share" Neil Degrasse Tyson and Bill Nye quotes on the "I fucking love science" Facebook page. That's the extent of their scientific knowledge and activism. And, at its worst, they often do this with the attitude that they are so much "smarter" and "above" conservatives because they can science.

Every movement has its fair share of dummies, and every movement can become dogmatic on certain things. Yes, even liberals. 

(As a related side note, many environmentalists also dabble in the whole organic, gluten free, anti-GMO trends that are mostly bullshit. And the worst of them go into new age, crystal worship stuff.)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 15:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But "science says!" doesn't demonstrate an understanding of the facts. I've met many liberals who have never read a single study about climate change or looked at any numbers, they are merely relaying information from authority*. That's a type of dogmatism to me.

*To clarify further: It's one thing to side with the experts on a subject you know nothing about. It's another thing when you probably can't even name a single expert in that subject, and instead just "like" and "share" catchy Bill Nye quotes on the "I fucking love science" page.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 17:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an atheist. But when someone says "I'll pray for you," I just tell them "thanks" - because I'm not an asshole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 16:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're in the middle of practicing meditation, it's okay to shift from negative thinking back to the breath. Don't see it as repression, just re-focusing.

That being said, there may come a time where you do want to analyze your anxiety more closely. Perhaps even do a meditation where the anxiety itself is the "object of meditation." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 16:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's FPP?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 22:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're probably disagreeing on semantics, but I don't find there to be anything selfish about wanting to serve something outside of yourself.  It's not about "wanting to be bigger," but recognizing that "there is something bigger" than you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great video. There have been quite a few articles about this topic coming out recently. I actually wrote one myself a few weeks ago: 

[The Powerful Lesson "Inside Out" Teaches Us About Emotional Intelligence](http://www.theemotionmachine.com/the-powerful-lesson-inside-out-teaches-us-about-our-emotions). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. Nonsense can be a good way to exercise the more creative faculties in your mind. In hypnosis, they often use confusion to induce states of trance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 18:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe try /r/selfimprovement or /r/howtonotgiveafuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 17:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I AM CALM!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 16:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a really bad methodology and conclusion. They essentially asked men if they experienced feelings such as "irritable," "more tired than normal," "increased cravings," and "easily upset" on a monthly basis. Then they took these symptoms and called it "man period." 

The men didn't actually say or agree that they get "man periods." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 07:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is that a failing of modern social science? From what I gather, Rand's philosophy is basically non-existent in the social sciences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 04:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found this bit particularly interesting:

What makes these violations of moral rules so instructive is how societies choose to deal with them. Ultimately, it all comes down to gossip. More than tool-making, art, or even language, gossip is a human universal that is a defining feature of our species (though this could change if we ever learn to translate the complex communication system in whales or dolphins). Gossip is intimately connected with the moral rules of a given society, and individuals gain or lose prestige in their group depending on how well they follow these rules. This formation of group opinion is something to be feared, particularly in small rural communities where ostracism or expulsion could mean death. Public opinion, facilitated by gossiping, always guides the bands decision process, Boehm writes, and fear of gossip all by itself serves as a preemptive social deterrent because most people are so sensitive about their reputations. A good reputation enhances the prestige of those individuals who engage in altruistic behavior, while marginalizing those with a bad reputation. Since prestige is intimately involved with how desirable a person is to the opposite sex, gossip serves as a positive selection pressure for enhancing traits associated with altruism. That is, being good can get you laid, and this will perpetuate your altruistic genes (or, at least, those genes that allow you to resist cheating other members of your group). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 16:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone notice the paradox in that not everyone can follow their passion, but that everyone can do their duty

Yes! I wanted to explicitly mention this in the article. "Passion" requires searching, but "duty" is right in front of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 01:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added a description as to why it's related. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 01:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? It's completely related. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 18:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And rebellion is often another act of violence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 14:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there an official video for this? I've only seen "Vanity" from this album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 16:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are similar because they both heighten awareness of a given situation, but different because "mindfulness" is usually more conscious and deliberate, while people can fall into "flow" unconsciously. 

For example, a person can go into "flow" while playing a video game (complete engagement, lack of self, merging of consciousness and action), but they aren't necessarily *mindful* that they are in a state of flow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 14:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was /r/seduction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 01:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I originally wrote this for a dating forum for guys, so that's why it's from that vantage point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 18:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a complete problem with people engaging in "harmless placebos" either, as long as you're not substituting them for real medical treatment. But as a "supplementary treatment?" Knock yourself out! If it lessens stress and anxiety, it could contribute to better medical outcomes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 04:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 17:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was *literally* raised Muslim by Palestinians. [I'm not joking.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nidal_Hasan#Early_life) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 17:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was first generation though - parents immigrated from Palestine -- that could've played a role in alienation and anti-American views. It's not completely irrelevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 17:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was first generation though - parents immigrated from Palestine -- that could've played a role in alienation and anti-American views. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 05:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another 2 week wait? Cause of Thanksgiving this time? UGH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 05:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I know they did this last season, but have they done it before that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 04:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely noticed that too. Awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 04:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/mindfulness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 02:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mindfulness is usually about focusing your awareness *toward a specific thing*.

For example, the most common exercise is "mindfulness of breathing" = just paying attention to the motions of your breathing. 

Sure, your mind *will* get distracted and drift toward other things. But the point is to catch yourself when you get distracted, take a mental note ("I got distracted"), then *refocus* your attention back to the object of meditation.

A great beginner exercise is to start with what I call the "[100 breaths meditation](http://www.theemotionmachine.com/100-breaths-meditation)."

(P.S. There's another form of meditation which I call [open mind meditation](http://www.theemotionmachine.com/open-mind-meditation) which is just watching whatever enters your consciousness, but this is a more advanced exercise.)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 22:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like when you get super conscious of how you walk when going on a stage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
