<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8542</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 23:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understood. I honestly didn't know that, and will keep that in mind. That being said, is it completely wrong to keep it on your person and have it slightly visible? I'll often drape mine over my hands when I become anxious at work, on public transit, etc. simply to use as an aid in counting my breaths.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 23:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. I would love to be able to afford a very good one eventually, but only if it's from the right place. It seems like they've become sort of trendy accessories sold on uppity yoga gear websites under the facade of some kind of magical crystal object, which is a shame. 

There's actually a very popular high-end yoga clothing website that sold them for awhile. Of course, they didn't even call them mala beads, just "meditation beads." The guru bead had the clothing brand's logo on it, and they sold them for $108. They put out a statement saying that they cost $108 as a "reflection of the spiritual number."

Yep. Yyyyeeeepppp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a relatively new Buddhist, coming from a sectarian Christian background. How can I overcome my obsession with wanting to choose the "right" way to be a Buddhist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 23:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was raised a strict Pentecostal Christian - for roughly 15 years, it was drilled into my head that our brand of Christianity was the only true form of Christianity - all the other sects aren't good enough, aren't Christlike enough, et cetera. I stopped considering myself a Christian a few years ago, but as many of you probably know, the ideas that we are taught as children often stay with us far longer than we'd like them to.

Lately, as I'm becoming more serious about finding a Sangha and incorporating Buddhism into my everyday life, I'm having difficulty parting with this childhood mindset. I find myself jumping back and forth between the various schools, unsure of which one is the "right" one, afraid that I will pick the "wrong" practices and not be a "real" Buddhist. I know that sounds silly, but this mindset has been very difficult for me to overcome.

Did anyone else find themselves struggling with this at any point, especially those of you who come from a sectarian Christian background? Have you ever changed which school or branch you studied? How can you overcome the indecisiveness?

Answers would be much appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 23:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, thank you! This is far more informative and thorough than I expected, and I really appreciate it.

I also have a simple rosewood Mala, and I planned on taking that one with me when I go to public services - that's the one that I often keep on my person. Unfortunately, the red stain on the beads is beginning to wear off - as I unfortunately noticed when I had it wrapped around my hand for a while last week, and then unraveled it to find a blotch of tiny red bead-shaped spots on my skin! - which is why I thought it might be nice to make my own.

To be honest, the one that I made is moreso for my own use. Crafting is a very relaxing and soothing activity for me, and so I thought that it might be nice to make one solely for use at home, hence why I used the vibrant colors and pendants. I'd never heard of the practice of keeping one for private use, and that's definitely something I'll keep in mind. 

That being said, this really is very helpful to know. I appreciate you explaining this to me. I was worried that I would be faced with condescension since I'm relatively new to Buddhism, but it's nice to be met with a genuine, informative answer. I'll be the first to admit that I often fall victim to being drawn to visual objects solely for their beauty (I partially blame my ADD, ha!) and this was a nice reminder to be mindful of seeing the underlying purpose in things that have surface-level beauty.

Thank you. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 21:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really into the adult coloring book trend, to be honest. I also just really like to draw my own designs. And I like to combine watercolors, ink, pencils...whatever medium I can find. I struggle with anxiety and ADD, and I've found that coloring patterns to be immensely helpful in soothing me whenever I feel really high-strung. 

I should take some pictures when I go back to work on Tuesday - they're all hanging up at my desk. :) 

Aside from that: making other crafts, various types of volunteer work, nature-ing, cooking. Currently trying to get back in the swing of vegetarianism after a 10-month break from an otherwise successful 2-year streak of not eating meat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 21:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean no disrespect, but could you please point me to some of these teachings regarding how a Mala should be made and cared for? 

I actually did do extensive research (and no, I don't mean I just read the Wikipedia page) on Mala beads before I decided it would be okay to make my own, and I would be more than happy to read information that I'm not aware of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 06:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, thank you! It was surprisingly easy to make, aside from having to put beads with tiny little holes onto very thick string - it was definitely a good opportunity to practice patience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Made my own mala necklace! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 06:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 19:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some really great recommendations here. I've also struggled with my weight for several years. I'm particularly guilty of eating large amounts in one sitting, without even being that hungry. I don't necessarily think that you need to sacrifice the pleasure of enjoying a good meal; I, too, love new foods, new recipes, interesting ingredients. I think that it's moreso about reining in the temptation to be OVER-indulgent.

It may sound silly, but I've found that trying to maintain mindfulness while eating often helps. Focus on the textures, the taste, the origins of the food, the effort it took to prepare the food, the nourishment that it will provide your body. When you grant so much attention to your food, you'll typically end up eating more slowly, and it will be much easier to recognize when you're full. There's a gap of time between eating a meal and feeling physically full, and we often eat so quickly that we don't realize how stuffed we are until we've already consumed far more than we needed.

Another recommendation: don't fall into the trap of thinking that radical, sudden changes are the key to weight loss. I've lost roughly 20 pounds in the past few months, and I did so by making small, gradual changes over a long period of time. When people decide they'd like to lose weight, we want to see drastic results in a short amount of time; such a regimen is very difficult to begin, and even harder to maintain. Establish a few small goals for yourself (x amount of water each day, x amount of sleep each night, x amount of exercise each week, etc.) and approach them one at a time, rather than trying to tackle them all at once.

Best of luck to you. :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 14:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tricycle Talks are really good if you're looking for discussion and learning that isn't too heavy. I listen to them during my morning commute, because they don't require intense focus, but they're still really interesting. 

As far as Dharma talks, Zencast is the best I've found so far. There are a few hundred episodes, too, so there's content for just about every subject and for every level of practitioner. The talks are a bit lengthier and more in-depth, so they may not be as good for "background noise" (I typically take notes when I listen to them) but I would still highly recommend. 

Hope you enjoy. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
