<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6412</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 09:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 09:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, well, what can I tell ya? Depression's a helluva thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 09:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God willing... god willing.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 09:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. I'll do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-04 09:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Bastards! But no, we don't give em out for free. Shitty chain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 19:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily one that goes south, but kinda strange nonetheless. One night about a month ago, there was this young couple (late teens) sitting in the section next to mine. It was late and as I was cleaning up, getting ready to leave, the guy approaches me and says he's looking for his waitress. I should note that this bag of rocks looked, sounded and acted EXACTLY like the character Sid from The Descendants (the oldest daughter's boneheaded boyfriend). Anywho, this guy had bought a ring and wanted to, "Like, propose to my girlfriend in the cheesecake." I kinda just rolled my eyes and found his server. Long story short not only was the ring plastic but when the dessert arrived her exact response was "You're so gay... yeah, I guess" followed by his laughter which sounded like a dying donkey. As a gay man myself, I wasn't so much offended by her use of the word, but more so by the fact that in my state these two morons could get married the next day, no problem... fuckers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While most will of course always remember Mr. Gandolfini as Tony Soprano, this will be how I'll always think of him... RIP sir... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 08:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 16:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bar Rescue and It's Always Sunny: "The Gang Gets Rescued." Already wrote the story and everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 09:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adventure Time.

I'm not even a huge fan but a lot of my friends are. I had a dream I was in charge of directing a live action version. While not "dark" or "gritty" per se, it sort of had this Where The Wild Things vibe going for it... kinda sad, kinda funny... realistic... well as realistic monsters and a talking dog can be. Anywho, I will say this: as far as my dreamland directorial career has spanned (didn't you know I've also had a hand in a reboot of Alien Vs. Predator as well as Jurassic Park IV!?), it was a pretty good one :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-25 08:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was a lad, I convinced my best friend at the time that I attended Superman's funeral (this was during the Death of Superman/Doomsday arc)... I swear to god, he believed this for years. YEARS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
