<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7533</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Is Exploiting LGBT People To Perpetuate Islamophobia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 07:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Husband Says Wife Went To Hospital For Kidney Stones, Ended Up Giving Birth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 05:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese gang kidnaps and cripples children, forces them to beg on streets of Malaysia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 05:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tunisian talk show host 'tells rape victim to marry her attacker': Thousands have shown their displeasure over the apparent remarks on social media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 04:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tunisia shocked by TV host's 'marry rapist' remarks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 03:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton is an actual feminist: She met Trumps misogyny head on, without apology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 03:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reuters projects Clinton to win with 326 electoral votes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arkansas judge who 'traded sexual favours' in return for lighter sentences indicted: "...dozens of men claimed he paid them to allow him to spank them with a paddle and to take photos of the red skin." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 16:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'It's surreal': is a Democratic uprising afoot deep in the heart of Texas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 16:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia says it is ready to cooperate with Philippines president Rodrigo Duterte after US snub: 'Formulate your wish list...think of what kind of assistance you expect from Russia' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 13:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'It's surreal': is a Democratic uprising afoot deep in the heart of Texas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 13:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Babies are not ripped out you f***ing asshole': Woman writes powerful response to Donald Trumps unscientific abortion comment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An entire town, in Illinois, has helped a terminally ill farmer harvest his crops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A judge gave a man who raped his 12-year-old daughter a short sentence so he could 'spend more time with his sons' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 12:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders demands to know why leukemia drug costs $200,000 a year  leading to fall in stock price: Ariad's shares reversed course to trade down 6 percent at $10.17 after rising more than 4 percent earlier on Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 12:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Norway integration minister faces resignation calls after telling Muslims 'we eat pork and drink alcohol': Sylvi Listhaug claims she was 'misunderstood' and says she meant Norway's Muslims should 'endure' others eating pork and drinking alcohol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 12:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump booed for calling Clinton 'corrupt' as bipartisan dinner turns sour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 12:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders demands to know why leukemia drug costs $200,000 a year  leading to fall in stock price </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 05:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders demands to know why leukemia drug costs $200,000 a year  leading to fall in stock price </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 05:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan to face criticism at international summit for flouting whaling ruling: Japanese fleets have killed more than 300 minke whales in the Southern Ocean despite a court ruling and three-decade-old ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 19:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italy abortion row as woman dies after miscarriage in hospital: The family of Valentina Milluzzo said the doctor treating her refused to abort the foetuses because he was a "conscientious objector" to abortion. The hospital has categorically rejected the family's claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 18:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With 19 Days to Go, Clintons Lead Is Bigger Than Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany rules parents with no day care options can sue cities for lost earnings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Germany rules parents with no day care options can sue cities for lost earnings: Germany's highest court has decided that muncipalities are the responsible party for the lack of legally-mandated day care spots for every child. The ruling comes after three mothers sued for lost earnings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 04:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed.. you can't undo the past but legally now their records of offences are wiped clean. 

Similarly action by German government recently:

[Germany to pay convicted gays 30 million euros - media: Germany is to compensate more than 50,000 men who were jailed for their sexual orientation under an old law. Paragraph 175 continued to be applied until the late 1960s.](http://www.dw.com/en/germany-to-pay-convicted-gays-30-million-euros-media/a-35996592) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German authorities tested drugs on unwitting children in state-run homes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 04:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German authorities tested drugs on unwitting children in state-run homes: In post-war Germany, authorities tested medications on youths in state homes. They even published their results and the methods they used in medical journals. The unwitting patients are still suffering the consequences. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 04:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alliance of 600,000 British Doctors Calls for 'Imperative' Coal Phase-Out: Doing so would constitute 'double win for tackling the twin health threats of air pollution and climate change,' report states </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 04:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alliance of 600,000 British Doctors Calls for 'Imperative' Coal Phase-Out: Doing so would constitute 'double win for tackling the twin health threats of air pollution and climate change,' report states </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 04:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alan Turing law unveiled by government will posthumously pardon thousands of gay men convicted of historic offences: The Enigma codebreaker's great neice says Government decision is 'absolutely tremendous' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alan Turing law unveiled by government will posthumously pardon thousands of gay men convicted of historic offences: The Enigma codebreaker's great neice says Government decision is 'absolutely tremendous' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alan Turing law unveiled by government will posthumously pardon thousands of gay men convicted of historic offences: The Enigma codebreaker's great neice says Government decision is 'absolutely tremendous' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comcast customers sue over fees that push price above advertised rate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim women's group inundated with hate mail after endorsing Hillary Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim women's group inundated with hate mail after endorsing Hillary Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journal article: 

http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature20112.html?cookies=accepted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monkeys 'throw spanner' in our understanding of human evolution by accidentally making tools: Capuchins have been observed in the wild smashing rocks together and creating razor-sharp flakes of rock just like those thought to have been used as knives by early humans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monkeys 'throw spanner' in our understanding of human evolution by accidentally making tools: Capuchins have been observed in the wild smashing rocks together and creating razor-sharp flakes of rock just like those thought to have been used as knives by early humans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Falwell censored anti-Trump column, Liberty U student editor says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marco Rubio Once Again Denies Climate Change as Florida's King Tides Inundate Streets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Racial Disparities in Police 'Stingray' Surveillance, Mapped: Cops are using secret cellphone trackers nationwide to collect cellphone dataespecially in poor, black neighborhoods. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Appeals Court Affirms NSA Surveillance Can Be Used To Investigate Domestic Criminal Suspects </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indonesia castration law 'will wipe out paedophilia' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Stop whining': Obama hits back at Trump over election rigging claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boy asks mother for two lunches to ensure his classmate does not go hungry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With so few people going to church, they may no longer need to hold Sunday services: Centuries-old laws stating every church must hold a service on a Sunday may be quietly dropped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peru's environmental agency is investigating the deaths of some 10,000 frogs whose bodies have been found in a river in the south of the country. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 06:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UNSW obtains 10-fold boost in quantum computing stability </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 03:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feds Walk Into A Building, Demand Everyone's Fingerprints To Open Phones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 03:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silent poison making whaling a political hot potato in the Faroe Islands: Whale meat and blubber has long been a staple of the Faroese diet, but with pilot whales increasingly contaminated by toxic substances, this traditional food source is silently poisoning the local population. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 03:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silent poison making whaling a political hot potato in the Faroe Islands: Whale meat and blubber has long been a staple of the Faroese diet, but with pilot whales increasingly contaminated by toxic substances, this traditional food source is silently poisoning the local population. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 03:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MIT nuclear fusion record marks latest step towards unlimited clean energy: Scientists create the highest plasma pressure ever recorded with the Alcator C-Mod reactor in a breakthrough for clean energy technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MIT nuclear fusion record marks latest step towards unlimited clean energy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MIT nuclear fusion record marks latest step towards unlimited clean energy: Scientists create the highest plasma pressure ever recorded with the Alcator C-Mod reactor in a breakthrough for clean energy technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ontario seeks to put a cap on water bottle industry with two-year ban: Officials say moratorium would give province time to better understand state of groundwater supplies amid climate change threat and increasing population </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arizona newspaper gets death threats for endorsing Hillary Clinton - the first Democrat endorsement in 125 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 17:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Strategists: Clinton Is in Good Shape With 3 Weeks Left </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Environmental Official Shot Dead in Brazil as Attacks on Land Defenders Rise in Latin America: Two men shot the official, Luiz Araujo, seven times as he drove up to his home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Environmental Official Shot Dead in Brazil as Attacks on Land Defenders Rise in Latin America: Two men shot the official, Luiz Araujo, seven times as he drove up to his home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Strategists: Clinton Is in Good Shape With 3 Weeks Left </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 03:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How climate change triggers earthquakes, tsunamis and volcanoes: Global warming may not only be causing more destructive hurricanes, it could also be shaking the ground beneath our feet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 19:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A child bride in Turkey has died of a brain hemorrhage after giving birth at the age of 15: The bleed thought to have killed her is believed to have been associated with going into labour at such a young age. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 19:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 420,000 More Workers in Cook County Will Soon Have Paid Sick Leave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 17:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 16:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ... and his wife flew on board to Haiti to personally ensure everything was distributed to plan.

I wonder if other royalties would do this. 

According to https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Haya_bint_Hussein

 HRH Princess Haya of Jordan is the junior wife of Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum. She is known as Her Royal Highness Princess Haya of Jordan, a title derived from her father. A graduate of Oxford University in England, she is an accomplished equestrian who competed for Jordan in international show jumping competition and is the two-term President of the International Federation for Equestrian Sports (FEI).

Brava!

edit: fixed link... thks u/juicius </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll: Clinton leads by 11 points in 4-way match up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 15:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump stuns experts by refusing to accept intelligence on Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 13:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 08:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A potential increase in drug-related crimes might become your neighbourhood's problem and that of the local authorities. It will eventually become your problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millions of Trees Are Dying Across the US: The reasons for the die-off vary from location to location - drought, disease, insects and wildfires - but the root cause in many of these cases is the same: climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 07:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 05:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's better than having them do it in an alley with a used syringe. 

Yup.

Needle Park: ['Between 1987 and 1992, the park was home to Europes biggest open drug scene, with hundreds of addicts and dealers'](http://www.swissinfo.ch/eng/drug-addiction_zurich-s-infamous-needle-park/37756262).

 Lessons were learned from the experience and eventually led to the creation of a more pragmatic and socially acceptable drugs policy in Switzerland, which includes prescribing heroin to severe addicts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 05:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Holland implemented a similar solution in the 90's](https://news.vice.com/article/only-in-the-netherlands-do-addicts-complain-about-free-government-heroin): FTA

 It was in the 1990s when the Netherlands started a program that provides long-term addicts with free government heroin.

 In practice, this means that addicts are allowed to inject or smoke heroin three times a day in a solemn, no frills room in a building run by municipal health services.

 Combined with a specified care program, it has been responsible for almost the complete disappearance of heroin addicts from public view.

*Edit: Added the following -*

[Heroin Assisted Treatment (HAT) program was successful in Switzerland](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Heroin-assisted_treatment): FTA

 And while it had been speculated that the availability of such treatment options might change public perception of the risks associated with drug use and might lead to an increase in illicit drug use, the incidence of heroin abuse in Switzerland has declined sharply since the introduction of heroin assisted treatment. As a study published in **The Lancet** concluded:

*The harm reduction policy of Switzerland and its emphasis on the medicalisation of the heroin problem seems to have contributed to the image of heroin as unattractive for young people."   Nordt, Carlos, and Rudolf Stohler, "Incidence of Heroin Use in Zurich, Switzerland: A Treatment Case Register Analysis,"[13]

 Also, the notion that patients in heroin assisted treatment are enabled to maintain "destructive behavior" contradicts the findings that patients significantly recover in terms of both their social and health situation. A clinical follow-up report on the German "Heroin studie" found that 40% of all patients and 68% of those able to work had found employment after four years of treatment. Some even started a family, after years of homelessness and delinquency.[14] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France's Solution to Drug Addiction: the government debut Friday a facility where drug addicts can safely take drugs under medical supervision the first of its kind in the country. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 04:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret Mayan tombs lend rare insight into rule of mysterious 'snake kings' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 02:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giant jade stone uncovered in Myanmar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A giant jade stone weighing 175 tonnes has been uncovered by miners in Myanmar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctors Without Borders refused a donation of one million vaccine doses from Pfizer: The heart of the refusalwhich could well imperil children who would have received those vaccinesis a principled stand against the extremely high cost of many vaccines.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 17:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big donors demand Republican Party drops Donald Trump amid sexual assault allegations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 16:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump just attacked Clinton on the Catholic church. He's definitely forgetting something </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 15:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Scottish National Partys conference has backed the decriminalisation of cannabis for medicinal use </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 15:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trade in Services Agreement (TISA) - FTA

 Along with the Trans Pacific Partnership (TPP) and the TransAtlantic Trade and Investement Partnership (TTIP), TISA is actually the largest of the "Three Big T's" of pending international agreements that seek to further shape the global economic and legal systems in favor of major corporations and elite interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 04:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "This year would be the last," Duterte said according to The Guardian on Friday (7 October) in the southern city of Davao. "For as long as I am there, do not treat us like a doormat because you'll be sorry for it. I will not speak with you. I can always go to China."

Craving for attention and being ignored by the US doesn't sit well with him. But it's his right to choose and the Chinese are eyeing [this disputed area of the South China Sea](http://edition.cnn.com/2016/07/12/asia/china-philippines-south-china-sea/index.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 17:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. 

[Norman Ohlers astonishing account of methamphetamine addiction in the Third Reich changes what we know about the second world war](https://www.theguardian.com/books/2016/sep/25/blitzed-norman-ohler-adolf-hitler-nazi-drug-abuse-interview)

 The book in question is *The Total Rush*  or, to use its superior English title, *Blitzed*  which reveals the astonishing and hitherto largely untold story of the Third Reichs relationship with drugs, including cocaine, heroin, morphine and, above all, methamphetamines (aka crystal meth), and of their effect not only on Hitlers final days  the Fhrer, by Ohlers account, was an absolute junkie with ruined veins by the time he retreated to the last of his bunkers  but on the Wehrmachts successful invasion of France in 1940. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 16:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He even likened his national crackdown to the Holocaust and said he would be happy to slaughter as many addicts as Adolf Hitler massacred Jews.

Oh.. that's a rather unfortunate comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 03:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Craving for attention... but not getting it is annoying him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 07:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/family-leads-outcry-at-blasphemy-death-penalty-2135011.html


 The precise details of Mrs Bibi's case are unclear. Reports say the woman, who lives with her family in the village of Ittanwali, west of Lahore, had been working in the fields in June last year when she was sent to fetch water. When she returned, some Muslim women refused to drink it, saying it was unclean because it had been carried by a Christian. The women then fought.

 At that point the other women went to a local cleric, Qari Salim, and several days later he filed a legal complaint with the police. When the case was eventually concluded last week, in addition to being sentenced to death, Mrs Bibi was also ordered to pay a fine of 300,000 Pakistani rupees (2,180).

 Last night, Mrs Bibi's husband told The Independent: "My wife was picking phalsa in the fields when she had a fight with her other workers over some triviality. The other three got together and accused my wife of desecrating the Holy Koran It was not even a men's fight in the village, but a trivial tussle between women."

All because of a bowl of drinking water...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 13:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am guessing if they were once used as platform for Balinese foot flexology.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 07:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journal article:

http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v538/n7623/full/nature19797.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 06:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   ... 'might be misinformed' about their value.

Is that coded speak for some secret military arrangements that he has yet to tell his boss?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 02:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an Instagram post, Paikdze made her decision very clear. This is a post for those who don't understand why I am boycotting FIDE's decision. I think it's unacceptable to host a WOMEN'S World Championship in a place where women do not have basic fundamental rights and are treated as second-class citizens. For those saying that I don't know anything about Iran: I have received the most support and gratitude from the people of Iran, who are facing this situation every day. Thank you MyStealthyFreedom for sharing my interview. 

Bravo!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes we have to be interested in Pakistan whether we like to or not. Maybe this might help jog your memory a wee bit: 

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Osama_bin_Laden%27s_compound_in_Abbottabad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTA: 

 He told Copenhagen City Court last week: I just praised Allah. I do that every day, Danish broadcaster DR reported.

 The Iraqi national was a former spokesman for the controversial organisation Called to Islam (Kaldet til Islam) which is said to advocate the introduction of Sharia Law in Denmark, according to Hate Speech International.   

 It was also revealed in court that he had been previously sentenced for threatening to decapitate the chairman of the Danish Syrian Association over his support for Syrian President Bashar al-Assad against Isis.

Should have deported him right away instead of 3 months and some conditions considering the above revelations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 14:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTA:

 The term encounter is a widely understood euphemism for extra-judicial killings in Pakistan. Police accounts often say that criminal or terrorist suspects were shot after they resisted arrest or tried to ambush officers.....

 As far as they are concerned encounters are the perfect way of getting rid of hardened criminals, he said. They do not consider it a gross violation of human rights and instead see it as an effective way of delivering justice.

Looks like Philippines President Duterte has some competition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 04:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journal article

http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/2/9/e1600931 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 15:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers man ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 02:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journal article:

http://science.sciencemag.org/content/early/2016/09/13/science.aaf2416 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 02:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journal article:

http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v537/n7620/full/nature19103.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 17:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germany recently passed a rape law that clarifies ["No means no"](http://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-36726095) and they are considered behind other developed countries on rape laws.

In 2015 California passed the ["Yes means yes"](https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2015/sep/10/yes-means-yes-sexual-assault-california-high-schools) law for affirmative consent in colleges which was adopted by a dozen states and cities.

Obviously Idaho isn't one of them... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As the National Anthem started, Howard was standing in front of both her daughter and her husband. When the song was over, she turned and saw Jessica crying and asked what was wrong.

 That lady next to me yelled at me because I didnt have my hand on my heart, she said and added, First she asked me if I was a citizen of the United States, then she yelled at me and kept yelling for being disrespectful.

I don't think its mandatory that you have to put your hand over your heart during the National Anthem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journal article:

http://www.pnas.org/content/113/36/10180.abstract?sid=0ef2aecd-df5e-41c2-9a23-8951aa5948b3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 15:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTA

 Among Federal Court Justice Robin Camp's remarks during a 2014 sexual assault trial, according to a notice of allegations posted on the Canadian Judicial Council website:

 "Why couldn't you just keep your knees together? Why didn't you just sink your bottom down into the basin so he couldn't penetrate you?"

 Young women, the judge said, "want to have sex, particularly if they're drunk," according to the notice.

 He also said that "some sex and pain sometimes go together" and "that's not necessarily a bad thing."

 Camp's controversial remarks resulted in an investigation by the Canadian Judicial Council, a federal body that polices judges.

Gee... he could have just stopped after making the first couple of comments. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 09:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some info about the Company involved in the trials:

http://medicalresearch.com/author-interviews/immodulon-aims-to-activate-both-arms-of-immune-system-to-fight-broad-range-of-cancers/27357/

 Building on the success of the Phase 1   2 trials of IMM-101 outlined above, Immodulon is now focusing on completing a Phase 3 trial of IMM-101 in the treatment of metastatic pancreatic cancer in approximately 350 patients, so as to bring IMM-101 to market in both Europe and the US.

 In addition, Immodulon is planning additional trials to be run in parallel, to be announced in the coming months. One such trial is an innovative basket trial to test IMM 101 in combination with a wide range of other cancer therapies. The first patient will enter the trial over the autumn of 2016 and the study aims to recruit 100 patients per year for the next three years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 04:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journal article:

http://www.nature.com/bjc/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/bjc2016271a.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't seem to access the link to the journal Aquatic Mammals for the article: http://www.aquaticmammalsjournal.org
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 05:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to u/Ar-is-totle there are quite a number of multinational pharmaceutical companies involved in this research:

https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/50jpnq/alzheimers_disease_breakthrough_as_new_drug/d74v5iu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTA

 "In other words," Nick Dearden, director of U.K.-based Global Justice Now (GJN), wrote in a Wednesday op-ed, "TTIP has been sacrificed to save the wider agenda of which TTIP was only one part"namely the Comprehensive Economic   Trade Agreement (CETA) between Canada and the European Union and the 50-nation Trade in Services Agreement (TISA), which Dearden describes as "a massive, super-privatization deal covering everything from finance to education."   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 23:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article:

http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v537/n7618/full/nature19323.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 12:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could but it's not within my means. 

And as I said earlier I can't fault your logic nor can I criticise you for your opinion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 12:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't argue with your logic I am afraid though it's ~~not~~ a tad of a selfish attitude but to each his own. 

Edit: not  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 07:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's not - it's about one person respecting another.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 04:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article:
http://www.cell.com/cell-host-microbe/fulltext/S1931-3128(16)30310-9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 03:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article:: http://science.sciencemag.org/content/353/6302/919 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 16:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ermias Haile, a 16-year-old from Eritrea, has been sleeping on a building site with his friends since they arrived on the island after making the treacherous voyage from Libya. 

 Ermias and friends told Sky News an Italian man had sexually abused them after buying them drinks and offering them shelter.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 16:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ermias Haile, a 16-year-old from Eritrea, has been sleeping on a building site with his friends since they arrived on the island after making the treacherous voyage from Libya. 

 Ermias and friends told Sky News an Italian man had sexually abused them after buying them drinks and offering them shelter.

 He find us in a place like this [park] and he invite us to a bar and he let us drink beer and then he take us to his home and there he give us beer, he said. 

 We start drinking and then he start touching us on our body. After we leave the house, he calls us and he gives us money.

~~Smack of pedophilia so~~ what are the Italian authorities doing about this? 

Edit: I stand corrected, wrong term and the age of consent is 14.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 05:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/08/10/1604472113.full </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 18:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article - Impacts of neonicotinoid use on long-term population changes in wild bees in England

http://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms12459 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 04:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if he had won that match... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 13:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boohoo yourself mate. Arsehole like you deserves to be banned from social media whenever it's possible. You are toxic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 13:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a such racist without any shred of evidence to support yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 08:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's not what you said earlier 

 The funny thing about Indians is that they are little good boys and love to snitch on anyone they can when climbing totem poles. They are essentially British people ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 07:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They are essentially British people !

How on earth did you manage to jump from a baseless criticism of the Indian race and equate that to the British in two sentences? Did you just simply pull them out of somewhere?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 01:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  According to Mr Brouillard, other Church members at the time knew about the abuse but they did not tell him to stop. Instead they told him to pray.

Great... priest said a few Hail Mary prayers in-between the abuses and it was business as usual for the church. The church should defrock all those responsible for the cover up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to see you moderating it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Thks for asking. Trust you are too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 07:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Daily Mail and Hotair are your source?!! Please... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 12:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conduct unbecoming of a Lt Col who once commanded the 3rd Battalion of the Mercian Regiment during a challenging tour of Afghanistan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 09:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of agree with this view. You can't have your cake and eat as the saying goes. 

Basically if you choose to wear it based on your religious beliefs then none should fault you but it has to be consistent and not on an ad hoc basis. If you choose to wear it as a fashion accessory then you can't be claiming its for religious reasons when it suits you. It's inconsistent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 05:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article:

[Thirst neurons anticipate the homeostatic consequences of eating and drinking](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature18950.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 06:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Satisfaction I guess. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 06:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Karma... perhaps but then there is an old Chinese saying: 

Before you embark on a journey of revenge, you should first dig two graves.  Confucius </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 05:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they did jail a few:

http://www.forbes.com/sites/timworstall/2015/10/24/if-iceland-can-jail-bankers-for-the-crash-then-why-cant-america/#6d1e37c94a67

That's a 2015 article about Ireland's part so the *headline might be misleading* since the US might have also prosecuted a few banker for their part in the 2008 banking crisis. 

FTA - an interesting point the author made:

 The truth is that those bankers jailed in Iceland did things that would get them jailed in the US too. And the bankers in the US did not do things that would have got them jailed in Iceland.

 There is, you see, a difference in doing something criminal to make money and simply getting things wrong in the pursuit of making money. Sure, theres criminals in every part of every system but the problems of the Great Crash in the US were brought about not by bankers being criminal but by bankers being wrong. And thankfully, otherwise wed all be in jail for we all make mistakes, being wrong isnt a criminal offence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 03:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "You can kill with the tongue as well as the knife," he said, in an apparent reference to a rise in populist parties fuelling racism and xenophobia.

I like this Pope more and more.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 15:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study:

[Emissions from Electronic Cigarettes: Key Parameters Affecting the Release of Harmful Chemicals](http://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/acs.est.6b01741) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 14:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mohammad Karim, who is believed to be in his sixties, was arrested after marrying the girl. He has told officials that he had been given the girl as a religious offering by her parents, Agence France-Presse reports. 

Good, he deserves to rot in jail. But in a Taliban infested country this filthy pedophile will be out in no time. I can only hope that I am wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 05:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calm down dude... sometimes I forget.

Sorry you feel offended ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 03:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first media reporting on this is from an Aussie based news site:

http://www.news.com.au/world/reports-turkish-troops-have-sealed-off-incirlik-usnato-nuclear-air-base/news-story/4d7bb16e4e86842218b5b0d7d70f582b

Not sure how credible that source is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 03:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any nuclear weapons on that base? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 03:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gosh..the news from Turkey is not improving. 

Looks like Erdogan and this failed coup is giving him the opportunity to purge anyone and any institutions and organisations who disagreed with him in the past.

Is there a method to this madness? Or is his adminstration simply reacting to potential threats as they appear - like playing "whack-a-mole"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 15:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno - if someone is threatened and that only weapon you have left at your disposal is a nuclear strike I think most would launch. 

It's a natural reaction to use whatever weapon you have at hand to protect yourself when your life is on the line. 

Edit: typo and tidying up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 08:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [There has never been a country that should have been so rich but ended up this poor](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/wonk/wp/2016/05/19/there-has-never-been-a-country-that-should-have-been-so-rich-but-ended-up-this-poor/)

 Venezuela has become a failed state.

 According to the International Monetary Fund's latest projections, it has the world's worst economic growth, worst inflation and ninth-worst unemployment rate right now. It also has the second-worst murder rate, and an infant mortality rate at public hospitals that's gotten 100 times worse itself the past four years. And in case all that wasn't bad enough, its currency, going by black market rates, has lost 99 percent of its value since the start of 2012. It's what you call a complete social and economic collapse. And it has happened despite the fact that Venezuela has the world's largest oil reserves.

 Never has a country that should have been so rich been so poor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 04:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The 18-year-old and his so-far unnamed accomplice ...forced 86-year-old priest Jacques Hamel to kneel before sliting his throat on camera in the style of an Isis execution video.

That's so frigging brutal. I can't even being to describe how I feel about this disgusting act of cowardice. F*ck! What is wrong with these people?

*Edit:* 
According to this [BBC news](http://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-36900233)

 One of the men suspected of killing a priest at a church in northern France was being monitored by police and was wearing a surveillance tag at the time of the attack, officials say. Prosecutor Francois Molins said Adel Kermiche, 19, was twice arrested last year trying to reach Syria.

What's the purpose of the surveillance tag? What does the police do with data collected from this monitoring system? I have no idea so perhaps someone can weigh in on this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 13:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High hardness in the biocompatible intermetallic compound -Ti3Au
- http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/2/7/e1600319 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 11:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So based on this study it's is pretty much confirmed that it's no longer correlation but causation...i.e. A leads to B? 

There is now evidence of causal relationships that one can infer from the body of evidence in the study?
 
Can some expert EL5 this methodology that establishes causal relationship in his study? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 09:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's article
 Vaulin was also charged with money laundering. The file-sharing site generated up to $22.3 million in annual advertising revenue, the U.S. alleged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 08:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  An American Airlines spokeswoman said in a statement: American [Airlines] was contacted by CAIR earlier this year. We thoroughly reviewed these allegations and concluded that no discrimination occurred. We serve customers of all backgrounds and faiths and do not tolerate discrimination of any kind.

That's it? "Case" closed? What a lot of crock from AA trying hard to sweep this under the carpet.

 Mohamed Ahmed Radwan had boarded a plane in Charlotte, North Carolina and the flight attendant went to the tannoy and said: Mohamed Ahmed, Seat 25-A: I will be watching you.  The employee made no other announcements about any other passenger.

There was discrimination and the passenger was singled out for special treatment

 The passenger then reported the incident to two other American Airlines employees. He was told he must leave the plane as he had made the first air stewardess uncomfortable.

He made her uncomfortable so he has to leave the plane? That's all the justification AA needs to escort someone off the plane?

I guess ultimately his words against them and AA concluded there was nothing to it.. no apology, no reprimand, nothing. Swell!

Edit: 

The complaint filed by CAIR said that the [flight attendant made the announcement 3 times] (http://www.cair.com/images/pdf/CAIR_Letter_to_DOT_re_American_Airlines.pdf).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 06:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And from same guy

 "If it was manned it could glide for a long way," Kennedy said. "You could glide it for further than our search area is, so I believe the logical conclusion will be well maybe that is the other scenario."

Mind blown... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 05:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  According to the complaint, federal investigators posed as an advertiser, buying an ad on KAT in March 2016 for $300 a day. He was given information for a Latvian bank for making his payment, but was told not to mention KAT anywhere. When he went to buy a second ad, he was told that only pricier ads were available for $1,000 to $3,200 a day. He kept buying more ads and by May, received details about a different bank in Estonia. Through this investigation, the authorities learned which bank account KickassTorrents was using and obtained records, including hosting records that showed KAT was hosted in Chicago for a little over three years.

Ads... led to his downfall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  According to state broadcaster TRT, Turkey's High Education Board has also ordered the resignation of 1,577 deans at all universities, part of a wide-ranging purge of dozens of state institutions following a failed coup in which over 161 people were killed.

Okay I can understand the sliver of justification Erdogna uses to remove thousands of judges, soldiers and policemen. I grant him that even if I find it hard to credit but state education employees??!!

Seriously what is wrong with this Erdogan? Suddenly the President of the Philippines is beginning to look like a saint compared to Erdogan and his escapades? Has he gone loco or something? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 14:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am really late for party but I truly hope your grandmother's genes got to you in a major way and I mean that in the nicest possible way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
