<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2223</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you do any research for this book?  Or has a lot of it come from your experience as a lawyer?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What books really made you love reading as a kid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the most interesting thing you have found in your research?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What topic would you most like to write about but have not yet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is a hotdog a sandwich?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your favorite cheese? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 11:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are welcome to read with us whenever you'd like :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 00:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have been active within the last 60 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 00:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The top moderator has been active within the last 60 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 00:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moderator there has been active within the last 60 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 00:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moderator there has been active within the last 60 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 00:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moderator there has been active within the last 60 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bruce Campbell is doing an AMA in /r/IAmA right now! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your writing process like?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 18:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What books really made you love reading as a kid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Don Coscarelli, screenwriter/director/producer, known for Phantasm, The Beastmaster, Bubba Ho-Tep and many more, is doing an AMA in /r/movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 18:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question!](https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/56c3ek/i_am_filmmaker_don_coscarelli_of_the_phantasm/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 17:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you become interested in developing new technologies?  Is it something you have always been interested in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 17:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your favorite cheese? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was your first musical performance like?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 21:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you working on any current projects that you are excited for?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What has been your most memorable interaction with someone the innocence project has helped?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you get into filmmaking? Has it always been an interest of yours?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Author Wesley Chu is doing an AMA in /r/books today! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question](https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/5664m4/im_wesley_chu_awardwinning_author_of_the/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Author Wesley Chu is doing an AMA in /r/books today! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your favorite cheese?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wesley Chu is doing an AMA right now in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Author Wesley Chu is doing an AMA in /r/books today! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question!](https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/5664m4/im_wesley_chu_awardwinning_author_of_the/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like it will be really interesting!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What books really made you love reading as a kid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there other cases that you are interested in making films about?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the most interesting thing you discovered in your research?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puk Grasten - director of 37 a new film about the bystanders of the 1964 murder of Kitty Genovese - will be doing an AMA in /r/IAMA tomorrow! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 00:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ##Here is a link to the AMA: https://redd.it/56651l

If you are not familiar with the case you can read about it here:

NPR ['The Witness' Looks Back At Those Accused Of Ignoring A Murder](http://www.npr.org/2016/06/02/480442769/the-witness-looks-back-at-those-accused-of-ignoring-a-murder)

[The NewYorker](http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2014/03/10/a-call-for-help)

[Washington Post](https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/style/her-shocking-murder-became-the-stuff-of-legend-but-everyone-got-the-story-wrong/2016/06/29/544916d8-3952-11e6-9ccd-d6005beac8b3_story.html)

[Newsweek](http://www.newsweek.com/kitty-genovese-murder-new-york-city-37-witness-503861)

Here is a summary from Wikipedia: 

In the early morning of March 13, 1964, at approximately 2:30 a.m., Genovese had left her job, and began driving home in her red Fiat. While waiting for a traffic light to change on Hoover Avenue, Genovese was observed by Moseley, who was parked in his car. Followed closely by Moseley, Genovese arrived home around 3:15 a.m., and had parked her car in the Kew Gardens Station Long Island Rail Road parking lot. It was about 100 feet (30 m) from her apartment's door, located in an alleyway at the rear of the building. As she walked toward the apartment complex, Moseley exited his vehicle, which was located at a corner bus stop on Austin Street, and approached Genovese armed with a hunting knife. Frightened, Genovese began to run across the parking lot and toward the front of her building located at 82-70 Austin Street, trying to make it up to the corner toward the major thoroughfare of Lefferts Boulevard, Moseley ran after her, quickly overtook her, and stabbed her twice in the back. When later confessing, Moseley said that his motive for the attack was simply "to kill a woman". Genovese screamed, "Oh my God, he stabbed me! Help me!" Several neighbors heard her cry but, on a cold night with the windows closed, only a few of them recognized the sound as a cry for help. When Robert Mozer, one of the neighbors, shouted at the attacker "Let that girl alone!" Moseley ran away and Genovese slowly made her way toward the rear entrance of her apartment building. She was seriously injured, but now out of view of any witnesses.

Records of the earliest calls to police are unclear and were not given a high priority by the police. One witness said his father called police after the initial attack and reported that a woman was "beat up, but got up and was staggering around".

Other witnesses observed Moseley enter his car and drive away, only to return ten minutes later. In his car, he changed to a wide-brimmed hat to shadow his face. He systematically searched the parking lot, train station, and an apartment complex. Eventually, he found Genovese, who was lying, barely conscious, in a hallway at the back of the building where a locked doorway had prevented her from entering the building. Out of view of the street and of those who may have heard or seen any sign of the original attack, Moseley stabbed Genovese several more times. Knife wounds in her hands suggested that she attempted to defend herself from him. While Genovese lay dying, Moseley raped her. He stole about $49 from her and left her in the hallway.[13] The attacks spanned approximately half an hour. Afterwards, "Genovese, still alive, lay in the arms of a neighbor named Sophia Farrar, who had courageously left her apartment to go to the crime scene, even though she had no way of knowing that [Moseley] had fled."

A few minutes after the final attack, a witness, Karl Ross, called the police. Police arrived within minutes of Ross's call. Genovese was taken away by ambulance at 4:15 a.m. and died en route to the hospital. She was buried in a family grave at Lakeview Cemetery in New Canaan, Connecticut.

Later investigation by police and prosecutors revealed that approximately a dozen (but almost certainly not the 38 cited in the Times article) individuals nearby had heard or observed portions of the attack, though none saw or was aware of the entire incident.  Only one witness, Joseph Fink, was aware she was stabbed in the first attack, and only Karl Ross was aware of it in the second attack. Many were entirely unaware that an assault or homicide was in progress; some thought what they saw or heard was a lovers' quarrel, a drunken brawl, or a group of friends leaving the bar when Moseley first approached Genovese.

I know this is not a unresolved case but what happened with the people who heard or saw Kitty's attack could be very relevant to a lot of other cases discussed here.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 22:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your favorite cheese? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 22:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What advice would you give to new filmmakers ad writers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 22:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was your favorite part of making Flock of Dudes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 20:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you say is the most interesting shipwreck?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Midge Raymond, author of MY LAST CONTINENT, is doing an AMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 20:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question!](https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/5602yt/greetings_from_midge_raymond_author_of_my_last/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was your favorite moment in filming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you get into filmmaking?  Is it something oyu have always been interested in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your favorite cheese?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Range, with Director Daniel Kaufman and Special Guests from Superimpose, will be doing an AMA in /r/music! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Range, with Director Daniel Kaufman and Special Guests from Superimpose, will be doing an AMA in /r/music! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Range, with Director Daniel Kaufman and Special Guests from Superimpose, will be doing an AMA in /r/music! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 17:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What books really made you love reading as a kid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Author Garth Nix is doing an AMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question!](https://redd.it/55uhg6) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read anything wonderful recently?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What books really made you love reading as a kid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garth nix is doing an AMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 04:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A giant duck is pretty close to being a dinosaur.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 04:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is on your tech wish list right now?  It's okay if it doesn't exist yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 04:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fighting is required  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 04:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you rather fight one horse sized duck or 100 duck sized horses?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 08:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you would like the book for free you should check your public library.  Illegal file sharing is not allowed in /r/books.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 00:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moderator there has been active within the last 60 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 00:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moderators there have been active within the last 60 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 21:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anyone you would like to write about and haven't yet?  An area of history that you would like to highlight?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 21:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How old were you when you first read Stephen King?  I feel like a lot of people scared the crap out of themselves reading his books at like 11 years old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 21:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I give you about a month to read the book and then the author does an AMA.  This one will be on 10/27 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 21:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you choose the historical figures you write about?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 21:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What books really made you love reading as a kid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seemed like a good choice for October.  We always get a ton of people looking for horror reads this time of year.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The /r/books bookclub pick for October is The Troop by Nick Cutter! He will be doing an AMA on the 27th. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 18:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 18:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm excited to have this one for Halloween.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The /r/books bookclub pick for October is The Troop by Nick Cutter. He will be doing an AMA on the 27th. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 18:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to see the announcement post in /r/books](https://np.reddit.com/r/books/comments/558m8s/our_bookclub_selection_for_october_is_the_troop/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our bookclub selection for October is The Troop by Nick Cutter, something scary for halloween. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 18:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am very excited to announce that our bookcklub pick for October is The Troop by Nick Cutter.  The Troop is a perfect Halloween read if you are looking for something creepy.

[From Goodreads](http://www.goodreads.com/book/show/17571466-the-troop)

Once a year, scoutmaster Tim Riggs leads a troop of boys into the Canadian wilderness for a three-day camping tripa tradition as comforting and reliable as a good ghost story and a roaring bonfire. But when an unexpected intrudershockingly thin, disturbingly pale, and voraciously hungrystumbles upon their campsite, Tim and the boys are exposed to something far more frightening than any tale of terror. The human carrier of a bioengineered nightmare. An inexplicable horror that spreads faster than fear. A harrowing struggle for survival that will pit the troop against the elements, the infected...and one another.

#[You can see our past bookclub selections here](https://www.reddit.com/r/books/wiki/bookclub) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 22:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong place!  Use the larger comment box up above.  There is a little save button under it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #There will be spoilers guys!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Clines, author of 14 and The Fold, is doing an AMA in /r/books for our monthly bookclub! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[click here to visit the AMA and ask a question](https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/553xpx/im_peter_clines_author_of_14_and_the_fold_and/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Clines, author of 14 and The Fold, is doing an AMA in /r/books for our monthly bookclub! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Clines, author of 14 and The Fold, is doing an AMA in /r/books for our monthly bookclub! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Peter Clines, author of 14 and The Fold, is doing an AMA in /r/books for our monthly bookclub! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question!](https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/553xpx/im_peter_clines_author_of_14_and_the_fold_and/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was your favorite experience meeting your fans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was your first time on stage like?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 00:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you most like to tell us that no one has asked about?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the best advice anyone ever gave you about writing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read anything good recently?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What were your favorite books as a child?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 06:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am pretty sure ER did the same thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Nicolas Winding Refn, Director of The Neon Demon and Drive, is doing an AMA in /r/IAmA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 20:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Nicolas Winding Refn, Director of The Neon Demon and Drive, is doing an AMA in /r/IAmA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 20:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What books really made you love reading as a kid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 20:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the most interesting thing you found in your research?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like other rural areas could have the same problem with guns and suicide.  Have you found that to be true?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Julie Mack - a reporter researching suicide in northern Michigan is doing an AMA in /r/IAmA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do people living in the area have an awareness that the suicide rate is so high?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really recommend checking out her article.  It's linked in the AMA text.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the most common misconception that you encountered?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Julie Mack - a reporter who has been researching gun related suicides in Michigan - is doing an AMA in /r/IAmA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the most surprising thing you found in your research? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was your first time on stage like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 00:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go ahead and try to reset your password again: https://www.reddit.com/password
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 23:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi!

Can you try logging in on the desktop site?  That should get you headed in the right direction to get back into your account.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 03:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/SkippTopp is right.  Our main concern is making sure people are not using reddit to hunt someone down and cause real life problems for them.  Links to documents will very often be okay but if it's posted to highlight the personal info that would likely be a problem.  

Posting home addresses or personal phone numbers on reddit is very rarely okay.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 02:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep!  I think most of the people who have posted personal info in relation to this case just did not understand the site rules or what we consider to be personal.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 01:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an excellent clarification.  Home addresses of public figures are generally not going to be okay.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 01:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I answered above but our main concern is making sure people don't go on a hunt for someone and cause real world consequences for them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 01:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posting links to documents can be problematic but we have decided that those are okay.  It is not okay to use information to start a hunt for someone and it is not okay to use reddit to search out more of their private info. 

What we are concerned about here is making sure people are not being harassed in real life based on activities here on reddit. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 23:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you guys so much for making this post.  If anyone has any questions about this please let me know.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 21:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is awesome guys.  I really appreciate the effort you are putting into this :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it like to ghostwrite a book?  Do you have a lot of contact with the person you are writing for?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read anything good lately? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Jeff Kositsky, the director of the newly formed San Francisco Department of Homelessness and Supportive Housing, is doing an AMA in /r/sanfrancisco! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 00:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question!](https://www.reddit.com/r/sanfrancisco/comments/541co2/hi_reddit_im_jeff_kositsky_and_im_the_director_of/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 23:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What small change do you think could make the greatest impact?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeff Kositsky, the director of the newly formed San Francisco Department of Homelessness and Supportive Housing, is doing an AMA in /r/sanfrancisco! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 23:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 20:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I really missed out not reading her books as a kid.  She just is not popular in the US at all and I have no idea why.  They sound great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Author Peter F. Hamilton is doing an AMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Author Peter F. Hamilton is doing an AMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question!](https://redd.it/53zg4i) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Follow this link to get to the AMA: https://redd.it/53zg4i </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Follow this link to get to the AMA: https://redd.it/53zg4i </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Follow this link to get to the AMA](https://redd.it/53zg4i) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter F. Hamilton is doing an AMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What books really made you love reading as a kid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that sounds neat.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 23:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is something you would love to write about but haven't yet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 22:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What advice would you give to other writers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Lisa Brown Roberts, author of The Replacement Crush, is doing an AMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 21:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question](https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/53ta3x/im_lisa_brown_roberts_author_of_contemporary_ya/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> got to click the link above to get to the questions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The actors who voiced Belle and Gaston in Walt Disneys animated classic, Beauty and the Beast are doing an AMA in /r/IAmA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lisa Brown Roberts, author of The Replacement Crush is doing an AMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 17:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read anything recently that was really good?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 17:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What books really made you love reading as a kid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 17:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of the misconception about pain could be related to how some TV shows have portrayed the donation process.  Fairly recently the show The 100 portrayed bone marrow removal really gruesomely and I remember an old episode of ER that made it seem pretty awful. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 16:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are certain demographics less represented in the donor pool?  Would more people signing up from a particular group of people be very helpful?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 16:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any stories you would like to share about your work?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 16:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your best story from the set?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 16:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the most common misconception about being a bone marrow donor?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 22:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yep](https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/4qfwoo/hi_guys_its_gordon_ramsay_back_for_another_ama/d4smn0m) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robert Cormier books were so scandalous in middle school!  One of them was rumored to be banned from class reading so we all had to take a look (I am not sure about the truth of the ban, the his books were in the school library) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dana Kaye, publicist and author of Your Book, Your Brand: The Step-By-Step Guide to Launching Your Book and Boosting Your Sales, is doing an AMA in /r/books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What advice would you give to new authors about finding an agent?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Crosspost] Dana Kaye, the owner of Kaye Publicity, a boutique PR company specializing in publishing and entertainment, is doing an aMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question!](https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/53npz8/im_dana_kaye_author_of_your_book_your_brand_the/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the first book you remember reading on your own?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 20:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brian and Kevin are using the account /u/StoryBundleAuthors  to answer questions today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the first scifi novel you remember reading? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kevin J. Anderson is doing an AMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brian Herbert and Kevin J. Anderson are doing an AMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keving J. Anderson and Brian Herbert are doing an AMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question](https://redd.it/53im9q) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What were your favorite books as a kid?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brian Herbert and Kevin J. Anderson are doing an AMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Kevin J. Anderson and Brian herbert, authors of Navigators of Dune, are doing an AMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question](https://redd.it/53im9q) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 22:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What books really made you love reading as a kid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Brodinski is doing an AMA in /r/hiphopheads! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 21:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question!](https://www.reddit.com/r/hiphopheads/comments/53dgeb/i_am_brodinski_ama/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 07:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an announcement of an upcoming AMA :) 

Don't ask your questions here, wait until Monday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 00:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moderator there has been active within the last 60 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 00:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moderator there has been active within the last 60 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 19:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What were your favorite books as a kid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 21:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What one thing would you most like to accomplish working on the BART board? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Gwyneth Borden, a long time transit advocate, is doing an AMA in /r/sanfrancisco! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 21:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question](https://www.reddit.com/r/sanfrancisco/comments/52xp9v/im_gwyneth_borden_a_long_time_transit_advocate/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 21:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you most like to tell us about your goals for BART?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 21:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just moved to the city from an area with almost no public transport.  It has been so nice to be able to get into the city without driving and parking.  The one less nice thing is the area immediately out side many stations.  Often it's not kept up very well and a lot of people congregate there who are not going to be riding.

What are your thoughts on the upkeep or the area around the station? Being such a high traffic area it can't be easy to maintain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 17:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think the moon landing was real?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Filmmakers from Operation Avalanche are doing an aMA in /r/movies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 17:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question](https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/52wlyt/iama_we_are_filmmakers_who_made_operation/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 17:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you get into film making?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 22:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say Nancy Drew and The Hardy Boys were the equivalent but they just aren't that exciting.  Enid Blyton stories sound a lot more interesting and she seems to have a good variety as well.  Not the same kind of story every time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fell like I missed out on Enid Blyton growing up in the US!  She is just not a thing here and looking at her books I think I would have really enjoyed them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Author Alex Lake is doing an AMA in /r/books! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question](https://redd.it/52pvsx) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What has been your worst reading experience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you get started writing?  is it something you have always been interested in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your favorite books from childhood?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd imagine that losing hope would be one of the biggest obstacles.  People tell you that things can get better but you don't see it happening.  Having her working in the prison is such a great example of overcoming the odds and moving on.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kathlyn how did you get involved with the If Project?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is really interesting.  Teaching probably appealed to you because you wanted to help people and especially for kids it's the most obvious helping people job.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For Kim, did want to be a detective as a kid?  Or is it something that came to you later?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really great.  Do you have any stories of women's experience helping other that really stand out?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 23:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the most surprising thing you discovered in your work?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 22:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes me sad that so many people can't understand that it's a personal choice and most women who wear hijab feel really good about it, empowered even.  In one of her answers Rayouf talks about how she enjoys answering people's questions about her headscarf and feels like it opens good discussions and understanding.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High school student Rayouf Alhumedhi submitted a proposal to Unicode for a headscarf emoji, she is doing an AMA today in /r/TwoXChromosomes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question!](https://www.reddit.com/r/TwoXChromosomes/comments/52l57e/im_submitting_a_proposal_to_unicode_for_a/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High school student Rayouf Alhumedhi submitted a proposal to Unicode for a headscarf emoji, she is doing an AMA today in /r/TwoXChromosomes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you tell me about how wearing a headscarf is important to you personally?  I know many women feel empowered by their choice to wear hijab.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your favorite movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Justin Bartha is doing an AMA in /r/movies! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question!](https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/52ka8v/im_justin_bartha_from_the_new_movie_white_girl/?sort=new) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 17:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any favorite moments from meeting your fans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 17:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What has been the funniest thing you have seen happen on set? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 00:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was your first stage performance like?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 00:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a discussion thread linked in the post above and the AMA will be a separate post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 15:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was your very first performance on stage like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 15:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What has been your favorite experience meeting your fans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Will Sheff from Okkervil River is doing an AMA in /r/indieheads! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 19:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question](https://www.reddit.com/r/indieheads/comments/51s93u/this_is_will_sheff_from_okkervil_river_ask_me/)

From Will:

Hey, this is Will Sheff, singer and songwriter for the band Okkervil River. Gonna be answering questions about our new record "Away," out tomorrow, along with whatever else. 2PM. https://twitter.com/okkervilriver/status/773925221908770816 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [crosspost] Will Sheff from Okkervil River is doing an AMA in /r/indieheads! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 19:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[Click here to visit the AMA and ask a question](https://www.reddit.com/r/indieheads/comments/51s93u/this_is_will_sheff_from_okkervil_river_ask_me/)

From Will:

Hey, this is Will Sheff, singer and songwriter for the band Okkervil River. Gonna be answering questions about our new record "Away," out tomorrow, along with whatever else. 2PM. https://twitter.com/okkervilriver/status/773925221908770816 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
