<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8631</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not anytime soon. I think it's at a good place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hatred = fame. 

I get hate messages and hate comments all of the time. 

Don't let it bug you. Let it be a reminder that you are reaching a broad crowd. Your story hsd reach and you need to use that momentum to push through and write another amazing story!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is best to write it all in one go and part it up accordingly.

I just write each part out, but that's not really the best method haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Haha also how strange D acted lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not anytime soon. 

Honestly, it's at a good point to take a break from! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Story! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If You're In a Big City Please Stick With The More Populated Areas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now let me tell you. I know that New York City and Los Angeles are gigantic cities, but it is nowhere as confusing as Seoul, South Korea. I have been here at least 3 times in the past 6 months, but I have yet to figure where anything is, but I still decided to stupidly walk around without my cell phone at 2 in the morning. 

It was in the middle of a conference and I just couldnt go to sleep. So I grabbed a coat and walked out of my hotel room. There really wasnt anything going on inside of the hotel. The bar was closed, and the computer room was locked. The swimming pool and gym closed at 10 pm so I made the dumb decision to walk around outside. 

I tried to keep track of which street I took, but after walking around for 20 minutes I quickly forgot where I was. Taxis are all around this city at any time. So catching a cab and getting back to the hotel would not be a problem. 

After a couple more minutes of walking I noticed that the huge buildings started to disappear, and the sounds of cars became extinct. This was absolutely perfect for me. I found a little convenience store and grabbed a couple of beers and walked down the street hoping to find a park of some sort. 

The lady in the front counter greeted me when I walked in, but I noticed how old the store looked. I looked at her and saw that she was a fairly short woman maybe in her early 20s. I know it doesnt seem important, but to me it felt strange that a young woman like her would work in a rundown store like this. I pushed the thoughts out of my head and grabbed 2 bottles of Soju. (The most popular Korean alcohol beverage and only around a dollar)

I paid for my drinks and walked out of the store. Something about this location made the weather feel just right. Usually its completely cold in the middle of February, but it felt so nice out I could take my coat off. This was definitely the most comfortable couple of hours of my life. The fact that there were far less people here than the rest of Seoul made it just that much better. 

While I was walking down the street while sipping on the Soju I looked around and noticed that there were almost no buildings around me. There was just a park in the distance and 3 other smaller buildings including the convenience store. I also noticed that I was walking up to the park without even noticing, but it did seem like a really nice place to drink the rest of my drink so I kept going. 

On the way there I finished off the first drink so I placed the empty bottle in my pocket. I took a little rest to catch my breath and open the next bottle. After my mini break I looked back up and noticed that the park seemed to be farther away. I rubbed my eyes, but the park still seemed to be farther away. For a second I thought about turning back around and catching a cab, but I decided against it. Already halfway there; what was the point in giving up with a full bottle of Soju anyways? 

This time I focused on the park while I walked towards it; only taking my eyes off of it occasionally to take another drink. I started to slowly calm down when I noticed I was definitely getting close. Around 50 paces away from the park I tripped on something and fell to the ground. Right as I was falling down I know for a fact I heard someone whispering to me. It was in Korean, but I will try my hardest to translate it. Come in. Come in. Its fun. You wont regret. I got up and looked around, but the only thing that was there was what tripped me. It was an empty bottle of beer. 

I picked it up to chuck it into the grass when I noticed how old it felt. I could make out the word Jinro Brewing on the bottle. I turned the bottle around to see if I could read anything else on it. My eyes finally fell on a series of numbers. 

*19531011*

I dont know why it was the beer bottle that made me run away from the park. I dont know why I didnt run away when I heard the whispers, but I just wish I never even went out of my hotel room. I bolted down the street and towards the convenience store, but every couple of steps I kept hearing the park call back to me. Dont run. So we can play. Come in here. Forever you can stay. I ignored the calling, but I will tell you that every time it called out to me I was just that much more tempted to just go back to the park. 

Just look back once and it will stop. Against my will I stopped completely and looked back. The park was gone, but a group of children were running around the empty lot. A man carrying a beer bottle was walking down the street towards the park. He took out a knife from his back pocket and threw the bottle on the ground. 

The kids stopped playing and looked at the man with curiosity. Without slowing down he walked up to the first kid and raised the knife up, but before he could even stab a kid the other children swarmed around him and each took out a knife.  A couple stabbed at his legs, a few jumped on him and the rest just stepped back and watched while laughing. The mans blood was flying all over the lot. I couldnt watch any longer so I turned around and continued to run to the convenience store. 

I kept running away from the park and from the laughter coming from the children. Right when I got near the convenience store the noise stopped. I turned around and the park was back there again. 

When I got up to the store I tried opening the doors but it was locked. I tried shaking the doors harder hoping it was jammed but the door wouldnt give.  Desperation started to take over my body, but I ignored it and started to walk away. That is when the door rattled from the other side. I walked back up to the door, and saw the lady that checked me out. I started to point to the door but she shook her head slowly at me. Bits of her skin started falling off of her face every time she moved her face. She said, Go to the park. You can stay forever. You can never die. Stay at the park. You will be happy.

I screamed and banged the door where her face was and kept running away from the park. I started to see familiar buildings and started to calm down. After a couple of minutes I started to walk. The streets of a busy Seoul started to come into view. I got on my knees and thanked the world for saving my life. I took out the second bottle of Soju and took a long chug of it. I finished the bottle off and threw the bottle in the grass and looked up. 

I was back in the park. 

The kids started to come out of the shadows and slowly walked up to me. I frantically looked around. Hoping there was some sort of place of shelter. My eyes fell on a older phone booth. 

I forced myself onto my feet and ran inside of the phone booth and picked up the phone. After muttering a quick prayer I put the phone up to my ear. The relief I felt when I heard the dial tone is beyond words. With tears falling from my eyes I put 500 won (50 cents) and called for a taxi. I thought about calling the cops for a second, but I knew there was zero chance in hell they would believe my story. The dispatcher answered my call and I told her that I needed a ride from a park close to Ibis Hotel. She asked me where the park was exactly but all I could do was describe out what the park looked like and what the stores around it looked like. She muttered silently for a second and said that a taxi was on its way. 

By the time I hung up the phone the kids had surrounded around the phone booth. They started to bang all around me, but I sat down as low as I could and put my feet up against the doors. A girl with long flowing brown hair walked up to me and stared me down with a smile on her face. Her body started to bubble around her midsection and legs. Her face started to stretch out until the woman from the convenience store was staring me down. She started chanting with the kids, Open the door. Live forever. Just open the door. Escape the terror. 

A couple of the kids started to jam their knives into the door and pry it open. I kept my legs in the same spot. Waves of pain overcame my body whenever they stabbed my feet, but I held on. I didnt want to die. I didnt care about my feet. I just wanted to live. I just wanted to be at the hotel. I wanted to go back home.

When my legs started to give out I heard a honk in the distance. I looked to my right and saw a taxi. I got to my feet and braced myself to be attacked by the children, but I was only met by the sound of impatient honking. I opened my eyes to see that the kids and the women disappeared. The park looked to be ages older. I opened the door and dead bolted to the taxi and got in the back. 

The taxi driver took one look at me and asked me where I was headed. I muttered Ibis Hotel and he drove off. On the way there the taxi driver kept giving me an odd look. 

I asked him why he was staring, but he just shrugged his shoulders and kept driving till we arrived at my hotel. I opened the door and started to head out when he grabbed me by my shoulder. He whispered to me, Every couple of weeks we get a call over there. Thats why we knew where you were. Avoid the park at all costs. It is still haunted by the ghosts of children that are responsible for 12 deaths in their town. Many men tried to stop them, but they were unsuccessful. Now they stay at the park and prey upon people that foolishly go near the park. You are lucky. You survived. Keep it that way.

Im at my hotel now. I wanted to give you this warning. 

If you happen to be in Korea and you find yourself in Seoul.  

Please only stay in areas that are heavily populated. 

I leave you this final warning before I head out to the park. I cant stop thinking about all of them. I want to live forever. I want to know what true happiness is. 

[Good Bye] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shhh, it's okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as bad as eight mile haha OP you know i love your stories! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe no it's a lot of comments and i am a very lazy man haha. :) but let's appreciate this story! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 13:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously though. Does this shit ever work? I thought this died in the 90's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 13:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to comment:) especially on the great stories of NoSleep:) truly OP let us know if you need any help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 10:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the other kids did too -.- haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just not allowed to say! Sorry!

*Falls back into the fires of hell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha hmmmmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I notice whatever is in my inbox haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's helped me a bunch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't, but I think I should start trying! Might make me better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 08:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a big fan of yours u/DaveTheDog027 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 06:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for connecting the dots! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 06:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually just took a piss and it happened. Always two drops, and it ruins my whole day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 06:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I will! 

One day/

I'm just gonna let this simmer a bit. Write a couple of other stories I have and get back to it!

Thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 06:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahhh i'm just gonna flee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 06:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahhahhah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am completely afraid of cannibals. One way for me to get over that is to just write about them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else actually read the rules of NoSleep, and not comment dumb ass shit like this?

P.S. Check your phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just use my original account:p

Hasn't really ruined it for me yet!:D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is her voice? how was that a point.

it definitely sounded creepy as hell.

I would bolt the fuck out and rent out a hotel room for a month to be quite honest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahah thank you very much! I just wanted to make a more adult version of it.

I will keep submitting stories!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually Dante's Inferno was more of a Charlie and the Chocolate Factory inspired hahhahhaha

I will do that this weekend:) I just need to make sure I have the order right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude here haha i do have a female name lol

thank you so much for that haha. 

I have gotten complaints about how my single series seemed rushed, but i smile at myself because i know i have another series to connect it haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually spend around 45 minutes to an hour for each part in a series, and about 1-2 hours for each single story! 

I don't plan it beforehand lol. I normally think up of a title and expand from there. I did plan the Dante's Inferno adaptation the night before though lol

And thank you so much!!! I love writing for all of you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anytime! I do cliches all of the time in my stories haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha thank you so much! It really means a lot to get compliments! I promise I will keep creating stories! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha the truth?

I sat in front of my computer for about 30 minutes. Looked at my phone and thought an app that could tell the future was really cool! Took me a while to finally think up of other series to connect it to though lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course you can! 

Just push your own experiences out!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly... cliches are cliches for a reason. 

I love how it was written! 

Keep pushing stories out. You're definitely talented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ask me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About my stories of course.

I mean I won't really answer anything about my actual life. It is far too dull compared to the lives of my characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would give away the surprise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i really hope you can overcome the never touching women thing OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It means out of character haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last Part of My Newest Series! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Now Control An App Called "Life Is Beta" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its over. I won, but satisfaction is the last thing I feel. 

Everything is over. I dont know how I can describe everything that has happened, but I will try. 

We didnt get any type of breakfast this morning. D just walked in and told us to get up. We followed him out and went to the boat. I got on last and took my seat next to D once more. He put his arm around me gave me a half hug. He put his yellow and black teeth close to my ear and whispered, Smile. It suits you better. Youll probably die today, but just make the last couple of hours the best possible baby. He chuckled and stared into the water. 

After a couple of minutes we stopped in front of a door. A drawing of a family gorging out of a meal was scratched into the wooden door. We all got off the boat and walked into the door when D opened it. Inside of the room was a massive feast laid out on 10 huge tables. I was walking up to one of the tables to grab a plateful of mashed potatoes and gravy when D cleared his throat. We all turned to him and he walked up to a dish piled high with steaks. He grabbed a steak and took a bite. He turned to all of us and with a mouthful of red meat he said, You take a bite of anything in here. You die. Simple. It seems like an easy feat doesnt it? I mean you just have to block the food out from your mind right? 

He snapped his fingers and 10 men stepped into the room. All of them looked severely malnourished. Their ribs were poking out of their torn up shirts and their legs looked like they could barely support the meager weight of their bodies. Each of them walked up to a table and started to shovel food into their mouths. My mouth started to water, but I managed to block out what was going on around me. I turned my back to the tables and closed my eyes. I didnt look around until I heard the sound of a bell. I quickly glanced around to see that no one took the bait. Alex and Kristy were standing together in a huddle, Jeremy and Andreas was talking to each other as loud as they could to distract themselves, and Jeremiah was cowering in the far left corner of the room.

The 10 men stopped eating as soon as the bell rang and stared at the food with their hungry eyes. 

Silence filled the room for the next 2 minutes. 120 seconds that I counted in my head.

The bell rang twice and the men grabbed two handfuls of food and started to walk towards us. I tried to run away, but they moved surprisingly fast. 2 men tackled me to the ground and started to hover the food over my nose.  They started to whisper about how I wish I could have the food. About how easy it would be for me to just take a bite. My mouth started to water, but I managed to resist eating out of their hands. This lasted for what seemed like forever. It only stopped when the sound of loud sobbing filled the room. The men got off me and I looked around the room.

Jeremiah was sobbing into the food that was now in his hands with small bits of meat falling from his mouth. He threw the food on the ground, but I already knew it was far too late. 

D walked in and pulled Jeremiah to his feet. After Jeremiah recomposed himself D told us to follow him. No one moved a muscle. We knew what was going to happen, but we wanted to allow Jeremiah to live as long as possible. D took out a gun from his shirt and shot Alex in the right knee. Kristy erupted into screams and Alex collapsed onto the ground and started groaning in pain.  

D then shouted at us, This is not a game. This is just what you all deserve. I am only getting rid of the bad from the world. When I say walk. You fucking walk. When I say come with me. You follow me. Do you understand or do I have to kill one of you? I want to give you a chance, but if it isnt possible I will just kill all of you and start with a fresh group. Believe me. I have plenty of people to use. Criminals around the world. Kids who are sold to us by their parents. Even kids that we get money for to get rid of. Youre not important to me. I can kill you right now. So get the fuck up and follow me.

Kristy helped Alex to his feet and started to follow D first. The rest of us quickly followed behind. Jeremiah was still sobbing while being dragged by D. We walked out of the door and saw D walking down a stairway next to the door. It wasnt there before, but I didnt have the strength or desire to question it. Kristy put Alex on her back and carried him down. 

It was dark the whole entire way down. I tried to feel around with my feet for the next step and slowly reached the end of the stairway. I heard a click and the room erupted with red light. Jeremiah was lying on the ground begging D for mercy, but D was laughing while he grabbed the knife from the back of his pants. He started to rub the sword on Jeremiahs neck and asked, Why do you deserve mercy? You failed. Jeremiah started to beg once more, but before he even muttered out the third word his head rolled away from his body.

D looked at us and said, I have a deal for you guys. He threw the knife in the middle of us and pulled out a gun. Whoever can grab the knife on my count and kill any one of you guys. You will be able to leave with a check for 150k. You wont know where you were so my men will transport you to the closest airport. Blindfolded, of course, but you will have more than enough money to completely forget what you went through. Okay.

He clapped his hands and giggled with excitement.

One.

Two.

Go!

Andreas was the first to grab the knife and tried to stab Alex. Kristy ran up behind Andreas and ripped the knife out of his hands. With both of her hands she plunged the knife into the exposed midsection of Andreas. He tried to rip the knife out of his body but Kristy took the knife back out and stabbed him through the chest. 

D clapped his hands and exclaimed, Oh Im proud of you, but one more offer. You kill Alex and I will raise up the money to 500 million dollars. With a smile he pointed at the knife in her hand and whispered 500 million dollars. Kristy looked down at Alex and started to rub his face. Alex kept muttering, Babe, I know you wont do it. Just please dont do it. You know I love you. I would never do it to you. She looked up at D and shook her head no, and I saw Alex sigh in relief. Kristy looked back up at D with a smile and with a scream turned back around and stabbed Alex in the neck. 

Alex lied on the ground for minutes before we could be certain he was dead. Once his body stopped moving D walked up to Kristy and patted her on the back. She started to ask for the check, but D stopped her short with a bullet in her head. Her body crumpled to the ground while D let out a huge laugh. People always forget about greed! They think its over! He started to jump up and down with excitement when the gun flew out of his hands and on the ground.  I grabbed the gun and without a second thought shot out all 11 bullets that remained in the magazine. 

Jeremy had three bullets in his head and D was lying on the ground face down. I walked over to him and rolled him over. His face took two bullets and his chest had been shot several times. 

He looked at me and muttered. I knew you were going to win. I just had to push you is all. Dont think of me as the enemy. Just as your mentor. You have two choices. Walk away from all of this or take what I have created. My whole life was dedicated to rid of the filth in the world. It has become far more than I can handle.

He died seconds later. 

It is now 4 hours since D died. I have decided to stay and continue what he has started. We have a house were we train young men to become part of this great organization. They come from parents either selling us their kids or from parents that actually give us money to get rid of their kids. 

Sometimes we send kids back home. Just so that we can properly locate where there shitty parents are.

We send people out using a wonderful app D has created. 

This app has produced more members for us as well as saved our members and future members lives. It has made us much more productive and efficient. 

I now control an app called [Life is Beta.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).

[Part 1] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5sk87k/out_of_9_people_only_1_will_get_to_live_part_1/?utm_content=title utm_medium=user utm_source=reddit utm_name=frontpage)

[Part 2] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ss6sn/the_circle_of_lust_part_2/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!:D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you give me too much credit!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get spooped! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will. Just after a couple of day when I'm not busy haha i will add in custom flairs lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Official Reddit Page! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 08:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright guys. 

This is where I will be uploading my new NoSleep stories on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 05:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of like a writing prompt, but you have absolute control over every single detail! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of a title.

Build off of the title.

That's what I do:p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just root for me. 

Not anyone else .
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Circle of Lust [Part 2] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5sk87k/out_of_9_people_only_1_will_get_to_live_part_1/)

I woke up to something softly scratching my face. When I opened my eyes I saw D rubbing his fingers on my cheek. I jerked away, but D managed to keep his finger at the same spot on my face and continued to rub. I tried to get up, but D told me to lay back down and relax. He smiled and kissed me on my cheek. I tried to get up again but he pressed my ear up to his mouth and whispered, I dont want you to die. Well not yet at least. Everything you see in the Lust circle will want you to dive into sexual activities. They will want you to fail so that you can die, but remember my face. Remember my kiss, and use it to keep you away from failing. I have a much better plan with you.

He walked out and closed the door. For the next couple of minutes I sat in the darkness. The sound of snoring surrounded me, but it was somewhat soothing for me to hear. It made me feel like I was back at home. The illusion was shattered when D burst through the door and turned on the lights. Seven other groggy people started to sit up. D snapped his fingers and three people walked into the door. They had a leopard, lion, and a wolf mask on. They carried in huge dishes filled with bacon, eggs, and toast. We started to walk up to the people, but they put their hands up and dumped all of the food on the ground and left with the plates.

D laughed and said, Well dont just stand there. Im sure youre hungry. You have 10 minutes and then we will go to the first circle. I started grabbing bacon and toast that were on the top and shoveled the food in my mouth. The rest started to pick up pieces of bacon and a little bit of eggs. Malcolm was last to grab the food and was left with the rest of the eggs.

D clapped his hands and told us it had been 10 minutes. He motioned with his hand for us to stand up and all of us except Malcolm stood up. He was grabbing at his stomach and wincing in pain. I walked over to him and helped him to his feet. I asked him if he was alright; he nodded and pulled away from me. D started walking out of the room and we followed him. 

After about 2 to 3 minutes of walking D opened a door to our right and walked up to a boat floating on a narrow but long pool. The pool seemed to be never-ending. It stretched down far past where my eyes could see. We all climbed in and took a seat. When I looked around to find a seat D tapped on the seat next to him. I took the seat and D pointed into the water. He whispered, Its red right now because we have colored it that way, but one day it will be filled with blood. He turned around and stood up. With a grin on his face he said, When we are on the boat you do not call me D. If you call me D I will throw you off the boat and watch you drown. Call me Charon. I am here to transport you to the lust circle and the rest of the circles as well. When I get off of the boat you can call me D. Hell, you can even call me Dom. Understood?

We all muttered yes and he pointed forward. The boat started to move on its own and turned left or right with a flick of Ds wrists. After a boat ride that lasted for less than 10 minutes D pointed down and the boat came to a stop in front of a door. He turned to look at all of us and giggled. With excitement flowing through every word he exclaimed, This is the first circle guys! Hop off the boat. I told you last night, but Ill tell you again. Dont fall for temptation. You show lust in your actions I will make sure you die. Dont grab anything that isnt yours. Ready? Ok. Lets go! He hopped off the boat and we followed him to the door. He opened it up and motioned us to go in.

The walls, floor, and ceiling were all a solid black. There were around 10 cameras all around the room. I was confused about what the challenge was but walked into the room. Alex and Kristy went to the opposite corners trying to avoid each other at all costs. Andreas, Malcolm, and Jeremiah stood in the middle. Gus and Jeremy stood near the doorway. I walked up to Andreas, Malcolm, and Jeremiah and stood with them. Malcolm was telling Jeremiah that he had a sore stomach, but Jeremiah just put up his hand and told him to stay completely still. I looked at Malcolm and saw that he had started to sweat. His pupils were triple the size as normal, and his breath was starting to get deep and long. 

A bell rang from outside and around 50 people started to pour into the room. The lights turned off and a soft single light took its place. A deep base filled the room and slowly progressed into a wonderful song that brought out every molecule of sexual desire out of me. They surrounded us and started to rub all over our bodies. I tried to get away from them, but fell into another group. The bell rang once more and they stripped themselves naked. While they were taking their clothes off I ran to the far right corner of the room and crouched down as low as I could. I looked around the room and saw that everyone else was trying to avoid being touched. 

Everyone except Malcolm. 

Malcolm was in the process of grinding against a woman. A naked man walked up behind him and started to kiss him on the neck. A loud groan came out of Malcolm and the bell rang once more. The two people immediately stepped away from Malcolm and stared him down. 

D opened the door and threw a duffel bag into the room. Gus ran towards the bag but the other people blocked his way and the rest opened the bag and they each took out a knife. Malcolm was oblivious to it all. He was still dancing along to the low alluring bass as the people gathered around him. Right as Malcolm opened his eyes they jumped on top of him and he became invisible. Within 10 seconds they got up and 8 people ran out of the room carrying the remains of his body. 

Before they got out of the door Gus took a good look at what Malcolm looked like. When they exited the door he looked up at us with a smile on his face. 

I got up and started to walk out the door, but the bell rang again and the people started surrounding us once more. 

This time they started whispering to us. A couple of women walked up to me and started to tell me everything they loved about my body. They talked about all of the nasty shit they would do to me. Every time I felt any type of urge my mind automatically bounced to how it felt having D rub his finger on my cheek. That is what saved my life. After a while of failing to seduce me they started to put their knives all around my body. One woman put her knife on my neck and whispered, Ill kill you right now if you dont fuck me right now. I tried to think of a response, but I didnt need to. 

The bell rang once more and I looked around the room.

Gus was covered in Malcolms blood with desire flowing from his eyes. He was halfway out of his pants when he noticed everyone staring at him. He started to scream, No, No, Ple-. 

They were on him like they were on Malcolm. I looked away from the scene until I heard Ds voice.

Good job everyone. This concludes today.

We took the boat back and we are back in Limbo. 

They gave us spaghetti and bread for dinner but no one had much of an appetite.

Today is over. 

3 down [5 to go] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarkshttps://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks).

[Part 1] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5sk87k/out_of_9_people_only_1_will_get_to_live_part_1/)

[Part 3] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5szpax/i_now_control_an_app_called_life_is_beta/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay gonna read! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you wake up. You should look into Lt. Dan. He's got legs now and I don't trust it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha i made a dante's inferno on earth adaptation!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have almost zero experience in writing.

Just write what you really want to.

If you're judged it's fine. Just brush your shoulders and move on to the next story.

Write as many stories as you can. You'll see yourself get better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahah you give me too much credit lol.

Congrats on the upcoming wedding by the way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O.O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what am I ?:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a wannabe:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://kiwiirc.com/client/irc.snoonet.org/NosleepOOC 


just log into the chat if you want help posting this... lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just a fellow writer.

Have a good one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there is a button on the same row called "Add Flair" there is a series option in it and then click submit on the bottom! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not suitable for work lol

not a problem! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> on your comment you said you put "NSFW" after the title. That is actually against the rules. 

Also make sure you hit enter twice between each paragraph. The maximum words for each paragraph is 350 words btw.

To tag it NSFW you have to submit the story first. Then you will see on your submitted page the story you just posted. Look at the bottom of that link and there will be a "mark NSFW" button.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 11:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's fine, but thank you for reminding me to make an exit door. 

Looks like you're stuck in the wrong subreddit. 

Or website.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 11:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a brain fart issue.

Sorry today has been absolute shit as you can tell:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 10:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can i say. 

I love you guys  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of 9 People Only 1 Will Get To Live [Part 1] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 09:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a rough hand ripped away the blindfold off of my face I looked around only to be met with complete darkness. Quiet whispers of prayers and begging came from all around me, but I couldnt see who or what was making those noises. After a couple of seconds I heard a pair of footsteps walk across the room and suddenly light flooded into the room.

Pain automatically erupted from my eyes and I instantly shut my eyes. I held them shut until I felt a hand rub my shoulder. I opened my eyes to see an incredibly pale faced man staring right at me. He was maybe an inch away from me while he kept rubbing my shoulder and breathing into my face. When he took his hand off my shoulder he gave me a smile. His teeth were a deep yellow with black specks all around the edges of each tooth.

He took a couple of steps back and I looked around the room. With me included there were 9 people tied to a chair. We all looked confused and frightened. Our chairs formed a half circle, and the man stood in the middle of us. I took a look at the man standing in the middle of us. He was completely bald and had absolutely no facial hair. He had a nice suit on, but the jacket was ripped in multiple places. After a couple minutes of silence he suddenly clapped his hands and said, Hello, I am now your god. I want you to engrave that into your head. I go by many names but just call me D. I want you all to look around. Those are now your enemies. You want them to fail. To die.  Which one of you wants to live? Two people to my right started to plead with him, but he held his hand up. One of the guys stopped begging, but the other man continued to beg. 

D walked up to the pleading man and grabbed the back of his chair and threw him face down into the ground. Blood started to surround his head while D untied the rope from around his wrists and ankles. D then grabbed the man by his shirt and dragged him to the door. He grabbed him by the hair and jerked his head up. D silently whispered to the man, but the man whimpered in response. After slapping the man across the face D shouted in to his ear, Do you know what is written on this door? The man sobbed and said, I dont know what that means. I cant even read it. Just please dont kill me. Im begging you. 

With a chuckle D said, *Lasciate ogne speranza, voi ch'intrate"* it means Abandon all hope, ye who enter here. Oh! I have a bonus question for all of you. What is this quote from? After a couple of seconds of silence he cleared his throat and said, This is from a part of the greatest piece of literature ever created. Heard of Divine Comedy? Of course not. How about Inferno? No? Well everyone does tend to call it Dantes Inferno. Its this wonderful little tale about how a man goes through 9 circles of Hell. Each circle represented a type of sin. I loved the concept as soon as I heard about it! It made me quite excited, but it still felt like something was missing. Then one day I was struck by an idea! Instead of just one man going through this incredible journey why not have nine? So I have made a little competition.

He stood around and watched us squirm with fear in our seats. A woman to my left started to whimper, but stopped immediately when D stared her down. 

D walked up to the guy in the far left and tapped on his head. Alex, you just love messing with peoples lives with your lovely wife dont you? He stops and turns to the lady next to Alex and patted the top of her head. Oh sweet Kristy, if only you realized how many deaths you and Alex have caused. Making fun of them online. Telling them to kill themselves. Laughing when you happen to hear that the person you taunted last night killed themselves. After he spit at their feet he moved to the next guy.   

Andreas, was next in line. He started off being addicted to watching Hentai, but quickly started to lose control. He was caught several times staring into the windows of women changing. Recently he started to flash himself to women around malls.

Then the person directly to the left of me. Gus, has already killed 14 people. You could tell from Guss eyes he had zero shame in what he had done. He stared D down with a look of pride and gave him a smile as D walked over to me.

My name is Grant, I am a kleptomaniac. I love stealing stuff. It has gotten bad to the point to where I have started to steal from houses I knew belonged to the elderly. I started to lose the feeling of guilt with each house I robbed. It was like a hobby to me. I wanted to stop, but I would always find myself outside of another persons house at 2 in the morning.

D walked up to the other three and pointed at the man lying on the ground. We all looked at him and saw that he had stopped breathing. He looked at us and said I did you a favor. He was the one that helped bring you all to me. He brought each and every one of you with his little sidekick here. He tapped on the leg of the other man that was begging for his life. The man looked up and begged once more for his life, but D ignored him and continued to speak. They brought each of you here. They did it for the money of course.  Only 10k a person, but you see they are both consumed by greed. The guy on the floor was John and this lovely mans name is Jeremy. Get to know him, but dont kill him.

He walked up to the final two and gave them a smile. With a much softer voice he said, Jeremiah and Malcolm. You two have the purest soul out of all of them. I have added you to in because I want to see if you guys will break with enough pressure. He gave each of them a kiss on their forehead and pointed up. We all looked up and saw over 40 people with guns aimed at us. 

D untied us from our chairs and told us to remain still. Once he untied the last rope off of Malcolm he turned around and said, Tomorrow I will tempt you with lust. Its the first circle in the story! Im so excited. You so much as show desire in your eyes you die. You are in the Limbo room now. This is not a safe zone. If my guys catch anyone of you sinning they will kill you. Alex and Kristy the same goes to you. I would suggest standing as far away as possible. I will have food sent to you, and you have one computer. You do not have any way of sending a message of help. We are in a place where locations cant be tracked. You can contact whoever you want, but you will find out quickly it is useless. He turned around and walked out of the room. 

I have the computer for 2 hours. I decided to reach out to you guys.

Please. If you have any suggestions. Let me know.

Dont send out help. 

[It wont help] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).


[Part 2] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ss6sn/the_circle_of_lust_part_2/)

[Part 3] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5szpax/i_now_control_an_app_called_life_is_beta/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/nosleepfinder will be able to help you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have 550 apples that made you grow an extra kidney after you eat it. How many kidneys would I be able to eat out of you?

If you could change the title on one of your stories what would it be and what would you change it to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so tornados </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay!!! Seriously amazing writing by everyone though!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 14:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha wait can i submit stories? Im feeling slow haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 09:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad Tom Brady didn't eat the dip:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 09:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahahahha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 09:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *gives you the tip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 09:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahahha XD just you watch.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 08:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait I don't really understand the questions:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly! good pizza too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omfg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn:(

Luckily I have two pizzas now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Has Been The Worst Super Bowl Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tonight I hosted my first and last Super Bowl party. Well, it wasnt really a party. Two of my best friends, Jerry and Brad, came over with a variety of snacks and two cases of beer. Jerry and Brad were two brothers that moved to Tennessee about 5 years ago. They both started working with me around 4 years ago. I became fast friends with them. Around halfway through the first quarter I went into the kitchen and brought out a six layer dip I bought from the local grocery store earlier in the afternoon. 

About 15 minutes later the dip was gone. I didnt even get to eat any of it. Brad sheepishly grinned at me and told me that it was really good. I gave him a little laugh and called the local pizza store and ordered 2 pepperoni pizzas. They told me it would be about an hour and I hung up the phone. 

The first quarter ended and I couldnt help but feel a little disappointed. Neither the Patriots nor the Falcons managed to get a single field goal or touchdown. I wasnt a fan of either team to begin with, but I just really wanted the Patriots to lose because they crushed my team in the Conference Championships. Jerry and Brad were from Massachusetts so they loved the Patriots.  

The second quarter was amazing for me, but Brad and Jerry were looking a little pissed off so I held back my cheers as much as I could. Right as the first half ended Jerry walked into the kitchen to grab a couple of snacks. I cracked open a beer and watched the next set of commercials. Halfway through Lady Gagas performance (greatest half time show ever) I noticed that Jerry wasnt back yet. I called out to him, but he didnt say anything back. I got off the couch and walked into the kitchen to see that Jerry was standing in front of my fridge. I asked him if he was okay, but he just didnt take his eyes off of my fridge. Brad came into the kitchen and tapped on Jerrys shoulder. 

Jerry shook his head and turned around. He gave us a confused look and started to walk back into the living room. I grabbed 2 bags of chips and followed Brad back into the living room. Jerry was staring at the tv screen with a blank look on his face. I asked him if he was okay and he just muttered, Im fine just spaced out for a couple of minutes. The halftime show ended and it was back on commercials. I tried to lighten up the mood by joking about how bad the Patriots were playing. Brad laughed and told me to Fuck off, but Jerry glared me down with a look of pure hatred. I apologized to Jerry, but he kept staring me down. He only stopped staring when someone knocked on the door. I quickly got up and walked up to the door. 

I collected the pizza and gave him 2 twenties and told him to keep the change. When he took the money he looked behind me strangely and asked what was wrong with the other guys. I turned around and saw Brad and Jerry tackling each other on my couch. I chuckled and told him they were brothers and probably just goofing off. After the delivery driver left I closed the door and walked up to them laughing. I asked them Yall want me to join? They stopped when they heard my voice. Jerry slowly started to raise his head up at me and hanging from the side of his mouth was a sliver of Brads flesh. 

I started to throw up a little but I swallowed it back down and tried to push Jerry off of Brad. After 3 of the hardest pushes I could muster they finally got off of each other. Brads chest was a mixture of exposed flesh, bones, and skin. Jerrys intestines were hanging out of the various rips in his midsection. 

I called 911 and made sure they were separated away from each other. 

It took 45 minutes for the paramedics to arrive. Jerry was completely silent now and already as good as dead. Brad was muttering words I have never heard of while they put him on the gurney next to Jerry and carted them to the ambulance. One of the paramedics asked me if they ate anything strange, but I told him that we just ate some chips and dip that I got from the local grocery store. The paramedic asked me what the brand name of the dip was and I told him it was called 6 Layers of Paradise. He asked me if I ate any, but I told him I didnt get to eat a single bit of it. 

I asked him if it was the dip, but he just put his pen and notepad back in his pocket. He started to walk away, but halfway to the car he turned back around and said, If you have any more of it dont eat it. Dont even touch it. Its getting pulled from the shelves, but over 150 people have been admitted into the hospital just in the past two hours. We are low on ambulances; that is why they are going in the same ambulance. They all have two things in common they ate the same dip and they developed a hunger only human flesh could provide. He got into the back of the ambulance and they drove away.

I probably lost my two best friends, I missed out on most of the half time show, and the Patriots fucking won. This was the [worst Super Bowl ever] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well welcome! Like i said earlier in a comment. I loved your story! Keep going!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subscribed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delete the original story. Message the mods and tell them that you are resubmitting a story due to whatever was wrong with it. Then submit the story again after you get the confirmation please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhhh :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 23 and stopped writing when I was around 12. Picked it back up 2 months ago haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well we are just one person away! Just gotta get some love in there too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am just the worst korean alive:/ oh my god </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha my wife would love you. 

I just for some reason do not like them haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 19:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha whatbl kind of kdramas do you watch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love your writing btw. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omfg i think it is!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 13:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is how i was created. Chopped up dicks and skewered nipples </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 06:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand!!!! Hahha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 06:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh there's a korean movie about a restaurant cooking human meat but i forgot the title :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 06:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just gonna keep an eye out for the suspicious sock puppet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought about you, but I'm sorry. You haven't killed me yet. 

Just kill me to make a statement! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 05:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yes i will! This is what I'm putting into my book whenever i write it! So this is far from finished. Sorry for giving you this awkward ending.

Just think phantom menace XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just spare my life:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or is it just the ending of this part?:) ooc as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go for it!!! 

I highly reccommend submitting anything you feel like you could make a nosleep story out of! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/manen_lyset idkkkk he really seems like a werewolf to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Just Came Back Home After Being Missing for 15 Years [Final] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We went to a nearby forest and Stephen buried Drews body next to an oak tree. Stephen cried throughout the whole process. Once he put the last scoop of dirt over the make shift grave he fell on his knees and started to sob. I thought about patting him, but decided he just needed his own space. After a couple of minutes Stephen got up and started to walk towards his car. I followed behind him and got in the passenger side.

For the next hour all I heard was the heavy breathing by Stephen. His eyes were blood shot red and his hands gripped the steering wheel a little tightly to the point to where his knuckles had started to turn white. He pulled into a small restaurant and we got out and walked inside. The lady in the front took us to a table and he ordered the bacon and egg special. I ordered the same thing and she carried our menus away and walked up to the cook. 

I looked around the restaurant. We were the only ones here, but the restaurant seemed to be doing fairly well. All of the tvs were newer and the seats were almost completely new. The kitchen looked to be very well maintained. The color red seemed to be the theme of the restaurant. The seats, tables, and the kitchen walls were all red. I enjoy that color, but I thought to myself about how I would have replaced the color from red to blue. 

I didnt realize how hungry I was until I saw the feast before my eyes. I started to devour every single salty strip of bacon and eggs. Halfway through my meal I felt my phone buzz. Stephen heard my phone buzz and started to stare at me when I decided to keep eating instead of check the phone. When he realized I had no intentions of checking he said, I really recommend checking the phone. Thats why youre still alive. It saved your from Andrew and Drew. He went back to his meal while I reluctantly took my phone out of my pocket.

When I turned on my phone it automatically went to Life is Beta. My character was glowing and floating in midair. Underneath his body New Experience appeared. I clicked the body and the screen showed my character standing in the same type of table I was. The screen slowly started to pan away from my character and went to the kitchen. There was a man lying on the floor gagged and tied up. He was flailing around the floor, and his legs were mostly cut out. The cook walked up to him and bent down next to his body. He used his knife to cut off part of his thigh. When he cut out a sizeable piece he started to remove the fat from the meat. 

Once he was done removing the fat he put the fat on the stove and cooked the bacon with it. He threw the meat in the trash can and focused on the bacon. The man on the ground started to sob but the cook walked up to him and jammed his foot on the guys mouth. The screen went black again and bounced back to my character. My character got out from his chair and started to walk out. Stephens character tried to catch up to mine, but he was far too slow. The cook came out and grabbed Stephen by the back of his shirt. Stephen tried to fight him off, but the cook was far too strong. On the next scene Stephen looked like he was there for days. His legs and arms were peeled off to the bones, and the cook looked hungrily at his midsection. The last thing I saw was the cook plunging his knife into Stephens chest and pulling the knife down. After that my phone screen went back to my home screen. 

I wanted to leave. I knew that was the only way to save my ass, but I just couldnt leave Stephen here to die. I didnt eat another bite of my breakfast, but I waited till Stephen was done. Once Stephen was done with his meal we went back to his car and drove away. 

After enduring the silence for over an hour I fell asleep. When I woke up I saw that we had parked outside of a huge 3 story brick house. He got out of the car and motioned to me to follow him inside. I walked up beside him right as he knocked on the front door. A man in a monkey mask answered the door and panic started to take over me. I tried to run away, but Stephen grabbed me by my right shoulder. He calmly said, Hey Grant, am I here early? The man in the monkey mask shook his head no and said Come inside. Its cold, 

Stephen started to walk inside but when he saw that I hadnt moved a muscle he grabbed my arm and dragged me in with him. 

A flood of memories hit me like a tidal wave. 

The woman dressed in all white that would come into our rooms. She would start by rubbing my thighs and telling me everything was okay. She would then start showing me pictures on her phone of men lying on the ground in several impossible positions. Men with their arms around their right knee and the hand sticking inside halfway through his mouth, and men with half of their midsection cut off and their tongue on the middle of their thighs. 

One guy that would come into our house with a knife in his hand; he would whisper, Are you the one? before finding the right boy and plunging the knife into his chest. 

They gave us schooling every week, but on Wednesdays they would tell us the best way to end a persons life. 

In the middle of my thoughts Stephen grabbed his pocket knife out of his back pocket and plunged it into Grants neck. As Grant started to cough up blood Stephen tossed me his keys and shouted, Go! 

I didnt want to leave him there. I really didnt,

In the last couple of days he was the only one that I have grown to trust. The only one that I have felt was actually family. He had taken down four people before getting stabbed dozens of times by three other people. 

I knew I couldnt help him. I knew that the only person I have loved is now dead.

I ran to his car and started up his engine. I watched him while he drove his car, but no matter how long I watched him drive. I managed to wreck his car within the first 10 minutes I drove his car.

I couldnt find any building to find shelter in. I decided to sit next to an oak tree. Drew may have been a messed up child, but that was how he was raised. That was the truth he grew up believing. Stephen had a normal life until he found the app. I only had a taste of a normal life through the app. I know it may seem like a bad thing, but I owe Life is Beta my life. They have showed me what it felt like to have someone truly love you like family. 

In the middle of writing this out to you all I have had two notifications. 1 being from Life is Beta. It was just a simple quote. Though 3 gave their life for our cause; 14,000 have joined today to kill. We will grow and we will make the world a better place. 

The next was the sound of people mimicking monkey noises all around where I sat.

Im sorry. I couldnt help get rid of them or find every single answer I wanted to get, but I now appreciate life. My life and everyone elses. 

Stephen couldnt get rid of them, but the 14,000 will make a bigger impact. 

If you find the app Life is Beta on your phone dont think twice.

Please choose [kill] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=bookmarks)

[Part 4] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5rn3ub/i_just_came_back_home_after_being_missing_for_15/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. Holy shit:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I chose to kill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 05:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My stats:

Stories written: 31

Words written: 36,467

Subs posted in: 4

Favorite subreddit to post in: r/NoSleep - 14 submissions

Least favorite subreddit to post in: 
r/ShortScaryStories -2 submissions

Longest story: Private School - 2,440 words

Story that I felt deserved more love than it got: My Father Keeps Laughing At His Broken TV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> guys....

https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5rqk28/youtube_channel/

He posted it on nosleep too -.- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you just gave me multiple flashbacks.   

*shudder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 02:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can use one poem by me. 

JUST ONE YOU HEAR ME?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just came together haha

I wish i had the brain power to think ahead, but i honestly just sit in front of the computer for about 2 hours and type away :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahah thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
