<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2069</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 14:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bit more information and pictures here:

https://imgur.com/gallery/crqIY

A lot of people are asking why his post says he's from Arizona but everything else suggests UK - it's his attempt at a joke. He's implying our city is shit (hence "shitsville") and he's writing it in the format of city, state. Arizona seems like an arbitrary pick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 11:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He came back and applied to go on benefits*, was awarded a cheque for 1p in benefits (1 cent for our American friends) and complained to the local newspaper who wrote an article about how he can't afford to eat/buy food.

He forgot to make his facebook private and the local public found it and had a field day, the pitch forks were out in full force, hilarity ensued.

*note: he's a teacher in England but is waiting for his qualifications to transfer to Scotland - there's nothing stopping him getting a job in the meantime. Also, he lives with his mum who is very well off (millionaire), so he really doesn't need the benefits.

Also, I used to work with him at a supermarket when I was a student, somebody was having a leaving do in the local restaurant (think Nando's/Olive Garden), and he paid a stripper to come in the middle of the day, when the place was full of kids/families.  

He's genuinely crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 12:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you from? What nationality? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 12:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think in front of friends is one thing, but in front of loads of strangers or just in public is another. Where are you from? I'm wondering if my British sensibilities are swaying my decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 11:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not from hell but pretty inconvenient:

Turned night into day to play online games - would literally be walking about in his dressing gown ready for bed as I was getting up for uni. As I was going to bed he was sitting eating cereal. 

Would laugh MANIACALLY at whatever he was watching on his computer while gaming. Since he turned night into day it typically meant there was mad scientist laughter emanating from his room as I tried to sleep.

Broke the front door lock at 7am and woke me up to tell me to sort it and that he was going to bed. Leaving me locked IN my own flat with no way out.

When locked in wiped his arse with a tea towel and put the shitty tea towel in the washing machine. I asked why and he said "what else was I going to use!?" Uhhh, like the biggest commodity we have as students - paper?!

He was having a flat party so I moved my PS3 and tv into my bedroom so it didn't break, I also bought and hadn't opened the new assassins creed game at the time. I went to work and came home to find him in my room, having opened the game and pretty far through it, I saw spoilers and never played it again.

Had a French girlfriend and moved her in for months at time and they'd go take romantic hour long baths together, even though it was a communal student flat and we had one bathroom.

Think that's about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 11:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strong arms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a question for the ladies signalling me   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 14:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Spark Knight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stick a torch handle up your arse and bend over. Like the bat signal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No able bodied Canadian can pound an arsehole like me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 11:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I flipped back the cover - oh my god, a rubber! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 11:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was like No, she was like yeah! I was like no!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair none of this is yet based on his actions but, rather, people's perceptions of what he may or may not do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 07:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Highly recommend "Two guys and a girl" and "Two guys, a girl and a Pizza place".

Very much like how I met your mother except the friend group is initially 2, but then grows to 4/5/6.

Ryan Reynolds is fantastic in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 00:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better show us it off and on for comparisons sake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll check it out, thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 14:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does water drain? Surely having the membrane means it'll eventually overflow? And not having chuckies/stones at the bottom means the soil can become waterlogged and kill the plants? 

I could be wrong, but I built a massive one of these (8m x 1m x 2m or something) and in all my research I saw drainage as a major concern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 11:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...? It is a cake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 10:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vote 456  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 08:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say he'd do it for bout three fiddy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not again, Dad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To spread your seed and die to make room for the next generation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That certainly would narrow it down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 12:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All those pesky foreigners speaking it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 12:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose not, but Europe could be anywhere from turkey, Ukraine, Iceland, England, etc. All are vastly different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 11:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, fair play to you! All our conversation has done is confirm to me I could never do something like this haha.

Glad it's working for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 09:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply!

And what's the long term game plan? Eventually marry one, or just keep this going for the foreseeable future? 

How did your boyfriend take it when you first broached the subject? 

Did you want to be poly, THEN found your girlfriend? Or did you want to be poly because you wanted her specifically to be your girlfriend?

Is there any jealousy from either of your partners?

Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 09:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whaaaat!!! Refrigerated watermelon is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 09:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you not getting any more specific than a continent? You could surely say a country without losing any serious level of anonymity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 09:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As above, each to their own but you need to go in expecting the worst as I don't think the majority of people would be down with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 09:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in this as well. 

Who suggested you try polyamory?

Does your boyfriend have another partner also or just you? 

Do you live with your boyfriend? How do you allocate your time between partners?

Is your girlfriend like a female version of your boyfriend (personality wise), or are they vastly different? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 08:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump being the leader of the free world, I imagine he'll be all of our problem soon enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 08:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on the cusp of betting 1000 but decided not to. Brexit should have told me to go for it. God dammit.

Someone should start a thread today of all trumps promises thus far and keep tabs on how many he actually sees through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 08:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not the future, no voter is. The rich will stay rich, the poor will stay poor and the world will keep on turning.

This is like Obama mania all over again - such hype, then a few months in everyone will realise nothing has really changed and become disenchanted.

Annoyed I didn't bet money on trump winning, the odds were amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 08:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ex friend now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 00:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was swimming with 2 guy mates at the beach while drinking when I was 16. Current was stronger than we thought and when we realised we were much further from shore than we thought. We started trying to get back in, frantically swimming, realising we were struggling.

With some persistence me and friend A realised we'd made it through the tip tide but friend B was struggling to stay afloat and wasn't going to make it.

I said to friend A let's go back for friend B (friend B was my best friend at the time). We were just keeping B afloat when A said "swim away from the rocks  in the middle of the water, they're sharp"! I said "wait! Swim towards the rocks" and the three of us climbed onto them, shredding our feet, where we waited for the tide to calm down.

Like 3 years later friend B (who I saved) slept with my girlfriend and I only found out cause he filmed it and was showing off the tape  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullet pointed and sequentially. More diagrams than text if applicable. Relate it to something simpler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly can't tell if this whole sub is sarcastic or legit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I think it's worse than being at, say, a dying relatives bedside. At least in that scenario they know what's happening, but because pets are oblivious, you feel like you're betraying them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw two teenage chav girls stand at the bus stop in front of me and make a huge scene out of dropping litter, laughing and walking away. I wanted to drop kick those little sloots something awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The intro to vikings. "If I had a heart" by fever ray. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not picture, but my favourite video is that person holding the dog that thinks it's swimming so it shuts its eyes and paddles, then it peeps to check that shits under control. Amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in our lifetime, surely? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dog being put down. My mum didn't want to be there when it happened so I had to.  I think it's the worst I've ever felt as a human, the doorbell went as the vet arrived, my dog wagged his tail, not knowing what was coming. I told him to lie down on his favourite rug and reassured him as the vet injected him. The most harrowing experience of my life. What a bastard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like buzz feed but not shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if you dedicate ever fibre of your being to make it happen then maybe, just maybe, you might. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who litter. Cunts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does your name rhyme with Pot Loose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 13:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At a train station in Germany, across the platform from us there a guy in sort of old school punk attire with massive clumpy boots staring at me and my friend.  I said to my friend, "stop staring back" and he said "why? What's German Michael flatly going to do, tap dance over here and kick my arse?"

Not really an insult, but it had me in stitches cause he said it so fast without thinking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 12:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to say that I very much doubt it... but I did almost bet 1000 on Brexit not happening.

So by that logic, trump will be president in 24 hours time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 08:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like when Susan Boyle's PR went with the hashtag Susanalbumparty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 00:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah man, just saw this now! Could've given you some tips if I'd looked sooner! 

How did you find it?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 16:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the very definition of bitcoin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 16:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything else interesting on her insta!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 15:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's name checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 15:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sort of feel sorry for her, no "normal" person ends up like this. Nor do normal people have the compulsion to post shit on social media for the world to see, it's sort of a "hey everyone, look! I'm happy!...aren't I?"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 15:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 14:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.facebook.com/Channel4News/videos/10154217028666939/

I've noticed something weird, that Donald trump genuinely speaks to his supporters like parents speak to children, everything is dumbed down and repeated several times, and there's so much theatrics to his speeches, it all comes across as very disingenuous to me. I think that's what puts me off him first and foremost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 14:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think intelligent is the wrong word as it implies they're actively thinking and planning what to do, whereas it's just their natural behaviour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 17:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, though, he has been bankrupt 4 times - in politics he won't be able to just wash his hands of errors and hope it blows over. Things he says or does wrong will have a lasting effect on vast swathes of the population.

And I think there's a difference between using leverage in a business sense to get what you want and having some decorum. Saying he can run a country because he can run a business is like saying Obama can now run a multi million dollar business because he's been president - it's apples and oranges.

I would say trump is lucky the visit went well, and it's presumably because of the good graces of the president of Mexico, after saying all he has said about Mexicans, building the wall, etc, another world leader may have perhaps been less forgiving and hospitable. Some things, once said, can't be taken back, and certain world leaders would perhaps be less amiable if trump were to openly insult them or their people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 16:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I see a lot of sense in what you're saying. It just seems like if you were to send someone to treat with leaders of other nations trump is not the person I'd visualise as being a good envoy for a country.

I mean, if nothing else, you've convinced me logical and rational thinking individuals do vote for trump - even if I don't agree with your reasons for doing so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 15:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firstly, thanks for the balanced and logical response - these sorts of topics very quickly seem to become heated!

I'm not sure I agree that trumps problems come from a lack of experience because, let's not forget, he has a team of experts helping him run this race.

I can't argue with your points about Hillary because as little as I know about trump, I know even less about her.

I just think to be president you need to have tact, patience and empathy, however trump is brash, impulsive and inflammatory. 

Was trump your first choice from the start, or is he just the best of a bad bunch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 09:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=Op7PKNCH65A

Do you really want a president who does things that you have to say "he's new to this and is learning as he goes"?

I don't know, I'm still not convinced. 

From an outsider prospective he's just a brash businessman who says whatever he wants to gain public opinion but then openly contradicts himself to gain the other half of the public later. He's like a plate spinner running around telling whatever lie he's need to to stay popular.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll give you the first point for sure there, hadn't considered that. 

Does he not regularly contradict himself on a massive scale? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done research and I'm still of the opinion he's not a fit candidate to rule a global super power. I'm curious as to other people's opinions as to why he is. Note I'm not comparing him to Hilary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is such a twonk  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 08:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't tell him how to spell, commie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 08:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry we can't all live up to your impossibly high beauty standards.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The men who stare at goats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 10:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said above but I think it's a couples costume - kkk boyfriend and black slave girlfriend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 10:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't get it either but it seems in the second pic the person doing black face is latching onto the kkk persons arm.

I suspect blackface is female and kkk is her boyfriend and the irony is that the kkk guy is dating his slave.

Regardless, horrible costume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 01:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two heads are better than one... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 12:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People always want more, typically measured against their peers. For some people to be "haves" some people must be "have nots" which leads to animosity and destruction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 12:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say my girlfriend is out of my league.

Just be yourself, really. To get a one night stand with someone out of your league there's perhaps an elaborate combination of words you need to throw together to lure them in, but for dating, any act you put on now is one you need to continue for the length of the relationship.

That is to say, if you're yourself and they're not keen, then the relationship wouldn't have worked anyway.

That being said, someone can be out of your league in many ways: attractiveness, socially, financially, etc. So whatever metric you regard yourself as lacking in, just ensure that you bolster yourself in other areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 07:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was biasing my answer based on being from Scotland. It's never not wet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 21:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While it's a good burn, it insinuates that there's a level of attractiveness where people can just be this creepy... which is probably true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 10:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't think of any other, short of writing the word. I mean that is what the numbers look like, there's not much that can be done about that...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 09:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair you could rotate the mugs to make the phrases close  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 09:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't slander caramel logs, you heathen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 09:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because then the sign would need to go on the outside of the window where it could blow away, get wet, get vandalised, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 09:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mix of capitals and lower case makes me nauseous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 09:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this not "4 for $400" with for replaced with a 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 09:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this one is fine as you presumably need to be right up at the sign to enter either room anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 07:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disagree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 07:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Touch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 07:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Americans say "hem and haw", not "hum and haw". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 09:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He must have saved a good 5...no, 6 dollars there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 00:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't afford kids there are plenty of measures you can take to ensure you don't have kids.

I couldn't afford another sick day at work, so I went knife throwing, on a tight rope, above a shark tank.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 00:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rum ham </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 00:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a 4 armed, blue Cell (from DBZ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 00:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha valid point. Now I can stop worrying... oh great, now I'm worried again that I'm no longer worrying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 00:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Binning clothes. My bin is in the same room as my washing basket so whenever I walk in holding something, more often than not, it's to bin it. So a few times I've walked through with socks or boxer shorts and chucked them in the bin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 00:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... yours is probably better than mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 00:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is seeing people litter. Honestly it makes me want to punch the person littering.  I think it's the ultimate show of laziness and self indulgence .

It's like saying "I can't be bothered finding a bin, I'll just drop this here and someone else can sort it for me". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 00:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's mental also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 00:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing bothers me. I honestly worry sometimes how little most things bother me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 00:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sex is no big deal at all. Literally felt like I was doing it for the 50th time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 13:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha I put this line to an EDM song I started to make.

"You know what it is, bitch" is my favourite line from the show.  Such a hilarious yet unnecessary use of "bitch". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 16:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, but I can almost guarantee I won't reciprocate... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
