<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3492</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My, What a Big Mouth You Have: Studying Dunkleosteus jaws and the injuries they inflicted provide clues to a violent lifestyle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That thing is *Dunkleosteus terrelli*, the biggest, baddest predator of the Devonian ocean (360 million years ago), when Cleveland was under a 300 foot deep tropical sea and south of the equator.

Check out this article about the menacing jaws and brutal habits of this monster fish: [My, what a big mouth you have](https://www.cmnh.org/blog/january-2017/my-what-a-big-mouth-you-have) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ice crystals are indeed a mineral. They have a classified crystal system based on the water molecule, and a characteristic chemical formula: H2O. Look it up on any mineral website or mineralogy textbook and you will see that ice is a mineral just as surely as quartz, copper, iron, plagioclase, hornblende, muscovite, or enstatite. Snowflakes *are* euhedral mineral crystals. I'm not making this up.


See:

http://www.minerals.net/mineral/ice.aspx

http://academic.emporia.edu/abersusa/go336/merhoff/


In geology, sediments are accumulations of individual rock and mineral particles. Sedimentation, the process of sediment accumulation, involves the transport of rock and mineral fragments in a fluid, followed by their subsequent deposition. Those fluids include liquid water and atmospheric gases, or air.


Sediments are sorted and classified first by particle *size*, then by particle *composition*. Sand is a sediment type defined as rock and mineral grains larger than silt and smaller than gravel. More precisely, particles having a diameter between 1/16 of a millimeter up to 2.0 millimeters. Geologists use a standardized scale, called the Phi Scale, to classify particles into a sediment group.

See:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Grain_size

http://www.planetary.org/multimedia/space-images/charts/wentworth-1922-grain-size.html



Putting all this together: Ice crystals are deposited in large accumulations during sedimentation events controlled by planetary atmospheric conditions. Ice crystals are mineral grains. As minerals they fall under the regime of geologic nomenclature. Ice crystals fall into the 'sand' and 'granule' particle size range of the Phi Scale.


Science has nothing to do with it. You're saying: 1. Snow is minerals. 2. Sand is minerals. 3. Therefore, snow is sand. That is a logical fallacy.


It's all about science. I'm saying: 1. Ice crystals (snow) are indeed mineral crystals. 2. Sand is a size classification for rock and mineral particles. 3. Ice crystals fall under the sand and granule size range. That is a demonstrable scientific fact.


Sand is just a word that describes a particle size for rocks and minerals. Sand isn't just quartz grains at the beach. Look up garnet sand. Or shell sand. Or basalt sand. Calcium carbonate sand. Oolitic sand. Coral sand. Gypsum sand. Glass sand. Volcanic ash, etc., etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 22:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say what you want about logic. This is science. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snowflakes are mineral crystals. Sand is an accumulation of minerals and rock particles smaller than gravel but larger than silt. Therefore, snow is a type of sand that rains from the sky. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Winteriffic Festival at Mill Stream Run Reservation!**

From the website:
Winteriffic!

There are many things to do outdoors in winter  especially within Cleveland Metroparks. Come outside and sample a few winter activities. There is plenty to see and do  ice fishing demonstrations, snowshoe rentals, winter hikes, horse-drawn wagon rides, dog sled demonstrations, ice carving, crafts, and more.

ACTIVITIES

Ice Fishing Demos 1:30   3 p.m. (at Wallace Lake)

Nature Hikes  1   3 p.m.

Dog Sled Demos  2   4 p.m.

Winter Survival Skills Demo  1   3 p.m.

Snow Bike Demos 1   3:30 p.m. (by Century Cycle)

Horse-drawn Wagon Rides ($5 fee, 14:00 p.m.)

Snowshoe Rental ($5 fee, ages 8 and up w/ adult)

 

Noon - 5 p.m.  MSRR

Chalet Recreation Area

Fee: free event, additional activities available for nominal fee

440-734-6660

http://www.clevelandmetroparks.com/Main/EventsProgramsCalendar/Winteriffic-10646.aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
