<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7495</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Camera at scene of 'neighborhood' mom murder was hacked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be but is not about the local residents, quite the contrary it's the international tourist dollar. And TV ratings.

The local residents tend to lose out if not get screwed when big high profile events come to town including traffic congestion including detours   security measures that kill local businesses. Along with inconveniencing residents.

The Olympics use host cities like millionaire sports team owners use them to fund their stadium/playgrounds. Tax payers and residents lose out on those deals as well. Both the Olympics and professional sports teams want someone else to build a stage for their events.

Also here is some more more information on venues and ticket prices.

http://olympics.nbcsports.com/2017/02/03/la-2024-olympic-bid-book-venues-ticket-prices/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we have activists judges, favor owing judges and judges who follow the law/constitution. 

Some stupid RINO staffers assumed since it was a Bush appointee that they would make decision based on the usual political favor system. The same system that fracks up the country every day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a black market for baby formula and diapers. Along Tide detergent. I doubt many of thefts are for family use but for resale. 

The baby formula is locked up or behind the counter in many stores around here. The diapers frequently have the security tags that need removal as does the Tide in many stores. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sports has always been used to achieve status and/or used as a distraction. The communist bloc countries seemed to have been the most recent utilizers of sports for political control and/or favor.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know an adult who "dabbled" or used adderall less than a year before a stroke and discovered high blood pressure which they now struggle to lower or keep low. 

I wonder if the tox screen found caffeine and/or diet supplements as well. Can't keep on shifting the body from high to low gear so to speak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Camera that could capture murder of DC grandma was hacked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London pair held over US police camera hacking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Price, internet news, fox sports, nbc sports, local cable sports channels, sports talk radio and outrageous ticket prices   costs associated with attending or participating in the sports they cover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 06:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL. It definitely will be interesting. 

Since the Kaepernick knee protests started tanking NFL ratings wonder what this will do for the NFL and what the protestors will be protesting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully Budapest or Paris is awarded the games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The security price tag especially with all the spread out venues will make the opening ceremonies look like change for a bus ride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UH-OH. Different point of view. How dare you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LA 2024 Bid Documents Show Average Ticket Prices of More Than $1,700 for Opening Ceremony </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does a diplomatic passport normally expedite entry into a country or only offers certain exemptions?

If it doesn't everyone should be treated the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LA 2024 bid documents show average ticket prices of more than $1,700 for opening ceremony </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thwarted machete attack clouds Paris Olympic bid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ex Clinton appointee now UC Berkeley "professOR" speculates or wishes that that right wingers instigated a riot. Who would've thunk it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More disclosure on privacy and mega merger issues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was to give to a party that will maintain a tax payer funded union represented school system as a defacto 'education' monopoly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The American Federation of Teachers gave almost all of their campaign money to Democrats in 2016

https://www.opensecrets.org/pacs/pacgot.php?cmte=C00028860 cycle=2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans have been a fan of charter schools for years. I doubt his vote was bought on this issue. Devos's donation/s to any Republican might have helped her appointment along with her views.

Public school teacher from a democratic union/sanctuary   soda tax city that wants public schooling. What a surprise. They weren't awarded the DNC Convention for nothing.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The timing of 'shortages' is uncanny. Basically a backdoor ban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some suspect information starting to come out among other things.

-474 arrested
-28 children and 27 adults rescued
-3 day operation

Information about Riverside County arrests-18

http://myvalleynews.com/local/eighteen-local-residents-arrested-statewide-human-trafficking-sting/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need to name   list the facilitators and participants. Masked rioters tells me they're probably wanted for vandalism and rioting somewhere else. 

Authorities need do things like follow these masked individuals back to their vehicles including buses because now they have a bus company and starting point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and no.

This is news from yesterday's court proceedings. At issue is bail and a psychiatric examination. Came out the wife actually made up or devised a cover story.

But yes since the arrest the authorities have been saying she knew. The question is now what was her level of participation.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FDA quietly bans powerful life-saving intravenous Vitamin C  NaturalNews.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UC Berkeley Riots Night: Globalists Dupes On Parade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FBI didn't lose her they were just pursuing "a lone wolf". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Otherwise known as establishment politics. Complete with jobs, money and power. "Professional" politicians have a bigger sense of entitlement to their jobs than a union does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hollywood loves to makes movies about Nazi occupied Europe, especially France where the "resistounce" fought them. Problem is there is no comparison between Hollywood's political desires and World War II. They think there is but there is not. 

Yet another misuse and abuse of a Nazi or Hilter comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> B list Hollywood celebrity speaks, uh-oh.

Same lady who called Bernie Sanders supporters "ridiculous" 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida nightclub gunman's widow knew of his plan: U.S. prosecutors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He probably laundering the money giving to one organization that distributes it to other organizations that facilitate these riots. 

Soro's Organizations should be tracked.

http://www.discoverthenetworks.org/viewSubCategory.asp?id=1237

Some of these organizations have probably changed their name or the same individuals have formed new ones. But as usual follow the money. In the case of these riots follow the money and find out who provided transportation, signs, permits, petitions, staff etc.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officer killed in Delaware prison hostage situation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Delaware prison officer dead, one in hospital after uprising </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 15:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 09:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Australian PM should've been and deserved to be scolded for tolerating and ignoring human rights violations.

http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/australia-politicians-refugee-policy-trump_us_589259cde4b0af07cb6b4eec

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 09:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does the US need allies who violate human rights without compunction.

http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/australia-politicians-refugee-policy-trump_us_589259cde4b0af07cb6b4eec </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 09:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because world human rights organization have declared Australian detention camps unfit and filled with human rights violations. Nor do the Aussies want to sent them back, give them asylum or fix the camps. Obama probably took pity. I'll take pity on them for just enduring the Aussie camps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The previous administration made it. And Trump is right because it was a deal for illegal immigrants from Australia's human rights violations filled camps. A deal for illegal immigrants? Why won't Australia send them back or give them temporary residency? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And more recently invaded Panama to remove and arrest Manuel Noriega. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 07:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the world saw someone that was blocking their globalization agenda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 07:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can call and ask Turnbull to apologize to the refugees in his camps filled with human rights violations.

http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2016/04/26/papua-new-guinea-australian-refugee-detention-camp-illegal/83532666/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 07:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australia doesn't even deserve the time of day for having another country clean up their mess when it comes to their own illegal immigration problem and detention camps filled with human rights violation as noted by several international organizations.

http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/australia-politicians-refugee-policy-trump_us_589259cde4b0af07cb6b4eec

https://www.yahoo.com/news/australia-causing-refugees-severe-lasting-harm-human-rights-150209306.html

It's not called down under for nothing.

The bad hombre talk is exactly that-talk. But it would not be the first time the US sent the military into a country to get criminals including Mexico. Army Expedition sent into Mexico in pursuit of Pancho Villa. 

http://firstworldwar.com/source/mexico_pershing.htm

And more recently to apprehend/stop Manuel Noriega in Panama. 

http://www.nytimes.com/learning/general/onthisday/big/1220.html 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Obama administration makes a deal because the Australian immigrant detention camps are crap and considered a human rights violation by many international human rights groups.

https://www.yahoo.com/news/australia-causing-refugees-severe-lasting-harm-human-rights-150209306.html

The Australian PM has a lot of gall to give more crap to the country that is going to clean up his mess



  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Milo just made the usual appearances like the talking head/pundit shows, book signings  or cable networks etc it would be "oh this guy", now it's Milo Yiannopoulos immediately followed by protest, free speech, intimidation etc. They're giving the guy unconditional support with these tactics. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Milo just made the usual appearances like talking head/pundit shows  or cable networks etc it would be "oh this guy", now it's Milo Yiannopoulos immediately followed by protest, free speech, intimidation etc. They're giving the guy unconditional support with these tactics. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're bringing more attention Milo Yiannopoulos keeping his name in the news with these riots. Most speakers are like a fad, sooner or later they fade or they go on something else. 

These "protests" are keeping his name in the news and the issue of free speech, intimidation, censorship etc at the top of the news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't National Guard units in the 60s attach bayonets to rifles to keep protestors back. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or professional anarchists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 06:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Purge is over for this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope this ends better than a prison riot in Brazil.

http://www.foxnews.com/world/2017/01/24/three-unfinished-tunnels-found-in-riot-plagued-prison-in-northern-brazil.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bolt seems to disappear or be picky about the meets he competes in. It could be he has a rested body or it helps him time his peds use and testing. 

He does have natural in advantage. He's a fairly tall quick man. Longer legs equal longer strides   more distance covered per step/stride. He also doesn't over train his upper body which can be an impediment. Not having the upper body fight against you is tough. 

Some are saying since he's directly around it he's using it. If his team mates have in the locker room so does Bolt. Not necessarily true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is newer information from the original policy.

The question now becomes when/how a can a visa be revoked.  
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was last night but his hair was bouncing all over the place with head motion while while talking/making a point.

At least he doesn't give Larry King interviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been seeing her leading in polls over the last month. This from two weeks ago.

https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-01-19/le-pen-moves-into-first-in-french-race-le-monde-poll-shows

Now I did see a recent poll in which the Macron person leads. Today 

http://news.sky.com/story/france-election-emmanuel-macron-leading-in-presidential-poll-10751720

Still have a timing issue with the story coming front and center. The EU and other have known her politics and would've/should've tried to take her out with stories like this as soon as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 474 arrested. Good. 

Wonder how many they snagged of the celebrity or government nature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are oil sheiks good tippers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unclear how well this 'scandal' was covered from the beginning but it is little suspect that this comes out or is played up around the time she starts rising/leading in the polls. 

The big scandal here is that she was in Paris handling personal business rather than EU business in Brussels. Sounds like an employee who calls out sick a lot. She should've been fired or reassigned for that alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically people of the same culture swimming in the same pond. They will all look the same when they get out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One income for all: far-fetched, or future fact? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only death penalty they are worried about is the death of a multi million dollar revenue generator.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would seem to be a win win in France frequently walking on the socialist line. 

Controlling speech is not good though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a day that people didn't even want to here your political opinions regards of which side of the aisle one came from. 

Now publicly stating political opinion seems to be the latest fad. Just like buying the latest fashion or music cd it seems one has to publicly announce their Trump hate or political views to be cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deny her entry into the US or a mandatory visit from secret service at airport if she wants to come to the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 08:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know they say a tooth infection can kill but I have to wonder if he picked up something extra in the dentist office which made an existing problem worse. Have had more than one infected tooth problem and they never got to the point of severe or prolonged swelling nor did I have respiratory problems.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, do they all they can for the tanking tourist business.

http://www.sigmalive.com/en/news/international/148067/tourism-to-paris-sees-a-sharp-decline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little old isn't it. People with green cards and visas will be allowed in. The green card omission or ban was a mistake that has been taken care of.

http://www.jambonewspot.com/priebus-green-card-holders-will-be-allowed-into-us/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were those stadiums used/resued by those who funded them without the Olympics in mind? How much did Aurthur Blank contribute?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was Mexico City able to reuse Olympic facilities? How many venues still stand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Los Angeles has already been warned and even Boston saw the potential for disaster.

http://www.ibtimes.com/summer-olympics-2024-why-experts-warn-los-angeles-proposed-budget-unrealistic-2048822

Money is already being spent/dumped into the LA rail system with a 1.5 BILLION dollar federal grant(US taxpayers). Garcetti has already used "the Olympics" as partial rationale for this money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are more worried about making a statement rather the accepting or going with the Olympics are supposed to be apolitical which is THE statement to make and/or reinforce.

Ironic the 84 LA Olympics were already tainted by the Soviet and communist bloc boycott in retaliation for the US boycott of the Soviet Invasion of Afghanistan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The money in the new nation state of Calexit could be called the snowflake instead of the dollar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These All Star games are a waste without anything at stake like home field, draft picks etc.

The NFL should go to a skills/combine type format and even then it's a push.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The legal system period should be a political as should the employees. It's one thing if they are at a loss as to how to defend the order and client(the government) in court it's one thing to say so but to refuse to do one's job is another. It's a lawyer's job to defend and/or argue for a client period. She should've resigned if she didn't want their business.

Hopefully this guy is a political. The suspension itself should hold but since the original order being unclear or wrong about visa holders should not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bills for the Olympics would go the country of Calexit then. I guess the Olympics would be a big event/needed income especially when federal are facilities/functions are moved out of the state as would the employees   population that spend on the local economy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Olympics are an outdated unnecessary concept. Most cities lose out after a temporary bump in the economy. Along with facilities security and logistics could very well eat up or offset any money saved by using existing facilities. 

With greater access to the same events and athletes year round with cable   satellite tv along with internet the novelty of the events or athletes is no more. It's a show of professional athletes. Who cares, in many countries including the US the athletes, events and outcomes are meaningless.

To top it off I thought the spirit, mission or policy of the Olympics was to be apolitical yet politics are being injected into the bidding process. Throw in FIFA and doping agencies are any of these events apolitical or an altruistic endeavor.





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outdated event period. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That many athletes who participate in international competition without visas and passports?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Los Angeles shouldn't host the Olympics for many reasons with the least being politics.

Most cities wind up losing out on high profile extravaganza events especially in the US where millionaire sports team owners already extort, cajole and/or beg for tax payer dollars. There is a temporary bump in the local economy but there are also many local businesses that lose out on things security measures and traffic control reasons.

To top it off the Olympics are outdated quite frankly especially since the pros are allowed to compete. And high profile record breaking athletes are able to be seen all year round, not just every four years in the day and age of cable, satellite and/or internet broadcasts.

There are also many international events year round every year so the annual get together for millionaire athletes is not necessary. Throw in cheating and/or the drug scandals are we really looking at the worlds greatest athletes or a pumped up show.

But politics, which shouldn't even be in sports are the least of any cities worries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No link to a news article about that tweet. They read the tweet themselves. It does come up under a news search. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Times Journalist Calls for Assassination of President Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're tariffs already in many markets. Germany has a 3% tariff on imports from the US.

https://www.export.gov/article?id=Germany-import-tariffs

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the time the Marco's shenanigans came out the US was already persona not grata. Even after that settled I think they made US close an airforce base among others.

There's resources but without 100% commitment is it worth it with all the other locations and techniques out there for what ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did though because they used countries listed in the previous administrations list of countries that needed extra vetting when it comes to refugees and immigrants.

http://fox61.com/2017/01/30/countries-targeted-by-trump-initially-idd-as-countries-of-concern-by-obama/

 The order didn't go far enough because it should've covered the likes of Saudi Arabia and Qatar which apparently didn't make the previous administration lists either.

I would've started with extreme vetting and worked up to a ban slowly but steadily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original order covered or was unclear about visa holders. It should not have been. It did affect her and they allowed visa holders in after the fact. Including current visa holders was a mistake , they got called on it and now will allow them in per DHS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best to wait until the stock really tanks after the boycott affects  results. Now might be a good time for to buy a short position.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thoughts exactly. Haven't liked it since day one. They literally left a bitter taste in mouth along with a heartburn tab/bill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starbucks is global. A boycott in the US eh Schultz could laugh it off. A boycott in big market European country in combination with the US boycott might be a different story.

Can't stand Starbucks, over priced bitter coffee but if I was a regular and worried about the baristas I'd buy the cheapest thing and still leave the same tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to give a star to anyone who doesn't want to and advocates not paying taxes.

That being said a federal tax money war goes both ways. The US could score big in the first salvo by cutting off the 1.5 BILLION dollar rail expansion money.

http://www.railwayage.com/index.php/passenger/rapid-transit/us-dot-commits-dol15-billion-for-la-metro-expansion.html

And they want to host the 24 Olympics they are completely on their own which they should be anyway.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California Could Cut-Off Feds In Response To Trump Threats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removing or setting themselves up to remove evidence of protest misbehavior? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a company is willing to accept import fees, taxes, tariffs on foreign made products sold in the US then move. If any company wants to move to the US knowing the regulations and taxes then go ahead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the what about the Christians wasn't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Trump or the executive order exempting Christians from those seven countries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current threat level is key. Still several domestic terrorists had recent travel history to Saudi Arabia. They'll probably claim pilgrimage to Mecca. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole problem comes down to an open borders concept. Extreme or better vetting is needed for all immigrants.

 And why wasn't Saudi Arabia listed especially since they produced what at least a dozen of the 9/11 hijackers and other terrorists had a fairly recent travel history to Saudi Arabia. I guess 9/11 is considered ancient history at this point.

Probably oil money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the US already has them why should they be transferred anywhere. Unless the company moving wants to deal with potential consequences. It is not bad to improve Mexican's lives BUT it is bad to diminish others to do so.

And the way this particular plant closing is in Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pesky details. The Republicans minimized it as to not ding Bush. The Democrats downplayed it as to not give fodder against Obama.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a head of state she could've halted that practice the minute she found out by talking to the police heads or simply going public right away and stating disapproval of the practice. Politicians use surrogates and subordinates for policy and practice. I doubt Germany is much different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes this was Republican in this case and thought for sure the Democrats would pounce on it last year. But they didn't and won't because they know this stuff goes. The two establishment parties have been benefiting from this behavior for years and it starts at the seemingly harmless local level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trudeau sounds like he's pandering for votes. Approval ratings in decline.

https://www.zerocensorship.com/uncensored/canada/justin-trudeau-booed-town-hall-polls-show-lowest-approval-ever-390721

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the meantime Merkel tells their police don't report rape committed by immigrants of a specific faith. 

http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/04/07/german-minister-told-police-to-remove-the-word-rape-from-cologne/

So Merkel can target a religion for political expediency but not security? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a temporary ban on immigration from 7 countries, not Muslims. Yes they have a heavy Muslim population but the point was to ban immigration from areas of the world heavily infested by radical Islamic terror groups. 

The details like including people with visa's, passports etc was wrong and/or part of the poorly written order. A US judge has already halted that. 

But the ban was on countries, not religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, greed and costs. Not just the US either. Some companies even want out of China for even cheaper costs in places like India or Vietnam. 600 people losing a job is not good in country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More details needed to be worked out. And they left no wiggle room to increase measures. It looks better incrementally increasing the limits on immigration rather a total ban and eventual retraction of the policy. 

Where the heck are countries like Saudi Arabia on this list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That will soil one's reputation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The administration should be using documented cases or current investigations as a starting point. Not studies which should be used for supplemental material. Multiple sources in multiple states such as dead people voting in California and Colorado would be an example and just a starting point. 

But neither party wants this because if nothing else it indicts the process that got THEM elected. Fraud needs to be looked at the local level and primary elections in particular because these lower level candidates wind up in positions of influence including ones that has the power to ignore issues at the local level. 

Still not completely buying the accidentally checked the citizen box but citizenship should be verified. Arrests were made in Texas this year in which an ineligible voter knowing lied about the citizenship to vote, 5 times.

http://www.nbcdfw.com/news/local/Woman-Jailed-on-Charge-of-Illegal-Voting-342158051.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CDC, the rubber stamp for the American Medical Industry and/or establishment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep that herd of sheeple together by any means necessary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard the stories and have seen the scammers. 'Renters', remorseful or impulse buying customers or those who broke it and return it saying it was defective. Throw in theft and/or criminal fraud yes it's a big problem. And yes they ruin for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about an audit of voter rolls and voters by the states rather than studies or investigative reporting which only use a sampling of data. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Law   Order Criminal Intent did an episode with this scenario a decade ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the ban was for those seeking asylum, visas etc, not those with a passport or visa or approved status/entry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamacare Architect Reveals: It Is Based On Lies And Fake Promises </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well at least their protest was more than a tweet or facebook post that could be censored.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence the corruption </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't need a study to realize and/or determine that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like it is not exactly what they wanted.

 And will come back to bite them just like filibuster rule changes they pushed for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh goody another government agency. The Limited Free Refill Police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about just lowering the original price? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or cheap sugary drinks period, especially when ordered with a meal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better living through big government don't you love it.

I don't know which is worse the government telling a business what they can do for their customers or telling the consumer they must pay for something that was complimentary.

Did they even do a study of those individuals that received complimentary refills? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the investigations and trial complete already? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it. This might be an action that could help unify Mexico into working on their very own country by themselves  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This mysterious classified briefing keeps on being referenced but at least differentiate from routine Russian or foreign nation intelligence gathering. Some experts think all those intelligence agencies are basically recirculating or recycling the same report, data and/or analysis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
