<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2868</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 21:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do - thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Skin - Liquid Bandage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 19:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This shit is fucking amazing for BJJ and has become a staple of my kit for training. Just wanted to share that with you guys.  

If New Skin sponsored me I would shill for them ALL DAY.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 19:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. This is the new video I'm going to show people when they ask me what BJJ is. 

Jeff Glover's style is always a great introduction to the sport (in terms of what will make sense to an untrained spectator) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 18:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would just add the following caveat: expect to get smashed at first when trying new stuff, but keep on, because it's better to learn new things and "lose" in class than it is to "try not to lose" and thus stagnate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 18:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI I recommend clarifying your post because without context this sounds like unnecessarily douchey sarcasm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 17:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seph is such a baller. Amazing instructor and one of the funniest dudes in bjj.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 17:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~Agree, and I would add to this, two options: Do you trust your coach?~~

* ~~If yes, trust that they accurately assessed your skill level and respect their decision~~
* ~~If no, find a different coach~~

EDIT: Read slideyfoot's better-articulated advice below
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 05:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to second this point. Striving for absolute control that allows a gentle finish made a huge impact on my game when I started doing this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 20:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, it CAN be an offensive position. But you talk about "playing" side control and "pulling" side control in tournaments. Sorry but that is simply absurd and going to limit your game in the long run. If you keep training I promise you will come back and laugh at that post later. 

I can think of at least 5 subs from bottom side control off the top of my head and have hit all of them in tournaments. However, just because you CAN hit subs from a fundamentally unsound position doesn't make it less fundamentally unsound. 

All fighting is probabilistic - while you CAN find instances of success, it's going to be low-percentage. Maybe you're finding a local maximum in an otherwise low-percentage area of techniques, but I'd say that's only because you're going up against people of similarly low skill. 

Where is /u/Who_Runs_Barter_Town when we need him to explain the Dunning-Krueger effect? 

TL;DR In sum, please stop posting if it's all going to be nonsense like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 19:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 19:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, that was the most unintentionally hilarious post I've seen on this sub all year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 20:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody is different, but for me that would be not nearly enough. 

For me, there are three things that ensure good performance and recovery:
1) 8+hrs Sleep
2) Potassium and Magnesium (and regular salt on your food)
3) Whey protein around workouts (plus casein before bed if I am training a lot) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 17:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was great, CCP! Loved it. 

Next year, maybe take inspiration from boxing chess?

Like between grappling rounds make them do some computations in Excel. I think this would make it more fair and also create some brand congruence with the true nature of EVE Online.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 22:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huge upvote sir. while this particular instance wasn't my cup of tea, you make an excellent point that parody/satire/humor is a really important way for a community to develop and cultivate its identity (i.e., the self-policing I referred to, which in retrospect is actually still too harsh of a term).

on reflection I think my problem with the song is that implies Royler himself said he dominated Eddie - when in reality it was just Royce being Royce, right? I wouldn't want to be held accountable for stupid shit my family says. so to me it seemed misleading, but I could be wrong about the facts here. 

from a more practical standpoint of media strategy, I think this post would have been more successful if it came a bit earlier - within a "window" so to speak, during which there's a surge of interest, but after which people were just tired of hearing about it. no criticism intended here though, just a thought for next time. 

Finally, I apologize again for my harshness up front - I'm leaving it though as evidence of my douchery and your much more respectful response. y'all are clearly stand-up dudes and I'll be checking out the rest of your site for sure. keep up the good work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 19:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> some things are bad enough they're funny. some things are so bad that they kill the very idea of comedy, corrupting the very nature of all man's redeeming qualities with an indelible taint. 

this is one of the latter things.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 19:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry guys, I was much harsher than I needed to be. thanks for being open to feedback; much respect. 

re-stated more constructively: while most of us (including me) are super happy for Eddie, and while most of us are disgusted by Royce et al.'s response to this fight, I think this kind of drama-mongering is antithetical to the type of community we like to think we're part of (whether it's true or not).  

I understand some people won't agree with me on this, but it's just the way I feel. I aspire to be part of a bjj community that generally avoids pettiness and drama, and instead focuses on sharing information and support to make us all better on the mat. (more effective, more sportsmanlike, etc.)

part of what I like about the bjj community in general is, while drama always exists, the community seems relatively self-policing against unnecessary drama in favor of a "shut up and train" mentality. i heard a couple times in the podcast that you're interested in "making jujitsu bigger," so in service of that goal I want to share my opinion that reveling in someone's lameness (i.e. Royce) while fun, is not going to help jujitsu.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 23:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how much more are people (like you) going to milk this one fight for low-effort content (like this)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 23:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I own this gi - it was my first one (not by choice). Not just the worst gi I've ever owned, but easily the worst gi I've ever even seen in person. The fit/cut is terrible (like a poor knockoff of a judo gi, possibly not even competition legal), the fabric is awful. It's just straight-up bad all around. 

Absolutely do not buy it. It is not worth 30 dollars. Spend a little more and get a Fuji, as others have said and will continue to say. 

EDIT: The only reason I still have it is for gi pullups, otherwise I would have trashed it long ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 15:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schaubamoris 2

Keenan is on a different level, this would be embarrassing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 19:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is explained if you bother to look into it. The guy was coming at Seph, who just had surgery at that point. 

That's why Ryan Batman'd him into the night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 19:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of people train with him in NYC too. Unless you're saying people on Reddit aren't always honest. Perish the thought! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 19:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have thought so too, but I have heard this is rarer for pros than you would expect. Unless they get them tailored or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me win a bet: What size gi does Marcelo Garcia wear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 19:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect he uses different size pants relative to the gi-top because of his epic thighs relative to stature. My buddy just says A2 all around (on average, recognizing that it varies by brand). What do you say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 23:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Head-and-arm chokes (aka arm triangle, kata gatame) ALL DAY. 

I have gotten to the point where I am actually better at finishing them with one arm, not even locking my hands. 

Lapel/collar drags (instead of the standard arm drag) should work for you as well. 

This might also be a good opportunity to work on various wrist locks - rather than learning fancy setups, I recommend just trying for them while going for more standard subs, whenever you see them. 

For something fancier, look up the "five finger guillotine." It's pretty old school, but still sometimes works for me. Basically it's a one-armed guillotine that you finish with wrist leverage.

Actually, interesting that you bring this up - I've lately been doing all of my subs from top position one-handed, because I am usually trying to finish them with just one hand while my other arm is holding a good crossface. I often get straight "razor" armbars/arm crushes from mount by underhooking the guy and jacking his arm up until I finish the straight arm crush with just my underhooking arm and my head/neck - my other arm never lets go of the crossface.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 23:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I would be in that division for sure. A friend of mine just fought in a boxing tournament in Asia exclusively for expatriate white collar-type guys with day jobs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 23:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is actually an interesting Game Theory problem. Dusty is talking about what would happen in an ideal case if you were just better than the other guy. You're talking about what happens when the guys are equally matched and going for roughly the same advantages. It's not their goal to end up there, but it happens because both guys are similarly good and have similar but mutually exclusive goals. I have to say I agree with you. It's not just ego and posturing - it's more like two guys throwing jabs at the beginning of a boxing match to feel out the distance and timing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 23:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I think forehead to forehead is what happens when neither guy is good enough to straight up blow through the other guy's defenses and get superior head position. 

If you watch top guys, once they get superior grips or superior head position, BAM they unload. Watch the guys in that video above - as soon as they get the wrist grip, they immediately go for an armdrag, lightning fast. 

Ryan Hall talks about this a lot. Guys like Marcelo Garcia and Rafael Lovato, when you watch them fight each other, they struggle tooth and nail to get these seemingly tiny advantages like a slightly better grip, slightly better head position. But as soon as they get them, they have to go immediately, because against someone good, you have to assume they'll be reacting as fast as they can to reverse that advantage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do pros interlace fingers when gripfighting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-18 17:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I watch pro no-gi fights, they often interlace their fingers when gripfighting from long distance (i.e., at the distance before actually clinching). Like the beginning of this fight: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FmcMj21Wprk#t=14

I have always heard that interlacing your own fingers is a good way to get them broken. Why do pros do it to each other when gripfighting? I've never heard my coaches talk about it, positively or negatively. It seems to just happen. 

My guess is that it's because interlaced fingers is a neutral 50/50 grip - neither person has the advantage. Contrast that with me gripping your wrist - I clearly have the grip advantage (path to your inside space and access to the natural levers of your body). So what happens when pros fight? They both would like to go for the wrist, but both know the other person would like to go for their wrist, so if they are roughly equally good, the result is a neutral position (interlace.) But that's just a guess. Obviously this doesn't happen as much in gi because there are better grips to get than wrist grips (usually). 

What do you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 20:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're definitely important to have in your "arsenal" or at least to be aware of what people will try on you. 

For me personally, as I've ranked up, I've found that techniques like that are more distracting (I think that is the right word) for me than they are effective on my opponent. 

I think it's because I've really changed my top game. I used to use my arms a lot to apply for submissions, like this guy does. Nowadays, going against better guys, I'm much less likely to use my arms for subs, and instead more likely to hold on to my crossface and underhook rather than let them go to attempt subs. More often than not, the smothering pressure makes the guy just give me his arm, so I rarely have to let go of my good control to get subs. Doing it this way, it's way less likely that I get swept or let the guy escape. 

This strategy has worked really well for me lately, but it's definitely interesting to see other ways to crack open defenses like you mention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 20:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great video to give some ideas, but what really strikes me about it is how much grappling techniques and "meta-game" have evolved. 

This guy clearly has an encyclopedic knowledge of techniques, but I was actually pretty surprised by how many technical details he seemed to be missing. 

Of course, it's always different when someone is demonstrating vs. actually applying techniques, but for example his straight armbars seemed very very loose. Also, the little pain compliance things like elbow in the neck to open them up seemed pretty cheesy - every one of those can be easily negated with a slight upa. 

I know this isn't the point of this video, but I much prefer to see many details about a few techniques rather than lots and lots of options - the options come naturally as you learn more. I personally get very little out of videos like this since there are very few "techniques" that I haven't seen at least once or twice. This is not a fair comparison on my part, but instructionals like Ryan Halls are a better use of my time personally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 21:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Illuminati Head Control

I am not voting. Voting is an illusion. Both candidates are working for the same team -- the Illuminati. The election is just a fake reality show. 
--Eddie Bravo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 19:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you on that dude, and agree I shouldn't prejudge the system based on the annoying practitioners (a handful on the mat but legions of them online).  

At the same time, the way you're going around refuting every post that's vaguely anti-Eddie is part of what turns people off to the system without giving it a fair shot! 

Take a page from Eddie's book and just be cool dude. Some are just haters hating and some have fair points. Let it go and let results speak for themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 19:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely agree. To be fair I should also have pointed out that Royler's reset shenanigans were horrible sportsmanship and a great example of Gracie entitlement (its own kind of extremism). If a dude tried to get reset on top when he was basically on bottom in dope mount, I wouldnt have taken it as well as Eddie did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 19:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand your frustration and I don't think you're wrong at all. It's just that we're making different points. That's my fault for speaking off the cuff and not being clear. 

So you're talking about how good fundamentals are taught at 10thP schools and I absolutely believe that is true. You're absolutely right that Machado is a core part of the evolution (also partly why Eddie has a great butterfly guard, as you referenced). I'm quite familiar with the 10thP system and how it is taught, and I think it's great in theory. Ideally, all 10thP guys would take that training to heart and make fundamentals (rather than specific techniques) the core of their game. 

While that would ideally be true, in reality, the newer 10thP guys I have trained with tend to disregard fundamentals because of how laser-focused they are on making specific techniques work (e.g., lockdown/RG). Of course, that's a white belt problem in general. But it is way more common (strictly in my experience) for 10thP white belts to be guilty of this. They are so convinced that Eddie just has a superior game that they disregard being fundamentally sound in their own game, and ignore the specific strengths/weaknesses of their own specific attributes (more or less flexibility, strength, size, etc.)

So what I really should have said is that's an issue with some of the practitioners more than it's an issue with the system (which I actually like). To be fair, the annoying experiences I've had with people on the mats are probably more guys who found 10thP techniques on youtube and decided Eddie was the messiah than those who trained at real 10thP gyms - so I apologize if I made an unfair generalization </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 17:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think, because it tends to be a polarizing topic, any Eddie-related discussion has to be broken down issue-by-issue to get any kind of meaningful conversation going. Otherwise people on either side of the issue just end up debating different things and getting nowhere. 

How has your view changed of:

Eddie as a jujitsu practitioner: No change. I always knew he was good at jujitsu and a good, humble guy on a personal level. I still think that despite his shameless self-promotion and hype as a businessman. Props to him for a great performance. 

The 10thP system: No change. I think it's great for people who are already good at bjj to incorporate some innovative ideas. On the other hand, I think it's a terrible place for people to start as beginners, because (for example) their new guys tend to use flexibility and clinching as a crutch to make up for their lack of hip movement, posture, and timing. I personally use 10thP moves selectively to good effect. My very early work on the electric chair has translated into a very effective deep half guard for me. And rubber guard concepts gave me a very dangerous omoplata and monoplata. Do I ever actually use the electric chair and rubber guard anymore? No, but the concepts sharpened my game. 

Eddie's views on [insert political topic]: Who cares? Tons of bjj guys smoke weed. As for conspiracy theories, again who cares? Tons of people believe stupid shit. It should have no bearing on bjj-related arguments. 

And finally, Eddie fanboys: Goddamn they are the worst. I'd say 99% of Eddie hate is misplaced and instead deserves to be pointed at the fanboys. Their internet presence (which admittedly is mostly guys who don't train seriously) places them among the most annoying fans of any sport ever. After Eddie's Metamoris performance, expect a flood of new guys locking down your leg in half guard, inevitably tapping to crossface pressure, and then getting all defensive about how if it was MMA they would have totally smoked you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 16:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering what fictional books/novels you can recommend that have great examples of leadership.

I am trying to avoid lame platitudes that you would see in something like business leadership books or self-help manuals. The more believable and realistic the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inspirational leadership in literature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 16:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering what fictional books/novels you can recommend that have great examples of leadership. 

I am trying to avoid lame platitudes that you would see in something like business leadership books or self-help manuals. The more believable and realistic the better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-14 06:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jesus keenan; trolling or not, your site template has literally made my brain bleed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Key Principles. What would you add? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 17:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR: What would you guys add to this list?

Hey all, 

I'm interested in your thoughts on the key principles/fundamentals of bjj. Ryan Hall and Demian Maia do an excellent job of addressing these in their DVDs. E.g., 

**Grip fight**

* Immediately break his grips, get your own, and immediately use them
* Why? To protect the line to your inside space and get inside of his  this allows you to access natural levers (his limbs, neck, etc.)

**Posture**

* Straight spine
* Hips low
* Elbows tight to sides and flush to knees (Maia's "block" principle")
* Why? Broken posture = structural weakness and smaller muscles engaged

I know this has been discussed before on /r/bjj, but I'm really interested in the way the answers have evolved over time. As recently as 2006/7 I remember the typical answers used to be less helpful, much more simplistic and less broadly applicable (e.g., "never be flat on your back..." not universally true). Also, the "why" especially has developed a lot since then: a lot of guys used to just say "Because Helio" instead of talking about leverage and mechanical efficiency. 

What would you add? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 18:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're absolutely right - his opponent's leg is trapped in half guard so it's probably not a true crackdown per se. For BJJ, if you can manage it, it would be great to come up into a nice half guard pass with head control like that (as the BJJ dude did in that video)

I think the head control is key - and you raised an excellent point - head control like that would often be hard to get because a BJJ guy will likely pull their head way back out of reach, transitioning to playing guard. 

I guess an alternative way of asking the question is: what is the best way to finish a "normal" single leg like that in BJJ to minimize the chance of getting reversed or submitted? Especially to avoid the triangle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 18:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree - that's why I'm struggling a lot with the position. My academy is known for having some of the sharpest triangle-specialists out there, so anything resembling that position tends to be a recipe for disaster on my end. It sucks because I constantly end up there and want to make it viable somehow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Crackdown/High Crotch Wrestling Position </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-27 16:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR - What do you guys think about using the wrestler's Crackdown in BJJ? Does it adapt well or no?

Hey guys, 

I'm a big fan of deep half guard sweeps. For anyone who has seen Ryan Hall's Deep Half Guard dvds, he suggests coming up on an over/under style pass when you use a single-leg style sweep. 

However, I find that I much more often come up on a Crackdown-style position (for the wrestlers out there) meaning that unlike Ryan's over/under pass, I do not have control of their far hip, only their near leg. 

See here for what I mean: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hjSVk-1mixg

I was actually inspired by /u/Remlikjj's awesome post with an amputee defeating another grappler (he does it off a takedown here): https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=xQ8CcFWBFd8#t=56

What do you guys think about using the crackdown in BJJ? It seems like you have to make a big reach for their head which could put your arm out of position. And it seems like you're really jamming up your own head and compromising your own posture. But I want it to work!

Caveat: "just fix your goddamn over/under pass already" is also a fair response.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who has the best no-gi guard retention? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 04:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all,

Out of all the world-class black belts competing today, I'd like to know who you guys think has the best guard and guard retention in no-gi. 

I have been struggling lately with my no-gi guard retention and would like to watch some videos for inspiration. 

Marcelo came to mind first (though I know he is not actively competing) so I'm wondering who else you'd recommend. 

As a bonus, I'd be very interested to see any nogi-focused guard retention videos or resources you can share. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 20:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DO NOT TRAIN until no longer contagious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 16:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For my recovery it's not super important what kind I use, but the standard Optimum Nutrition Natural Whey around workouts is my go-to. 

If I know I'm going to be really sore, I will add ON Natural Casein before bed. I'm sure brotein hipsters will scoff at this, but I will add chocolate Muscle Milk sometimes as well to improve the taste.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 21:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was never really a believer until I started doing it. It made an undeniably huge difference with my recovery time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 21:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I have large traps, shoulders, and neck muscles (maybe unnaturally large, from defending chokes in BJJ - but my neck was bad before I ever started training). Glad to hear the more aggressive approach doesn't sound out of the ordinary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 23:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly the kind of thing I was looking for - thanks! I am blown away by how useful his advice is, given how toolish he seems. Thanks again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 21:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Responses so far are very much appreciated - I should have mentioned that my PT already had me try the basic scalene stretches, including first rib self-stretches involving a belt/towel/sheet. 

The problem for me is, just pulling down on my first rib with a towel isn't enough to get a stretch. The only thing that has done it so far for me is hanging a 22kg kettlebell on a belt off of my first rib, then applying additional downward force with my arms. Which is probably a bit dangerous. 

Do I need surgery or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Desperate for first rib (scalene) stretches. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 20:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have chronic intractable upper back/neck pain. After doing lots of PT, the only thing that has helped me is my therapist's direct manipulation of my first rib. 

Can you guys recommend any first rib stretches I can do on my own? I can feel a stretch there if I place my hand against a wall, humerus flush to my side and forearm perpendicular to the wall, and then lean away from the wall. 

Thanks!

EDIT: Just wanted to say thanks to all who responded. With your advice, I've come up with what I think is a good way to mobilize my first rib. I'm using an adjustable band (the kind that is used to mount olympic/gymnastic rings to the ceiling): stepping on one end of it and then looping the other end around my opposite shoulder (positioned at the first rib). By leaning away from the foot that traps the band to the floor, I can apply good downward pressure on the first rib.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
