<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3902</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Why are you always lying, Carl?](http://imgur.com/eT5P8sQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Does anyone else want an open world Avatar game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are dem triangular tiddies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pretty much </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm the realest Spider-Man fan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best penalty I have ever seen on FIFA 17! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [*HE HAS RISEN*](http://imgur.com/hGCdhV0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best web slinging EVER (Spider-Man 2) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I still can't get over how beautiful this game is (The Last of Us) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I still can't get over how beautiful this game is (GIF) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ellie   Riley dancing to cheer you up! (GIF) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is a little preview (sketch/idea) of what the /r/thelastofus digital art might look like. My friend and I are brainstorming at the moment and could really use your tips/advice, so feel free to leave your ideas in the comments! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys! i have an amazing idea :) please read </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going to make a /r/thelastofus digital art piece with a friend that we will be working on for a couple of weeks. We want to include as many of you guys as possible! 

**If you want to be a part of the art, please read along!**
Its pretty simple, all you need to do is leave a comment, with the options we are going to give you bellow so you can join the art with a character of your choosing! Kind of like a customization. 
You can make it look like you or just entirely fictional. Choose as you wish! Lets go! :)

(your reddit name will appear above the character you customized) 

You don't have to fill everything in but it would be greatly appreciated. these are just all the options we give that you can choose from. and if you decide to not fill in everything (your choice ofcourse) we will think of something that fits :)

- **gender**  M/F
- **age group**  10/12  13/15  15/18  18/20  20/25  25/30  30/40  40/60  60/80  80+
- **hair colour**  brown/blonde/black/grey/red
- **hair style (men)**  long hair, short hair, men bun, buzzcut, reggea
- **hair style (women)**  long hair, bun, ponytail(s), short hair, buzzcut, reggea
- **beard (only on male characters)** yes  no
- **skin colour**  pale/fair/tan/dark
- **tattoos**  yes/no , (you can choose to leave 1 personal idea for the tattoo. 100% chance it will be implemented as long as its nothing offending)

clothing  

- **pants** jeans/ripped jeans   regular pants, ripped regular pants ///colours: black, grey, dark blue, dark green or cammo.

- **shirt** hoodie with or without hood/ sweather/ t-shirt/ jacked/coat.  colours: black, grey, white, blue, dark blue, yellow, dark green, cammo.

- **shoes**  boots, sneakers, army boots. coloursblack, brown, white

- **head** OPTIONAL: cap, helmet, backwards cap, beanie, gass mask, balaclava (choose 1)

**glasses** optional

**weapon** yes//no ((if yes, what weapon? and how do you want your character to cary it point it or hold it?

**facial expression** angry, sad, happy or anything else put it in your comment.


**body**  skinny, fat, regular/average, jacked(something like henry) **height**  short, medium, tall

alright, that was all! thanks for your contribution! :)
at last you can leave any ideas behind aswell and we will try to implement them as long as its nothing too extreme. 

**This wont be a low effort post with some stickfigures or anything.  We are really approaching this as a high quality project, which we gladly do.**

**The vision is to make a /r/thelastofus squad digital art standing all together(or at least near) interacting with eachother in a badass way with allot of attention to detail and a personal touch to it.**


**DISCLAIMER:**
Max 30 participants. 

The first 20 people to submit will have a 100% guarantee they will be part of the art!

(Excuse the bad grammar, its not my first language)

Thanks for your time and

Greetings from, Goofydos   Robin (he doesnt have a reddit, yet.) 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who would win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where boys became men </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best web slinging EVER part 2 (Spider-Man 2) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 13:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McDonald's new happy meal will be a success </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I still can't believe I met Ashley Johnson yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
