<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4418</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is destined to face protests everyday of his presidency. He hasn't faced that reality yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what he meant, and we both know it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the beginning of the end of the government's war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry sport, no one is a bigot because you say so. I sleep well at night.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump attacks on judiciary raise safety concerns for judges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask trump's previous wives. They all have an expiration date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump doesn't need me to help him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's the bigot. Perhaps she would be picking grapes on trump's winery with the rest of the illegals. It won't be long until he dumps her too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't get out much, do you?

Where would she be if she hadn't married Trump. Probably working as a maid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did that day, that was the beginning of the end of the war.  If such and event occurs they will burn down Trump's America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing is believing. Have you ever met these two? He's not even concerned for her safety or she wouldn't still be at Trump Tower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most crimes have a statue of limitations. She should have been deported long ago or not at all. 

These people do work under false identity. That simply contributes to the tax base.  Finding a way to citizenship is a better avenue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No comment on the video? You asked for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does he understand the government the lost at Kent State? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop playing the reverse racist card. 

Did you see her face at the inauguration?

http://www.huffingtonpost.co.za/2017/01/24/were-terrified-for-melania-trump/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fine, I'm just a people person. Why aren't you pro-everyone? Why are you so afraid that you need someone like trump to protect you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, such a humanitarian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I look in the mirror and I see white </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just stating the obvious. She has been mentally abused.

She came here illegally, worked here illegally, married a privileged white guy and is still here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can see the fear in her eyes, his wife is abused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's married to Trump, she has white guy privilege. I will say, however, that I'm certain Trump has threatened to deport her or her family many times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, we have a President who is vindictive and now is going against his own statement to only deport people accused of a crime.

Remember when he said we couldn't have a female President because she would be moody and vindictive? They don't come any more moody than Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why Ignore it for 30 years and then suddenly enforce it just for spite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cutting deductions increases taxes, not cut them.

I think you mean Warren, there is no Pocahontas    in the Democratic party. You seem to have as little regard for people as he does. 

Trump tells me to boycott certain American companies and in the same breath buy his daughters shit from China. This guy is a fraud, the only regulations he wants cut are those that affect his family's business. 

He's already committed impeachable offenses.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This lady did not commit a crime. Trump said that was the criteria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why should a US citizen be forced to move to be with their family? How did they know when they've been here for 30 years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Trump is vindictive. Do you support tearing apart families? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I question his idea about a 15% business tax when the average company paid 14% last year. Obviously none of his numbers have been run by anyone, just as his ban was never run by his legal advisers.

Expect impeachment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a liar and only wanted the Presidency to line his pockets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was Saturday moron. Why do you think the chose that day? Don't they have the freedom of movement rights? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, they aren't the President's wife. 

This is all show by the Republicans and it will get people killed. Including ICE agents. Most deported people come back into the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's all speculation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You stand with a illegal law? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a republican. Where did you get the notion all Trump haters are democrats? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That won't happen, she has white privilege. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Educators.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What talking heads?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Our court system is broken"- Donald Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's wife came here illegally and worked as a model. When is she being deported? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, she didn't get caught. She's been in the open for 30 years. Why do you fear her?

Why did we handcuff a 5 year old and question him for 5 hours at an airport? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to find a Trump supporter who can tell me why I should boycott a US company and yet buy his Daughter's shit from China. How is that "America first"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His tax cuts will be reduced by Congress. He still has to pay the bills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump said only those who commit crimes. Did he lie to us yet again?

Why do we take someone who has reported to her immigration officer for 30 years and suddenly deport them?

Obviously you fear them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you fear these people? Why are trump supporters such babies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama wasn't impeached, Trump will be.

Trump is the poster boy for in over his head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took 30 women to the woman's march. None of them are paid. They were all professionals in their field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Backlash Could Make 2018 a New Year of Women at Ballot Box </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, but earnings always drive stock prices long term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is a fraud on so many levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe, if he's still alive and sane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current prices are based on earnings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 12:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is learning he is not the Dictator he hoped to be. All his executive orders will be challenged in court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, his supporters have always been terrorists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, the number of strikes has decreased everywhere under Trump. They will decrease even further because Trump has caused their government to stop them without getting permission. That means no surprise strikes. By the time we get permission the target will be gone. That's what happens when you kill 30 innocent women and children during your strike.

Two courts have now ruled against him. Only 1 was from Seattle. Trump should read the Constitution sometime and learn what he can and cannot do. He is not our Dictator. He should stop acting like he his.

Truth be told a ban will not keep real terrorists out of the country. They will find a way to come here. Terrorists are not concerned about any law.

Personally the little Christian boy next door, who's Mom owns a gun and shuffles him off to church every Sunday worries me more. Then one day he rebels, takes her gun and kills a bunch of first graders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Threats against judges in immigration ban cases leads to increased security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, the court rules on Constitutionality, not national security. He should do these things the right way and have Congress pass a law. All his Executive Actions are going to end up in court.  Several others will be shot down. Learn to live with it and stop being afraid of the world.

His team failed to show the threat because they simply have nothing to back it up. He is not a dictator and we are not at war.

What coming military actions?

The wall is a pipe-dream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The court is interpreting the Constitution. That's their job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch those TY Beanie Babies. They are known terrorists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Childish. Someone tell him he was in court, but be gentle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what's changed? The courts have every right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump border 'wall' to cost taxpayers $21.6 billion. FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corporate welfare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give her a break, she is the dumb blonde they coined the term by. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how he responds every time he loses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2TnkJ8_BmSI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watch as many of those shows as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calm down Donald, go tweet for awhile.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Federal hiring has been flat since the recession. All Trump has caused is important positions to go unfilled. No money has been saved.

This was thought out about as well as the travel ban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost makes you think this was all a set up to make the judge seem less bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my, here come the thumb screws, although I know Trump prefers water boarding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't a Muslim crime. That's all he rants about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the problem is space at airports vs traffic. Improving them will only help slightly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, but they'd rather put off the expense. Makes no sense. 

Meanwhile Trump is easing regulations on these people. Making a spill much more likely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I heard everyone in Benghazi voted for Clinton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/arts-and-entertainment/wp/2017/02/07/melissa-mccarthy-on-snl-shows-the-power-comedians-have-under-a-trump-presidency/?utm_term=.c90e1bb8e30a </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An attack would crush his ego. He'd probably launch all our nukes at God knows where. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump blasted treaties in the debates but never once offered what as wrong with them. I don't think he knows what's in any of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump deported my neighbor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait for one of these pipelines to leak. Trump will claim he didn't know that could happen. That his advisers should have alerted him to the possible problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for her, the Presidents resident airhead.  Or as Trump would say, one of my best people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing "potential" about it. It's flagrant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/donald-trump-vote-twice_us_5816ad80e4b0990edc31e17f </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't find them. There have been numerous studies into this. Are you going to look for illegals who voted for Trump as well? If not your study will be flawed.

https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/post-nation/wp/2016/10/29/trump-supporter-charged-with-voting-twice-in-iowa/?utm_term=.e15864847960 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Trump voter voted twice in Iowa. So we'll call this even. Nothing is impossible. Studies have already been done about this. Congress will not approve funds for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, what you were told is this rarely happens. I'm sure this turned the tide in the election. Why should Trump's advisers be registered in 2 states to vote? You're just a few million examples short to prove Trump's insane claim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big deal. What constitutes "attacking"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a PR stunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't see a single thing in this that isn't currently being done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump also said Obama wanted to bring in 100,000 refugees immediately, while the real number was 10,000 over 2 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's the best thing for the show since GWB.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has revived this show. It will run as long as he's around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our youth are destroying themselves. Don't want drug lords, don't buy drugs. Blame the parents too for setting bad examples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they've shown they have no balls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Puzder has a history of replacing workers with machines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This woman is a disgrace to education. She barely made it through her confirmation hearings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything at the WH is a pitch for Trump's goods and services. It's all illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thoughts precisely. A ploy to get this guy confirmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bush appointee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is dreaming if he thinks US troops are going into Mexico to get rid of drug lords. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bush appointee, get over it. Oh and he was confirmed unanimously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Initially. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump can't handle criticism. He's used to being the boss, and has never had anyone to answer to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but Americans once had a great work ethic, Not anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robart was appointed by Bush. The 3 judge panel are all democratic appointees. You are confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now he claims he wanted a 30 day delay, but he never initially said that until the immigration ban went south. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Trump, the buck stops there -- or anywhere else </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manufacturing jobs are the most boring on the planet.

 Immigrants do simple tasks like picking fruit. Without them America would starve to death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Trump who is screaming about Judges. And the press and Nordstrom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would any of our younger generation travel 100 miles on foot to get a job? No, they want a job where they can play video games half the day. Would this generation sit at a sewing machine 8 hours a day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our workers are mentally inferior, they have no work ethic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't you here, America has no plans to be part of the planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where was Trump in Vietnam? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His base is fearful people, people who need protected from the evil world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is an idiot, one of Trump's good people hires. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> North was fine, he took a fall for others. Hardly treasonous.

Reagan was an excellent speaker, hardly a quality of someone with dementia. Don't buy the hype. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't have Trump's thin skin disorder, a trait that will eventually do him in. He also surrounded himself with good people, Trump hasn't. Forgetfulness is not akin to paranoia.

So you're saying he passed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nor did he have Trump's thin skin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bummer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They might, Reagan wasn't mentally ill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
